Previously on Face Off...
The artists went
to hell and back.
Anthony won his fourth challenge
in a row...
Thank you, guys.
And Katie was sent home.
Now, 11 artists remain,
and tonight, they'll tackle
the sweetest challenge yet.
Oh, my God,
there's candy everywhere.
- This is awesome.
- Wow.
But some will * on their
confectionery creations.
I'm feeling pretty screwed
at this point.
My actor is stuck to the floor.
What the hell was I thinking?
I can't let this crap
send me home.
Fuck.
Your makeup didn't work out.
This is such a great concept.
I am so proud.
There was absolutely no candy
anywhere in this makeup.
In the end, only one
will win the opportunity
to be a guest lecturer
at Make Up For Ever's academies
in New York and Paris,
the all-new 2013 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Welcome to Face Off!
Sync and corrections by n17t01
I feel sad.
I miss Katie.
Yeah, me too.
I'm sure she's upset because
she had to work with somebody
who could not perform
to their full potential.
It's difficult
to have Katie gone
because I feel
directly responsible.
All I can do is just try
to put it out of my mind.
- Let's rest that wrist up.
- Yeah. Yeah.
It did
'cause I seriously thought
we were top looks going in.
I'm starting to think maybe
the judges expect more of me.
Well, I was surprised that me
and Eric were where we were.
We thought
that we would be safe,
but to be in the top looks
was very exciting,
but I don't think
I deserve to be there.
So I'm gonna try to do better,
and I'm really excited to see
what's gonna happen next.
So I walk into The Federal bar,
it's an old 1920s building,
and I'm thinking that we're
probably gonna do 1920s makeup.
Welcome to The Federal bar.
Built in 1926, it was the site
of the first ever
Los Angeles
beard and moustache competition,
which is the inspiration
for today's
foundation challenge.
Now, here to tell you more about
these outrageous competitions
is the founder and president
of the Los Angeles
Beard and Moustache Club
and National Beard champion.
Please welcome John Myatt.
Howdy, y'all.
I've only laid
about two or three beards
in my whole life,
so I am a little worried.
Can you tell our contestants
just a little bit more
about this quickly
growing sport?
The best way to describe a
beard and moustache competition
is a mix between a male
beauty pageant and a dog show.
Your challenge today
will have you hand-laying
your own outrageous
facial hair.
Let's bring out your models.
Of course!
They're not men.
Your foundation challenge is
to take these beautiful models
and transform them into
a bearded lady from the circus.
Oh, that's awesome.
The winner
of today's foundation challenge
will receive immunity
and cannot be eliminated
from this week's
spotlight challenge.
We have provided you with all
kinds of hair as well as racks
of circus-themed wardrobe
to finish off your looks.
John, any last-minute tips
for these guys?
One big thing I notice
in fake facial hair
is it doesn't really match
the face or jawline,
so I'd keep a lookout for that.
Your models have been
randomly assigned,
and you have two hours
to complete your looks.
Get ready
because your time starts now.
There's this huge wall
with all these different hairs.
I'm really excited to see
what we can come up with.
I find this beautiful
saloon girl's dress.
In my mind, I start making
my model into a bearded lady,
leprechaun burlesque dancer.
I need immunity this week.
I need a little bit more time
to figure out how to use my hand
'cause I don't want to go home.
When you're laying hair,
it's all in application.
You can't hide the edges,
so I want to go
completely natural.
I don't do facial hair.
I personally can't even
manage my own hair.
I'm just gonna put some glue
on their face
and start sticking hair
into it.
If you're a bearded lady,
you're gonna do
some wacky stuff,
so, yeah,
you go and bleach your beard
and dye it a little pink.
You don't need much
to lay a beard.
You just really need a hackle
to separate the hairs.
A hackle is
a dangerous tool to use.
It's like a really sharp comb.
I'm hitting my knuckle, like,
four or five times on there,
and you tend to bleed
a little bit.
Ten minutes, everybody.
I'm noticing that everyone
is going crazy over the top.
They're picking
different colors.
Some of them are using braids,
and I'm a little concerned
with how conservative
I've approached it.
Time's up, everybody.
Brushes down.
- Hi, Alex.
- Hi, McKenzie.
How are you?
So explain your concept to us.
It's like a modern circus.
I like the pink faded into it,
and the curls are very nice,
but...
?
- Yeah.
- So I would've tried
to clean up the loops
a little more.
A little symmetrical,
but it's good.
I went with an Irish
burlesque carnival feel.
I love this.
Yeah, it matches
the wig very well.
- Laid a bit weird on the cheek.
- Yeah.
It's a little high,
but for the most part,
no, the curls are nice.
My bearded lady is
a little more masculine.
You know, it's well laid.
Like, the cheek line
follows the face
where facial hair
will really grow.
Thank you.
A hard part
about believable moustaches
is the thickness
right under the nose.
So I think if you maybe had
thickened up here a little bit,
it would have been
a little more believable.
All right, John, how do you
think they did overall today?
- Overall, pretty good.
- All right.
Well, who were some of
your favorite looks today then?
Eric Z.
The color, the blending
of the hair that matched.
It was very nice,
and it was just laid very well,
looked very natural.
My second one, Alex.
I like the white and just
the light slight accent
of the color,
and I know curls are
a very hard thing to do,
really nice.
Okay, John, who is the winner
of today's challenge?
The winner of today's
challenge is...
Eric Z.
- Great job!
- Yay!
- It looked realistic.
- It really did.
It looked like a bearded lady.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
You have won immunity
in the next challenge
- and cannot be eliminated.
- Awesome.
All right, well,
this was a lot of fun,
so I will see you all for
your next spotlight challenge.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
- Nice meeting you.
- Bye.
Uh-oh.
Oh, my God!
There's candy everywhere
in the lab.
I feel like jumping in there
and just swimming around it.
So what do you think
of the place?
- Wow!
- It's candy land.
- That's beautiful.
- Looks yummy.
In films like Charlie
And The Chocolate Factory,
characters who overindulge
eventually fuse
with their favorite treats.
That is the inspiration for this
week's spotlight challenge--
to create an original
candy creature or character.
It's gonna be really fun.
It's gonna need
a lot of creativity,
and that's what I like.
To make your looks
even sweeter,
you must incorporate
some of the candies and treats
into your makeups.
I've done
candy-themed model shoots.
It's portfolio work.
It's not where my heart is.
All right, guys, go pick
your models and get started.
As soon as we pick our models,
we all grab a bag,
go get our candy,
and just fill it up.
It was like
trick-or-treating.
The first candies that catch
my eye are the candy corn.
I got to eat one of those.
Mm.
So I want to incorporate
the candy corn and licorice
as the main candies.
My concept is kind of like
"night of the living candy."
Kids eat all the candy
on Halloween,
and now, it's the candy's turn
to eat the children.
First thing I think of
is the lollipops and swirls
and incorporating them into
some kind of a colonial wig,
and thus,
colonel candy was born.
What are you doing?
I think I want to do,
like, a witch,
like,
a candy-witch-type thing.
I'm gonna play with the idea
that Hansel and Gretel witch
will lure children in with candy
and entice them,
and then, you know,
use it to destroy them.
I think I'm gonna make all
the costumes out of the candy.
I'm gonna make really,
really big eyes and give her,
like, pointy, perfect nose,
something cartoon-ish.
I'm gonna take a really gross
approach to this.
My design is going to be
the Incredible Melting
Gummy Glutton.
Big, obese,
couch-potato-type look
dissolving
into a big gummy mess.
Wah.
That's bad.
I named my character
Sweet Tooth Susie.
Her sweet tooth is this belly
that's just gnashing teeth.
- I love your stomach idea.
- Yeah.
Just insanity.
I have three pieces that need
to be sculpted, molded,
and run foam latex into it.
The only candy I could see
to make a character out of
is a gummy bear,
so my concept is the gummy bear
that's half eaten and undead.
But it's harder than I expected,
turning this into a bear face.
I'm not feeling good
about this challenge.
I'm getting a little frustrated
'cause it's taking
way too much time,
and I can't let this crappy
gummy bear send me home.
It looks like shit.
Coming up...
I cannot get the mold apart.
I'm feeling pretty screwed
at this point.
There's an appalling lack
of makeup.
This is a great concept.
I'm *, getting his head to look like
a freaking bear head, man.
- It's just--
- Yeah, bears are tough.
I'm not feeling good
about the candy challenge
at all.
It looks like shit.
I am tired of looking at it.
I'm tired of thinking about it,
and it's killing me.
I just want to do
whatever I can do to be safe.
What's that, like, a ballerina?
Sugar Plum Fairy.
I grew up on dance.
I love the ballet,
and I'm gonna go that route
because I'm very strong
at beauty and pretty things.
What are you gonna do
with the candy?
So I'm thinking about putting,
like, horns in here,
trying to incorporate some
of these, like, crystal things.
My concept is
it's a sugar rock candy troll,
so he's gonna have
sugar rock candies
coming through his chest
and through his face.
- Looks radical.
- Thanks.
- Jenna, how are you feeling?
- My hand is totally numb.
I'm just not even thinking
about it.
I'm sorry.
I'm not gonna let it get
the best of me this time again.
Hey, guys!
I'm back with my dad
to do the walkthrough.
Having a little difficult time
getting him to look like a bear
- out of a human face.
- You know what you need to do?
Your nostrils
are more like a cat.
A bear actually has a hook
in his nostril as it come--
Yeah, I was trying
to get it--
The hook comes around this way
'cause a bear's head comes right
straight down into that nose.
- I see, I see.
- Mm-hmm.
I gotcha.
Yeah, I've been waiting
for you all day.
I was hoping you'd come today.
So basically,
it's a little pageant girl
that ate too much candy...
and she became the rock candy,
and she's a little crazy.
I wasn't sure if I
should add more candies to it.
I mean,
that's what the challenge is.
Yeah.
So I would take advantage
of the candy.
Otherwise you're gonna wind up
just a face with a couple
of little things here and there.
Now, how are you doing
time-wise?
I think, so far, so good.
I want to get these molded
today, so--
- Everything?
- Yeah.
- That's aggressive.
You know, you're at a point
now where it's--
everything is rough,
so you need to leave yourself
enough time to...
Certainly.
- ...smooth it out.
- Yeah.
Tell us
what you have going here.
Okay.
She's a sinister tooth fairy.
She gives candy to the kids
to rot their teeth.
Try to think of something else
to do with the nose.
Either give yourself a little
bit more of a bump here...
- A bump.
- ...or extend it down.
'Cause this from a distance
is almost going to read
like a regular nose.
- Regular nose, right, okay.
- Yeah. Yeah.
I like your sculpture.
It has a nice flow to it.
What are you planning on doing
with the mouth?
All I'm gonna do is--
this arm's actually gonna be
sculpted in with a chess piece.
Right.
So the actor's real arm
could be underneath
to operate
the tongue moving around,
so it's not
just a big, rubber head.
All right, everybody,
good luck tomorrow.
- Thank you.
After hearing
from Mr. Westmore,
I don't feel so nervous.
And I know it still looks
like a kitty cat,
but I have to keep going.
I can't waste all this time
sculpting just the face.
So I finished
with my sculpting,
and I'm ready to mold
my facial prosthetic.
I chose silicone because I want
to color the silicone,
so I don't have to think
about airbrushing it
on a vacation day.
This is my second time
pouring silicone.
Every day here, I'm learning,
and I feel
that I'm getting better.
I think I'm gonna be
silicone master.
I finished the face mold,
and now,
I want to incorporate licorice
into the chest,
and I pressed the candy
into the clay,
so that way,
I know where it goes
when the foam latex
is complete.
It's kind of like a map.
End of day one,
I'm sitting pretty good.
I've molded my face sculpture,
I've molded my head sculpture.
But I'm looking around, and
everyone's hustling, bustling,
trying to finish their pieces.
And I'm kind of
in a relaxed mode, man.
- Nice, man.
- Have a good day.
That's time.
Tools down.
Good job, buddy.
- Coming in.
- All right.
You're getting
really nice edges.
Thanks.
Day two.
It's another ten-hour day.
I still have quite a bit to do,
but I'm gonna get busy.
I'm sculpting the arms
and blocking out the feet
and getting ready for texture.
Overnight, I thought of adding
another element to my character,
which is going to be
this gingerbread house
that's morphing
out of her back.
It's something
that the hag would use
to lure children
into their homes.
My plan for the day is
to get this headpiece finished
and ready for foam.
And because this wig piece
is one
of the main elements
of this makeup,
I'm spending
quite a bit of time on it.
Are you gonna put licorice
in that or--
No, I'm-- I think I'm gonna
color it like cotton candy.
I have to finish
all my sculpting
for all my pieces
that are gonna go
all over her body.
I think I'm gonna go
with silicone
just for it being
a little bit more flexible
and moving more natural
with the face.
But it's definitely a risk
because I don't have
much experience
at all applying it.
I already have the face,
and I'm working on the costumes.
I'm making a top
out of the burlap,
so I can put the candies on it.
- This looks awesome.
- Thank you.
I'm actually having
quite a bit of difficulty
with my grip strength
in my hand.
What the hell?
I'm really frustrated
because I cannot get
the mold apart.
Why aren't you coming out?
And then my mannequin rips off.
I'm feeling pretty screwed
at this point.
I don't-- I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
Why aren't you coming out?
It's the second day
of our candy challenge,
and this issue with my hands
is really compounding things.
I went to pry it off,
and the whole core broke.
I'm feeling pretty screwed
at this point
because you have to have a core
for that foam to form around.
But I'm not a quitter.
I don't like to give up.
So I start looking around trying
to find the exact same mannequin
that I can actually use
as a core
because I have to try
to get it run in foam today.
It's gonna work,
but prying the previous
mannequin out of this mold
wasted lots of valuable time,
but I'm trying not to think
about it at all,
trying to power through it.
I'm able to get my foam latex
face and head molded,
and I start pre-painting.
So I'm a little bit
ahead of the game.
I need to pre-paint them
because I'm adding candy
into the head.
Finally finished
molding my wig piece
and the rest of day two,
I'm basically trying to get
all the elements I need
for the costume.
Start building the applets
by taking the lollipops
and gluing licorice
all the way around it.
We have a little less
than an hour left,
but I only have one half
of my body molded.
This fat suit turns out
to be
a 250-pound mold,
and I have a lot of work
ahead of me
to get this completed.
All right!
Hoo-ha!
It's the end of day two,
and I'm actually pretty happy
with my character.
Everybody, time's up.
I've already glued
all the candy in the face.
I already have it
pre-painted,
so I think I'm ready
for tomorrow.
It's application day.
We got four hours in the shop,
one hour at last looks
at the stage,
so I'm gonna have to hustle.
Going into an application day
with immunity
is a completely
different feeling.
If there is ever a time
where I'm gonna take my time
on something
that I want to see
done correctly,
it's gonna be the application.
Oh, boy.
Hello!
- How's it going, man?
- Good. Thanks.
- Nice to meet you.
Can you try this on?
You're gonna be Colonel Candy.
This leg's gonna be out,
and this leg will be tucked in.
First, I glue on
her belly appliance,
which works fabulously.
All right, let's try this on,
see what you think.
I glue on her face appliance.
This thing is literally
coming to life,
and it's grotesque.
I love it.
I'm just starting to glue down
my silicone piece to my model.
This is not sticking right,
and it just keeps on lifting up.
I'm a little bit nervous
since I worked with a material
that I don't normally
work with.
I just have no time
to lose today.
How does that feel?
I have to paint my model green,
and the head still looks
a little catlike to me,
but it looks a little better
than I thought it would look.
All right, buddy.
This-- oh, it does come up
really nice and hot.
Oh, thank God.
I'm melting bag after bag
of gummy products
to start coating my model with.
Alex, look at the blob.
I know!
Isn't that crazy?
I'm starting to get nervous.
I'm going really subtle,
and that might be
the wrong thing to do,
so I'm really worried about
what the judges are gonna think.
I start painting,
and I'm having some issues
controlling my airbrush.
I'm pushing the trigger harder
than I think I should,
but with my fingers being numb,
I can't tell until it comes out.
And then I realize,
oh, no, it's too much.
This is not
my favorite challenge.
There's a lot of bright,
vivid colors in candy, which--
I don't use a lot of those
in my makeups.
So I really don't know
what my color palette's
gonna be at this point.
I'm just trying to make the best
of it and get the pieces done,
get the candy in there,
and then see what happens.
Close.
Turn your head slightly
that way.
I really want it to read
as a lollipop.
I think incorporating glitter
and also sprinkles,
it might give it
a fun, playful look.
You're gonna be smelling
like gummies.
I'm making the biggest mess
of melted gummy bears
and dumping gelatins
on my blob.
It's so fun.
Eric's makeup is just
a pile of mess.
It's disgusting.
It's just gross.
What's the time?
Seven minutes.
Ahhh.
At this point, I can't even
look at what other people
are doing around the lab
because I am
definitely in trouble here
with this makeup.
So I'm just concentrating
on what's on my plate.
Time.
I am absolutely terrified.
I should have gone
with more wacky
instead of such a subtle look.
But I can't really throw
in the towel
because I don't want
to go home.
Coming up...
My actor is stuck to the floor.
There was absolutely no candy
in this makeup.
It's just so wrought
with technical issues.
This is one of
the best depictions of gluttony
I've ever seen.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
We have an hour for last looks,
and I've got to get
the mouth glued down,
and I've got to start
incorporating the rock candy.
I know I need to incorporate
more of the rock candy
coming out of her skin,
but I'm really nervous
because I don't know
if I'm gonna make it
prominent enough.
With all the melted down
gummy bears,
my actor is literally
stuck to the floor,
and I only got ten minutes
to get this solved.
Brushes down, guys.
That's time.
I'm really embarrassed
to have this go out onstage.
I'm not feeling very good
at this point at all.
Welcome
to the Face Off reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
First,
say hello to your judges--
owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
- Hey, Glenn.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
Hello,
you sa-weet things, you.
Creature and concept designer,
Neville Page.
Hello, everyone.
- Hello.
- Hi.
And joining our panel
this week,
he's an incredibly
talented artist
whose work often features
a confectionery utopia
and has been showcased
in galleries all over the world.
He's also been a frequent
Katy Perry collaborator
and was the artistic director
for her sweets-themed
California Gurls video.
Please welcome Will Cotton.
Thank you so much
for being here.
Thank you.
I'm so excited to be here,
and I can't wait to see
what you guys do.
Will Cotton is art director
for Katy Perry.
My creature looks
like Katy Perry,
and they got Will Cotton?
He's awesome.
So this week,
your spotlight challenge
was to create
a candy character or creature
incorporating actual treats
into your makeups.
So let's see
what you've come up with.
It's grotesque and yet
hilarious at the same time.
Everyone's cracking up
watching this belly come to life
so I'm feeling pretty
positive about it.
I'm hating the stupid wig.
What the hell was I thinking?
I hate it.
She looks grey.
All the colors
just turned muddy.
I wish I had
just a little more time
to incorporate more candy,
and I wish I would have
pushed myself a little harder
to be more creative
with the candy elements
in my character.
I wish I had made
different creative choices.
Everyone has so much candy
on theirs,
and I'm definitely the person
with the least amount of candy.
I feel pretty confident
in my makeup,
and hopefully,
I'll be in the top.
Reba's a lollipop character,
and I think she looks cute.
It's a little more playful
than the other designs,
but I like that.
It looks like he walked
out of some cartoon
and into the real world.
I feel good about this makeup
'cause he looks creepy.
He's missing hands,
so that's the only thing
I'm worried about.
My character looks pretty.
She looks like she just popped
up from, like, candy world.
This creature is everything
I hoped it would be and more.
I am feeling so proud
of this creation.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look?
It's just amazing.
- Oh, my God.
- Do you belly dance?
I like the fact that he used--
all these are different colors.
I didn't even realize it
till we got up close.
- Wow.
- It's a bit of a mess.
Now, this is a curiosity.
The top of my fairy's head
is starting to collapse.
The whole thing looks
like a mask to me.
I don't have a good paint job.
I don't have enough candy
incorporated into my makeup.
I'm going home.
The whole thing looks
like a mask to me.
The top of my fairy's head
is starting to collapse.
And the wrinkles
have no weight,
- they're just gouges again.
- Yeah.
Look at this beautiful little
diorama happening back here.
That in itself is
a really powerful image.
This edge
is absolutely aberrant.
- It's off.
- Yeah.
I can put my finger
underneath it.
It looks like he embedded
this candy in cookie dough.
That's, like, out of the park.
- Is it silicone?
- Looks like it.
I love its translucency.
Wow.
Careful.
Might bite you.
He tried a lot of things here.
I mean, I'll definitely
give him that.
There's some beautiful work
on the back.
All right.
Will, how do you think
they did tonight?
It's so much more demonic than
I would have ever anticipated.
But really incredible work.
Okay, the judges have scored
your creations.
Let's find out
what they thought.
Eric Z,
Meagan,
Anthony,
Wayne,
Eric F,
you are all safe and can head
back to the makeup room.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
The rest of you
were the best and the worst.
The judges will now speak
with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Alam, please step forward.
Tell us about your creation.
She's the Princess
of the Candy World,
and I got inspired
from Asian animation.
The lifeless approach to the
face gives it a toy quality
that I think merges very nicely
with the aesthetic
of this challenge.
Alam, I think you did a great
job of integrating the candy.
- It's very sweet.
- Thank you.
The costuming piece
is really smart
how you built
these different layers
and components
out of the candy.
She's a cohesive package.
I like this.
Alam, I love
the reference to anime.
I think it's a great piece.
- Thank you.
- Alam, thank you very much.
Jenna.
Okay, Jenna, would you tell us
a little bit
about your character?
She tries to get
the children to eat candy
so that their teeth will rot
so that she can have them.
I understand that you have
that rock candy crown,
but there was
absolutely no candy
anywhere in this makeup.
It doesn't really feel like
you've accomplished
the challenge for me.
Your sculpting just looks
like big gouges and cuts.
It really makes me think
of the Hansel and Gretel witch
because she uses this attractive
item to bring the children
in this gingerbread house,
and that's the part that's
missing from this character.
She's missing
that effective lure.
Jenna, thank you.
Alex, you're up.
Tell us about the concept.
This is a character
that ate too much candy
at the pageant
and then became the candy.
So it was coming out
of the skin,
and she became evil,
and she goes after
and kills the other kids
'cause she wants their candy.
In regard *
make up application.
You've got some troubles
going on there.
There's
an appalling lack of makeup
for the amount of time
that you have.
I just don't know what you did.
It's not even glued down.
How did that happen?
She wasn't in it that long.
Well, this is the first time
I actually applied
a silicone appliance.
But you have to seal
the edges on silicone.
You can't just, like, stick it
down and hope for the best.
Alex, thank you.
Please step back.
Kris, you're next.
Hi, Kris.
Well, first off, let me hear
about your concept.
I came up with a character
that is night of Halloween
where the candy comes alive,
and so the kids
eating the candy--
- he would eat the kids.
- I love that.
To me, it feels
anatomically believable.
There is something
about the way
the candy corns grow out
of the face.
- I love it.
- Thank you.
Most of all, I love
his candy corn fingernails...
And his lovely
candy corn teeth...
Which are very disturbing.
- Thank you.
- This is a lot of work.
Head-to-toe has been addressed,
and I love the concept of using
the licorice on the chest
as pectoral muscle definition.
It's a great piece.
Thank you very much.
- Kris, please step back.
- Thanks a lot.
House.
Please tell me the concept
behind your candy character.
The belly was the first thing
that came to me.
A large stomach that she kept
feeding with candy,
and it had a voracious appetite
of its own.
Did you know
that she is a belly dancer?
- No, I did not.
- Can you do that some more?
- That's awesome.
- Oh, my God.
This conceptually
is a really great piece.
The mouth
is a show-stopper.
The gullet's a great shape,
but the worst part of this is
body paint that abruptly stops.
But this one is such
a great concept.
I just love it for that.
House, this is one of
the best depictions of gluttony
I've ever seen.
- It blows me away.
- Thank you.
House, thank you very much.
Please step back.
Thank you.
Autumn, please step forward.
Yow.
Autumn, explain to us
your concept.
He's a gummy bear, and he's
the one everybody picks out,
so he's going sour.
Most of the things
that you tried to do
didn't work out for you.
You're in trouble when
my favorite part of your makeup
is the wardrobe.
I think your idea
of the little hands
with the gumdrops is very cute,
and you matched his feet.
That's all great.
He does, however, look more
like a cat than a bear.
There's no transition
whatsoever
between piece of rubber
and skin.
It's just so wrought
with so many technical issues.
Autumn, please step back.
Okay, the judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they make
their decisions.
All right, guys,
why don't we start with some
of the looks you like the most?
Alam.
I absolutely adore
the combination of the candy
with the lifeless doll face
that she put on the thing.
This was the only character
here for me tonight
that I would actually want
to put in a painting.
Let's move on to Kris.
He works from far away
as just a demon...
Yeah.
And then when you get close up,
it has all the notes of
the candy, which is a challenge.
I think it's probably
the most well done makeup.
- Yeah.
- Let's move on to House.
The concept is so bold,
and that's what I personally
love in a character design.
I felt like I was seeing
a new character
that I'll probably
never forget.
Let's move on
to the bottom looks.
Let's start with Alex.
We can go on all day
about the technical problems
because there's
no shortage of them,
but it starts with the idea.
Yeah, I understood the notion
of eating so much candy,
and it's starting
to work its way out,
but why did it have to be themed
in a pageant?
Okay, let's move on to Jenna.
She's making a lot of mistakes
sort of week after week.
It's almost something
that had a cool idea behind it
that could have been awesome,
but it's not getting there.
I feel bad for her
that her hands are messed up,
but she still doesn't have
the ability
to make smart decisions,
and that doesn't have anything
to do with her hands.
Let's move on to Autumn.
- A gummy bear gone bad.
- Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry,
but a gummy bear head
- is not a very tough sculpture.
- Yeah.
And if you're struggling
with that,
what else have you got?
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
Yes, we have.
Okay, let's bring them
back out.
Glenn,
tell us about the top looks.
Alam, you had
a really cool, artificial,
toy-like nature
to your makeup,
and you did a really good job
bringing the candy
into that design.
Kris, really interesting
design choices,
and you also made a lot
of great decisions
in the way that you integrated
the candy into your makeup.
House.
Extremely strong concept,
and we really appreciate
what you did
with your character's profile.
Glenn, who is the winner
of this challenge?
Tonight's winner is--
- Glenn, who is the winner
of this challenge?
Tonight's winner is...
Kris.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
Your use of candy,
the different textures,
the sculpture--
everything worked well
for you tonight.
Fantastic.
Thank you so much.
Well done.
I am in complete shock.
Finally, I stopped
Anthony's winning streak.
It's truly a good feeling.
Kris, congratulations.
You can head
back to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Alam and House,
you are also safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Unfortunately,
that means the rest of you
were on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Alex, we had a really
hard time understanding exactly
what it was that you spent
all of your time on this week.
Jenna, candy really
didn't integrate
into your makeup at all.
Autumn, your second-guessing
was very evident
in your final makeup.
So who is going home tonight?
The person
going home tonight is...
Alex.
If you're going
to only show us one piece,
it needs to be perfect,
and this wasn't.
I absolutely agree.
Alex, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
That means the rest of you
are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
You have talent.
It's obvious,
so I wish you luck.
I appreciate the chance I got
to actually show you
a little bit of my craft.
It's been really great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
This has been a wild ride,
and I definitely think
I made friends till the end.
Third time's the charm.
- What?
I knew this was gonna be tough
competition coming out here,
but I am so not ready
to go home.
Even though I am not proud
of the note that I'm leaving,
you haven't seen everything
from me yet.
I'll definitely be around.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.tvsubtitles.net