Previously on
Face Off...
Kris's terrifying werewolf
brought him to victory.
- Wow.
- Whoa.
I'm in shock.
And Autumn was sent home.
Now seven artists remain.
They'll face
a harrowing challenge
with a terrifying twist.
- Oh!
- Aah!
This is gonna be awesome.
And I've also left
a little surprise for you
back at the lab.
That will push them
to the limit.
Whoa!
It's something that
we have never seen before.
You can't be in the bottom
this week.
I'm very, very worried that
I may be going home on this one.
Fuck.
The hands are atrocious.
Some sculptural flourishes
which are quite impressive.
You have got to
do better than this.
I don't want
to go home.
In the end,
only one will win
the opportunity
to be a guest lecturer
at Make Up For Ever's academies
in New York and Paris,
the all-new 2013 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next
great name in movie magic?
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Last night was the most
stressful night of my life.
Dude, I can imagine.
In the last challenge
I had to stand up for myself
because Autumn tried
to throw me under the bus.
She's a good artist,
but she just needs
to change her attitude.
It meant the world that
I knew you guys, you know,
were behind me
on that one.
100%.
Guys, listen.
No negativity.
If I can survive
two team challenges with Autumn,
then I can survive
just about anything.
- Time to go, guys.
- Let's do it. Yeah.
We walk down this path
towards the beach
and we're at the ocean.
It is such a gorgeous scene.
The waves hitting the rocks,
ocean breeze,
and there's McKenzie.
Welcome to Leo Carillo
State Park.
This beautiful coastline
and amazing sea caves
have served as
a filming location
for movies like Inception,
The Usual Suspects,
and Journey To
The Center Of The Earth.
Our planet
is a vast place
and much of it
remains a mystery.
Each year,
new plants and animals
are being identified
that seem out of this world.
Our undiscovered species
are the basis
for this week's
spotlight challenge.
To create a new species
that might live
in any of Earth's ecosystems.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Awesome.
We're making
an undiscovered species
that could be from the water,
from the mountains,
from the caves,
something that
we've never seen before.
So I'm immediately very excited.
Oh, but wait,
there's more.
In films like
Avatar and The Abyss,
Hollywood harnessed one
of nature's biggest secrets.
Bioluminescence,
the ability to emit light.
Okay
Biolumi-- whatever,
I don't even know what that is.
Your final makeup
must contain two unique looks.
One under normal light and
a second that becomes visible
only in ultraviolet light.
- Oh!
- Yes. That's awesome.
This challenge
is going to be tough
because you have to consider
two separate paint jobs.
So it's a little scary.
This is gonna be awesome.
We can have that UV light,
really pop that second image
of our makeups.
It's gonna
be really interesting.
I'm gonna leave you here
to sketch
in this unique and beautiful
place for inspiration.
Oh, and I've also left
a little surprise for you
back at the lab.
I'll see you tomorrow.
As I'm starting to sketch
it's hard for me not to think
of the ocean,
because we're right there.
So my concept
comes to me immediately.
I'm working on
a prehistoric creature,
a fish-woman,
sort of the link between
humanity and the aquatic.
I want her very sexy,
and once the luminescence hits,
I think it will take on
a new level of beauty.
I am working on a fish person
that's been watching
the human race for a while
and now it's time
to start making contact.
That's my story
and I'm sticking to it.
He's an underwater creature.
I want it to be
like he's a warrior.
And I want the bioluminescence
hidden but also flowing
with the stripings
on his chest.
What I'm going with
is an aquatic theme.
I'm sketching out
a crab humanoid character,
and I'm still playing with
how I'm going to incorporate
the bioluminescence.
Plus it's gonna
have a full head sculpt
and probably
something on the chest.
Come on, guys.
We're all very excited
to be heading to the lab
to see what's in there.
Ah-hoo.
We walk in, we see
this huge jungle scene.
And in front of it
we see this button.
I really want
to push the button.
Touch.
We're all waiting to see
who's gonna be the first person
to get the guts
to press it
and I just decide,
"what the hell?"
- Whoa! No!
- Double elimination!
Oh, shit.
This is messed up.
We see the dreaded
"double elimination this week."
I don't want to go home.
Wow.
The stakes are extremely high
and two people are going home.
Everybody is freaking out
but we have to just get to work.
We have five hours
in the lab
and today is just
about sculpting.
I really want
the body form sculpted
because she has lots of gills
all around her head
and her spine.
This challenge
gives me anxiety.
Undiscovered species,
beautiful paint job,
bioluminescent paint job,
double elimination.
Trouble.
How's it going, girlie?
I don't know,
I keep changing it.
I'm thinking a bat creature,
but plant.
It could be some kind of seaweed
but I don't know.
I'm going to have to continue
to work on my concept.
It's gonna have,
like, plant life up here.
- I like it.
- No, you don't.
Well, it's getting there.
It's getting there.
- This is my inspiration.
- That's sick.
You can see everything
inside of it.
I'd like to do
an amphibian girl.
I'm going to do
an underlying face piece
and a silicone overlap piece.
So when the black lights
kick on,
you can see the bone structure
and organs illuminate
through the silicone,
like you would see
in a jellyfish.
I'm trying to do something
so big, so crazy
and so out there,
but for me it's worth the risk.
While I'm sculpting,
I'm sweating and I feel like
I'm dehydrated.
It's kind of weird.
And it's getting hard for me
to focus on my work.
I would love to lie
on the ground right now,
but unfortunately
I have a lot of work to do.
Are you making a squid,
Anthony?
No. It's, like, an amphibious
deep-sea creature.
I'm working on the face
and I'm gonna give it,
like, a really cool
paint job in daylight
and then it's gonna
have something that goes
a lot further
for the bioluminescence.
Once again,
another kick-ass sculpture.
Not too bad.
The crab is gonna
have these mandibles
that the crab eats with.
He does move his jaw,
they do have a little bit
of movement in them
so that way they're not,
like, a static piece.
Dude's got crabs.
You've actually
got a face in there?
Yeah, there's, like,
a face that was in the rocks
that I wanted to translate
into a makeup.
I want to let loose
for this challenge.
So my creature is
a cavern-dwelling tough guy.
He's a mix between
an amphibian and a reptile.
That's cool, man.
I sort of played around
with it but I want
to see how I can get it
to fit onto a makeup
the best I can,
you know?
I really don't feel good.
I feel very nauseous.
I feel like I'm gonna
throw up right now.
- What?
- Why? You all right?
- Like, I feel hot.
- You feel hot?
I feel like
I have a fever.
I have to continue to sculpt,
but it's incredibly hard
and this challenge
is a double-elimination.
If I don't get anything done,
the outcome's not gonna be good.
The room starts spinning
and my head is, like, burning up
and I'm, like, hot.
I feel nauseous
and I have to throw up.
As I come back to my desk,
Megan's not there.
So immediately
I know something's wrong.
I'm so dizzy.
I'm completely dizzy.
I'm scared
I'm going to go home.
Coming up...
Oh, man.
I don't know if
I'm gonna pull this off.
Dude, I'm a fucking mess.
As much as my head wants
to be in this competition,
I can't be.
I'm terribly disappointed.
I have to be honest.
It's day one
and I feel awful.
The room starts spinning.
I really want to focus
but I can't,
and I know if I don't get
anything done, I'm going home.
I'm really scared.
I'm not feeling good.
I'm worried for Meagan, 'cause
this is a double elimination.
You can't be in the bottom
this week.
This is the worst time
for me to be really sick.
As much as my head wants
to be in this competition,
I can't be.
Dude, I'm a fucking mess.
I have to go to the hospital
and I'm terrified
I'm not coming back
to the lab.
- Ooh, that looks cool.
- Thanks, buddy.
I start doing some
finishing details on the face.
I really want to keep
this makeup simple,
especially because
of the double elimination.
It changes
the game altogether.
This is definitely
not the time to go too big.
I want to incorporate
the starfish into the center
of her chest.
And I want to work into
the design orange and red.
So it won't just be
so much green and yellow
luminescent paint.
How much time do we have?
We got 35 minutes.
So by the end of day one,
I still have
a lot more work to do.
It's just stressful,
especially coming off
the last two weeks
of being in the bottom.
Time's up, everybody!
Let's go!
All that's going
through my mind is,
"you better not be
in the bottom this time,
'cause if you are,
you're going home."
Let's do it.
I'm, like, the delinquent.
It's day two and
I'm back in the lab.
Turns out
I had food poisoning.
Yesterday was
a complete waste of day.
So my goal today is to get
the face sculpted and molded.
But I still have
to figure out the concept.
I'm not feeling 100%.
I would say I'm 40%.
Oh, thanks, man.
Right away I know
I have to start
blocking out
the cowl piece.
That's one of the biggest pieces
I have to get done.
As I'm sculpting
I'm always thinking about
how I'm going
to paint this piece
to really bring
this sculpture to life.
And it's kind of scary to me,
'cause I'm always
pushing things
to the last minute
and that can't happen
in this challenge.
I have to get the cowl
and the chest done today,
so I'm going to work on them
at the same time
so I can mold them
at the same time.
I decide to run a latex polyfoam
of my face sculpture
so that I know what it
looks like in three dimensions.
I can use it to sculpt
the rest of my cowl
so that I know
it lines up properly.
Hey, guys.
Michael Westmore
and McKenzie come up
to do their walkabout
through the shop.
It's gonna be interesting
to see what they have to say
about our makeups.
- Hey, House.
- Hello, guys.
So tell us
about your creature.
Well, we're basing it
out of the water.
Kind of a fish-human hybrid.
You know, it's really
important with the paint
to have some direction
as opposed to just spotting it.
That's right.
'Cause, I mean,
whatever you do
with your non-iridescent paint,
you know,
should be highlighted
so it pops the same thing out.
This is a painting challenge.
All right, so tell us
about your creation.
Actually where I got
a lot of the shapes
for my character
were looking at the rocks.
How are you going to end
the back of this?
Um, actually
I'm not too sure yet.
Okay.
- I'm still--
- Working on it?
Yup.
- I would keep the back simple.
- Okay.
Just so you don't
waste time.
My creature, he kind
of comes from the waters
of the rainforest.
He's a mixture between
an amphibious creature
and also like a squid.
My goal is for tomorrow
just to really sell it
in the body painting.
The painting is going
to be very important.
When they switch lights,
it emphasizes what you see
without the light.
- Right.
- Yeah.
I saw this thing
on the beach.
It looked like it was
from another planet.
So I wanted to
incorporate that on this
so at first it will
just look like rocks.
- Like he's a cave person.
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
And then when the lights go on
it will turn into that.
- Oh, nice.
- Mm-hmm.
The ecosystem
that it comes from
is the mangroves
of, like, swamp areas.
So he's gonna
have crab elements.
Very nice.
How are you planning on
picking up
the highlights and shadows?
Uh, I'll probably
do some washes.
And then on the very edge,
I'll probably hit it
with the luminescent paints.
The initial paint job
is so very important.
And then your luminescent one,
just to make everything pop.
- Right.
- You know?
- I'm going for ocean.
- Okay.
My inspiration
is translucency.
So what I did here
was I had actually
sculpted out some inner organ
and bone structure.
Are you going to put silicone
over your latex piece?
Yeah, so that when you see
all the bone structure
illuminate through the silicone.
- I'm going with ocean.
- Okay.
And I'm doing
a female fish-being.
I want to use silicone
this time,
just to kind of give it
more of that fish qualit
- right.
- Mm-hmm.
So we can see into it.
- Is this gonna be luminescent?
- Oh, yes.
- Where it will pop out itself?
Great.
Okay, everybody,
we're heading out.
It's looking great.
Good luck tomorrow.
- Thanks, you guys.
- Bye.
Bye-bye.
The chest sculpture
is complete.
And, it being
a full chest and back,
it's gonna take some time
to make this mold.
My goal is to try to get this
completed by the end of the day.
By the middle of day two,
I'm really rushing on the hands.
They're not as stylized
as I would like.
I just don't think
the sculptures look that great.
But I'm running out of time,
so all I can do
is hope for the best.
I'm looking around the room.
I'm noticing there's
some really great pieces.
- Pulled right out.
- Look at that! Whoo!
I'm starting to worry
about my creature,
considering mine is
so much bigger and crazier.
I love this whole making molds
at the last minute.
I don't know if
I'm gonna pull this off.
But I start
the molding process
and it is taking
longer than expected.
There's still
so much to do.
Time's running out and it's
double elimination this week.
I'm worried about
potentially going home.
Oh, shit.
The black light room
is actually working.
Would you take that in?
Let's test it.
Mr. Westmore and McKenzie
are really exited to see the
face piece that I did
in the black light room.
Your head-band is glowing.
You, girl, you
have white teeth.
McKenzie looks like
* girl.
Thanks a lot!
You gotta have fun, or, you know,
why are you doing this.
♪ I looking like ♪,
lets get out of here.
Guys, it's really fun
in there, you gotta go!
I find myself here
every time.
It's day two,
we've got one hour left,
and I'm running really behind.
I still need
to finish my molds
and all I can do is
forge ahead, guns a-blarin'.
You know,
I could add some more of these
in here
where they're painted.
For the sculpt,
I want to make a Venus flytrap.
So I figured that
I can make the teeth
coming out this way.
So I'm going to take nails
and make them into teeth
and then pull them out
before I mold it.
On top of that,
I'm going to create the leaf
so it looks like the actual face
is more of a plant.
Pretty cool.
I'm exhausted.
I look like shit.
I feel like shit.
But I am not a quitter.
There is a slew
of different UV paints.
So I grab some
and go to the black light room,
and it's glowing.
I'm gonna use this.
This will look cool when
they kick on the black lights.
I want to put
some more yellow in there.
- Does that look lame?
- That'll be cool.
For my character,
I am playing on the idea
of making his hands,
feet, parts of the top
of his head and his back, red
to bring the color pattern
throughout the entire body
as well as to play off
of different amphibians,
like poison dart frogs
who have red extremities.
Oh, that looks cool, man.
I'm just trying to,
like, see how it would layer.
Yeah.
All right.
The end of day two,
I've got all my molds done,
but unfortunately I really
did not get a chance
to test out the paints.
Time's up, guys.
Let's go!
I think the trickiest part
is to be able to pull off
the two paint jobs
that are required.
So I hope it works.
Oh, man!
I'm really upset
this morning.
I have four hours
to get this makeup on
and my foam piece
has huge steam pockets.
Oh, shit.
Steam pockets is when
you're baking your foam rubber--
if there's too much moisture
still accumulated in the molds,
it leaves
really deep, ugly pits.
This right here is easily
an hour out of my day
to try to repair.
This was not in my schedule
for this morning.
- How are you doing?
- Great, man. How are you?
- You're gonna be translucent.
- Ooh.
Application day
is going well.
The pieces are
going together great.
I'm having fun applying,
you know?
I like applying makeups.
I just want to show them
what I can do.
So I'm going
to take my time.
I'm going to make this makeup
look as good
as I can make it look.
The first thing I see
is that my face looks fine.
But I've sculpted
such large gills and fins on her
that they don't quite turn out.
Most of them are
trapped in the mold
and I'm digging them out
and reconstructing them
with cotton and latex.
I'm starting to sweat a bit
because fixing all the gills
is eating
into my work time,
it's eating
into my painting time,
and it's double elimination.
Every minute counts.
After I have
the chest piece applied,
I begin to stencil her back,
her arms, her legs.
And I know by just
turning the stencil
it'll break up
the whole stenciling process,
so it doesn't
look like I'm using it
in the same pattern everywhere.
Looking around the room,
everyone has, like,
four pieces, three pieces,
and my creature is going
to have one piece.
It's not a good feeling,
and I know that,
if I don't get enough done,
I'm going home.
If I could just
cover the chest area
with even latex,
a little cotton, or sand,
maybe it will translate
that it's a beach plant.
Even if the look isn't the best,
I just want a completed look.
Timing on this challenge
is everything.
Now close your eyes.
Keep your mouth closed.
So this is probably
around the last 20 minutes
and I'm basically
just taking him
into the black light room,
and doing a little bit
of spattering on him.
I use some yellows
and greens and whites.
And basically
spatter it up the chest.
As well as put
some strong yellow dots
coming out from the center.
I've got basically
the brunt of my painting done,
but there's still
a lot more painting to do.
15 minutes, everybody.
Everyone has paint on them.
They have almost
all their pieces on,
and it's, like,
here we go again,
falling back
in those same footsteps
the judges always
tell me not to.
That's time, guys!
I'm really stressing out.
It's a challenge that
I'm very familiar with.
So to fall behind on this one,
I'm kind of letting
myself down in a way.
Coming up...
I may be going home
on this one.
Fuck.
You have to understand more
about these choices.
I could see that on Pandora.
Go, go, go, go.
Walking into last looks,
one of the first things I do
is start painting the legs.
Can you turn back
around for me? Thanks.
We're about
to get crazy now.
I have so much to do.
I'm gluing latex to her,
I'm stretching the veins,
I have her blow-drying,
'cause I'm gluing veins on.
All I can do is just work
like a madman to get this done.
I'm in the UV room
checking my luminescent paint.
I'm probably not
utilizing them in the best way,
but whatever happens,
happens.
Ten minutes, everyone!
At this point
I don't even have
any bioluminescence
paint on at all.
I'm putting it
in my airbrush
and I'm just
outlining the black.
I'm very, very worried that
I may be going home on this one.
Time, guys!
Fuck.
Welcome to
theFace Offreveal stage.
Tonight, two of you
will be eliminated.
Say hello to your judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
- Evening.
Three time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
Hi, guys.
- Hi.
Creature and concept designer,
Neville Page.
Hello, everyone.
- Hello.
And joining
our panel this week...
he's an Oscar-winning producer
whose work includes
the two highest-grossing movies
of all time,
Titanic and Avatar.
Please give a warm welcome
to John Landau.
Howdy.
He's probably one of
the most successful producers
in movie history.
And if he doesn't
know these creatures,
nobody does.
John, thank you so much
for being here tonight.
It's a pleasure to be here.
I'm very excited to
see what we have in store.
This week, your spotlight
challenge was to create
a new species that could exist
in one of Earth's ecosystems.
But it also had to
have two very distinct looks.
One in normal light
and another visible
only under ultraviolet light.
So let's see
what you come up with.
The glow is stopping
at the top of her head
and a lot of the colors
that I added
just got masked over
with regular paint.
And I feel I let myself down
on this one.
My character comes out and
I'm noticing all of the flaws.
There's some part of me that
feels like I didn't do enough.
It looks good,
especially from a distance.
He's bold, but I'm thinking
he's bold in a good way.
Black light kicks on,
and I'm okay with it.
I'm not 100% confident,
but it is what it is.
I'm worried that they're not
going to understand the concept.
I really don't
have a backstory.
Even though I didn't get
to take it where I wanted to,
I still think
it looks really cool.
You can see the fins
and everything,
so I'm really
excited about it.
So at this point
I can just hope for the best.
My black light effects
work great.
It's gonna help compensate
for the fact that
my ambient lighting paint's
not so hot.
Judges, why don't you
take a closer look?
Yeah.
Now is all of this
black light?
Is that why the color
is so different?
No, I don't think so.
I think all we saw on this guy
is just splotches.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's just splotches.
The judges have gone in
for their closer looks,
and it's making me
very, very nervous.
And this being a double
elimination does not help.
The paint is rubbing off
of the foam right there.
There are some
pieces up there
that have a more
complete look than mine
and that may
do me in this time.
Now is all
of this black light?
Is that why the color
is so different?
No, I don't think so.
I think all we saw on this guy
is just splotches.
Yeah, just the splotches.
The judges have gone in
for their closer looks
and I'm very, very nervous.
This being a double elimination
does not help.
This is all really cool.
Yeah, it has
so much more detail.
There's a lot of frickin' work
in that thing.
Pretty complicated paint job.
I think this one's
really, really inventive,
the sculpture elements
happening with this.
Interesting things
happening through here.
These leaves sculpted in.
You're on your own
on that one, man.
- This is cool.
- Oh, yeah.
- Even better close up.
- Yeah.
Really nice job.
Perhaps we have an artist
who said the challenge
is all about the change
to the bioluminescent version
of this thing,
and that's a risky decision.
The judges would now
like to speak with each of you
to learn more
about your work.
Kris, you're up first.
Kris, can you
explain your design?
She's a humanoid
from the deep.
I used a silicone prosthetic
for the face,
a foam latex chest,
everything else
is pretty much paint.
It feels like a stylized
sort of '60s, '70s approach
to the makeup,
and I think that's brilliant.
To take a stylized version
that would allow you to work
in broad strokes was
a really intelligent way
about approaching this.
I think that there's
some really adventurous forms
that you're applying
to the body,
particularly in the belly
and just around the chest.
There are some
pretty cool things going on.
I think this looks much better
under the black light
than it does this way.
I don't like the leaf treatment
of the lower region.
I think you would have been
much better off just leaving her
really sleek looking.
When you're
designing characters,
they need to have expression.
And I think that's
a tough mouth design
to get to really convey
any of that emotion.
- Kris, please step back.
- Thank you.
House, please step forward.
House, tell me
about your concept.
I was thinking of an ancient
race of fish-human people,
and I wanted something familiar,
yet beautiful.
She's definitely
familiar looking.
Beautiful? I would not
say she's beautiful.
I'm not too thrilled
with the way she appears
under the black light,
and the hands are
absolutely atrocious.
The graphics around the chest,
on the arms,
they don't feel even
like it's organized chaos.
You have to understand
a little bit more
about these choices.
I really don't like
the colors.
It doesn't have
the purposeful asymmetry
of what mother nature
does in a fish.
House, please step back.
Anthony, you're up.
All right, Anthony,
tell us about your concept.
He's kind of
an amphibious creature
and the bioluminescence
of the character
is attributed to age and rank.
There's some really
beautiful things here.
There's a lot
of asymmetry with it,
but it's okay
because it feels natural.
- It's a beautiful looking piece.
- Thank you.
I love that you tied
the extremities together.
Not just, you know,
the feet and the hands,
but also the top of the head,
and I could see that
on Pandora.
Good job, all in all.
I love the fact that when
the bioluminescence comes up,
it's green.
It was just so cool.
It was completely unexpected.
And I thought that was
really beautifully done.
You did an amazing job.
- Anthony, please step back.
- Thanks, guys.
- Meagan.
- Thanks.
So, Meagan, tell me about
the concept behind this design.
I wanted it to look
like a Venus flytrap,
but inside a cave.
I had no idea,
when I saw the character,
what the concept was.
Instead of being organic,
I think you were
trying to mix, you know,
too many things
and for me,
unfortunately, this missed.
What I don't understand is,
if he's a Venus flytrap
and you have
these leaf elements,
why they aren't delineated
with a different color of paint
so that you can
at least see what you did.
How do you feel
about your work this week?
I was actually sick
the first day
and I'm okay with it
because it's completed.
I think I would swallow that
a little bit better
if we had something
really great,
even if it was something small
that was really great.
So I'm terribly disappointed.
I have to be honest.
- Meagan, please step back.
- Thank you.
Wayne.
Wayne, tell us about
what you were thinking
when you put this together.
I wanted to go
with a crab theme.
I had more that
I wanted to do to it
with the big vacuform claws,
but I had to conserve my time.
There's a lot
about what you've done
that I absolutely love.
Significant improvements
over some of the stuff
that you've done
in the past.
I think that
you're presenting
a really solid
piece of work here.
You really didn't
make the black light half
of the challenge
come to life for me,
but I have to give you the kudos
to the sculpture on the face.
It's just absolutely gorgeous.
Thank you.
So I think this is a piece
that works better
when you're close up to it
than when you're far away.
But I think the detail
that you got right in the face
was a great job.
- Thank you.
- Wayne, please step back.
Eric Z.
Eric, tell me
about your concept.
He's a tough guy,
he's a brawler,
and he's a cave dweller.
He lives on the beach,
in the caverns and in the caves.
For me, he just looks
like a big cookie monster.
What happened with
your bioluminescence paint job?
I had some designs on his face
and on the back of his head,
so I decided to go back in
with the regular makeup
and, like, enhance some things
and that covered up
some of the bioluminescence
that I had done on the face.
You have got to
do better than this.
If you brought this out
as a character
for us to consider
putting on film,
I'd say, "absolutely not."
I look at this and
I don't see any originality.
Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry,
it just did not work.
Eric, please step back.
Eric F.
You got a lot
of explaining to do.
- What's this all about?
- It's unfinished.
I was going to go with
a translucent
jellyfish type approach,
and I ran short on time.
I think it's a really,
really bold concept.
It's a great idea.
But she does look best
with the bioluminescence.
When you went
to the bioluminescence,
I felt like we were
getting to see the bones
and the inner structure.
Yeah, that's--
Yet the ribs
weren't bioluminescent.
It would have all brought it
much better together for me
had you been able,
you know, to do that.
I love the way her legs look
when she lights up
under the black light.
I thought she looked fabulous.
So there you go.
Thank you, Ve.
Eric, please step back.
The judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you would please
head back to the makeup room
while they make their decisions.
All right, guys,
why don't we start
with the looks you like
the most this week?
Let's begin with Anthony.
So good.
It was a creature
without bioluminescence
that transformed
with the bioluminescence.
He did a great job.
Of everyone up there,
he's the only one who did that.
It was genius.
All right,
let's move on to Wayne.
He's got a really, really
mature artistic sensibility
when it comes
to sculpture and form.
Often times people design and
it looks good from one angle,
but here you were able
to turn his head
and you saw
little details coming out
and it all played together.
I don't think
I've ever seen
a chest sculpted that way.
That's impressive to me.
All right, let's move on
to the bottom looks of the week.
Let's start with House.
Been there, done that
a little bit, you know?
Yeah.
I feel that something
didn't pop out as original.
You want familiar touchstones,
but the overall impression
can't be familiar.
And the paint job
is so bad.
It's bad paint
over coarse sculpting.
All right,
let's move on to Meagan,
who as you know
was very, very sick.
I get that, but I don't know
that it would have made
a huge difference,
to be honest.
I think the concept
wasn't bad.
She did not have an idea.
When she tried
to articulate what it was--
you have a Venus flytrap
and it's opening this way
on a face.
Let's move on to Eric Z.
I don't know
what he was thinking of.
He said he's a rabble-rouser
or whatever-- it's, like, really?
What was he rousing, you know?
A bunch of bakers?
There seemed
to be no thought
to the specific design
of the head.
- Mm-hmm.
- It was strange.
And the bioluminescent makeup
looked like child's
finger-painting.
Yeah.
Okay, judges, have you
made your decisions?
- I think so.
- Yup.
- Yeah.
- We have.
Let's bring them back out.
Glenn, tell us about
the top looks tonight.
Anthony, your sculpting
this week was phenomenal.
And the amount
of conceptual work
that you did from the beginning
was truly impressive.
Wayne, some of the moments
in your sculpting this week
really stood out.
It's an extremely
unique piece of work.
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner of tonight's
challenge is...
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner of
tonight's challenge is...
Anthony.
Your creature was a standout
in both lighting conditions.
Very, very strong work.
Thank you guys so much.
Thank you.
It's so humbling again to win,
especially when one of
the guest judges is John Landau.
It's one of those geek moments
that, you know,
I'll never forget.
Anthony, congratulations.
You and Wayne can head
back to the makeup room.
Kris and Eric F,
you are also safe.
Please head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you again.
Unfortunately,
that means the rest of you
are on the bottom this week,
and two of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
House, there were
some fundamental flaws
with both function and form
in your makeup this week.
The finished product
was kind of rough.
Meagan, we realize
that you had some physical
struggles this week,
but the finished makeup
was devoid
of any recognizable design.
Eric, we didn't see
any really original ideas
in your makeup.
It just didn't work.
So who is the first person
going home tonight?
The first person
going home tonight is...
Meagan.
You really struggled with
your time management this week
and unfortunately you
just weren't able to recover.
You know, Meagan, one thing
I have to give you credit for
is yours was really
the only land-based design.
And I think that was
really great and bold,
and take that
forward with you.
Thank you.
Meagan, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
It has been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you so much.
I wish I did
a cleaner makeup.
Even if it was one piece,
made sure that piece
looked amazing.
That is my biggest,
biggest regret.
- Oh, stop.
- I'm gonna miss you.
Glenn, who is the second
person going home tonight?
The second person
going home tonight is...
Eric Z.
We had major issues on nearly
every level with your creature.
I'm afraid that you just
lost your way this week.
Eric, I'm sorry but
you have been eliminated.
That means, House,
you are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
See you, bud.
Eric, I think you've done
some really great things
on this show.
And I'm absolutely certain that
you will grow in the future.
Thank you so much, Glenn.
Eric, it's been great
having you here with us.
Would you please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit?
Thank you, guys, so much.
- Good luck.
- See you, Eric.
Thank you.
I'm really bummed out
that I got eliminated.
There's a big part of me that
knows that I have more to offer.
I'm going back
to Texas, y'all.
- Aw, man!
- Oh, my God!
- We all love each other, yo.
- We do.
Big one.
This experience
was a roller coaster,
but if you're not
gonna challenge yourself,
what's the point?
I know that I am
capable of doing so much more
and I'm so lucky
to have had this experience.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net