This is a search for the next
great name in movie magic.
Face Off is back
for our biggest season ever.
14 talented makeup artists
will take the ultimate plunge
in a competition
unlike any other.
That's just freakin' crazy.
They'll face
breathtaking challenges.
Your challenge is to create
a Goblin King.
But wait, there's more.
She has some kind
of crazy twist.
- Bioluminescence.
- Wow.
- Create a werewolf.
- This is gonna be awesome.
- An original giant character.
- Oh, my God.
- They went big.
- It's freaking cold.
- Unbelievable deadlines.
- Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Fuck.
- I can't do this shit.
- Take it off.
- Just take it off.
- I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
It's a disaster.
Some of the most talented
artists in Face Off history.
I'm really blown away.
Along the way they'll come
face to face
with industry titans.
You guys really pulled it off.
It's a great silhouette
and a great first impression.
But to come out on top,
they'll have to impress
our award-winning panel
of judges--
Ve Neill, three-time
Oscar-winning makeup artist
whose work includes
Beetlejuice,
The Hunger Games
Catching Fire, and The Host.
I think you did a great job.
Glenn Hetrick,
cutting edge makeup artist
on CSI New York, The Hunger
Games Catching Fire,
and costume
designer for Lady Gaga.
I'm pretty thrilled
with this to be honest with you.
And Neville Page, creature and
concept designer on Star Trek,
Green Lantern, and Tron Legacy.
It's fantastic.
In the end, only one will win
the opportunity
to be a guest lecturer
at Make Up For Ever's academies
in New York and Paris,
the all-new 2013 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Our contestants
have just arrived in Los Angeles
and are on their way
to meet me here
on the beautiful Queen Mary
for their first challenge.
My name is Alam, and I'm
originally from South Korea.
I recently graduated
makeup effects school.
I know the other artists may
have more experience, but I know
I have a lot of creativity,
and I'm passionate.
My name is Michael.
My brother is Matt Valentine
from season two.
Being here means
I finally broke the barrier
so people will see
I have talent on my own.
I'm my own person.
I want to make a name
for myself
and get out of his shadow.
I'm Wayne.
I'm a self-taught artist.
I was awarded the Dick Smith
scholarship legends of makeup.
It was a $10,000 scholarship
for cinema makeup school.
Winning Face Off
would be huge to me.
It would make my dreams come
true, because I would like
to have
my own special effects shop
within about five years or so.
- Hi, how are you?
- Hi, I'm Alex. How are you?
- I'm Wayne. Nice to meet you.
- Wayne, nice to meet you.
I've been working
in special effects
for approximately
ten years now.
My husband and I have a company,
and we've done everything
from music videos to TV shows.
Isn't this place,
like, haunted?
I think so.
Hi. Meagan.
I do beauty.
I do high fashion effects.
I also do hair.
My ultimate goal
in the effects world is to get
to the status of Ve Neill.
I hope you don't get mad
when I win.
No, I'm joking.
My name is Eric Fox,
and I make monsters.
I've worked in indie films
for over 16 years.
Specialize in horror.
Specialize in everything that
normal people don't wanna touch.
When I walk away
with that 100 grand,
I can actually be able
to provide for my kids,
my wife, the way that I should.
Got another one.
Hi.
Katie.
I currently freelance
as a makeup artist.
I grew up
in a small coastal town,
and I was
kind of like a little rebel.
My dad was an artist.
He passed away due to cancer.
I get a lot of my creativity
from him,
so to think,
if he could see me here,
he would be totally blown away.
- Anthony.
- I'm Autumn.
As all the contestants
are walking in,
I notice right away
that we are all different.
I mean, we obviously have, like,
jocks here with the goth kids.
This is definitely
an interesting group of people.
Look who's here!
- Oh!
- Whoo!
McKenzie comes walking in,
and everybody goes...
- Hey.
- Oh.
Hey, everyone.
Welcome aboard the beautiful
Queen Mary
and another season of Face Off.
Is this really starting?
Somebody, just pinch me
right now.
Once upon a time, this was
the grandest ocean liner
in the world,
carrying Hollywood royalty
and true royals
like Queen Elizabeth.
That brings us to your first
foundation challenge.
From Shakespeare In Love
to Alice In Wonderland
to Cleopatra,
Hollywood films are filled
with an incredible array
of memorable queen characters.
So your foundation challenge is
to select one of these crowns
and use it to inspire
an original queen character
that shows us who you are
as an artist.
I'm going back and forth from
McKenzie to the crown I want.
Because this is the very first chance
to showcase
what I can bring
to this competition.
The stakes are huge here,
guys, because the winner
will earn immunity
and cannot be eliminated
from this week's
spotlight challenge.
Hell, yeah.
I want to win immunity so bad,
because, at the end of the day,
who wants to be safe?
Everyone does.
Before I begin,
I'd like to introduce you
to your judge
for today's challenge.
He is an Oscar
and nine-time Emmy award-winning
makeup artist.
Please say hello to my dad,
Michael Westmore.
Holy crap.
This guy is a definite pioneer
in the makeup effects industry.
I am so excited.
Thank you so much
for being here.
- Pleasure.
- What you guys don't know
is he's not only your judge
for this foundation challenge,
he's also going to be
your mentor for the season.
Oh, yeah!
- Wow.
- That is cool.
- So cool.
- He'll be coming
by the lab each week
to give you advice
and share his years
of experience
to help you make
the best creations possible.
The one and only wonderful
Michael Westmore.
That definitely
takes my breath away.
Being mentored by Michael
Westmore will be amazing.
I'm gonna have the creative
insight that he's had
for all these years.
I'm looking forward to it too.
What are you going
to be looking for
from these guys today
in their makeups?
Well, the makeup and the crown
must complement each other
and tell a story.
I want to see the both of them
really working together.
All right, let's bring out
your models.
You have a huge selection
of wardrobe and accessories
to help create your characters.
And you've got two hours
to complete your makeups.
On my go, grab a crown
and get started.
Not yet, not yet!
Your time starts now!
Damn you.
Wow, that sucks.
I really wanted the black one.
- It's crazy.
- Everybody wanted that one.
It's insanity.
My first pick actually
had got taken by Alex,
but I'm really happy
with the crown that I got
'cause it's basically my style.
So my queen's actually gonna be
the queen of lost souls.
Normally when you think queen,
you think beauty,
and with this I kinda want
to go for the opposite.
My name's Autumn.
I'm a part-time
special effects artist
and full-time
stay-at-home mom.
I've been working
on independent films,
doing lots of blood and guts
and death and dismemberments.
And I would like
to work on things
that my child
could be proud of,
instead of hiding what
I'm doing in the basement.
All right, relax.
Breathe.
Okay.
Okay, look up for me.
My name is Troy.
I do beauty makeup.
From my perspective
in the black community,
makeup is not gangster.
Where I'm from,
there's not a whole lot
going on in this industry.
So, as far as I'm concerned,
it's my last chance.
All right, let's get
a little bit of this.
She's a warrior princess
whose father was murdered,
so she revenges his death.
And I'm actually using
a chip brush
to kind of splatter
the makeup onto the skin
so it looks more broken up
like a real blood pattern would.
- How about the queen of scars?
- Ooh.
My name's Kris.
For the last 15 years,
I've been teaching and working
at makeup effects houses,
gaining all this knowledge
and experience.
Ultimately, being in this
competition,
I just would love to make
my family and kids proud of me.
My name is Eric Zapata.
I am the youngest contestant
here.
My friends that I met in film
school,
we decided to open up
our own film production company,
and we do all aspects of film,
whether if it's a commercial
or music video.
Glue your ear.
I picked this crown over here.
I wanted to pick something
that was a little more real
and organic,
so right now I'm just pasting
those prosthetic ears,
and then grease paint
so I can go back over them
later on
and bring it back
more to her skin tone.
I picked this crown
with the feathers on it.
And it immediately makes me
think of a warrior queen.
That to me is
a personification of myself,
because in 2008 I was diagnosed
with ovarian cancer.
And during that my husband left
and I lost my job,
but I came out of it
a stronger woman.
And for the first time
in my life,
I'm finally doing
what makes me happy.
Do you want it
on top of your nose?
Guys, we have one hour left!
Okay.
My name's Anthony.
I own my own effects company.
When I was 16, I created
my first foam latex mask.
I was tired of all the stuff
you saw in the Halloween stores
and knew I could do better.
I'm a very competitive person.
I think this will definitely
take me to the next level.
I'm trying to create some kind
of an alien queen creature.
She's gonna have a bunny nose.
Why not?
We'll see where it goes.
I've worn more makeups
on myself
than I've done on other people.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
My name is David Greathouse.
Everyone calls me House.
I had a fascination
with monsters
probably since the age
of three,
so I've spent my whole life
in haunted houses
and low-budget films.
I've scared thousands of people,
thousands.
I chose the golden crown,
and I'm taking influence
from the Queen Mary ship,
and there's lots of gold
around us,
so she's the queen of currency.
My queen, she's evil.
She lives, like, in the woods,
kind of like a Halloween kind
of evil queen.
And she has, like, all these
injuries in her face and stuff
because, like,
she's been through a lot of,
like, bar fights.
Man, she wasted
that damn crown.
Five minutes left.
All right, everybody,
time is up!
Brushes down.
- Hi, Troy.
- Hello.
Hi, Troy, Mike Westmore.
So explain your concept to us.
I wanted to go more
for a warrior type princess.
I also wanted
to use my beauty skills
as well as my effects skills.
It's a nice, subtle
beauty makeup,
but you selected a crown
that is so ornate
that, to me, it calls out
for more fantasy.
- Gotcha.
- I kinda grew up in, like,
unicorns and rainbows,
and so I think
this really reflects
my kind of style.
I saw that crown and immediately
thought ice queen.
And this whole room
and all these costumes,
it reminded me of, like,
a masquerade kind of party.
Well, I think, by saying
masquerade, it totally justifies
- what you did around the eyes.
- Yeah.
- Nice job.
- Great, thank you so much.
She's the queen of scars,
and, instead of blood,
there's magical glitter.
Mm-hm.
It doesn't look like a scar.
It looks
like a slash of glitter.
Give it some third dimension,
so that it isn't just laying
on the surface of the skin.
Whoa.
This is the queen
of absent souls.
- I believe it.
- Basically, I didn't get
- a prosthetic--
- You put it all together.
Yeah. This is just pieced--
random pieces to--
I'm a very outside-the-box
thinker.
- I try to...
- Yes, you are.
...go big.
I think you've been able to
put together the whole package.
Thank you so much.
She's a princess,
and her mother was cast
into the underworld,
so now she's heir
to the throne.
I was trying to keep her
really young,
tried to focus a lot of
the attention on the eyes.
I'm not thrilled
with the makeup,
'cause I think
you missed the concept
of trying to bring
the crown you selected
into her face to be able
to tell a whole story.
The paint across her face
is worn like a badge of honor.
I really like that.
I think
it's a very creative thought.
And how does this
represent you as an artist?
I've been through a lot of
trials and tribulations
in my life, so I love to create
my inner strength
and put it into a makeup.
Well, I think you did that.
I think you were very successful
in doing it.
I love playing with color.
I'm a painter,
so that's kinda why I tried
bringing as much color into her
as much as possible.
I think you've done
such a good job
this could actually shoot
on film.
Oh, thank you.
I am so humbled and taken back
and almost geeked out to the
fact that he said what he said.
But looking around and just
seeing for the first time
what everybody's capable of
and trying
to measure up how mine
compares with everybody else,
some of them
are really beautiful.
I feel a little intimidated.
All right, so who created
our top looks of the day?
Eric F.
It was a very creative,
out-of-the-box makeup
that showed us
who you really are as an artist.
- Thank you so much.
- Anthony...
your makeup was the total
package from head to toe.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Jenna, your makeup utilized
your personal strength.
It was very subtle
and well applied.
That's a real honor.
Thank you.
Okay, dad, who is the winner
of this foundation challenge?
The winner is...
Coming up...
- Fuck.
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
This is looking like sabotage.
I'm really blown away.
Okay, dad, who is the winner
of our first
foundation challenge?
The winner is...
Anthony.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Whoo!
Good job.
Yours was the only piece
I think
that could be put on film
and literally work.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
I can't believe it.
I'm coming out of the gates
with immunity.
Just means that I'm not
gonna get kicked off
this next challenge,
and that is huge.
All right, why don't you guys
go check out your new house?
I'll see you tomorrow for
your first spotlight challenge.
Thank you.
- Oh, my God. This is awesome.
- Wow!
- This is cute.
- Sweet.
Oh, my God.
Wow, this is where
we're gonna live?
I'm super stoked.
- Wow.
- Bigger room here.
- Awesome.
- Whoo!
- Check at the view.
- The house is super cool.
Now I wanna see the rest.
There's just a room
that's got pictures
of all the past contestants.
And just knowing
that you're gonna be
one of them
on that wall one day.
It's beautiful, 'cause it's
on top of this big mountain,
and you have
this beautiful view.
- The winner has to toast it.
- All right, guys.
- This is gonna be an adventure.
- Here, here.
- Cheers!
- To Face Off, guys.
To Face Off.
The morning
of the spotlight challenge,
we're walking down the street,
and we see
this beautiful cathedral.
Amazing, amazing architecture.
And I'm so excited.
I'm thinking,
what could the challenge be?
Wow.
Welcome
to St. John's Cathedral.
This masterpiece
was built in 1925
and is one of
the most recognizable examples
of gothic-style architecture
in the city of Los Angeles.
It's gorgeous.
Now, not only are cathedrals
a place of worship,
but they have
also historically been
the place
where royalty are crowned.
Your first spotlight challenge
will start
right where we left off.
You've already created a queen.
Now it's time
to make your king.
However,
this is no ordinary king.
You'll be making a mythical
creature featured in films
like The Hobbit, Labyrinth,
and even
the Harry Potter series.
Your spotlight challenge
is to create a Goblin King.
Yes.
Many things are running
through my mind.
Goblins are obviously
very scary creatures,
so I'm really getting excited.
But what would a king be
without his kingdom?
The ancient world
shown on this map
has been divided
into geographic regions.
Your Goblin Kings
must be physically influenced
by the lands that they rule.
You're going to be working
in teams of two.
Your teams have already been
randomly selected, and they are...
Jenna and Eric F.
Me and Jenna were top looks
in the foundation challenge,
so I know we're gonna nail this.
Michael and Troy.
Alex and Wayne.
Alam and Kris.
Anthony and Meagan.
In my mind it's, like, really
great that I'm working with him,
because he is
an amazing painter,
but at the same time
he has immunity.
Katie and House.
Eric Z and Autumn.
Will you please go ahead
and stand next to your teammate?
Team one, you're up first.
- Desert.
- Team two.
Ooh.
- Volcanic.
- Alex and Wayne.
Swamp.
- Alam and Kris.
- Our choice is the forest.
Anthony and Meagan.
- Definitely the mountains.
- Arctic.
Jungle.
And before you leave here
today, I want you
to take some inspiration
from this incredible cathedral
and get started
on your sketches.
When you're done,
head back to the lab,
select your models,
and get to work.
Good luck.
I think he needs a staff.
He needs a staff and his tunic
will be like his cape.
Yeah, that'd be cool.
Yeah, yeah.
That'd be awesome.
Me and Troy sit down to sketch,
because the first step
in creating any makeup
is to get a good, solid design.
We need dark black around the
eyes and black inside the eyes.
That'd be creepy.
Our concept
is a volcanic dark king
who doesn't have a kingdom,
so what he does is
takes over other kingdoms.
That looks pretty cool, maybe
for some armor or something?
Right now we're just working
on overall visual concept.
We're going
for a very dry, emaciated look.
Lots of sand textures.
- Very heavy cracking--
- Cracking.
We are doing
the mountain Goblin King.
There's so much you can do
with mountains.
There's such an aesthetic
about it.
And I'm thinking
about how his heart
is made out of stone
and he's so evil
that it's just consuming him
and turning him completely
into stone from the inside out.
Our Goblin King is the forest.
He's going to be a wood texture
with a pine tree beard.
Kris really know
what he's doing.
He's been around, like,
long time,
and he comes up with this really
good tree-looking face.
So, like, why don't
we do branches for a crown
and wood arms?
Love your sketch.
I wish I could draw like that.
What rules the swamp
is usually alligators
- and crocodiles--
- Exactly.
We're both from Florida,
so I think right off the bat
that we knew what we wanted.
He's gonna be this gator king
of the swamp,
so he's gonna have
a lot of, like, scale
and a lot of texture to him.
Like, even if we did, like,
some type of fin
- that was webbed around it.
- I like that.
All right, guys, that's time.
Let's rock this.
We leave the cathedral, and we
can't wait to get to the lab.
- Oh, my God!
- Whoo!
Wow.
Walking into the lab, I feel
like a kid in a candy store.
- They have everything here.
- I'm stoked.
- I love Make Up For Ever.
- Yeah.
Lifecasts.
The lifecast is a stone copy
of the model's face,
and first thing we have to do
is choose our models.
We're doing a wood creature,
so we pick Maleek
because he has
a nice dark skin tone like wood.
Our concept of a Goblin King
is to make him out of wood,
very tribal,
kind of like a tiki warrior.
Nice to meet you, Tim.
We only have five hours.
I'm gonna start laying the
foundation of wed clay on this.
The next step
to creating a prosthetic
is putting clay on a cast
of the model's face.
Do you think this should
all be one piece or two pieces?
- One piece.
- One piece, okay.
Our plan of attack
is sculpt the face,
sculpt the chest today.
We'll need razor blades
to start shaving down icicles.
Yeah, yeah.
The concept that we're going for
is that he's
kind of this, like,
decaying king
of this ice kingdom.
The first thing I start doing
is start hacking away
at all these foam tubes
that we're going to turn
into the icicle hands.
And house begins sculpting
the face, and he's really fast.
Immediately I'm sculpting it
in mind
for it being a silicone
appliance, because it needs
the icy translucency
that silicone provides.
I'm gonna get started.
Okay.
Fuck, dude.
- Damn, I'm sorry.
- Oh, my God.
He drops it.
There's not, like,
three casts back there
that we can work on.
This is the only one.
Fuck.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- Okay, I can fix this.
It's all good.
Anthony has immunity,
and he broke our form.
That sucks.
And it could be my ass
that's going home.
I'm sculpting the chest,
and we're adding
some nice pecs,
which I was having some
difficulty with...
What I wanted was a full front
picture of somebody's body,
that's what I wanted.
Where is Beefcake, man?
- Yeah. - He's, you know,
take out his shirt for a sec.
Beefcake is Wayne.
I believe he was
a football player.
He is very muscular...
He is like your dream beefcake.
That's one studly dude.
I'm gonna get started.
- Fuck, dude.
- Damn.
So we only get this one cast,
and Anthony drops it.
- Such an ass.
- I just totally
did not mean that.
And it's the nose
that he broke.
This is so bad.
It's good.
I can fix this.
He's gonna have to handle it.
I can't--
I have to walk away.
I can't believe he dropped it.
- Fuck.
- What happened?
He dropped his life--
the lifecast.
It's 'cause he has immunity.
I told Meagan that would happen.
All I'm thinking is
this is looking like sabotage.
Fuck.
In this moment, I can't panic.
I can't think
about anything else
other than fixing this nose.
So I immediately glue
that big chunk to his nose,
and I start sculpting the other
side with palmer's epoxy
which hardens in about five
minutes to match his form
the best that I possibly can.
- That looks good, Anthony.
- Thank you.
Told you I'll fix it.
I fixed it, but it sets us back
about a half hour.
It means that I have to go
and sculpt that much faster
to get this face done.
That's looking good, man.
I know I wanna sculpt the face.
I have Eric start
sculpting out the arms.
- This is just the wrong angle--
- Right, right, right.
Look, the muscles,
they go this way.
I'm struggling a little bit
because I feel like I'm a little
underestimated by my partner.
Yeah, you actually can cut
that whole piece off right here.
That's gonna be way thick.
Eric is wonderful to work with.
He has no pride.
He's completely humble.
- You're such a good boy.
- What am I, some dog here?
It's going very well.
I think we're the first ones
to be making our molds.
- Yep.
- After your sculpture is done,
you make a mold.
You take
a cement-like substance,
brush it onto your sculpture.
Once the substance hardens,
you can clean out the clay
and then fill it with your foam
latex, silicone, or latex.
That's what happens when you
put two bad asses together.
Hell, yeah.
That's freakin' incredible.
Just all that, like, dude,
look at that.
Thanks, man, that means a lot.
In the time that you did it.
The day's almost over,
and right now
everything's going really well.
Looking around the room, like,
yeah, a lot of people
have a lot of, like,
hands and feet stuff going on,
but our sculpture
is definitely full of detail
that they don't have.
Time's up everybody!
It is extremely intimidating
that Eric and Jenna
are the only team
that have their molds
ready to go.
It seems like it will take
a team of four or five people
to do the work
that they're doing,
and there's just two of them.
Yes.
So it's day two in the lab,
and we have a lot to do.
It looks so freakin' cool.
- Like my six-pack?
- Yeah.
I've been working out.
Eric starts working
on the skull
that's gonna go on the crown,
and I start sculpting
in wed clay the skin.
Our plan of attack, since we
have so much skin to cover,
we can pour up large sheets
that we can wrap
around the actor
to give the full body
that really cool sandy, cracked
desert floor look.
Yeah!
That looks great.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you.
What if we made the crown...
like a volcano?
Our king needs a crown.
You can't be a king
without a crown.
And I assume--
what's a volcano?
Volcanoes are pointy-shaped,
so from there
I try to figure out,
how am I going to make
this crown?
I'm gonna get some silicone.
This is a risk doing this makeup
out of silicone.
The weight of the silicone
might be too much
for the makeup.
Foam latex is the tried
and true material.
Silicone, when done right,
can be stunningly beautiful,
but do it wrong,
and you may not have
another chance at it.
Hey, guys!
We're here to do a walk-through
and let you get
some tips and advice.
All right.
Having Michael Westmore
as a mentor is awesome.
It gives me confidence knowing
that I'm going to have someone
like him guiding me
through this process.
We're doing a headpiece,
a chest piece,
and an arm as well--
- And a face.
- It's going to look
like there's a mountain
coming out of his heart.
- Some rocks forming.
- You've got a great direction.
One thing that's gonna be
very important here
is your paint job.
Do a little sample
before you jump into something.
You don't realize it
until you really take a rock
and you look at it
and you realize
how many colors are really
in there, light and dark.
- Thank you.
- This is the Goblin King
of the Arctic,
and this is a shot of his face.
His face will be in silicone.
Are you planning
on coloring it a certain way?
Yeah.
Whites and blues underneath.
A lot of intrinsic painting.
Ice has so much depth
and luminosity to it.
- You might try a little thing--
- Like mixing it just right in.
With glitter or if you have
something small
like a fish scale.
We are going
almost
like a tiki jungle warrior.
We have him
all carved out of wood.
I have knots for ears
that go up into points
that are almost like a crown.
It looks great here in clay
but once it gets painted,
all of a sudden,
it could flatten out.
Any texture we don't achieve
with the sculpture, we should go
- in with paint and just--
- Yes.
Try to create as much depth
as possible with paint.
Yeah, yeah.
A brush
that has nice long furrow on it.
Okay.
We're incorporating elements
that you would find
in the desert such
as, like, tumbleweeds--
- Animal bones.
What are you gonna use
for a crown?
For a crown we're actually
using part of the tumbleweeds,
and, when it's tied in,
it'll have, like,
a really cool, like,
gold crown effect.
- Excellent.
- He's pretty much wood,
and we're gonna build
a stick crown for him.
Wow, very nice.
When they walk, though,
these are going to flatten.
I'm sure they'll probably move
and bend a little bit.
It would help putting a wire
coat hanger down on a few of 'em
maybe, 'cause a few of 'em
might just help the rest of 'em
as a bridge.
That's a good idea.
He's a king with no kingdom
who also hunts other kings.
- Oh.
- He's conquering
the other kings
in this challenge in a way.
It's almost a crown,
but it's like a big volcanic--
volcano on his head.
And then possibly give him
a shield as well.
You've picked a character
where you have
a lot of detailing
that you have to work on.
Yeah, we wanted
to kinda keep it pretty simple
as far as how many pieces
we actually had to apply.
- Mm-hmm.
- So we can concentrate
the rest of that time
on the actual paint.
Good.
- Wow.
- Oh, wow.
I love the protrusions
that you've carried through
from the back here
into the mold here,
the alligator theme
and the alligator skull.
Color-wise,
you gonna bring any...
- We're going...
- Greens into that?
Very reptilian.
Yeah, we're going-- the greens.
- Real alligator.
- Yeah.
And, you know, I think
it's a good idea too.
- Yeah.
- As much painting
as you can do,
it's gonna be important.
What are your thoughts overall
with everybody, first off?
Overall, I think
everybody's doing a great job,
- although I have a favorite.
- Mm?
With the alligator makeup.
They're doing a beautiful job
doing it.
I'm concerned
about how they complete
their detailing
and their painting.
Okay, is there anybody
that you are definitely
concerned about?
- Mostly is the Arctic.
- Really?
Yeah, any time you get
into ice and snow,
you could run into problems.
It has to have a sheen to it.
It has to sell a different--
a whole different texture.
That's interesting.
Then we have jungle.
Wood always concerns me,
because it really has
to look like wood,
or it doesn't.
So their problem again is
going to be in the paint job.
- Mm.
- To be able to sell
the idea
that it is a piece of wood,
not just
a brown fantasy character.
All right, guys,
it's looking great!
- Good luck tomorrow.
- Thank you.
Bye.
It's moving.
It's time to open the mold.
All the way out.
I wanna take it real slow.
And I notice
that it's kind of sticky.
- Hold it there.
- Uh-huh.
I'm holding the head cast,
and he's pulling the negative.
I'm really nervous.
Not sure what's going to happen.
Finally, the whole thing
just kind of comes off,
and it's this gorgeous ice blue
silicone prosthetic,
and it turned out exactly
the way that we wanted it,
and I'm like, "thank God."
- We have a piece.
- Yes.
I want to do a latex bald cap,
and there aren't any.
How the hell am I gonna
build my own friggin'--
So I use the mannequin head.
I'm, like, I'll just build
a latex bald cap.
I'm painting it on--
Fuck.
It's running off.
I'm frustrated.
I just walk away.
They don't have
fucking latex bald caps.
- Make one.
- I'm tr-- can't.
Autumn has a meltdown
about the bald caps,
and I need her to come down
from that very quickly
so that we can
get what we need done.
It won't fucking set up
on the fucking mannequin.
I'm, like, furious over it.
Right now, let's worry
about getting these open
- and cleaned up.
- Yeah, exactly.
'Cause I don't know how we're
gonna put the crown on, though.
Autumn's freaking out, and
Eric Z's cool as a cucumber.
Somebody on the team has to be
the voice of reason.
That's my partner!
All right, so we need
to start painting these babies,
don't we?
We got our latex port up.
We're ready
to start base coating.
Jenna!
So I look up, and I'm tripping
out because it's just too dark.
This isn't the color
that we originally planned on.
Jenna!
That's really dark.
I'm just getting
some more depth inhere.
We have less than half an hour.
After all this hard work,
I'm worried
this could be
a complete disaster.
So day two is almost over,
and I start painting
our skin pieces,
make 'em a little darker,
and then I hear
Eric go, "Jenna!"
Jenna!
I run over to the booth,
and I'm kinda panicked.
- That's really dark.
- I know.
I'm just getting some more depth
in there.
In my opinion it's not too dark,
'cause I know we have
to go darker to get
the look we're wanting
and the definition
in the cracks.
It looks like our undertones.
I'm worried at this point.
We have less than half an hour.
- All we can do is forge ahead.
- It'll be okay.
Yeah.
I see it working.
I think the basecoatark
was a good idea.
Yeah, no, it was great.
You know,
after final inspection,
you know what,
she got it right.
- I'm stoked.
- I was worried, though,
'cause you had this look
on your face like, "uh-oh.
Not what I wanted to do."
Jenna has some great points,
you know.
It needed to be a lot darker
so, when we brushed
the lighter color over, it's
just gonna pop a little bit more
and add a lot more contrast.
- This is all teamwork right here.
- Yeah.
Hey, brushes down, guys.
It is time to go home.
Our hands stick together.
Tomorrow is huge.
We might have
all of our pieces done,
but, if we don't get it applied,
I don't know.
At this point,
it's anybody's game.
Wow, that was a long day,
wasn't it?
When we get back to the house,
everybody's feeling tired.
Michael and I sit down
and have a conversation
so we both are
on the same page.
Painting is gonna be
the main, main focus tomorrow.
I think we're sitting
pretty good, I think.
- I think so too.
- Troy tells me he's noticing
all the other artists
have so much going on.
And that's
what we didn't wanna do.
We didn't wanna have
so much going on
that we have no time for it.
Everybody else has,
like, a million pieces.
You're gonna run out of time
to paint them.
- Yeah.
- I think a few people
might be in over their heads.
I definitely think
we've got an advantage.
I feel like, you know,
that my brother's given me
this knowledge,
and I'm gonna use it.
I trained side-by-side
with my brother,
and I gotta take any advantage
I can in this competition.
All right, man.
We're gonna do it.
- Yeah.
- I'm nervous.
I think right now
everyone's stressing
more than they have to.
We have, like, a lot of,
like, applying and stuff,
and we're debating
whether or not to just apply
the actual face
in the one hour last looks.
Personally, like, me and
Anthony are gonna do that last.
Everyone seems really
confident and everything,
but I just wanna be, like,
"don't you guys realize
"that someone's gonna get kicked
off, and it could be you,
it could be me,
it could be anyone?"
So to leave after three days
would be probably
the worst thing ever.
- Nice.
- Oh, yeah, it's thick.
So it's application day.
We have four hours in the lab,
and we still have a lot to do.
Like, Wayne wants
to now fabricate these cuffs,
but now I'm starting
to get nervous
that we might run out of time
with this.
Hi, nice to meet you.
- I'm Alex.
- We're literally gonna just
have you sit there
for the moment,
'cause we're gonna start
pre-painting stuff.
Right now we need to paint.
We need to make sure
everything's pre-painted
before it gets on him
because I really don't want him
sitting in the makeup
longer than he needs to.
It's nice.
Kris and I have a lot to do.
We have to make a crown.
We have to make the staff.
So, ah, I'm panicked.
I needed to get my shield done.
I need to get my staff done,
the crown done, and the costume.
- How you coming along, Troy?
- Good.
Putting-- laying down the wire,
and I'm gonna spray orange
all over it,
and should be pretty quick.
Troy's still over there
painting the face and chest.
He's a little more relaxed
than I feel that he should be.
And now I'm starting to sweat,
because Troy
still hasn't
picked up the pace.
- It's like one super edge.
- Yeah.
I'm not happy with
the application around the lips.
Some of the edges on it
are a little thick,
so I'm having a bit
of difficulty.
Let's see
where that other piece fits
before we start gluing it.
We are still applying the piece
when I'm looking around,
and I see everybody has paint,
and we're the only people
that don't have paint
on our model yet.
- That's good.
- We need to put
some kind of paint on this guy
before we leave.
I do the hands
and the feet now, right?
Yeah, yeah.
'Cause I wanna do
so much detail on him,
you know what I'm saying?
We're planning on painting
a lot of wood grain in
and hoping we have time
to really pop out the detail
on this.
Dude, an hour's
like nothing, man.
That's kinda scaring me now.
I'm a little nervous
because we don't have time
for what we have planned.
Troy, within 30 minutes
we can start getting this
on him, you think?
Yeah, I think so.
Um, volcano guy right over
there with the 39 minutes left,
and he's got a chest on.
We're almost done
with the four hours at the lab,
so going into last looks
really all we need to do
is touch up around the edges,
finish painting his actual body,
try to get our contacts in,
also working
on distressing the teeth.
That's a lot to do, but I am
feeling like we can get it done.
Everybody, we got two minutes!
Right now I'm feeling
kind of nervous
because we still don't have
any paint on our model.
That's time!
Grab your stuff, let's go.
We're gonna have
to rely on last looks
to really pull this together.
I mean, we're fast, but I
don't know if we're that fast.
Coming up...
- You did an exceptional job.
- Oh, my God.
I really loved it.
What you just said,
that is not okay.
We only have an hour in last
looks to pull this together.
As long as we can get the paint
on there quickly,
I think we'll be okay.
I'm gonna worry
about the mouth and the eyes.
We are trying to get the mouth
to stay down,
and it's not working.
The area around the mouth
looks like a horror show,
- and not the good way.
- That's not gonna stay on.
Putting on the crown
is a nightmare.
Oh, lord.
The last thing
Michael and I want
is for the model
to walk on stage
and his crown and wig fall off.
After this wing, will you mix
the base colors?
Yeah.
- Yeah, I'm gonna mix the colors.
- Sweet.
Wayne's moving
down the back piece,
but, dude,
we gotta get painting.
At this point,
I just think we have to get
some kind of color on him.
I don't know how much time
we have left.
Is there a clock?
It's a mad race,
and time is going so fast.
Five minutes.
Way faster than anything
I had ever imagined.
Time's up!
- That's it.
- I'm sweating bullets.
This is really not the product
that I wanted to show.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
Say hello to your judges--
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick...
Good evening.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill...
Well, gang,
welcome to Face Off.
Thank you.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page...
- Hi, guys.
- Hi.
And joining our panel
this week,
he is an iconic actor,
starring in some of Hollywood's
biggest franchises
including
the Indiana Jones films
and The Lord Of The Rings
trilogy.
Please give a warm welcome
to John Rhys-Davies.
To you.
John, thank you so much
for being here tonight.
Thanks for having me.
I loved him
in Raiders Of The Lost Ark.
He's worked on several films
where he's worn
prosthetic makeup.
It's really awesome
that he's our guest judge.
So, guys, this week
your spotlight challenge
was to create a Goblin King
physically influenced
by the land
that he reigns over.
Let's see
what you've come up with.
I could see the detail from
where I'm standing so I'm happy.
It looks beautiful on stage.
I love it.
I love our makeup.
I'm excited.
This thing looks scary.
No matter what the judges say,
I'm happy with my work.
Maybe we could
actually wing this and win it,
because it looks
pretty cool under these lights.
I'm just really nervous
that the hat's gonna fall off.
That would be
such an embarrassment.
I'm nervous.
I'm really nervous.
I wanna win this challenge.
I think he stands out.
I think he's shimmery,
he's icy,
and I think we have
a good chance of winning.
I am terrified
at this point to see
what the judges are gonna say.
Hopefully it's good.
I don't know.
There are a couple areas
on the inside of the arm
where you can see
a little bit of skin.
I'm hoping the judges
won't notice.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look?
Can you try to emote
through the makeup for me?
Scrunch your face up.
I want to see how you read
through it.
It looks really thick,
but it's not.
- Oh, look.
- He's got a bug.
He's got a bug.
Some of the other characters
have such a big presence.
Our character
might have a little more
of a simplistic look,
and I'm not sure
that that's what the judges
are looking for.
- Did they look at the shoulders?
- A little bit.
This is cool.
I like the way
they did all this.
That's even,
like, gold wire on that.
- What nice detail.
- Very impressive.
Yeah, things look great
from far away in the dark,
but, once you're up close
poking at it,
that's a whole different story.
It's a fine sort of
lizard-like effect, isn't it?
Yeah.
There is some nice little
stippling and stuff.
It just doesn't read
because I have not seen
a gator this color,
have you?
I feel pretty confident.
I think we have
a very strong concept.
Why is he all covered up?
I don't understand
how this face is supposed
to transition into this.
This looks like a hat.
It's the top of a volcano,
and that's his crown.
I notice Glenn's
just picking this thing apart.
I'm utterly confused by this.
I'm terrified.
I'm not shaking,
but on the inside
I'm screaming.
If you're on Twitter,
use #FaceOff to tell us
what you think
about tonight's designs.
I don't understand
how this face is supposed
to transition into this.
- This looks like a hat.
- I noticed Glenn's
just picking this thing apart,
and I'm terrified.
I'm not shaking,
but on the inside I'm screaming.
- Do you have any teeth in?
- Yes.
Oh, you didn't see those
before.
- Very good.
- That's creepy.
Oh, good.
The way that that head
goes up into it,
it's much better up close.
Could you bend your head a bit?
Don't strain your knees,
my boy.
You'll need them
over the next 70 years.
If anything happens with
this creature, it falls on me.
I'm the one going home.
- God, that's a lot of work.
- Yeah, no kidding.
I wanna see what this looks
like if the grass wasn't there.
I'm really interested in seeing
what that structure looks like
if they hadn't made
this decision.
Stressing out,
it's not gonna help me,
so I'm trying to be happy.
And I am happy because it's
crazy that I'm already here.
John, you were exposed to some
pretty amazing fantasy kings
as part
of The Lord Of The Rings films.
How do you think
things turned out tonight?
Extraordinary.
Just extraordinary.
Far beyond what
I was expecting to see.
The judges have scored
your creations.
Let's find out
what they thought.
Kris and Alam,
Katie and House...
congratulations,
because you are safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
- Nice.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
So the rest of you
were the best
and the worst of the week.
The judges would now like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Anthony and Meagan,
please step forward.
Before I begin, I want
to say to all of you,
I'm really blown away.
The work is
just exceedingly high.
So well done to all of you
this week, I mean that.
So to start, please tell me
who was responsible
for which aspects
of this makeup.
I handled the sculpting
of the head, the face,
the staff,
and Meagan did the--
- Shoulders.
The chest piece
that's kinda hidden.
And we applied and painted
together.
From far away,
I had serious concerns
about the tonality
of the makeup.
The paint job up close,
very happy with.
And I love that there's
some subtle shifts in tonality
on the half of face
that's more human-esque.
I'm extremely impressed
with this piece.
- Thank you.
The ability to sculpt
natural things such as rock,
it's difficult thing
to pull off.
You did an exceptional job.
The painting of it
is executed so well,
it looks like the real stuff.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
I thought
this was just wonderful.
I love the geology.
I think the execution is good.
I would be very happy
to wear that makeup.
I think it's--
well, no, let me rephrase this.
No, no, never will I
wear a prosthetic makeup again,
but--
but were I young and mad,
I'd be happy
to be seen in that.
Thank you so much.
That really means a lot.
Anthony, Meagan,
thank you very much.
- Will you please step back?
- Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you.
Michael and Troy, will you
please step forward?
Tell us what is going on
with this character
and whose idea was what.
He's a volcano. You know,
a volcano's generally ugly.
They erupt.
They leave destruction
in their path.
I did all of the fabrication
as far as the costuming
and the top,
and then I sculpted the chest
piece and the shoulder.
I handled
most of the paint work.
I also sculpted the face,
also painted the chest piece.
All right, can you open up the
coat so we can see the chest?
I've gotta tell you something,
sorry to say
you covered up the best part
of your makeup.
I think the face is just a big
charred, scratchy-looking thing,
and this headpiece
is like a clown hat.
I don't think you did
so well on this, guys.
You have a very specific
aesthetic happening
just in silhouette
that feels more like a witch.
I like the staff, actually.
It's pretty cool-looking.
It clearly is the product of
two guys dividing their labors,
working apart,
and then bringing them together
and going, "whoops."
It's black and gray
with a little bit of mishmash
of yellows and crimsons.
It doesn't work.
Michael and Troy,
please step back.
Eric F and Jenna.
First I wanna ask you,
on a scale of one to ten,
how you think you did
in this challenge.
- We probably did an eight.
- I would say an eight as well.
Just because it was
the very first challenge.
We are just learning the shop.
That's great, because I think
that that's very accurate.
There's some exceptional details
in the sculpture.
I really like the sort
of hieroglyph.
It very simply harkens
towards an Egyptian theme.
It ties in well
with the desert.
What I see going on
with the eyes sculpturally,
definitely asymmetrical.
There is a very fine line
between crooked
and purposely asymmetrical.
Interesting, unique,
cool to look at.
When he walked out
and I saw the head,
I'm thinking, "oh, my God."
I really loved it.
And then when I got up close
and I saw a lot more
of the details, I liked the fact
that you've tied
all of those details together
with that gold wire,
and your gold paint,
the gold nipple ring.
All those details
really finished it off for me.
It really is a very
comprehensive work of design.
The lack of water
in that parched skeletal desert
comes through wonderfully.
Eric, Jenna, can you
please step back?
Oh, my God.
Wayne and Alex.
What was the original idea
behind this?
We're both from Florida.
We picked the swamp,
so we wanted to come up
with the gator theme
just because it's
the king of the swamps.
Is that face a gator color?
I'm not overly familiar
with your gators.
The last thing
we wanted to do was put
a nice cream-colored dry brush
over the front of the face,
but we really
just ran out of time.
What you just said,
that is not okay.
I'm perplexed
by how you could have
such a fundamentally
sound concept
and have succeeded so well
sculpturally.
Not leaving yourself
enough time to paint it
was a horrible decision.
Who did what in your character?
I sculpted the face,
the belt piece,
and then the little transfers
that we did on the feet,
and then the transfer that went
down the back of the head
with the scaling.
And I sculpted the cowl
and made, basically,
the chest piece.
First of all, your chest piece
looks like
a psychedelic washboard.
Your proportions
are completely off.
His head is so big.
If you were gonna put a head
on him this big,
you should have built
his shoulders out
so that he was very robust.
The sculpt of the head,
it's such a good design.
How much time did you
give yourself for paint?
It's probably 40 minutes.
- 40 minutes?
- Oh, man, guys.
You must in future
balance your time better
so that you don't give yourself
so little time
to add that polish.
Wayne, Alex, could you
please step back?
Eric and Autumn.
Please start off
by explaining your concept.
We didn't really get to pick.
We were the last
to get a decision,
so we got stuck with jungle.
I came up with the concept,
and Eric sketched it out
beautifully,
and I based the sculpture
off of his drawing.
I'm really happy
with this thing.
I think that you did
a great job.
Who did the arms?
- I did.
- I think it's really cool
that you actually incorporated
what appears to be
sort of a musculature,
but you did it so that it looks
like it's in a tree form,
which is really great-looking.
Choosing to do knots for ears,
another great choice
of figuring out a feature
on the tree that's going to work
for the metaphor of ears.
That is a fantastic head.
Eric and Autumn,
thank you very much.
- Thank you.
- Please step back.
Thank you.
Okay, the judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you'd please head
back to the makeup room
while they make their decisions.
So let's talk about the looks
that you liked the most.
Why don't we start
with Anthony and Meagan?
The makeup itself
was exceptional.
The transition and the colors on
the more human side of the face
were really thrilling to me.
I was impressed with the fact
that they sculpted
the rock and had it
look like rock.
- Looked like rock.
- Organically accurate.
Yes, it was.
Yeah, that's hard.
I think it was terrific.
All right, let's move on
to Eric F and Jenna.
It's one of my favorite makeups
because there was
a lot of attention to detail.
Right down to the little gold
wire that they used to tie
all the different things
together.
That's really
a testament to the fact
that their teamwork
was exceptional.
What I liked about it
was that you could tell
the features from a distance.
You know, they really had used
contrast and shade
to make the features stand out.
Okay, let's move on to
Eric Z and Autumn.
I loved this piece.
I loved the head sculpt.
I loved the design of the head.
I thought it was such a
beautifully executed piece.
The tree form, sculpturally,
follows the deltoid down
into the tricep and the bicep,
and that's really brilliant.
All right, let's move on
to some of the looks
you liked the least.
Why don't we start
with Michael and Troy?
Everything that they chose
was a mistake right down
to the best thing they did
being covered up.
Even the chest sculpture
wasn't very good--
No.
But it was better
than the face.
It is literally just lines
carved on the shape
of the actor's lifecast
with red underneath
and black on top.
All right, let's move on
to Wayne and Alex.
Out of all of the times
we've asked the question,
"who did what?",
this seems to be
the single most
inequitable division of labor
I've heard of yet.
- She barely did anything.
- That's scary for her.
Well, I think
we all loved the sculpture,
but there was
so many other things
that were screwed up on it.
I can't even believe that they
didn't get at least a base coat
on it before they got here.
If they would have left
themselves some time to paint,
they could have been on top.
All right, judges, have you
made your decisions?
- Yes, we have.
- Think so.
Let's bring 'em back out.
All right, Glenn, why don't you
tell us about the top teams?
Our top teams tonight
are Anthony and Meagan.
We thought that you did
a really great job
sculpting the rock textures
on your makeup,
and we really loved the way
that you handled
the transition onto the head.
Eric F and Jenna.
We really appreciated
some of the finer details
that you brought
to your makeup.
And you certainly created
one of the most complete
overall looks this evening.
Autumn and Eric Z.
We're very fond
of your tiki face design,
and we really like
the tree textures
that you sculpted for the arms.
Okay, which team came out
on top?
Our top team tonight is...
Okay, which team
came out on top?
Our top team tonight is...
Anthony and Meagan.
Oh, my God.
- Thank you so much!
- Thank you. Oh, my God.
We thought that this was the
best makeup out there tonight.
We especially loved
the right side
of the face and the profile.
- Well done.
- Anthony and Meagan, great job,
but we can only have
one winner.
- Glenn?
- The winner tonight is...
Anthony.
Thank you so much.
Ultimately, we felt
that the sculpt on the face
and the paint job is what made
this makeup a success.
Thank you.
It really-- I can't believe it.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Winning
the foundation challenge
and then winning
the spotlight challenge,
I just feel so incredibly
awesome at this moment.
Anthony, congratulations.
You and Meagan can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you.
Eric F and Jenna,
Eric Z and Autumn,
you guys are also safe
this week.
Please head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Unfortunately that means
the rest of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Michael and Troy.
There's some good ideas
in the design of your makeup.
You just weren't able
to execute them.
Wayne and Alex.
You had a really, really nice
sculpture, but you screwed it up
with a horrible paint job
and some egregious fabrication
and wardrobe decisions.
All right,
so who is going home tonight?
The person
going home tonight is...
Troy.
Unfortunately, even though a lot
of things weren't right
with the design tonight,
we felt
that the biggest letdown
was the facial sculpt.
Troy, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
The rest of you are safe.
You can head
back to the makeup room.
I just want you to know
that this one experience
does not define you.
So I'm hoping that
we do get a chance to see
some of your work
down the road.
Thank you very much.
Troy, it's been great
having you here with us.
Can you please head
back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit?
- Thank you.
Good luck, Troy.
This competition is no joke.
You have to be
on your A-plus game,
especially with the artists
that are here.
Going home, guys.
Oh, man! Dude!
Oh, you can't go!
I tried my hardest.
I did the best I could.
I worked my butt off.
So I can't say
I have any regrets.
I know I have a lot to learn.
It's just more motivation
for me to get better.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net