Previously onFace Off...
Kris's butterfly creation
brought him his second win.
But Alam's incoherent design
failed to impress,
and she was sent home.
Now eight artists remain
and tonight they'll face
two of their toughest
challenges ever.
We're in the zombie apocalypse.
Where's my fucking sponge?!
Your spotlight challenge
is to create
an original werewolf.
This is awesome.
For some, the pressure
will be too much.
I just need to take a breath.
Gonna fucking punch him.
Oh, he blew apart.
It really does not work.
It's terrible.
The proportions are nightmares.
He is so beautiful,
it's an amazing job.
In the end,
only one will win
the opportunity
to be a guest lecturer
at Make Up For Ever's
academies in New York
and Paris,
the all-new 2013 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
I miss Alam.
- You guys missing Alam too?
- Yeah.
Super talented.
The mood in the house is sad
because everybody really liked
Alam's aesthetic.
Both Meagan and I are nervous
about the next challenge
because it seems like
the judges
are really gonna be looking
at us
with a magnifying glass.
I liked your moth.
Looked like it had
Joe Dirt in a headlock, but--
I can't continue to put work
out like that moth.
I need to show
that I am a strong artist
and I belong here.
- Let's go, guys.
- Let's go.
Let's do it.
I have to knock it
out of the park this week.
We're walking up
to this country house,
and we see this barn,
and we're thinking
that it's going to be
some kind of a animal challenge.
Maybe it's some kind
of an alien challenge.
I brought you out here today
to talk
about one
of the most iconic makeups
in film history.
They've been featured
in everything
from Dawn Of The Dead
to 28 Days Later
and even the massive hit
The Walking Dead.
- Yes.
- That's right.
I'm talking zombies here.
- Yes!
- Excellent.
Whoo!
I'm from Pittsburgh,
and zombies were invented
pretty much in Pittsburgh.
So I'm very excited
about this challenge.
I'd like to introduce you
to your guest judge.
She has produced some
of Hollywood's biggest hits,
including the Terminator films,
The Incredible Hulk,
and Aliens.
She's also
the executive producer
of The Walking Dead.
Please welcome Gale Anne Hurd.
Hi.
Everything Gale Anne Hurd
has done
has been classic.
There's no messing around
when she's on set.
What advice do you have
for these guys
to make a convincing zombie?
Think about how
your particular zombie died.
Were they bitten in the neck,
maybe the arm?
And that will help you create
a believable makeup.
So let's meet your models.
Aah!
This is rad!
Literally a stampede
of people come out.
I'm hoping we're not doing
all of these people
because there's, like,
80 of them.
That is gonna be rad!
These models are coming out.
It's so fun and so scary.
We're in the middle
of a zombie apocalypse.
Professionals in the industry
are often tasked
with not only making up
the stars,
but they also have to make up
an army of background actors.
Working in teams of two,
your foundation challenge
is to transform
all of these extras
into a horde
of flesh-eating zombies.
We have 20 zombies each team.
This is insane.
Your randomly selected
teams are...
Eric F and Wayne...
Dude!
Meagan and Anthony,
House and Eric Z,
Kris and Autumn.
And I'm sure you've noticed
that we don't have
any makeup stations set up
for you today.
So you're actually
going to be working
in the farmhouse over there
with just the most basic
items necessary
to get the job done.
You are working in teams today,
but only one of you
will receive immunity
for winning the challenge.
So make sure
that you each create
at least one featured zombie
that showcases
your individual work.
You've got 2 1/2 hours
to complete your horde.
Your time starts now.
Just another day at the office.
- I--
- You know?
- Ready to be a zombie today?
- Oh, yeah.
Our strategy is to get
as many of their faces
built up as possible,
so like in the last hour we can just
run through 'em painting
as fast as we can.
I'm thinking that it's
probably around eight minutes
per zombie.
For an eight-minute zombie,
I'm going with cotton
and latex.
It's quick, you can form it
to the face,
so it looks like
the skin is open.
They just need
to look gross and bloody.
I've done hundreds
upon hundreds of zombie makeups.
So I want to win
this challenge.
I want the immunity.
I gotta speed up.
Let's have a lady up.
Here you go.
I love working
on lots of people.
This is perfect.
I use a lot of airbrush
and spatter,
things that I know
are gonna be quick.
Autumn's painting with a brush.
We don't have time
to be elaborate
with any of this makeup.
Should I go further with this?
No, let's move on
to the next one-- next!
I'm basically gonna
line them up
and just start sponging them
with different colors.
Me and Wayne,
we need to speed this up.
So I just line them all up
and start smacking them
in the face with stuff.
I got the one hero,
and I got one, two,
three, four going.
We have one hour left!
Eric Z's knocking 'em out.
His makeups
are looking fabulous,
and we're keeping up
with each other per zombie.
It's really about just
getting everyone done right now.
Can I get all the people
that aren't done
on both sides of us?
We are running out of time.
So I decide to start
an assembly line
just to paint quicker.
30 minutes left, guys!
- Boom.
- Scrape more...
They're probably outside
on the table.
Okay, not a team player.
Man, we got a lot left.
We gotta hustle.
If you want me to hustle,
pull one out of your kit,
seriously,
'cause I have no sponges
in here.
Use your hands.
I don't know
if Autumn's expecting me
to stop what I'm doing
to get sponges,
but time's ticking.
I need to get my job done.
Where's my fucking sponge?
If you see any
that need something, Anthony,
tell me, and I'll grab 'em.
Here's another cup of blood
going around.
Pass it around.
Five minutes, guys!
How many more?
I think just one after this.
- Last one, last one!
- Great.
In the last three minutes,
I'm just slapping them
with blood.
- One minute!
- Boom! Here it comes.
Boom!
I'm just raining blood
down on my zombies.
There we go.
Time is up!
Put your blood down.
Can you show us one
of your featured zombies?
This young lady, I just thought
she was a fresh victim
and lots of bites.
This gentleman,
he has great bone structure,
so we wanted to keep more
of a traditional look.
Eric did
this wonderful job here
on the severed arm.
Your attention to detail,
I think, was terrific.
So I think overall,
you did a really good job.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, guys.
Tell me about the choice
of the color palette
that you went with.
I think mine are
slightly different.
He airbrushed a lot,
and I hand-painted mine.
So mine have more green
and purple hues to them.
I went
where the blood stops flowing,
the veins start to blacken up
and purple up a little bit more,
a lot of bruising,
things like that.
Can you guys turn around?
- So you didn't address the back.
- We ran out of time, so--
The big issue that I have is
you are going to see them
from the back,
the camera will be there.
Producers will be calling you
to set saying,
"I'm sorry, we need them now.
The time's running away."
Right.
This one's mine,
with a tooth from a fight.
I really liked her
and the guy with the tattoos.
There is a uniformity.
They all look like they're
in the same film or TV series
even though you worked on them
separately.
I built up cotton
with this one.
- Nice.
- Also right here under the eye.
Hers is
a complete silicone buildup.
And then I did a little
nice bite wound in her cheek.
You have a total aesthetic.
All of your zombies look like
they're in the same TV show
or film.
Zombies, would you mind
turning around, please?
They have blood and gunk
in the back.
- Yes.
- You did it.
- I smacked them on the back.
- Good job.
- Good luck, guys.
- Thanks.
So, Gale, that was probably
the most difficult foundation
challenge
we've ever had on the show.
How did they do overall?
I think they did great.
I was really impressed.
All right, which teams
had the best zombie hordes?
- I would say Eric Z and House.
- Good job, buddy.
They had fantastic work.
And Meagan and Anthony.
You guys were able to create
a single aesthetic.
All right, Gale,
which team came out on top?
It was a difficult decision,
but the top team is...
Coming up...
Where's my fucking partner?
I don't know.
I'm already
in a world of trouble.
This is a great concept.
It wasn't a collaboration.
It was a dictatorship.
We're getting up and
getting ready...
My style is
go big *, that means
my hair too.
- * good, guys! Good morning.
- Wow!
I love it!
Can I touch it?
The cool thing about
my hair is it's a mohawk.
It's just as crazy as I am.
It's... it's getting there.
It's still quite...
He's gonna * his
war paint on, he's ready to go.
Yeah, I'm ready
for this battle.
- You look like a badass.
- I like it.
I wish I could pull that off.
This is like my brand here.
All right, Gale,
which team came out on top?
It was a difficult decision,
but the top team is...
Anthony and Meagan.
Awesome.
You paid attention to detail,
to the prosthetic makeup,
the clothing, even twigs
and moss in the hair.
Congratulations,
Anthony and Meagan.
However,
we can only have one winner.
Gale?
The winner is...
Meagan.
Meagan!
I won, and I have immunity.
And it feels really good.
I saw you directing
the entire operation.
You could start work
on The Walking Dead tomorrow.
- Good job, Meagan.
- Oh, my God.
- Thank you.
- Awesome job.
As the winner
of this challenge,
you have won immunity
in the next spotlight challenge
and cannot be eliminated.
All right, guys.
You better get out of here
to avoid
getting eaten
by your own zombies.
We're walking
through this field,
the moon is shining,
this fog is rolling in,
and it feels like
we're about to go into battle.
Throughout history,
the full moon has had
an unsettling effect
on humans and the world
around us.
Its power has been associated
with violence
and werewolves.
Yes.
Werewolves are featured
in all kinds of movies,
everything from
An American Werewolf In London,
the Underworld films, and
even Michael Jackson's Thriller.
But Earth isn't the only planet
in our solar system
that has a moon.
Each of these planets also has
at least one moon.
Working in teams of two,
your spotlight challenge is
to create an original werewolf
that might exist on another
planet in our solar system.
This is awesome and crazy.
Your randomly selected teams
of two are...
House and Meagan,
Eric Z and Autumn.
Autumn is, for the most part,
very negative.
And no one wants to work
with somebody
they don't get along with.
Eric F and Anthony.
- Yes.
- Wayne and Kris.
- Yeah, man.
- Stand with your new teammate.
- What's up, man?
- Dude!
House and Meagan,
which planet would you like?
Mars.
- Eric Z and Autumn.
- Jupiter.
- Eric F and Anthony.
- Saturn.
- Wayne and Kris.
- Neptune.
Since the moon
is the inspiration
for this challenge,
I'm gonna leave you guys
out here all alone
to start work on your designs.
I will see you all tomorrow
in the lab.
All right.
Let's go.
- I'm counting on these guys--
- Doing a...
- A typical werewolf.
- Wolf form.
So the surface of Saturn
is very dry.
It's got real jagged
rock formations,
so we're gonna incorporate
all those elements
into our design
by making the skin very jagged
and then utilizing
the color palette of Saturn.
And the model is going
to walk backwards.
That's badass.
He's a human that was on Mars
and has become infected.
'Cause I have immunity,
I really feel
that House should take
the wheel on this.
We have a pretty cool concept.
He is an astronaut
that was bitten by a lycan
and transformed
into this crazy werewolf.
And maybe, like, um, keep
the teeth, like, more metal.
Mm-hmm.
I want our creature to be
morphing into the werewolf.
I'm thinking, like,
shapes and silhouettes
and bone protrusions
coming out of his back.
Pretty darn intense, dude.
Neptune's temperatures are
as low as 218 degrees Celsius.
Our concept is this alien being
who would stay in the dark area
of Neptune.
But when he has to eat,
he comes into the moonlight
and changes
into this massive beast.
Dude, I think
we got something here.
That's time.
Let's rock this.
It's day one, and there's
a lot of sculpting to do.
So we want to sculpt the face
with the other clay.
Autumn and I decide
to break up the responsibilities
pretty evenly.
She beings to sculpt
on the face,
and I begin the sculpture
on the chest.
Let's make it pretty.
We want to do a full bodysuit.
Wayne's focusing on the front,
and I'm gonna focus
on the back.
I think
we're gonna end up using
about 200 pounds of clay
on this thing.
I'm giving, like,
the bicep, tricep, bicep.
Yeah.
Me and Anthony have a lot
of crap to get sculpted today,
but we have a solid game plan.
I have Meagan blocking out
arms and chest for me.
I start sculpting on the face
and the head.
I will not be doing
a long, dog-like snout,
but I have a good feeling
that it will come together.
I look over
at Autumn's sculpture,
and it's looking
a little rough.
It's looking kind
of, like, piggish.
You mind if I take that off
a little bit?
Yeah, that's fine.
We switch off, and Eric
completely resculpts it.
Autumn gets offended
very easily.
It's just not a way to work.
If at all you're uncomfortable
with going on
- with this particular look--
- No.
I just want it to be
slightly different.
I already had it blocked out.
All he had to do was detail it.
I don't know
if I can fully trust him.
- Hey, guys.
- Hello.
- Here for a walk-through.
- How are you?
So tell us about your werewolf
and what planet you picked.
- We picked Mars.
- Mars.
So your coloring's gonna be
on the red side?
Red coloring, dried skin,
it's gonna be very sparse.
Except for, like,
a stripe of mohawk
that's running down his head.
Pre-paint the skin
and texture
maybe with
some spotting or something.
- So you see it underneath.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Tell us what planet you picked.
Saturn.
Because of its strong winds,
we're actually
incorporating wings.
With the wings,
make sure your model is aware
- of what they can do.
- Exactly.
The face will sit on top
of his head,
so his face is actually
the neck of the werewolf.
What are you gonna do
with hair?
We're putting
the hair on sparse
so that you could see
through it.
How are you gonna put
the hair on?
- Telesis.
- If you work together on it...
one paints,
and the other lays the hair.
Jupiter has a lot of gravity,
so he's gonna have
internal structure of rock.
Show me the face, Eric,
'cause that--
it seems like you haven't
really gotten into that yet.
No, I had it roughed out.
And then Eric completely
resculpted it.
Why did you resculpt it?
It was looking a bit cartoony.
You've got a long way
to go on this.
- Yeah, definitely.
- Mm-hmm.
The worst part is, if I make
a big deal out of it now,
it's going to slow down
the process even more so.
If we're going to show up
with something,
our only hope is for me
to keep my mouth shut.
- Okay, guys. Looking good.
- Bye, thank you.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
Sculpting in circles
over there.
Fuck it.
I just have to step outside
and take a breath.
Where's my fucking partner?
Gonna fucking punch him.
I don't know where he is,
and I'm getting pissed
that he's given up completely.
- Oh, man.
- He's given up on me.
I'm choosing to bite my lip.
If I don't, we're not gonna
have anything on that stage.
She told McKenzie
and Mr. Westmore
that I totally resculpted
her face.
And I was like, "that's not
what happened at all."
What?
This isn't
what a collaboration should be.
You know
she's gonna say that onstage.
Yeah, I know.
That's what scares me.
Right there.
That's time, everybody!
I'm hoping that day two
is going to be better,
but I'm dreading it.
We have ten hours,
and we still need to finish
sculpting the body, the head,
some teeth, and some claws.
- We're about to make a mess.
- I think so.
Fox is going to block out
the false arms,
and then
we can start molding it.
So there's still so much to do,
but we do have a game plan.
- It's gonna be a rush.
- It always is, man.
It always is.
Ooh.
We know that we have
to start getting things done.
I'm gonna get these pieces out
that I know that I at least
have some control over.
I'm not looking forward
to working with Autumn,
but today I've decided
that I'm going to just work.
I thought
I was going into it simple,
and I'm already
in a world of trouble.
Chest, arms, and hands need
to be sculpted and molded.
The back needs
to be constructed.
Hollow it out,
so it hugs her back.
I'm doing seven different
projects all at one time.
Meagan's doing the hair
on the back.
The hair work is taking
a long time.
- We gotta move.
- House is very meticulous.
A little heavy on the purple,
but we'll fix that.
- He's very stern.
- Running out of time.
He might just think
that I'm, like, silly.
Meagan is moving too slow.
How's your turkey cutting?
- I cut my finger.
- Of course.
We have our foam piece,
and it's beautiful.
It's massive.
Damn.
You just start laughing
because it's a full suit.
Oh, it's gonna be perfect.
Look at the muscle
you got in the neck.
That's gonna blend in
perfectly.
I think
we're intimidating everybody
just because of the mass size
of everything that we're doing.
That looks fucking awesome.
It smells like cookies.
Three minutes!
There's a lot of tension
with House today
because I think he's concerned
he could go home.
Meagan has immunity.
If something goes wrong,
it's gonna be my butt
on the line.
That's time!
I feel I'm in trouble.
Day three, I have a lot to do.
Whee!
So it's application day.
We have four hours in the lab
and one hour at last looks.
I run in right away,
I grab the head,
and I'm ready to fill it
with polyfoam.
Kris is pulling a leg,
getting ready to cast
the other one,
and slush latexing the hands.
So we have a lot to do.
Basically you're gonna
be walking backwards.
Uh-huh.
You know, you're gonna be
a werewolf from Jupiter.
Should we start brushing
that shit?
We have so many pieces
that we have to run today.
It's never a good idea
to have to run pieces
on application day.
That's great.
Fox is gonna finish running
everything else.
I'm gonna start cutting
the seams
of the legs and the arms.
He brings me the chest piece.
Keep 'em coming.
I start cutting the seams off
of that.
We're both kind of panicking.
It just feels like that,
you know,
in a way, we've bitten more
than we can chew.
As long as we can get
everything painted
and assembled, we can apply it
at last looks.
I don't care if we got
to duct-tape this shit on.
- It's gonna look good.
- We'll do it.
Makeup!
Yeah, your butt's
gonna be covered.
Congratulations.
We get to the lab,
I just start painting
and pre-painting everything.
We got to get
this model covered.
- Almost like his color.
- Mm-hmm.
And then we'll do
the dead wash on it.
Okay.
And if you want
to start painting.
Let's do that.
I hop on painting
the pieces with her.
They're not my favorite colors,
but I'm going with it.
I trust you.
Kind of.
15 minutes, everybody.
Keep it organized, Eric.
Okay, you're gonna help me
lead the way.
Grab the edge of the mask.
I want my model to have
her wolf head on.
I don't want it glued down
completely though.
I want to save that
for last looks.
- My chin is right here.
- Okay, let me pull it back.
But I made a bad mistake.
The head doesn't fit.
And the face is not snug
like it should be.
The face is odd, the mouth is
2 inches away from her mouth.
I'm gonna go in there and loosen
that up a little bit,
so I can pull it tighter.
That's time!
I tack her down,
and then it's time's up.
I need to fix this makeup.
If I don't,
this one's all on me.
Coming up...
- Hot-glue it up top.
- It doesn't look very good.
It's an amazing job.
There's some beautiful work
going on in there.
It's a travesty.
- May I interject?
- Sure.
There are some things
that I need to explain.
We're at last looks.
We have one hour
to finish it off.
And we're really trying
to budget our time
the best we can.
Have a seat, my man.
We have to finish
the paint job, let it dry,
and then get all this hair
laid on.
It's very stressful.
If you can just adjust this
a little lower.
Mm-hmm. Okay.
I have to get the face
glued onto her.
It's not going to look as good
as I would like it to.
But I'm going to take
the heat on it.
Positive and negative,
bring it on.
The spray glue's right there.
Fox is playing with the wings.
And I've got to get something
on the guy's head
so that it covers his face.
Hot-glue it up top.
I'm gonna have to cover that *.
I don't care.
The last thing I want to do
is cover half of the sculpture
with this big red wig.
It doesn't look very good.
Just drape it over.
Yeah.
Time!
I'm very proud of our werewolf.
I never thought it was possible
to get that much amount
of work done
in such a short amount of time.
I'm just glad we got everything
on our character.
The makeup came together
in one sense.
It is a piece.
A piece of what, I don't know.
Welcome
to theFace Offreveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
Say hello to your judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve
Makeup Effects Studio,
- Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
- Hey, Glenn.
- Glenn.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist,
- Ve Neill.
- Hi, guys.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
- Hello.
- Hi.
This week
your spotlight challenge
was to create
an original werewolf
that might exist
on another planet
in our solar system.
So let's see
what you've come up with.
The makeup application
isn't perfect,
but the face sculpture's
looking okay.
There's something beautiful
about her to me.
It just looks so big
and so massive up there
that Eric and I
are just really hoping
that the judges see
where we're coming from.
It looks a chihuahua
that's just been shaved
by a child.
It obviously is a piece
that Autumn did
and not me.
Wayne and I are excited.
I mean, we really love
what we did.
It was a lot of fun working
with Wayne,
and we're both just ecstatic.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look?
There's no reason
why we shouldn't.
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
Mm-hmm.
One thing I'm
kind of digging about this is
I feel like I see a story.
See what I'm saying?
I also like the direction
of some of this.
Wonder what's happening here.
Is this
where it was scratched, maybe,
and that's how it got infected?
I thought that's
what it looked like too.
Right?
That's a lot of scratch marks
if that's the case.
As a whole, what an
interesting sculpture going out.
Dude, it's, like,
hot-glued and--
- let's take a look at this.
- Oh, he blew apart.
They don't get much bigger
than that.
- It's almost full body.
- Turn around.
They went this far and then
made stubby, little feet.
Yeah, they look more like
the heels than this foot does.
Man, that's a lot of work.
Yeah.
It is absolutely a ton of work
for the time that they had.
The question is,
is that the right decision?
I don't think it is.
This hair work
is pretty crappy, guys.
What's with cousin itt wig?
The overall shape
of this head sadly
is looking terrier-esque.
It's not like a wolf head.
Can you open your mouth?
Articulate that at all?
Oh, man.
Is there a fantastic four theme
here?
It sort of has, like, a
thing-esque rock texture going.
And turn your head
to the right.
It's--
Damn.
I don't like muzzle werewolf.
I never have, and I never will.
It doesn't work.
That shape on a human head
does not and will never work
because the rest of the shape
of our skull
- doesn't flow into that.
- Mm-hmm.
The piece is bad.
They're not judging my work.
They're judging this piece
that I helped on.
It wasn't a collaboration.
It was a dictatorship.
The piece is bad.
I might as well go
up there * guillotine.
I want to explain to the judges
this is not
what I wanted to make.
This is not my work.
He's pretty.
I like the blue wolf.
It's an interesting concept.
All right,
let's see the back then.
This is interesting stuff.
There are these strokes
where they're just
going in and, like,
subdividing up muscle
and making it look interesting.
Also the flow through the neck.
- Mm-hmm.
- See, I like this thing.
They're doing a whole suit
in 19 hours.
Like,
there's definitely latitudes
that I'm willing to grant them.
The judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
House and Meagan,
you're up first.
Begin by explaining the concept
and how you divided up
the duties here.
The concept is
an American astronaut on Mars
that's bitten by one of
the native lycanthrope species
and is
in mid-transformation.
I sculpted the head,
the chest, the hands,
painting, and constructed
the latex suit.
I did the hair and the back.
I think
this is a great concept.
When it walks out,
there's
a very conspicuous backstory
fulfilling that aspect
of our challenge.
- I'm pretty happy with this.
- Thank you.
I do like the fact that
she can actually use her mouth,
which is something some
of our others can't do.
And that's really good.
Massing out the shoulders,
keeping the head small,
those are all things that feel
very classic wolf-like,
so that's where the success
is for me on this.
Meagan and House,
please step back.
- Thank you.
Eric F and Anthony.
Tell me what your concept is.
Our werewolf is from Saturn.
And there's 62 moons,
so we figured
we'd be pretty wolfed out.
I think you really did
a lot of work this week,
and I have to give you a hand
at how much you accomplished.
However, the head looks like
a big, rubber Halloween mask,
guys.
I'm not really happy with this.
And it could have been
so bitchin'.
Having your character
in reverse
is a neat concept,
but it really does not work.
There's no way
this guy could perform.
Somewhere along the line,
you had to have stopped
and looked at the proportions
that are nightmares,
especially on a wolf creature.
You need mass and bulk up here,
and then the head is way too big
even for that construct.
Anthony, Eric,
please step back.
Thanks for everything.
Wayne and Kris.
Start off by telling us
the concept.
Basically our werewolf
is from Neptune.
Neptune is
218 degrees below Celsius,
so it's very, very cold.
So we wanted to keep
those blue tones
to where he's camouflaged
into this environment.
Turn to the back,
if you don't mind, real quick.
What's really cool is
the detailing that you're doing
along the spine
and up into the neck,
extending that into the skull.
You're messing with
the forms appropriately.
There's some beautiful work
going on in there.
When you were sculpting,
did one person focus
more on the front
and another on the back?
Wayne pretty much handled
the front,
and I did the back.
I really appreciate
all of those flourishes,
and it is amazing amount
of work.
For me, he is
a very cohesive makeup.
And you did a whole suit.
It's an amazing job.
- Thank you.
Wayne and Kris,
please step back.
- Thank you.
- Good job.
Good job, man.
Autumn and Eric Z.
Please explain the concept
behind this creation.
Being the Jupiter werewolf,
he has a stone structure inside
to help him withstand
Jupiter's gravitational pull.
This is a nightmare.
Tell me what the breakdown
of responsibility was.
Eric had blocked out the chest,
and the spine and
I had blocked out the head,
and then he resculpted it,
- and then I resculpted it again.
- Well...
- Can I-- may I interject?
- Yeah.
Sure.
I had not resculpted the face.
I did do sculpting on the face.
- Yeah.
- But I did not resculpt it.
I felt that I needed to fix it
or make it better.
The overall execution--
the giant, gaping holes
on his arms that are covered
with dental dam,
the shoes--
there's no attempt at all
to make those blend
onto the legs.
It's a travesty.
Could you turn him around
for me?
So you blocked out
the whole sculpture...
- The spine.
- I did, I blocked out--
- And then Autumn
finished it off? - Exactly.
Once again, this is not exactly
what I had sculpted.
It is very much the same idea,
but it turned out
completely different.
It seems like the relationship
was dysfunctional,
and Autumn--
It seemed great until we
got right here actually.
Until this moment?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
We asked you at the beginning,
both of you, who did what,
and you finished
that dissertation.
But you're a team.
So I don't know
what's going on.
But I know
what the end result is,
and it's not good.
It's a match made in hell.
You're walking all over him,
and he's sitting back
and not talking up enough,
and that combination
is what led
to this travesty of makeup.
I didn't feel at the time
that I was walking
all over him at all.
And he didn't let me on
to feel that way.
- That I was--
- I find that hard to believe.
You were too busy being bossy
probably to hear it.
Enough said.
Eric and Autumn,
please step back.
Thanks, man.
The judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you'd please,
head back to the makeup room
while they make
their decisions.
All right, guys.
Let's start with some
of the looks you liked the most.
Why don't we begin
with House and Meagan?
I felt they had some really
good ideas that told a story.
Right off the bat, you knew
that it was like
some sort of astronaut
went to a foreign planet,
got attacked--
A lot of brilliant decisions
in the terms of sculpture
and the paint job.
Huge amount of work
in a small amount of time.
I did like the head sculpture.
In comparison
to the other head sculptures,
- it felt the most plausible.
- Mm-hmm.
All right, let's move on
to Wayne and Kris.
Beautiful sculpting all around.
The back was
a cooler featured element.
When it turned around,
it looked so amazing.
I mean, it was just all there.
I see a color pattern here.
It's starting to head
in the direction
of professional paint job.
It's not just blue,
and it's not just highlight
and shadow.
It's also
some really nice patterns
on top of it breaking it up.
And it looks good from far away
and close up.
- Truly impressive.
- Yeah.
All right, let's move on
to the looks you liked the least
this week.
Why don't we start
with Eric F and Anthony?
I think they needed
to think it through
and realize that actually
turning somebody around
is a neat idea,
but it made the performer
unable to perform.
Yeah. At all.
Except for to wave
his wings around.
Yes.
I think Eric's got
some really cool ideas,
but he's going to continue
to do what he's doing,
as long as he keeps getting by.
He's gonna swing for the fences
with these gigantic concepts
going, "ah, yeah, I know
it's not as good as I can do,
but I'll get through
this week."
And eventually,
it's gonna be the wrong week.
Let's move on
to Autumn and Eric Z.
Oh, my God.
The core concept of this
was so asinine.
I find it almost insulting,
this completely
ludicrous concept.
I concur completely,
and I've just about had it.
I think that her teamwork,
her attempt at getting through
this challenge is loathsome.
She's ready to throw him
under the bus
for something that she did.
I also think
what's unacceptable
is the fact that Eric
is not defending himself.
He needs to address it,
not just for the competition,
but just to set the tone
for himself professionally.
If you put it
into a studio environment,
the way that they explained it,
I'd probably fire both of them.
- Yeah.
- It just doesn't matter.
- No.
- All right, judges.
Have you made your decisions?
- Yes, we have.
- We have.
Let's bring 'em back out.
Glenn, tell us
about the top teams.
Wayne and Kris.
There were
some unique sculptural moments,
and it was
a very comprehensive makeup,
the whole thing accentuated
by a really well done paint job.
House and Meagan.
We really liked the shape
and proportions of your makeup,
and your backstory
was very conspicuous.
We saw what it was right away.
Which team came out on top?
The top team tonight is--
- Okay, which team
came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Wayne and Kris.
- Yeah.
- Good job, man.
You found a really nice balance
between werewolf and alien.
And it was
a very complete character.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
Kris and Wayne,
great job, guys.
But we can only have
one winner.
Glenn.
The winner tonight is...
- Kris.
- Wow.
Wow.
Thank you.
It came down to figuring out
what our favorite part
of it was.
And that was the sculptural
detail on the back.
Thank you so much.
I am really happy to hear
the judges call my name.
I don't know what to say
other than I feel great.
Kris, congratulations.
You and Wayne can head back
to the makeup room.
Good job.
House and Meagan,
you are also safe this week.
Please head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you.
Unfortunately,
that means the rest of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Eric F and Anthony.
Once again,
you tried to do so much
that it was a detriment
to your work.
The head,
some of the proportions
really killed the whole thing
for us.
Autumn and Eric Z.
This was
a horrific collaboration,
start to finish,
which resulted in a truly
disjointed final product.
So who is going home tonight?
The person leaving
tonight is...
Autumn.
This was your concept
and a lot of your work,
which you took credit for,
but then you didn't take
ownership of the end result.
That means the rest of you
are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you.
- Keep in touch, guys.
Thank you.
Autumn, it's been great having
you here with us.
Please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you, guys.
- Good luck, Autumn.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
I'm out.
I feel let down by Eric Z.
And to say I didn't listen to
or I didn't take input
is absurd.
I'm not ready to leave
the competition.
To go out like this
is a little harsh.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.tvsubtitles.net