Previously on Face Off...
the artists headed
to Comic-Con
and brought
original superheroes to life.
Anthony's fiery creation
brought him to the top.
Oh, my God.
And Michael was sent home.
Now 12 artists remain.
And tonight, they'll face
a demonic challenge.
Welcome to Hell.
This is my kind of challenge.
And an unexpected twist
pushes them to the limit.
The note will dramatically
impact your designs.
- What?
- Oh, no.
Quit irritating me.
My partner
isn't pulling her weight.
The face sculpture
is very rough.
Those are beautiful pieces.
It punches you in the face
with how bad it sucks.
In the end, only one
will win the opportunity
to be a guest lecturer
at Make Up For Ever's academies
in New York and Paris,
the all-new 2013 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
It's tough.
I really feel bad for Michael
and honestly thought
that maybe he had more to offer.
I think we all just want
to beat Anthony at this point...
We want to see a new winner.
...than let Anthony win
another challenge.
Anthony won the last challenge.
He's probably gonna be
my biggest competition here.
I would feel really good
about myself
if I could just beat Anthony
one time.
This one's for Michael!
Michael!
It is early morning.
Where we're going,
we have no idea.
All I know
is it seems like we're
in the middle of the desert.
It is hot.
There's these pitchforks
stabbed into the earth,
and then there's
signs hanging from them.
And I don't recognize
any of the names.
They're, like, foreign.
I have no idea
what we're doing.
Welcome to Hell.
We brought you
all the way out here
in this horrible heat
to get you
in the right frame of mind
for your next challenge.
Beside me here
are several pitchforks,
each one with the name
of a demon
from a different culture
around the world.
Awesome.
So working in teams of two,
your spotlight challenge
is to bring one of these
horrific demons to life.
Oh, yes.
This is my kind of challenge.
Finally get to make
some cool monsters,
and I'm loving it.
Your teams have been
randomly selected.
- Team one, Kris and Eric Z.
- Nice.
Team two is Alam and Anthony.
- Yay.
- There you are.
We were all talking about,
"we can't let Anthony
win again."
But this one,
I'll let him win again.
Team three, House and Meagan.
Team four, Alex...
I'm just hoping,
"don't pair me up with Autumn.
Don't pair me up with Autumn.
Don't pair me up with Autumn."
- And Autumn.
- All right.
I'm really looking forward
to working with her.
Team five, Katie and Jenna.
Yay.
Team six is Eric F and Wayne.
All right, go ahead and stand
next to your new teammates.
Yeah, dude.
This is a good one.
Kris and Eric Z,
you're up first.
- Pick us a winner.
- All right.
None of these names
of the demons
are ringing any bells.
But if it is a demon
from a certain culture,
it's gonna be something that
we can do a lot with creatively.
- That was fast.
- Yeah.
We picked Abraxas.
Deumus.
So many good ones.
We like Azi Dahaka.
He's half-man, half-snake,
and he's bound with chains.
Pazuzu.
Eurynome.
Chort.
I really want you
to soak up this place
and let it inspire
your designs.
So I'm gonna leave you
out here all alone
to sketch.
And watch your step out here.
This is rattlesnake country.
Of course.
Okay, go grab your sketch pads
and get started.
So now that we know
what we're doing,
we have 30 minutes
to sketch it.
But we have to do it out here
in the scorching heat,
so we're just trying
to find a "comfortable spot."
You want to keep him--
his skin, like, really fleshy
- and pink and, you know...
- Yeah, yeah.
Pazuzu is
an ancient Babylonian demon.
He has the head of a dog,
eagle-like feet,
two pairs of wings,
a scorpion's tail.
And the only way we thought
of incorporating it
is a gargoyle theme.
We're pretty sure we nailed
this design, actually.
That is gonna be incredible.
We have Azi Dahaka.
It means "fiendish snake."
And he's gonna have an arm
that is a snake.
And that'll be
a foam latex puppet, almost,
that wraps over his hand.
And so we couldn't ask
for a better demon.
I really want to try
to change, like, human form
as much as possible.
Right.
Chort is a Russian demon,
and it has a pig face, hooves,
and it has horns.
We have the most iconic demon.
We will definitely
be top looks on this.
It's saying that she's got
feet like a rooster
and then, like, a really pointed
and hooked nose.
So we got Deumus,
a Hindu goddess.
We both really want
to make this demon beautiful
to take it away
from a grotesque nature,
which we know that's
where everybody else
is gonna take their demons.
Come on, guys,
get out of the heat.
- I'm tired of being safe.
- Yes, me too.
I got to be honest.
Time is up.
We're hot, we're flustered,
and really excited
to get in the shop
and get started.
We get to the lab,
pick our models,
and the first thing I do
is go search the lab
to see what kind of
electronics I can find.
It's very fun
working with Eric.
We're just, like, thinking big
right off the get-go.
- Do the other axis?
- Yeah.
Our goal is to have animatronic
blinking eyes for this demon.
So we're gonna have
the actress look out the mouth,
so we can really elongate
the head
and leave room
for the eye mechanisms.
All right,
animatronics are a go.
Eurynome is a Grecian demon
who is covered in sores
and has wolf-like teeth
and eats dead flesh.
We have four hours
in the lab today.
And the first thing is
we start sculpting the face.
And we have a lot to do
because we want small horns,
a big mouth
with wolf-like, gnarly teeth.
I want to tackle the legs,
just to be, like, okay...
Yeah.
I just want to make sure
that it works.
Katie wants to do a walker.
A walker is a creature
that has very long arms
so it looks
like they're walking.
Just hoping that
we can pull it off.
We want the mouth
partially open, right?
Well, if we're gonna do
any of the extensions,
it's gonna have to come out.
Yeah.
Our demon, Abraxas, is a demon
from Egyptian culture.
He has the head of a lion,
and a whip,
and the feet of a dragon.
And there's deserts in Egypt
where it's, like, hot as hell,
so we want to use
dry, crackly browns and beiges.
- You liking it?
- Yes.
- Cool.
- Good.
Wait, there's more hands
in here.
Yeah.
The pieces that we intend
to complete
will be a full headpiece
facial prosthetic,
a snake glove,
a full chest piece,
a back piece.
So there is quite a bit to do.
It is a snake hand.
It's looking
a little turtle-ish.
I'm just doing
the inside right now!
House has really strong ideas,
and one of the ideas is
to create a puppet on the hand.
Okay. Let me work on it
for one minute.
He doesn't like
what I'm doing to the puppet.
Don't do the outside yet.
I want to just
do the inside right now
so that it's really detailed,
and then--
because I'm gonna put it--
- I think you're spending
too much time on it right now.
I'm just gonna
let him finish the puppet,
but I'm a little nervous
that none of my ideas
are gonna come through.
- How's this?
- Ooh... uh...
Alam is going
to sculpt one rooster foot,
and we're gonna mold that,
cast it twice.
And I'm working
on the facial prosthetic
and figuring out how these horns
are going to work
in relation to that.
We need a lot
of really cool wrinkles in this.
- Yeah.
- This sculpt has to be bad ass.
Yeah,
that's what's gonna win it.
Autumn's telling me
what a great sculptor she is,
so I'm gonna trust her on that
and let her
really sculpt her vision.
The only thing
I'm really afraid of is,
is this entire concept
gonna marry itself
really well together
with the scorpion tail
and the wings?
'Cause it has to have
an overall look.
It just can't be random parts
all thrown together.
I can't feel.
I'm pushing on the clay,
and since it's numb,
I can't feel...
what I'm doing at all.
I have a tumor--
it's a growth--
in this hand,
and it's pressing
on a bundle of nerves,
which cause my fingers
to be completely numb.
Quit irritating me.
I'm already a slow sculptor,
so I'm really, really worried.
I'm like, "how am I
gonna sculpt this?"
I can't believe how fast
some of these guys are.
Mmh-mm.
The last thing I want to
do is let Katie down.
Hey, guys.
- Come gather 'round here.
- Hey!
McKenzie walks in,
and she doesn't have
her dad with her,
so, um, you know
something's up.
Uh-oh.
As you know,
Hollywood producers
often give script notes
that can completely
transform a story.
Well, that's the case today,
'cause the note I have for you
will dramatically impact
your designs.
Oh, shit.
- Coming up...
- Ow! Dang!
Oh, my God, what am I gonna do?
What am I gonna do?
- Are you happy with this?
- Not really.
There's no way
I could put a camera on that.
Hey, guys.
So McKenzie walks into the lab
and stops us all from working.
I'm nervous.
As you know,
Hollywood producers
often give script notes
that can completely
transform a story.
Well, that's the case today,
'cause the note I have for you
will dramatically impact
your designs.
Oh, shit.
Hell has frozen over.
- Oh, no.
- What?
- That's right.
You're now going to need
to turn your designs
into ice demons.
The twist for this challenge
scares me
because it's
the exact opposite feeling
that we were going for.
Good luck
changing your designs.
I'll see you all tomorrow.
Bye.
Waah!
- Maybe for the toenails...
- Uh-huh.
...we can do icicles,
like, icicle talons
or something clear.
Oh, nice.
We're gonna change our concept
by changing the color scheme.
Our warm colors
are obviously gonna be turned
into some colder colors.
Let me go see
if there's any white hair.
Okay.
We don't have
to make it made of ice.
Just, it dwells
in a cold climate.
Our demon's from Russia,
so we already had
these kind of cool elements
going in anyway.
So we're like,
"okay, cool."
Well, like,
since he has so many teeth,
we can make them
look like icicles... maybe.
He should definitely
have icicles somewhere.
I think that would
translate well as icicles.
We're not gonna change our demon
too drastically,
'cause he still needs
to be a demon
even though he's
in an ice environment.
So we're just making his skin
a little more chapped
and adding
a little more snow elements.
- But it's, like, completely...
- Frozen over.
That would be awesome.
You know what would be cool?
What if you made the cowl,
the back of it, like that?
- Or is it too much?
- Maybe, maybe.
- It's-- I don't know.
- Just so it fucking like...
Yeah.
I think we should have
two different snakes
on the body.
You know, especially since
you get this room
to play with it,
why not make a big cobra?
That would look so dope.
- I think Glenn would love that.
- Okay.
That's what we're doing.
- Six minutes.
- Awesome.
Let's keep going.
The end of day one,
I'm not happy with the way
the sculpt is going.
I'm getting
more and more frustrated,
especially when Katie and I see
all the amazing stuff
that's going on.
Time's up, everybody!
I feel bad for Katie
because she has
to work with somebody
who cannot perform
to their optimum level.
Now here it is, day two,
and, man, we got a lot to do.
I start blocking out the horns.
Wayne's working like a madman
finishing detailing up
the head.
We are on track.
Definitely no playing it safe
on a demon challenge.
So I start sculpting,
and my hand feels a little bit better.
Still not optimally
but I'm feeling
more positive about this.
That looks good.
Hey, everybody.
Hello.
McKenzie and Mr. Westmore
come out,
and we're not
where I'd like to be,
so I'm apprehensive of what
they're going to say to us.
This is Azi Dahaka.
He's a Persian demon.
Our character has two snakes.
So this snake is actually going
through into the shoulder,
and the big texture
from the cowl
will go right here.
It would be very helpful
if you, you know,
within your hood--
to have a different color
or a shade-- a variation
of a shade or something.
Otherwise, it's all gonna look
as one flat plane.
Give yourself
a little depth in there.
He's a Grecian demon.
And this particular demon
feasted on dead bodies
and has wolf-like teeth.
I'm concerned
with the face here now,
'cause I'm seeing
a pair of lips
peeking out of a mask.
And so how are you going
to hide that?
We'll have little teeth
and then more teeth.
Double, maybe even triple.
If you have a moment to do it,
just make a little teeny piece
that you would glue over
the lips.
Just bring it down
over his lip.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- That's smart. Okay.
This is the horn
we just blocked out.
We have the hoof, the hands.
We have
these shoulder sections.
And the cool thing too
is we are actually
adding some animatronics.
You know,
if you don't have time for it,
don't let your paint jobs
suffer for animatronics.
I want to see
the time management, you know?
- That is one of my specialties.
- Okay.
- Not mine, but his.
- I know.
Our demon has lion features
mixed with dragon feet.
Just a thought...
with all of these characters
that are put into it,
some kind of a hump
on the back, possibly?
'Cause, I mean, most of all,
like, the lions and the cats,
when they walk,
they have that arch
in the back, yeah.
- See the shoulder blades move.
- Yeah.
Mr. Westmore had a lot
of great advice for us.
We're definitely going
to take that in consideration
and kind of beef up the neck
a little bit.
- She's a Hindu goddess.
- Hindu? Oh, wow.
She's known for her four horns,
hooked teeth, hooked nose,
and a soul
that she holds in her hand
and is ready to devour.
- You going to do it in foam?
- Yes.
It's gonna shrink.
So by making him
just a little but larger,
you're gonna allow
for that shrinkage.
Otherwise, you're gonna have
this lip up here
and down here...
- I see.
- ...when the foam dries.
He is Pazuzu from Babylon.
He has features of a man's body
with a dog-lion face.
He's almost gonna look
gargoyle-ish.
You don't have a lot
of-- of depth detail,
so you're gonna have
to do shading and things
to really pop that.
All right, everybody,
we're heading out.
Good luck tomorrow.
- Bye.
- Bye. Thank you, guys.
How's it going?
You know, I took
so much ibuprofen this morning.
As the day progresses,
my hand's getting more painful
and more numb.
You doing okay still?
No?
No. I mean, it's always--
it's just
gonna be like this, you know?
There's not much
I can do about it.
It's really frustrating
knowing that my partner
isn't pulling her weight,
but not 'cause
she doesn't want to.
It's just 'cause
she physically can't.
Being not able
to do things the way I want to
is just really pissing me off.
How am I gonna sculpt this?
I can't sculpt it.
Ow! There it goes again.
Dang.
Oh, my God, what am I gonna do?
What am I gonna do?
And I start
going into panic mode.
Damn. I cannot sculpt
with my hand like this.
I can't.
- Damn, there it goes again.
- Mm.
It feels like I just stuck
my hand in a light socket.
I'm trying not to yell at her
or tell her that she's
not doing enough
because I understand,
her hand doesn't work,
but I'm worried
because I don't know
how that's going
to affect our time management.
We got to hustle on molding this
'cause it's our base.
Yeah, yeah, we don't want
to screw that one up.
At this point, there's not
really anything that can be done
about my hand,
not even temporarily.
It's just so frustrating
when I can't make my hand
do what I want it to do.
I'm nervous about it,
but I've beaten
way worse things.
I've been
in way more pain before.
I can deal with this.
We only have
a couple hours left,
so I start hacking out the wings
as quick as humanly possible
just to at least get them done.
They're a little low?
We could-- boop--
move 'em.
We got 40 minutes.
I get my sculpt finished.
Now I have to mold
these things.
We're in good shape
but we're not there yet.
40 minutes, dude, is insane.
We still got to mold the hands,
mold the second half
of the thing...
and get
these molds cleaned out.
We're cutting it
down to the wire.
I don't know about this.
I'm running out of time today.
I'm working on the feet,
and I still have a lot to do.
Yeah, dude.
- Nice.
- Yeah.
Time's up, everybody!
At the end of day two,
I'm pretty nervous
because Alam and I
were hoping
to have both feet cast.
- Let's go.
So now we are gonna have
to cast them
on the day of the application.
There is a lot
that has to be covered tomorrow,
and I'm just hoping
that we can finish it.
Let's go.
Good luck, guys.
- We're running.
- Running.
So it's application day.
We only have four hours
in the lab.
I'm a little bit concerned
'cause I got a lot
of painting to do,
so I'm loading up
my airbrushes right away.
There is no time.
We got to get this show
on the road.
- Here they are.
- Hi.
Get comfortable.
- This is gonna go on your back.
- Okay.
I'll start pre-painting it
then.
Okay, cool.
Got the first horn.
Got my mechanisms laid out.
Wayne and I have the impossible
in front of us.
Not only do I got
to cast two horns,
two gloves, two hooves,
and do
a full animatronic unit...
Check this shit.
Nice.
We got to get
this thing pre-painted
and on this actress
in four hours.
It usually takes stuff longer
than four hours just to dry.
I don't know.
I still think
this doesn't look right.
I'm not too happy
about the leg extensions
'cause they're not turning out
the way that I want them to.
One claw is totally sideways
and doesn't match the form
of the leg
that we had tried to make.
And they were my idea,
so I want to make sure
that I can pull them off.
It's not working.
Damn it.
All right.
One of the things
that is so easy to do
with opening any mold
is opening it way too fast,
which could damage the piece.
And unfortunately,
under these conditions,
we have to do that.
- Yay.
- Awesome.
Luckily, there was only
a slight tear in the seam,
so we have a successful cast.
- You want to take care of those?
- Yeah.
All right.
The clock is ticking down
and no paint is on yet.
I am freaking out.
We start base-coating
our model,
painting her like the outside
of a house.
Meagan and I are both
painting the snake demon.
Are you happy with this so far?
Not really.
I'm a little frustrated.
It's not really coming together.
It's just sloppy.
We do paint different,
and House wants to start
with hard detail,
with airbrushing,
and I'm used
to going in with sponges
so that it has a nice balance.
Which part is sucky that
you're, like, annoyed about?
The paint, particularly.
15 minutes, everybody!
That's time!
Time is up, and I'm,
once again, freaking out.
We're gonna have to paint
our piece at last looks.
To be painting at last looks
puts the weight
on my shoulders a little bit,
just because it's been
a recurring thing with me.
If we are in the bottom,
probably gonna be the one
to be sent home.
Coming up...
This is crazy, dude.
First time anyone's done that.
The face sculpture looks
like you just carved it out
with a spoon.
Those are beautiful pieces.
It punches you in the face
with how bad it sucks.
Good luck, everybody.
- Eric, I'll work on the hooves.
- Okay.
We have an hour at final looks.
The mechanisms
are working great,
but nothing is painted.
The thing is just
the base coat.
Definitely, this is gonna
be a good one.
You look awesome,
awesome, awesome.
Autumn feels super confident
with our demon.
She's convinced that she's
gonna get a standing ovation,
and I don't think
that's gonna happen.
30 minutes, guys!
30 minutes!
If they called time right now,
we'd be comfortable with it.
Good, got some purple on there.
- I got the black.
- Cool.
I'll start blacking out
his fingers.
Should we do that
or a smaller one?
- I'm okay without it.
- Okay.
You want to go ahead
and get the head on?
Oh, no... the mechanism.
I knocked the cable loose.
So all of this mechanics
that I did
just slipped off the servo.
Oh, fuck!
All that hard work for nothing.
Thank you.
That's time!
Whoo!
- This is crazy, dude.
- I feel sick.
I'm not happy
with the paint job.
Eric's not happy
That's probably what's gonna
put us in the bottom,
and I could be going home
at this point.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
First, let's say hello
to your judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Special Effects
Studio Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening, guys.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
Hi, everybody.
Hi.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hi.
This week,
your spotlight challenge
was to create a demon character
from somewhere around the world
and bring it to life.
Then we threw you a twist.
Hell had frozen over,
which meant that you
had to adapt your demons
to their new, icy environment.
So let's see
what you've come up with.
I'm so excited
about our creature.
I can't take my eyes
off of him.
It's the cutest little gargoyle
I ever saw in my life.
So we're feeling really
confident about this character.
I'm not feeling very good.
What's bothering me the most
is the snake puppet.
The finishing piece
that makes this character great
is just, like,
a wobbly rubber snake.
I'm disappointed by that.
The silhouette is crazy
on this creature,
and the 3-foot demon horns
look beautiful.
The paint job sucks,
but overall,
the thing actually
looks pretty damn cool, man.
He does look different,
but not in a good way.
I know that it's crap.
I have a feeling
that it's going
to be one of us
that's going home.
He came out
and snapped that whip,
and both Eric and I
were very happy.
Our demon looks beautiful
on the stage.
It's pretty,
it's very colorful,
with all those sparkly things.
I like how it turned out.
Judges, why don't you
take a closer look.
I don't see any teamwork
on this thing.
Yeah, 'cause there's
a definite disparity
between components.
Different styles.
And the sculpting on this face
is actually rougher
than I thought it was.
Yeah.
Can you turn around for us?
I think the whole thing
could've been much bolder.
Could've been bigger.
And no matter what you do
with this,
it's still a hand puppet.
Yup.
You know what?
I like this better up close
than I did from far away.
I love the fact
that we're using the mouth
as an orbital cavity.
First time on Face Off
anyone's done that.
I'm really not thrilled
about those giant eye shades.
My heart is beating
about a million miles an hour.
Turn for us.
Our guy didn't come out looking
the way we wanted him to
at all.
I just know we're gonna
wind up in bottom looks.
We want to know what you think
of tonight's transformations.
Tell us on Twitter,
using #FaceOff.
There's an attempt
to change the physiology
a huge amount, which is great.
They made a huge mistake
in doing it, though.
I'm terrified
for the both of us.
Our demon looks
like a big, black mess.
The top part's kind of groovy.
You get the whole feeling
of a goat from there up,
but that's
very demonic-looking.
Normally, this would
just be grotesque.
The detailing here.
It's still very beautiful.
Yeah, it's pretty.
- I like the turquoise.
- Yeah.
The judges have scored
your creations.
Let's find out
what they thought.
Meagan and House.
Kris and Eric Z.
You guys are safe and can
head back to the makeup room.
Thank you.
The rest of you
were the best and the worst.
The judges would now like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Anthony and Alam,
please step forward.
Tell me a little bit
about the inspiration
for this makeup.
The character is called Deumus.
She's a Hindu goddess.
I sculpted the face prosthetic
and the horns.
And alam did the feet
and the body painting.
Overall, it seems
like the themes
that we asked you
to present here
have been
very successfully addressed
in your creation this week.
It's an absolutely
gorgeous fusion
of the demonic
and the cultural references.
Thank you.
What made you choose
the colors that you used?
Initially, we were gonna go
with kind of more purples.
But it changed to
a "hell froze over" situation.
We both recalled having seen
some Hindu artwork
that a lot of their gods
are blue in tone.
Well, that was really
a great choice.
You do have a real
super strong furrowed brow,
but it's handled
in such a delicate way,
particularly that little crease
just at the nose,
that you maintained beauty
in something
that normally would have turned
into a classic witch makeup.
That's a testament to reserve.
Thank you.
Anthony and Alam,
please step back.
- Thank you.
Alex and Autumn,
please step up.
Okay, ladies, can you tell us
who your demon is
and who did what?
He is Pazuzu.
He's a demon
that actually protects humans
from other demons,
so we incorporated
something endearing about him.
I sculpted the face
and made the wings.
She did the chest piece,
the hands,
and all the airbrush work.
How do you think you did
on your creation?
I think he's adorable.
I got to tell you,
I'm not quite sure
that he's adorable.
Autumn, I think
the face sculpture
is very, very rough, honey.
It looks like you just carved
it out with a spoon, basically.
One thing
that really makes this
so difficult
for me to enjoy--
there is no anatomy
in the wings,
and the fact
that they're out doesn't help
because he looks
like he's broken and damaged.
What did you change
when McKenzie came in
and gave you the twist?
- The color scheme changed.
- Yeah, the color scheme.
Like, we decided
to make him, like, paler
and more, like,
sickly-looking.
A lot of what you've done
tonight works from far away,
but when we get up close,
there's no way I could put
a camera on that
in a close-up.
Autumn, Alex,
thank you very much.
Please step back.
Wayne and Eric, please step up.
Tell us about the character
and the division of the work
that you've done here.
Our character's demon name
is Chort.
It's a Russian demon.
It carries a lot
of the same similarities
to the iconic pan.
I sculpted the chest
and the whole back piece.
And while I was doing that,
fox was blocking out the head.
We actually had an animatronic
mechanism for the eye blinks.
But at last minute,
the cable slipped
and we didn't get a chance
to fix it.
You just got to be so careful.
But the silhouette
is wonderful.
There's nice, big moments,
graphically.
The dark horns,
those are beautiful pieces.
They really, really are.
There's some
really smart decisions here.
Letting the performer
see through the mouth
and extending the form up
and past the top of the head,
that's awesome.
That would happen in my shop.
I really dig the thing overall.
But you cannot
paint something this huge
on the day here.
Give yourself time to paint.
This thing could have been
so much cooler
had you given it
a good paint job.
The fact that you put
all that pink into the face
to turn it into
more of a pig character
was really helpful.
Really beautiful work, guys.
- Thank you.
Eric, Wayne, please step back.
Jenna and Katie.
Begin by explaining where
you took your reference from
and what everybody's role
in the makeup was.
Well, this is
the demon Eurynome.
He's covered in sores
and feeds on dead bodies.
I sculpted the back
and the leg extensions,
and Jenna focused mostly
on the face.
How successful do you feel
in creating a demonic character?
Not at all.
We had time-management
issues
because Jenna's hand
is completely numb--
her dominant hand.
- So he's a hot mess.
- He is a hot mess, yeah.
Well, that's good, that you're
both on the same page as me.
That's awesome.
When you have so little variance
in your colors,
it's always gonna be
a problem for me.
You've got to show me the form
of what you're doing
with your colors.
You must do that.
Unfortunately, I don't see
any sores on this demon.
I sculpted a bunch of 'em
in there,
but I think
the paint job ruined it.
That's unfortunate, you guys.
You can fix a bad sculpt
with a good paint job.
Right.
It's such a huge concept to do
this physiology manipulation.
So with the time you have,
it can only have failed.
Katie, Jenna,
you can step back.
Okay, the judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you would please head back
to the makeup room
while they make
their decisions.
Why don't we start with
the looks you like the most.
How about Anthony and Alam?
I dig this one.
That furrowed brow.
That pointed chin.
The hooked nose
with four nostrils.
That stuff
shouldn't have worked,
but they just handled it
so well.
I think it's beautiful
and very God- and goddess-
and demon-like,
all rolled into one.
Let's move on
to Wayne and Eric F.
Such a beautiful piece.
Yeah, I mean, from head to toe.
That body sculpt is so amazing.
I mean, the anatomy
was all there.
They managed to evoke "demon"
with those beautiful horns,
and then they went off
in their own direction.
All right, let's move on
to some of the looks
you liked the least.
Why don't we start
with Katie and Jenna.
Now Jenna, she did
the head, the face?
Katie did the back
and the arms.
When you look at the arms,
those extensions,
they were abysmal.
They were un-definable
as canes or sticks or anatomy.
The arms don't match
the rest of the body.
The pustules are--
there's zero effort.
So when your head fails,
your arm extension idea fails,
what else is there
to talk about here?
It's really just
whose fault is it?
- Yeah.
- Last one, Alex and Autumn.
The concept,
there was nothing there.
They just executed verbatim
what they were asked to do
and poorly at that.
Autumn had a single plane
of wet clay
that she just gouged in
some marks to be wrinkles.
If she's happy with that work,
there's little hope for her.
The chest was savable,
but the face was--
like, I don't even know
what it looks like.
When you walk up to that thing,
it punches you in the face
with how bad it sucks.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- No doubt.
- Yes, we have.
Let's bring 'em back out.
Glenn, tell us about
the top teams.
The top teams tonight are...
Anthony and Alam.
There's a very strong synthesis
between your demon's attributes
and the region
that it was from.
We could immediately
tell a lot about it
just looking at it.
Wayne and Eric.
The sculpture on the abdomen
is really beautiful.
And we also felt that yours
was probably
the most uniquely "demon"
tonight.
Which team came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Okay, which team
came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Anthony and Alam.
Awesome job.
Basically,
it came down to the fact
that everything
that you guys did
worked so extremely well
together.
Well done.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, guys.
Anthony and Alam, as you know,
we can only have one winner.
Glenn?
The winner tonight is...
Anthony.
Couldn't have done it
without you.
The whole character
is really very strong,
but the stand-out
is the face and the horns.
Thank you, guys.
I can't believe it.
I won four challenges in a row.
It's one of
the most amazing feelings,
but it puts
a lot of pressure on me.
Anthony, congratulations.
Thank you.
You and Alam can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thanks again, guys.
- Thank you.
Eric and Wayne,
you guys are also safe.
Please head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you, guys.
Unfortunately, that means
the rest of you
are on the bottom this week
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom teams.
Alex and Autumn.
You made some really big
sculptural mistakes,
and it ended up coming off
a bit confused.
Jenna and Katie.
You had a really great concept,
but the sculpture
and the paint job
really let you down tonight.
So who's going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Katie.
There was a lot wrong
with the makeup tonight,
but the back
and the arm extensions
were particularly rough.
Katie, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
That means the rest of you
are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
It's okay.
Katie, just keep practicing,
keep doing your art.
We've really loved
having you here.
It's been a huge honor
to be here.
Thank you so much.
Katie, it has been great
having you here with us,
but please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you.
- Thank you. Good luck.
- Good luck.
It just sucks to go home
before you're ready to.
- I'm going home.
- Oh.
It took a really long time
to get here,
and it's just been great
that I was able to come
and just meet everyone.
I'm proud
of what I've done here.
I will definitely
move on past this
and create something
really awesome.
I really want to show
what I can do.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.tvsubtitles.net