Previously on Face Off...
Anthony swept the competition,
winning both the foundation
and spotlight challenges.
- Anthony.
- Thank you so much.
And Troy was
the first artist sent home.
Now 13 artists remain.
Tonight, they'll take on
a legendary genre.
- Welcome to Comic-Con.
- Wow!
The pressure rises
as they tackle
their first
individual challenge.
- This mask is pissing me off.
- Fuck.
Oh, my God, what did I make?
Fuck.
- I don't know what to do. I'm
going home. - Turn around, please.
- Oh, my God.
- Blowout.
What's happened to you?
It was a huge waste of time.
- I really enjoyed this piece.
- That's quite genius.
In the end, only one will win
the opportunity
to be a guest lecturer
at Make Up For Ever's academies
in New York and Paris,
the all new 2013 Fiat 500
and $100,000.
Who will be the next
great name in movie magic?
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- Morning.
- Eric.
Morning.
We're all standing around
the breakfast table,
chit-chatting.
Hey, guys, check it out.
I look over in the corner,
and there's--
it looks like a letter.
"Good morning, artists,
please grab a ticket
and come join me
in San Diego for Comic-Con."
No way!
Awesome!
Comic-Con is a circus
of comic book, fantasy,
science-fiction,
horror movie geeks, man.
- Oh, my God.
- It's all there.
We're going to Comic-Con.
I've dreamt of going
to Comic-Con every day
since the day I was born.
Right here.
Here we go.
Come on.
All of us love movies
and pop culture and comic books,
and to be able
to go to the biggest
celebration of that is awesome.
Welcome to San Diego
and one of the world's biggest
pop culture conventions,
Comic-Con.
It's here that superheroes
jump off the pages
and onto the silver screen.
That's why we're here today.
Your spotlight challenge
is to create
an original superhero.
Whoo!
I know it's not easy
these days to come up with
a completely new
and original character,
so that's why
these guys are here.
They are two of the biggest
names in comic books
and co-publishers of
world-famous DC Entertainment.
First, we have the man who
spearheaded best-selling titles
like Blackest Night,
Green Lantern,
All-Star Superman,
and All-Star Batman.
Please welcome Dan Didio.
Hey, guys.
And next to him
is a world-renowned
comic book artist
whose work includes
Justice league,
All-Star Batman & Robin,
Batman Hush, and
Superman For Tomorrow.
Please say hello to Jim Lee.
Hey, guys.
I just want to scream.
Jim Lee's one
of my artistic heroes.
I'm just trying
to hold it all in.
What advice do you have
for these guys today?
Well, if you look
at superheroes,
they really reflect the era
that they come from.
Also, think about the colors.
If you look at all your main,
powerful, iconic characters,
they tend to have primary colors
of the color palette, right?
Red, blue, and yellow.
So start thinking about that.
Also, you've got to look
at the character's silhouettes.
Look at the powers
of the characters
and how do those powers relate
to the way the character looks?
I'm nervous about this,
because comics are definitely
a genre that
I'm not familiar with.
Since we heard you're gonna
be creating new characters,
we decided to bring some
of DC's top artists to you
and give you a hand helping
come up with the sketches
and the designs
for these characters.
- Whoo!
I can't wait to collaborate
with DC artists.
They definitely
will know their stuff
when it comes to superheroes.
Before you guys get started
on your sketches,
Jim and Dan have
a surprise for you
that they'd like to share.
We're very pleased to announce
that the winning character
will appear in an upcoming
DC comic book.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, wow.
That's so cool.
My daughter loves superheroes,
so I would love to do this
really great superhero for her.
All right, everybody,
go ahead and get started.
I'm paired with Jim Lee,
and it's just
so incredibly exciting.
I feel like
this is all a dream.
My father is my hero,
and I think in--
in my character,
whatever I create,
I want it to reflect families.
My superhero is based off
of my father,
a hardworking man
in a biochemical factory.
What about if he has some--
like, those tubes,
those oxygen tubes, like-- right?
Like, kind of come out
to the side kind of thing?
- That would be really neat.
- Okay.
She's gonna say,
"By the power of Ra..."
- Okay.
- "I'm Mercury Ray."
My concept is a flashback
character from the 1970s.
If you're thinking
of the belt extending down,
whether this--
- I want to go down
to, like, here.
Okay.
Punk rock?
- Absolutely.
- Cyborg woman.
- Yeah.
- Sexy.
My concept is robot girl,
a kick-ass cyborg chick.
And she will kill you.
So watch out, bad guys.
I'm trying to think
of a character
who is trying
to kind of redeem himself.
Okay.
My first instinct is
to go with a lava character.
Texturally, do something
shiny here, like volcanic rock.
- Like, you know?
- Okay.
My thinking is,
stay away from a costume
and go with a suit that's
actually a living part of him.
Maybe, like, the force
comes out of his hands.
Yeah.
I'm traditionally
a horror artist.
Yeah.
But the character
I'd like to do is a '40s,
Dick Tracy type look.
Okay, yeah.
What you want
to be thinking about is,
what is the context
of this character?
Are they in a vintage,
'40s metropolis kind of city?
Something like that.
The character I was thinking of
is somewhat of an antihero.
My concept is Elijah,
Bringer of Plagues.
He's one of the sons
of one of the Horsemen
of the Apocalypse.
Oh, okay.
He controls
all the sickness, plagues.
That's what he
has dominion over.
I think I'm gonna keep it
where it's very, kind of, like,
pale and white.
But then I'm gonna come in
with these blue washes
in the darker areas,
and they'll really
bring the blue into it.
- Right.
- Yeah.
My superhero's name
is Solarion.
He protects Earth,
and he's very muscle-bound.
It's time to go to the lab.
I have Tony's sketch,
and that is Robot Girl.
And I can't wait
to bring her to life.
Thank you, guys.
You guys are all awesome,
by the way.
Side by side once again, girl.
It's day one of our challenge,
and I'm really excited.
Mine is called Freedom Fighter.
He is derived
from the Twin Towers.
And I'm gonna have two
of the Twin Towers here
and also on the leg piece,
and he protects New York City.
I want to really
stick to the drawing,
and I need to just
get this sculpt out.
That's it.
My character is Revolt.
He's kind of just
a regular, punk-rock dude,
but he has the power to shoot
electricity out of his fingers.
And he's still
very much a person.
For my superhero,
I decided to go with
a time traveler
from another world.
He has mental powers.
I want bold colors, also a lot
of shading and highlighting.
My dude's a cop.
I'm giving him a little gut.
Everybody else is all ripped.
- It's looking like a cat.
- Yeah, it does look like a cat.
Maybe it's one
of the Thundercats.
Get away.
This is really nerve-wracking.
I look around, and I see
a lot of strong sculpts.
And everyone's moving so fast
that I'm cutting corners
trying to keep up with them.
That's messing me up
big-time,
'cause I keep
sculpting a cat robot.
God, what is wrong with me?
The sculpt is the worst
sculpt in the room.
I don't know
what to do at this point.
Oh, my God, what did I make?
This looks like shit.
Coming up...
I'm having a very hard time
putting these pieces together.
They're not fitting properly.
Fuck!
Ugh, this mask
is pissing me off.
That's quite genius.
It was a huge waste
of time for you this week.
It's day one,
and my sculpt looks really bad.
It looks terrible.
I can't stand it.
I keep sculpting a cat robot,
and I want a freedom fighter.
So I'm kind of getting
frustrated at this point.
I thinned out my superhero's
nose a little bit,
'cause a lot
of comic book characters
have a very thin nose.
I'm also strengthening up
his jaw.
Just making him look bigger,
because I know that
that has to all tie in
with the muscle suit.
Yeah, that's good.
What's your color scheme
gonna be?
My superhero
is made out of big,
sharp pieces of glass.
Glasses from the building
all, like, break down
and flying towards to him
and makes his costume.
Everyone's pieces
are already so epic.
I'm just making a face.
I was not expecting
a individual challenge
so early on in the competition.
I just hope I stack up
with everyone else.
My concept is gonna be
an underwater female superhero.
She's going to have
the whole nine yards, like,
gills and huge octopus tentacles
coming out of her head
and scales all over her body.
I'm still trying
to figure out my sculpt,
but it's not working.
Just try to finish it today.
No, I'm getting this done.
I'm asking everyone's opinion.
I'd say just try evening out...
- The corners.
- ...the points.
I want to cry right now,
but I can't let this defeat me.
I spent a little more time
sculpting this chest piece
than I had planned to.
I'm really trying to stylize
the muscle patterns
of the torso and the chest.
For me, it is the most important
piece for this character.
Anthony's sculpting
a chest and back piece.
The mold's probably
gonna weigh 200 pounds.
It's kind of crazy.
My character's gonna
be wearing a mask
that's supposed to resemble
an old plague doctor,
where they have the long nose.
That's where they used
to stick the incense in,
so they wouldn't smell
any of the death
or anything that stunk.
The incense would
block all of that.
Still looking good.
What do you think
about the mask underneath?
I've come up
with this character
and her name is Silversight.
She is an animal
conservationist/biologist.
I want her to be beautiful
and strong,
kind of like
Wonder Woman with wings.
I think that's gonna be cool.
It'll be, like--
like, a lot of dimension.
- Yeah, yeah.
- A lot of layers.
That's my hope.
I'll finish this up,
and I'll be getting ready
to mold both of these things.
After the sculpture's finished,
you need to make a mold of it.
You make a mold out
of a stone-like substance;
you de-mold it,
clean the clay out;
and then you fill it
with gelatin, silicone, foam;
and then you push
the two pieces back together
and you get a nice appliance.
There we go.
It was missing a jaw.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, I've been
staring at this like,
"what's wrong with it?"
It's the jaw.
There's a lot more to be done,
but now I'm okay.
I like the way it looks now.
As the day goes on, I started
getting worried about time.
I don't have my mask done.
And I don't want
to be in the bottom looks,
just 'cause
I was there last week.
And having two back-to-back
bottom looks is not great.
Time!
That's time.
At the end of the day,
I feel like
I'm in a pretty good place.
I'm a little nervous that mine
is really super simple
compared to some
other people's.
I'm just hoping that the rest
of the costume pieces
come together
and everything works out.
Oh, thank you.
It's day two
in the superhero challenge.
Today, I have to get done
the armor and the helmet,
which I know is gonna take up
a huge chunk of the day.
Oh, that's cleaning out
really nice.
I'm trying to think
outside the box on this one,
so what I want to do
is expose the human anatomy
using clear domes,
as well as have the lungs
actually function.
- Pretty cool?
- Yeah, it looks good.
Today, my primary thing
is making my wings.
So I need rods, poles, wire
to build the actual shape.
And I need feathers
for this as well.
Nice, dude.
Alam's making these
big glass shards,
and it looks scary.
Those staying on?
If it doesn't,
I'm gonna kill myself.
I'm worried.
I have to make all these
spiky things on the back.
It's really hard, because
I don't know the materials well.
Oh, you fucker.
I don't know
how you did all this.
I really don't.
It's not done yet, man.
I'm still working on my mask
and I'm not happy
with it at all.
Every cut, every fold I make
just creates a new problem.
It's frustrating,
'cause I'm wasting so much time
that I can't afford.
Ugh, this mask
is pissing me off.
It's just not looking right.
It's still just looking
like a block.
I'm not confident that it's
gonna pull everything together
like I want it.
I'm not feeling it anymore.
I start working on
my silicon make up.
The silicon I'm working with
kicks off a little faster.
That's not gonna work.
It's a complete failure.
It's too thick.
I start scrapping
silicon off like a mad man.
A possible elimination...
I ran over, uh, just trying
to help anyway that I can.
God, please!
I'm worried.
This is what I get for
trying to go creative.
Finally, I decide to
go with foam latex
and it turned out beautiful.
Awesome!
We're getting towards
the end of the day,
and I know I still need a mask.
This mask is pissing me off.
I'm looking around in the lab
when I see a spandex cowl.
This is gonna be the best bet.
I've worked with stuff like this
where you make sock masks.
I'm going back to my
old haunted house roots.
I feel that this is the
direction I want to go.
And I'm going to cut foam eyes,
put some of the detail,
and then make a nose.
How much time we got left?
Right now, I'm running
very behind.
I have to mold
the chest and back pieces.
There is that thought in my mind
that I am going too big.
My character has a mask
that he wears
when he becomes Revolt.
And it's supposed to look
a little homemade
because I want
everything to look
as if my character made it.
I want top looks
for every character.
This one particular,
she's very dear to my heart.
I think she has
a different style to her.
Instead of the traditional
comic book hero,
mine is leaning more
towards Japanese anime.
The mask finally
starts to come together,
and now it's starting to
resemble an old plague doctor.
I'm actually liking
the direction
it's starting to take.
Time's up, everybody.
Put your stuff down.
There's not enough time
to finish the chest.
So tomorrow,
I have to open my mold,
clean out all the clay,
get a casting of my torso piece,
apply all these pieces,
paint all these pieces,
and have a finished piece
for the judges.
It's showtime.
It's application day,
and I only have four hours,
and I'm getting a little bit
nervous just because
there is a ton of stuff
that I still have to do.
I still have to finish my
tentacles and my chest pieces.
The first thing I have
to do is open my mold,
get it cleaned out,
and fill that with foam.
Since I got a little bit
of extra time today,
I really want
to focus on a prop.
So I decide to make
this bizarre-looking
blaster gun for my character,
and it's coming out sweet.
You can make
yourself comfortable.
You're gonna be
a time traveler superhero.
That's her, like,
whole costume look.
My model, Jenny,
has a beautiful head of hair,
and getting that all
tucked in to the appliance
is really my biggest challenge.
It'll be kind of like a--
more of an anime flop mohawk.
I have so much to do.
I have to get the face on.
I've got to get the helmet on,
the chest piece on.
And I'm pre-painting
everything.
All right, sir.
You can go ahead
and modify this,
and I'll doctor it up
real quick.
I feel like I'm in
a pretty good place.
All my pieces are done.
I just have to apply them.
Some people
are still running pieces.
The application
is really tight.
I have to make
the most important element
of my character, which
is the chest and back piece,
but I'm having a very hard time
putting these pieces together.
They're not fitting properly.
The core is sticking out
slightly.
I'm, like, pounding
this thing to get it down,
but it's not going down.
Hopefully, I'll be okay.
I'm just gonna glue
these on the side.
- Are you gonna paint me here?
- Yeah.
I'm thrilled about how
everything's coming together.
It looks beautiful.
She looks like a phoenix.
And I'm feeling pretty good.
We're not going home.
Turn.
Everything fits him,
even the shoulder piece.
I actually rigged
lights through it.
I'm struggling with
the back piece right now.
No.
It doesn't want to stay on.
Maybe I'm using,
like, wrong glue.
It's not strong enough.
Oh.
I think the back piece
might be too heavy.
Kind of worrying.
I'll be right back.
I run to go check on the mold
and pry it open.
I'm having a hard time
because of the suction
that's inside that mold.
Fuck!
I end up smashing
one of my fingers.
Fuck!
I'm not able to open
this mold by myself,
and everybody's so engrossed.
I don't want to take them away
with what they have to do.
Fuck it.
I'm not gonna have a chest
piece for this character,
and it's time to go
with plan B.
One hour, guys!
I do not feel good
about this situation,
'cause the whole concept
of calling him the core
really relies on his chest.
And now I have to have this
character standing up there
with an incomplete makeup.
Time!
Coming up.
I'm freaking out now.
I just don't know
what to say about this.
And I really dug that.
It is just not good enough.
Last looks.
We have one hour.
The only thing remaining now
is just finishing
her face makeup.
Oh, dang it.
My superhero came
into the makeup room
with the back piece
on his hand.
I don't know what to do.
It's supposed
to stick on his back.
I'm freaking out now.
We're gonna do tape again.
I'm sorry.
The velcro came off
the arm pieces,
so I have to duct tape it.
I had a little trouble
around the sides,
but I believe
I've left myself enough time
to get everything complete.
15 minutes, everybody.
I'm dying about
that chest piece, man!
When you walk, not try to move.
Time!
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
Say hello to your judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effect Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
- Hi, Glenn.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
- Good evening, everybody.
- Good evening.
Hi.
And creature and concept
designer Neville Page.
- Hello, everyone.
- Hello.
This week, your spotlight
challenge was to create
an original superhero.
And we have a big prize
on the line.
The winner's character
will be featured
in an upcoming DC comic.
First up
is Michael's superhero.
Just seeing it up there,
it's my baby.
That's my boy.
I'm really proud.
I'm a little worried.
I know this is
a makeup competition,
but this being
a superhero challenge,
I probably should have spent
a little more time
on the costume.
I'm pretty scared
at this moment,
just because it's, once again,
not a finished paint job.
I'm extremely nervous
and just wishing that
the judges could have seen it
complete with the chest piece.
I feel awful.
It's a disaster.
I feel like I'm definitely
in bottom looks.
She's sexy.
A little bit gory.
I think it's impressive.
Totally looks like a superhero.
Her panties are on the outside.
She got a cape.
Man, she's looking
like something DC
could really use right now.
I love the superhero image
that I made.
No one knows
it's not completed,
because they're not
seeing my mistakes.
I just love how the lights
are hitting her.
And it's really shining
and throwing
this wet look over her.
She looks powerful and awesome.
And her colors
are just so amazing.
I think she looks great.
I know that he's not really
Glenn's kind of style.
I just hope that they like him.
I'm feeling pretty good,
and it's a character that
I would love to see
walking around on the pages
of DC comics.
He comes out in full character,
and I'm loving it.
Judges, why don't you
take a closer look.
Does this come off?
Or can you push it up?
I'm a little worried
when they lifted up the mask
'cause he's sweating
under there,
so I know that paint
is starting to run on his face.
The one thing
I was wondering about,
the squareness of this
and the fact that it was
in front of a Mayan temple.
More bird God,
less plague doctor.
Can you lean down
so we can see the very top?
I wonder why that's green
and yellow up there.
It's a cool idea to go with
this snake-head-y thing
on top of the lava
and the cracks in the paint job.
Good God almighty.
Can you just lift your chin up?
Dude, just walk away from him.
There's something sort of cool
about all of these steps
in this neck piece
and the lighting.
Other than that,
I just don't know
what else to say about this.
As sloppy as everything is,
it feels most superhero
of them all.
Can you turn around for us?
Please don't make him
turn around.
- Oh, my God.
- Blowout.
There was a big,
giant hole on his back
and there's big,
giant hole in my heart.
I'm going home.
What do you think
of tonight's designs?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff
Uh-oh.
- Oh, my God.
- Blowout.
What's happened to you?
There was a big,
giant hole on his back.
I'm going home.
Okay.
This is cool.
Yeah. Yeah.
The judges have scored
your creations.
Let's find out
what they thought.
Katie, House, Eric F,
Meagan, Anthony, Michael.
You were the best
and the worst this week.
That means
the rest of you are safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
All right, the judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
House, you're up first.
Please begin by telling us
the backstory of the character.
This is Robot Girl.
She was a pro fighter
in the future.
And she left the lab
to strike revenge
on those who wronged her.
I think this is extremely
unconventional.
And it's risky to do that,
and I think you succeeded.
I actually liked it
a lot better close up
than I did from far away,
because I realized that
it wasn't really bloody.
It's just the under-skin
of what we see.
What I'm seeing
is something that's
more horror than superhero.
To me, it reads
a little more science-fiction,
Japanese hero,
and this really speaks to me.
House, thank you very much.
If you'll please step back.
Meagan, you're up.
Okay, Meagan, what's your
backstory on your superhero?
I basically wanted
to make him out of the metal
from the Twin Towers.
Is that what these pieces
on his arms are?
Yeah, it was glued down,
but it fell off, so...
They look like TV controls
with gaffer's tape around them.
Okay.
I'm really concerned
about your sculpting efforts
on this face piece
because it's really
terribly, terribly rough.
You could've sculpted planes
and hard angles and stuff
and put rivets in it.
That said,
the neck thing is cool.
- I see what you were going for,
it just didn't work out. - Okay.
Meagan, thank you very much.
Please step back.
Eric F.
Explain the concept
behind this.
Detective Dick Gritty
was left for dead
by the evil crime syndicate.
His body was brought back
from the brink of death
to seek vengeance on the people
that did him wrong.
It's such
an entertaining piece.
And how tight it is underneath
that acrylic chest plate,
in terms of your
anatomical prowess.
I'm really, really
pleased about that.
When he walked out,
I immediately felt like
I was in a 1940s movie.
And I really dug that.
- Thank you guys so much.
- Eric, please step back.
Michael.
Tell us about the backstory
of your character, if you would.
His name's Elijah,
Bringer Of Plagues.
He sucks in any type of plague,
and he would spew it
out of his mouth,
inject it back into a villain,
destroying him that way.
Am I to assume that
the shape of the mask
is based on a traditional
plague doctor?
Yes.
Unfortunately, I don't think
you were very successful
in achieving that look
with that mask.
This was the third version
of the mask,
and it wasn't
the best of ideas.
It's a simple shape,
and you could have
made it so cool.
When I look at this, I wonder,
"what the hell
did he do the whole time?"
There is nothing there
but a costume and some rags
and a goofy little mask
with a snout on it.
I think it was a huge waste
of time for you this week.
Michael, please step back.
Anthony.
Tell us about your guy,
and I want to hear
his backstory.
He's from the Earth's core,
and he eliminates all the people
who are destroying the planet.
He initially
had a full chest piece
- and a back piece.
- Uh-huh.
But I was having a hard time
getting it out of the mold
and decided to abandon it
and go to plan B.
We've had several
characters with this theme,
this cracking
lava-type theme.
Yours is the first one
that's been successful.
I really like this guy.
He actually, for me, is like
a full-blown-looking superhero.
I think you turned lemons
to lemonade with the problem
that happened with your
front piece and back piece
and ironically created
a strong silhouette.
The sculpture on the head
is quite amazing
because it's partially
a makeup, partially a cowl.
That's quite genius.
I absolutely adore the way
the colors come up the arms,
and then you follow this
exact same scheme on the face.
That puts it all together.
Well done.
Thanks so much.
Anthony, thank you very much.
Please step back.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Katie.
Katie, explain the concept
of Revolt.
I wanted to create
a vigilante, homemade hero.
Punk-rock superman.
Would you mind
taking the mask off
so we can see
the sculpt underneath?
I fear that you're not
as well-versed at anatomy
as you need to be.
There are some very arbitrary
shapes that are happening.
They don't make him look
more heroic or more menacing.
They make him
look more deformed.
That juggalo tiki mask
that he's got to cover his face
looks like it belongs
at a Halloween frat party.
It is just not good enough.
Katie, please step back.
All right, the judges have
heard what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they make
their decisions.
So why don't we start
with the looks
that you liked the most.
How about we start
with Anthony.
The gradation of the paint
really saved it.
Yeah, excellent.
I love the way
the black just--
it looks like
the perfect cowl mask.
But it's all integrated
into the makeup.
That center split
with the color going down
was another graphic piece
that just made it
a bit more unique.
Let's move on to House.
What are your thoughts?
He did all of these
super-cool metallic tones,
and it took it away from
the blood and gore and viscera
and more into
the cybernetic human.
All that golden metallic
gave it a really beautiful,
cohesive, exposed
muscle tissue look,
and it was kind of cool.
Let's move on to Eric.
It's a big success to me,
mainly because it compels
the audience to say,
"what the hell
happened to this guy?"
Yeah.
And that is probably
the single most important thing
in designing a superhero.
And the fact that
he was smart enough
to have him come out
with the scarf and the hat
- and do that whole '40s thing.
- Excellent.
Okay, let's move on
to the looks
you did not like so much.
Michael.
I didn't agree with the fact
that he's a superhero.
It is unacceptable to present
a fabricated mask
as the main piece
of your character.
It isn't even a full makeup.
Nothing about it succeeds.
All right,
let's move on to Meagan.
I am so disappointed in that.
When you see
sculpting like that,
I have grave concern for what
we can expect to see out of her
in the coming weeks.
The tape--
she actually
presented something with--
- Duct taped arms.
- And it wasn't thematic.
All right, Katie.
What are your thoughts there?
- The outer mask was wretched.
- It's frightening.
I can't believe
she sculpted that.
She needs to learn how
to appropriate her time
into things that are going
to make sense and be seen.
Judges, have you made
your decisions?
- Yes, we have.
- Yeah, we have.
Let's bring them
back out tut then.
All right, Glenn,
why don't you tell us
about the top looks tonight.
Anthony. Some really nice,
classic superhero elements
to your character.
And you did a really splendid,
graduated paint job
on the makeup itself.
House.
We thought that your infusion
of the Japanese aesthetic
into the makeup
was incredibly successful.
And Eric.
You really went for it
this week,
and it paid off in what was
a very, very complete character.
All right, Glenn,
who is the winner
of this challenge
and the DC comics prize?
Tonight's winner is...
All right, Glenn,
who is the winner
of this challenge
and the DC comics prize?
Tonight's winner is...
Anthony.
Oh, my God.
You did a lot of things
right tonight,
but we were particularly
impressed with the sculpture
of your character's head.
Very, very strong work.
Thank you, guys.
It really means so much.
Anthony, congratulations.
Your superhero will be featured
in a DC comic.
Awesome.
To be in a DC comic
with a character
that I designed myself
is just surreal.
I can't wait to see it.
Thank you very much.
You can head back
to the makeup room.
Thanks, guys.
House and Eric,
you are also safe.
Please head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you, guys.
Good job.
Unfortunately,
that means the rest of you
are on the bottom this week.
One of you will be eliminated.
Please step to the center.
This is scary.
All right, Glenn,
tell us about the bottom looks.
Michael, you really
squandered your time,
and as a result,
we didn't really
see your concept
in the final piece.
Meagan, your facial sculpt
did not seem like
it belonged with the rest
of your character.
Katie, you spent a lot of time
working on things that
just made your character
look haphazard.
So who's going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Michael.
You made so many
bad decisions tonight,
and ultimately,
you just didn't give us
any makeup to look at.
Michael, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
The rest of you are safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
You're obviously
full of creativity.
I, for one, would love to see
what else you come up with.
Michael, it has been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- Good luck.
I bid you all
a farewell, adieu.
- No.
- Oh, oh, no!
This experience
is a milestone in my career.
I feel more confident
in what my abilities are.
Aw!
I'm very optimistic.
There's so manings to do now.
I get to go home,
practice, and hone skills.
My future's not written.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net