Previously on Face Off...
Anthony's
bioluminescent creature
brought him his fourth win...
Thank you guys so much.
And Meagan
and Eric Z were sent home
in a surprise
double elimination.
Now, just five artists remain.
Tonight, they'll tackle
a challenge
inspired by one of the most
iconic film franchises
of all time.
Everybody loves this film.
Use this as inspiration
for your designs.
With the finale on the horizon,
the pressure begins
to take its toll.
I don't have any paint
on the body at all.
I'm not gonna be able
to get this out,
and if I try
to rush this thing,
I could destroy all the work
that I've done.
It's time, guys!
This is really rad.
Oh, wow!
You totally ruined
your whole makeup.
If I'm gonna be eliminated
for this,
this is a good one
to go home on.
This is pretty much camera-ready.
In the end, only one
will win the opportunity
to be a guest lecturer
at Make Up For Ever's academies
in New York and Paris,
the all-new 2013 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- Good morning.
- Morning, dude.
What's this?
Ah, Meagan left a little note
for me, man.
"Rule number one, don't fart
in women's faces."
Meagan and Eric are gone.
I got a really sweet note
from Meagan
saying that it's nice
that she can call me a friend
and to definitely give
the other boys hell,
which I'm planning on doing.
Good morning, guys!
Last Eric standing.
Can you believe it's just us?
The elite team of badasses.
- Final five.
- It's insane, man.
I can't believe
we made it this far.
I got to be honest.
It's really crazy at this point
because the five of us
that are left,
we're all very run down.
This is the longest I've been
out of communication
with the wife and kids,
and I really
want to make them proud,
so, that is the biggest drive
to do well in this.
We can take on anything, guys.
We're walking through this
awesome, very historic theater,
and it's very beautiful.
It's decked out in Egyptian art
all around the building.
McKenzie's standing there,
and there's six tablets,
and on the tablets,
there's these sculpted beings,
and they all have these
headdresses on and staffs.
Welcome to American
Cinematheque's Egyptian Theater,
the location of Hollywood's
first-ever movie premiere,
but we're actually here to talk
about the cult classic
Evil Dead.
Yes.
I love this film.
My kids love this film.
Everybody loves this film.
It's Evil Dead.
The original franchise
was so successful
that it's currently
being remade
and is set for release
by Sony Pictures in April.
In the film, five friends are
holed up in a remote cabin,
where they discover
a book of the dead
and unwittingly summon
dormant demons
which possess them
in succession
until only one is left intact
to fight the survivors.
The real Book Of The Dead
is actually
an ancient Egyptian spell book,
and some of the most
iconic images from the book
are the gods they worshiped.
Those gods are the basis
for your spotlight challenge,
select one of the Egyptian gods
and bring it to life.
Evil Dead
meets an Egyptian God.
- This is right up my alley.
- But there's more.
Ancient Egyptians
had a very specific way
to ensure they would find their
way back from the afterlife...
- mummification.
- Hm.
So, inspired byEvil Dead,
you will create
an Egyptian God mummy
rising after thousands
of years of decay.
Oh, yeah.
You know, that's a lot
to incorporate.
I've never made a decomposed
or mummified body,
so this challenge is gonna be
really, really interesting.
Kris, you're up first.
Khnum.
Anubis.
Ra.
Sobek.
Thoth.
Before I send you off
to work on your sketches,
I have a special message
for you.
Hi, folks.
Bruce Campbell here.
Oh, wow.
Bruce Campbell is great.
He is the star of
the Evil Dead franchise,
so it just really pumped me up.
I am very excited
that you are creating makeups
inspired by Evil Dead.
I want to give you
a couple pointers, though.
The latest movie has a more
serious tone than the original,
so make sure your makeups
are very haunting, creepy,
and scary,
so have fun, be original.
Good luck.
Everyone who knowsEvil Dead
knows Bruce Campbell.
He's a horror icon.
All right, look around
and use this great place
as inspiration
for your designs.
When you're finished, head back
to the lab and get started.
I will see you tomorrow.
We get 30 minutes to sketch.
There was all these great
Egyptian symbols on the wall.
I open up my sketchbook,
and there's a small paragraph
about the God that I chose.
He is the God of water
and creation,
and he's got a ram's head.
I want to make sure
that the head really shines
to impress the judges.
I'm excited
about this challenge.
I love The Evil Dead.
This makeup's very important.
I've been on the bottom twice.
Luckily, I was able
to bounce back.
I just got to continue
to bring it
because everybody's so good.
I chose Anubis.
Anubis is the God of embalmers
and death and everything.
The skin's gonna be very tight
to the bone structure,
and parts are gonna be torn
as well as he's obviously
gonna be wrapped
in a lot of cheesecloth.
So...
I picked Sobek.
The Egyptians would pray to him
because the Nile river
was so important to them,
and he's the God
of the crocodiles.
To bring in
that Evil Dead sense
to where it's mummified,
I'm gonna exaggerate
the rib cage.
This time, I'm really gonna
try to focus on the paint.
I know I've said it before,
but they know I can sculpt,
but it's pointless
to have good sculpting
if you can't bring it to life
with your paint job.
LoveEvil Dead.
One of my favorite films
growing up as a kid.
Yeah, this one, I got.
Ra is the God of the Sun,
and I'm really gonna
put the Evil Dead spin on it,
a real stylized,
predominant brow.
So it's gonna be sweet, man.
Thoth is the Egyptian Moon God,
and he's a scribe.
He writes on his tablet,
but I'm seeing his body
as the tablet.
He's gonna have etchings
all over him.
I thought last challenge
was something
that I was familiar with
as well,
but I came up short
on that one.
So I have to redeem myself
on this week's challenge.
Come on, guys.
First day at the lab,
we got five hours.
We get to pick our models.
I decide to pick a female model
just because it's hard to take
one of these
big, muscle-bound guys
and turn them
into an emaciated mummy.
I want to spend time
on the chest
which is going to have
a lot of detail
with all the hieroglyphics
on it,
and the face, which is going
to be very busy,
and rotting, and decaying.
I'm also creating a headpiece.
So I'm juggling three
different sculptures at once.
I'm gonna go ahead
and start on the body first.
I'm gonna do
a giant chest piece,
almost like a giant vest,
that he just slips on
over his head.
I'm gonna sculpt the body first
and then make the head
fit the body,
so, that way, the neck matches
better to the headpiece.
You know, at this stage
of the game,
we're all such great artists.
They're gonna be really, really
picky on every aspect.
Someone's gonna be going home
with a really good makeup.
It's really important
that I get my face sculpted
and get the body started,
so, that way, they're all
textured uniformly
as opposed to sculpting a head,
and, then, going back,
and sculpting a chest,
and hoping everything lines up.
To give it the Evil Dead twist,
I'm just gonna go with
'80s-style zombie corpse makeup.
My plan for my mummy
is to give him
this wolfman-esque,
mummified face
that will entail a foam latex
prosthetic on the face,
a chest piece, a back piece,
and then I have to sculpt
some kind of headdress.
I finish the sculpture
of the chest,
and now it's time
to make the mold.
You do this by putting
a cement-type substance
over the sculpture.
Once it's hardened,
you open it up,
clean out the clay, and fill it
with silicone or foam latex
which becomes the prosthetic.
How's your mummy coming
along there, House?
It's coming.
The last challenge
didn't go so well for me.
That was a nail-biter, man.
Yeah, that last challenge
was seriously
the most stressful one yet.
I am a little stressed out
because, for a piece this size,
it's almost impossible to do
in 14 hours,
but I'm still trying
to keep it together.
I really am missing the family
at home really bad right now.
It's the longest I've been away
from my kids and my wife,
and it's really taking its toll
on me at this point.
You're gonna make them proud.
Thanks, man.
I'm trying.
It's been really difficult
to be away
from the wife and kids,
and it's hard.
I'm feeling
very, very worn out.
I don't know
if I can pull this off.
I'm exhausted.
This is a lot of work.
Coming up.
I may need some help
on this one, Kris.
If I can't get
this mold finished,
I won't have a prosthetic.
There's a couple of odd things
about this.
All that's going
through my mind
is "three strikes,
and you're out."
I think you all
did a great job.
It is day one of our
Evil Deadchallenge.
It's been really difficult.
I'm tired.
But I just remember
I'm doing this for my family.
That, to me, is the biggest
drive to do well in this.
So I'm going to work
like a madman to get this done.
- 45 minutes, Kris.
- 45?
- 45.
- Fuck.
I'm trying to finish up
my chest mold.
I've got a hairdryer
on the stone part,
trying to speed up the process.
I'm really racing
against the clock here.
I want to get
this thing done...
37 minutes.
So close, baby.
So close.
And then I realize that I'm not
gonna get this done.
If I try to rush this thing,
I could break the mold
and destroy all the work
that I've already done.
I'm not gonna be able
to get this out in time.
There's no way.
In the end, I opt to just wait
till the next day.
Gonna keep rubbing it down
until they call time.
All right, guys!
It's time!
So close.
Always ten more minutes.
When I come in tomorrow,
all I have to do
is clean that thing out,
and that's all ready to go.
Then I can jump on the face.
It's day two.
Today, I have
to finish sculpting
the chest and back piece,
get that molded,
jump onto the headpiece,
and get it casted.
I open my mold,
and I'm trying to be
very careful so it won't crack.
Luckily, everything
opens up okay.
Everything looks beautiful.
First thing I want to do
is get that giant, two-piece
mold open and cleaned out.
I want to let it sit in the sun
so it bakes
all the moisture out,
so my chances of getting
a really good
foam latex appliance
is gonna be better.
I still have
to fabricate my headdress
as well as get my face
and my body molded.
I got a lot of molds to make
and a lot of sculpting
to finish up.
The mood in the lab
is a nervous quiet.
There's only five people left.
I was bottom looks last week.
I would like to redeem myself.
I have to, man, go big.
There's no more room for error,
no more room
for just making it good.
Good's easy.
It's great
that I strive for it.
Oh, that's cool.
That's super cool.
- Hello, guys.
- Hello. - Hello.
Here to do
a walk-through.
Yeah, I'm looking
forward to it.
I was an art history major,
so I know all about Egypt.
Let's see what you're doing.
- Hi.
- Wow.
- I like it already.
- Excellent.
- Okay, so you have Thoth--
- Thoth.
Yes, he was known
as the scribe,
and instead of writing
on a tablet,
I'm using his body
as the tablet.
With your scribing
that you're doing on the body,
make it deep enough
and wide enough
so when you go to paint,
it'll actually read,
and it doesn't look
like just a scar.
Yeah, good point.
All right, so you have Anubis.
Part of my inspiration
for this,
especially with the face,
is kind of a mixture
between Boris Karloff's mummy
- meets Lon Chaney Jr.'s Wolfman...
- Wolfman.
I'm gonna paint the skin, then
do a little bit of open latex
to just give some texture.
It wouldn't hurt to maybe have
a little bit of flesh hanging,
a couple of little spots
that are hanging
that you could paint,
that would make it
look more like rotting flesh
than just--
- Laying over.
- Yeah.
All right, so tell us
about the god you chose.
He's a human
but with a crocodile head.
Now, how are you feeling
with your time on everything?
Really, the only pieces
I'm sculpting
is the chest and the head,
and so I really wanted
to take time
to really show that sculpting
ability that I have.
I know in the last challenge,
where you had all
this wonderful sculpture,
your luminescent painting
didn't pop
like some
of the other ones did.
It all disappeared.
Did you leave that
to the very end
and not have enough time
to do it?
Yeah.
Yeah, pretty much.
Yeah, if you make it down
to the end,
this is what could make or break
your chances of winning,
is not having
your time management down.
So you have Ra?
- Ra, God of gods.
- That's right.
I'm trying to incorporate some
of theEvil Deadaspect.
Therefore, I did the kind of
traditional, like, arched brow,
extended the chin,
which are two characteristics
used in the Evil Dead makeups.
What are you gonna do
that's extra
to give it a mummified look?
I'm actually using these
Make Up For Ever sponges.
Once I get
my detail carved lines,
- I go back in and...
- Show me.
Give that kind
of beef jerky-type look.
Yeah, the rougher,
the better probably.
Yeah, it'll really pick up
the washes.
- Oh, yeah?
- Very good.
All right, so tell us
about Khnum.
Khnum is the God of water
and creation.
What are you doing to mummify?
Latex and tissue,
or cotton or whatnot, yeah.
I don't want to wrap it up
all the way in the bandages,
'cause I really want to show off
all the work I put into it.
With the eyes here, are you
going to be able to see eyes?
Yeah.
As long
as they're gonna be there,
and he's gonna be blinking.
- When he blinks-- because--
- It'll look young.
- Yeah.
So blend your eyelids
right into the makeup.
Thank you for that tip.
All right, everybody.
We're leaving,
but it's looking great.
It's gonna come down
to time management.
Be thinking of that
as you're working now.
It's gonna be very important.
- Good luck, guys. Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
That's gonna look
so frickin' good, dude.
Thanks, man.
I sculpt two horns,
and I get to a point
to where I know
they're gonna fit perfectly,
and once I have that,
I put my final touches
on the goat face,
and I start molding then.
One hour.
I'm really nervous about time
on this one.
I need to get the chest molded
and ready to run foam in it.
I'm gonna have to make
the fastest two-piece mold
of my life to try to get
this thing ready for foam.
For the blow-dryer?
Extension cord?
The ultracal has to set up
in a certain amount of time
before you can
de-mold it.
If not, it's just gonna crack
and fall apart,
so I'm gonna throw a plastic bag
and a blow-dryer on it,
get this dried
as fast as possible.
Tomorrow is application day,
and if I can't get
this mold finished,
then I won't have
a chest piece.
How is your mummy
coming along there, House?
It's coming.
Fox and I start talking about
the Evil Dead.
I saw Evil Dead in a movie
theater when I was 12 years old.
Evil Dead 2, saw that one
when I was 17.
Army Darkness, that
movie is so cool.
The Evil Dead franchise
is huge to me.
Mi kids would love
the Evil Dead 2.
Thant thing is playing
quite often over
at the Fox family house.
I saw these films
as a kid too, so,
I'm all in favor of it.
One of the ultimate
party flicks.
Today is the second day of our
mummifiedEvil Deadchallenge.
I'm really nervous about time
on this one.
If I can't get this chest
finished, I'm gonna be screwed.
You need help, man?
I may need some help
on this one, Kris.
I have to pray that this mold's
not gonna crack or break.
These pieces
are gonna be foam latex,
but foam latex needs
to bake overnight,
so I have to get it done quick.
Clean the core for me, please.
Here's some paint sticks
right here.
We get my mold ready for foam,
and it's gonna be able
to bake overnight,
but there's still a lot to do.
I start sculpting a headdress.
Unfortunately, I only have
about 40 minutes
to get this thing roughed in
and sculpted
before I have to put it
into molding.
Otherwise, I'm not gonna have
this piece,
and it's very stressful towards
the end, very hectic.
Four of us are in there making
molds in the last 40 minutes.
Fox starts his
at the last 15 minutes.
I'm just hoping to get the front
and back halves made
before the day goes out.
Agh!
- Is that hot water?
- I think so.
All right.
We're all doing the same thing
at the exact same time,
and we're rushing really fast,
but we don't have enough time
to open them
and clean them
and fabricate them...
That's it!
Wrap it up!
...which means that we have
to do it on day three.
Not a good sign.
What a day.
End of day two,
we're physically
and mentally exhausted.
We know we have a lot to do
on day three.
The four of us have
to open our molds,
clean out the molds,
latex them up,
- and polyfoam them.
- Polyfoam 'em.
Opening the mold and getting
that piece polyfoamed
will take a good chunk of time
for all of us.
They're all gonna be so badass.
It's gonna be a small detail
that's gonna send someone home.
You know, somebody's gonna be
going home with a good makeup.
I love you guys like if you were
my brothers, man.
- Yeah, same here, man.
- Right on.
- Pound it.
So application day,
the first thing I do
is run straight
for that Anubis headpiece mold,
just try to slowly
and easily open it.
I clean out all the clay
so I can start running it
in polyfoam.
We have four hours in the lab,
and an hour at last looks.
I mean, it's kind of funny
because everybody
is in the mold room,
pulling their pieces,
cleaning out clay,
and slip latexing
and polyfoaming.
I'm already behind.
I have to open my molds.
I have to clean them out.
I have to do latex
and polyfoam.
So much to do.
You're gonna be Ra.
- Nice.
- What's going on?
- Ready for another one?
- Yeah.
- Ready to become a mummy God?
- Right on.
- You'll be actually inside the head,
- Yeah.
so you'll be able
to move the jaw with your jaw.
Really?
I make a vac-u-form copy
of my model's face
for the chin piece,
and also for the horns
to rest on his forehead,
so it's comfortable
for the model.
And this will be
your headdress.
I test fit the Anubis head.
- Is that really tight?
- It's tight.
It's initially too small...
Yeah, it's pretty tight.
So I have to rip out
quite a bit of foam
in order for it to fit
and sit properly.
That's better.
I immediately get the torso
on my model.
Okay, go ahead
and blow-dry down.
Get the arms covered,
get the legs covered
using a build up of latex
and paper towels.
It leaves
a really cool texture.
With this makeup, no jumping
jacks or anything crazy.
Okay.
I'm planning on getting some
of those good color bursts
in his skin to get this old,
amber-type look.
I'm noticing it's looking
a little flat,
so I'm doing some drybrushing
over that
to push those layers
of color deeper within the skin,
and, like, sink in the shadows,
and bring out the highlights.
All right.
That's good for now.
I sculpted on a pretty
big mannequin, dude,
but we'll see.
I know it's still gonna be
a little tight.
The face
is mostly pre-painted.
It needs some paint to bring it
a little more to life,
but the headpiece doesn't come
out as nicely as I planned.
My sculpture is a little rough
in the chest area,
but it's a mummy, so...
and I'm thinking
it will come off okay.
Ten minutes left, guys.
Looking around the shop,
everyone else
has a paint job going, and
pretty much a finished piece,
and I don't have any paint
on the body or arms or legs
at this point.
Let's go.
It's time, guys!
At last looks,
when I get there,
I'm gonna have to,
faster than a ninja,
put this thing on his face.
I am very worried at this point
that I'm not gonna get any paint
on him at all.
Coming up...
It's stuck, and I still have
to push it back
another four inches.
I'm sorry
about the face thing, dude.
At this point in the game,
mistakes will cost you.
This guy
is camera-ready.
So we get to last looks.
It's gonna be one
of those crazy times again.
We have one hour
to finish this makeup,
and I have to base out
my entire character,
put the face on,
and, then, put the wardrobe on.
So I have a ton of work to do.
Let me see the inside
of your hands.
I put the telesis
over your eyebrows
so the pros-aide
will stick to it.
Awesome. Thank you.
I glue his face down,
and I'm feeling
it's underpainted,
so I drybrush a gold
onto his body
to really lift them up from
the lower cracks and crevices.
How's that hold?
Do I need to make it tighter?
There's ten minutes left,
and I'm having some problems
putting the face on.
It's literally stuck,
and for it to fit properly,
I still have to push it back
another four inches.
I'm sorry
about the face thing, dude.
I thought it would fit better
than that.
I think the headdress
looks great.
- Does that feel okay?
- Yeah.
It lines up right
above his eyes,
so you can see a little bit
of a brow.
That's it.
Time's up.
Brushes down.
You're actually
looking pretty good.
Nice.
Good job.
I get the head on,
but it's sitting off his face
by about two inches,
but it still moves enough
to where I'll be able
to get by.
Welcome to the
Face Offreveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
Say hello to your judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effect Studio Glenn Hetrick...
- Good evening, gentlemen.
- Hey, Glenn.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill...
- Hi, guys.
- Hey, Ve.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
- Hello.
- Hey. - Hi.
This week,
your spotlight challenge
was to bring one of the ancient
Egyptian gods to life,
but since this challenge was
inspired by the Book Of The Dead
from the Evil Dead franchise,
we asked that you make
a mummified
or decomposed version of them.
So let's see
what you've come up with.
My crocodile God Sobek
walks out on stage.
It looks like he just came
right off that tablet,
and he's standing out there.
It's a really cool presence,
and I'm so excited
to see this makeup.
I feel like the design
is super.
I'm hoping the judges notice
all of the hieroglyphics
that are carved into the skin.
I think he's pretty striking.
I do like the way he looks,
but the gauze
is a little too white,
and some of the paint job
does kind of meld together.
I'm definitely nervous
on this one.
Ra comes out on stage,
and it is
just "Ra-kin'" it, man.
The thing is cool.
I got a good feeling
about this.
I feel pretty good
about my makeup.
I'm pretty proud of it,
and if I'm gonna be eliminated
for this,
I did a good makeup,
and this is a good one
to go home on.
Judges, why don't
you take a closer look?
Can you turn around for us?
Yeah.
Now, see, he even did the back.
- That's bitchin'.
- Wow.
There's some great
sculpting detail.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Odd things about this.
I personally
don't like the gloss.
It takes it out of the vibe
that it is a dried, dead mummy.
Turn.
Yeah. Actually, see--
- That's cool.
- Wow, that's great.
That's emulating the wing.
There's some really nice
sculpture going on,
which is a total waste
because of the paint.
Yeah, the paint job everywhere
is kind of bizarre.
These high yellows, I don't
feel like they belong
in the color scheme at all.
It's a shame that these
are not blended much better.
The judges seemed to be
spending a lot of time on mine.
It's a scary place to be in,
especially having been
on the bottom twice before.
All that's going
through my mind
is "three strikes,
and you're out."
It's a shame that these
are not blended much better,
or at all.
The judges seemed to be
spending a lot of time on mine.
Having been on the bottom
twice before,
all that's going
through my mind
is "three strikes,
and you're out."
This is always fun,
at least to me.
Mm-hmm.
_
- Hmm.
- Full size.
Let's open and close,
and see how much it moves.
Not a great deal.
- Love the dryness of this one.
- I know.
- I really like the paint job.
- Yeah.
Can you open your mouth?
Snap at us.
Give me a grin.
Now, relax your forehead.
- Oh, okay. Oh.
- Good. Nice line, nice eyes.
It's like more than
camera-ready, all this stuff.
Glenn, this challenge
seems right up your alley.
How do you think they did?
You know, it is, and this
is one of my favorite challenges
I've ever seen on the show,
and I mean this.
- I think you all did a great job.
- Thank you.
Okay, the judges would now
like to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Wayne, you're up.
Wayne, tell us
about what you've done here.
The god that I have is Sobek.
The Egyptians used to pray
to Sobek to protect them
from the crocodiles
in the Nile river.
He's said to have a human body
with a crocodile head,
and I wanted to keep the head
a different color from the body
to really have that contrast.
I think you did a lot
of great things,
and I'm pretty happy with this.
Thank you.
I'm glad to hear
that it's purposeful
that you go
from crocodile to human,
but there are probably
some better ways
to handle that transition.
Wayne, I'm really proud of you
because you finally did
a complete makeup job.
You finished
the whole character,
which is really awesome.
I love the whole chest cavity.
It really looks
like he's sunken in.
I love all the textures
and everything.
Did you not put eyes in there
for a reason?
Yeah, I figured the eyes
would rot away, yeah,
so that's why I didn't want
to have it.
But it does look like
they are missing
as opposed
to it's an orbital cavity.
That's really
my only negative criticism.
That is a good sculpt.
- Impressive work, man.
- Thank you.
Wayne, please step back.
Thanks.
House.
Tell us about your character.
This is Thoth,
the Egyptian God of the Moon,
and he is known as the scribe,
so, I made his finger a pen,
and made his body the tablet.
I think that possibly
was kind of to your detriment.
I think you've created
a bulkiness to this character
which made him look
a little chunky.
It takes away from the fact
that he's supposed
to be decimated and mummified
a little bit.
Why did you paint him all gold?
Being a god, I thought he was
deserving of the color gold.
The fact that the color
is so unified is a huge issue,
because you've got
all this cool work,
and we can't really see it
because it's all blended
together into one color.
That puts you in a bad spot
this week
because, at this point
in the game,
those kind of mistakes
will cost you.
There's some
really cool ideas in this.
The mask does feel a little more
Venetian to me
in terms of the sculptural form
language that you chose.
I love the ideas,
but the makeup itself
just feels a little rough.
- House, you can step back.
- Thank you.
Kris, you're up.
All right, Kris.
Tell us about the concept.
My God is Khnum.
He's the god of life
and creation.
In regard to the palette,
it's flat, dead, and is dull,
appropriately so.
I think you nailed it there.
From my perspective, this guy
is pretty much camera-ready,
and, up-close
camera ready.
There are moments on this
that are just so tight.
It's really quite beautiful.
- Thank you.
- This is really rad.
Like, I think you did
an exceptional job this week.
You handled the sculptural
detail in the face
with exquisite nuance.
Also, it emotes really well.
- Well done.
- Thank you so much.
I really like this as well.
I love the texture of the skin.
I love all the coloration.
I mean, it really reads
like a mummified body to me.
- Really well done.
- Thank you, Ve.
- Kris, you can step back.
- Thank you.
Anthony, step forward.
Tell us about the ideas
that you used
to bring this concept to life.
I had Anubis
who is the god of death
and also the patron god
of embalming,
so I wanted to keep his face
relatively preserved,
and the concept
was to make him proud
and having a lot of strength
within death.
I've got some huge issues
with the angularity
of the sculpture of the face.
The biggest concern
is the proportion
of the death mask.
In order to accomplish that
regal feeling that you wanted,
that headdress needs to be
pulled out much wider,
and the shoulders
need to be pulled out,
and that would have changed
the proportions
of everything
that you're doing here.
I think that
you have accomplished
that Evil Dead look
with the face,
which is something I have
to give you credit for,
but it's disproportionate,
and I've seen so much better
from you.
Anthony, I think
you've totally ruined
your whole makeup
with that paint job.
I mean, you've completely
wiped out
any sculpting
that you did on the chest.
I mean, all I can see is a flat,
messy, splotchy thing.
This is not what I expect
out of you,
and I'm very disappointed
this week.
Getting past the paint
is a tough one,
but looking at the rib area
in particular,
there's some really
beautiful sculpture going on.
There's moments that I like,
but you kind of ruined
the whole thing
as a result of the paint work.
Thank you, Anthony.
You can step back.
Thank you, guys.
Eric, you're up.
So, Eric, I bet
you really had fun this week.
Would you tell us
about your character, please?
My God was Ra.
He is the Sun god.
I wanted to go with a real kind
of '80s zombie style
to kind of pay tribute
to The Evil Dead,
the stuff I grew up on.
You definitely got
theEvil Deadthing going on.
All in all, I think you did
a great character.
- I really love this makeup.
- Thank you.
Your propensity
and appreciation
for a particular period
in filmmaking and Evil Dead
feels so on the mark.
I want to caution you
about having
this permanent open mouth.
I don't know
if that was necessary
to have it be open
all the time,
so, just be careful of that
in future.
Okay.
I am not a big fan
of the colors that you chose.
Contrast should have come
from brown, mummified tones,
and I don't understand
the redness in it.
But I think that your sculpting
style works well
because of the Evil Dead aspect
of this challenge.
If that aspect
was not one of the parameters
of the challenge this week,
I think you'd be
in a lot of trouble.
Show me something
super realistic
the next time
you're standing in front of me.
- I will.
- Okay.
- Thank you, Eric.
- Thank you, guys.
Okay, the judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they make
their decisions.
All right, why don't
we talk about the looks
you like the most this week.
Let's start with Wayne.
There's so many cool things
about that crocodile head,
and I don't think I can pick
anyone that's come before him
that has sculpted
as much as fast as well
as what Wayne is doing
on this show.
- It's unreal.
- And it was symmetrical...
- Yeah.
- And it had scale details.
I mean, are they perfect?
No.
But within the time
that he did it, they're perfect.
He wanted it specifically to be
a gator head with a human body.
I would have liked
to have seen it blend in
'cause it just looks a little
wrong to the eye, you know?
You're absolutely right,
and the eyes,
it's the same thing,
but I'm really happy with
this week's makeup from him.
All right,
let's move on to Kris.
My favorite thing
was the use of subtlety.
It was exquisite.
He didn't go too far
with the zombification,
but it is not absent
from what he did.
For me, it felt so complete.
I think it's the best thing
Kris has shown us so far.
- Yeah, it is.
- I think so, too.
I think he did
a really great job this week.
- How about Eric?
- Oh, I loved it.
It was really clean.
I know you didn't like
the redness.
That didn't bother me.
I thought he did a really
cohesive, really nice makeup.
For this challenge,
that Evil Dead aesthetic
is what he's doing.
The problem is everything
Eric does looks like that
because he's so influenced
by those types of films.
That being said, this was
a fun, cohesive makeup for him.
All right,
so let's move on to the looks
you liked the least this week.
Let's start with House.
- Great idea.
- Strong concept.
Yeah, it was very, very strong.
Brilliant way to integrate
the scribe aspect of Thoth.
It was awesome conceptually,
but that's bigger than what
he was able to deliver.
Yeah, it was just too scruffy.
You know, I don't even know
that it would have been good
without the paint scheme.
It was very bulky.
It didn't read zombie.
It didn't read, you know,
Evil Dead.
Okay, let's move on to Anthony.
I was really disappointed
with Anthony this week.
If you would have told me
that was his makeup,
I wouldn't have believed you.
The paint is unfathomable.
It was just a big bunch
of splotches.
None of that bothers me
as much as his inability
to look at that headdress,
and the proportions,
and want to make it regal,
want to make it majestic,
and not be able
to look straight at it,
and go, "of course."
The Anubis headdress felt like
a toy on top of his head.
- So bad.
- All right, judges.
- Have you made your decisions?
- Yes. - Yes. - Yes.
All right,
let's bring them back out.
Glenn, why don't you tell us
about the top looks?
Kris, we love the ram look
of your makeup,
and some of the smaller
sculptural details
were very impressive.
It was a very
comprehensive makeup.
Wayne, your use of proportion
was excellent this week.
We were also blown away
by how much killer sculpting
you pulled off.
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of this challenge is...
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of this challenge is...
Kris.
Whew.
We thought you did
an exceptional job
at handling all
the various components
of this week's challenge.
- Well done.
- Thank you so much.
It means so much to me.
I am just floored.
I finally got the comment,
"this is camera ready."
That just makes me feel
so good as an artist.
Kris, congratulations.
You and Wayne can
head back to the makeup room.
Thank you, guys.
Eric, you are also safe
and can head
back to the makeup room.
Thank you, guys.
Good luck, guys.
Unfortunately,
that means, Anthony, House,
you guys were our bottom looks
this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
House, we thought you had
a lot of really good ideas,
but the overall appearance
was bulky
and more than a little rough.
Anthony, between
that angular facial sculpt
and the wretched paint job,
suffice it to say
that this was not up
to your usual standards.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
House.
Your character looked
pretty cool from afar,
but when we got up close,
there were just too many
problems to overlook this week.
House, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
Anthony, that means
you are safe this week
and can head
back to the makeup room.
Thank you, guys.
House, while you
have been with us,
you've brought some absolutely
huge concepts to the table.
And I can't wait to see,
as you grow into your skill set,
how you express yourself
as an artist
and bring those things to life.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
House, it's really been great
having you here with us.
Please head back to the makeup
room and pack up your kit.
- Thank you, guys.
- Good night, House.
I should have done better,
certainly.
My hieroglyphics
could have been read better.
I bid my adieu.
Dude...
You know it.
This season had some incredibly
talented people,
and I fought
with the best of them.
- You're gonna be missed.
- Thank you.
I definitely enjoyed
my experience here.
How many people really get
to represent their artwork?
There's many things
that I still want to create.
So I'm going to go home
and make a bunch of new stuff.
It's all good.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net