Previously onFace Off...
Kris's Egyptian mummy
brought him his fourth win.
It means so much to me.
And in a difficult elimination,
House was sent home.
Now just four artists remain.
Tonight, the artists are transported
to a whole new world.
Being on the set ofDefiance
is pretty amazing.
Action.
And with only three
advancing to the finale,
the stakes
are higher than ever.
I'm panicking right now.
I'm feeling completely lost.
This is a nightmare for me.
There's a cool vibe
to the character here.
It's so mediocre.
I think
it's anyone's game right now.
Guys, come on, he's a mutant.
Give him a break.
In the end, only one
will win the opportunity
to be a guest lecturer
at Make Up For Ever's academies
in New York and Paris,
the all-new 2013 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next
great name in movie magic?
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Hanging in there?
Yeah. You know,
yesterday was pretty rough.
I thought they were gonna
call my name. You know?
Last week, I really believed
that it was gonna
be me going home.
But there's one challenge left
to get to the finale,
and all the time my mind is,
"don't be in the bottom again."
Sucks that House
is gone, though.
Yeah. I'm really bummed.
It's definitely tough
saying good-bye.
It is, man.
We're down
to the final four now.
Somebody's going home.
Nobody wants to go home.
It's time to really
push the envelope
and make sure
the makeups are shiny.
Final four, guys.
Final four.
We're in the lab.
McKenzie's standing there
with four monitors,
and again, there's
that whole fear of the unknown.
- Good morning, guys.
- Good morning.
For the minds
behindBattlestar Galactica
and Caprica
comes Defiance, a sci-fi
drama series and video game
about human and alien species
forced to coexist on Earth
after years of war.
Now before I tell you more, I'd
like to introduce you to someone
who has helped
bring Defiance to life.
Please welcome executive
producer and co-creator
Kevin Murphy.
Kevin, thank you
so much for being here.
Oh, thank you for having me.
So can you tell these guys
just a little bit more
about Defiance?
Defiance is a brand-new
science-fiction adventure drama
set 35 years in the future
after aliens arrive
and war breaks out.
The setting is a small
frontier town called Defiance.
Seven races of aliens
and human beings
learning to live side by side,
it's a melting pot
bubbling over
with really,
really cool creatures.
Defiancehas got
a lot of great concepts,
and it's got
really cool makeup.
So I'm really excited
about this.
Your spotlight challenge
is focused on some
of the more exotic aliens
in the Defiance universe.
And they are Liberata,
99er, Bioman, Volge,
Sensoth, and Mutant.
I really like the Mutant.
It's right up my alley.
I just don't want
any of those fuzzy things.
If all these aliens
happen to be living together
in the town of Defiance,
they might begin to procreate.
So your spotlight challenge
is to choose
two of these alien races
and create their offspring.
I love aliens
because I think they'll give me
the chance to do
something more original.
Anthony, you're up first.
I decide to pick
the Mutant and the Liberata
because I like
more organic things.
Kris.
I'm going for the Bioman
because he's extremely buff.
And then I picked the Mutant
because I like
his deformed body.
Damn it.
Kris grabs the last Mutant.
This is not going
the way I hoped it would go.
Wayne.
I'm watching
all the characters I want
get snatched up,
and it's driving me crazy.
Eric, your pick.
I pick the 99er
and the Sensoth.
Whatever.
The one thing I did not
want to get was a fuzzy critter.
Not happy about this.
Now, before you get started,
we've got
one more surprise for you.
Kevin?
If you guys really want
to get inspired,
you've got to immerse yourself
in the world,
and for that reason,
we're sending you
to the actual town of Defiance
in Toronto, Ontario,
where you're gonna
tour the set and spend some time
among the actual aliens.
That's right.
Oh, man.
Unfortunately, due
to some family circumstances,
Eric will not
be joining you guys.
Everything's okay,
but he'll be staying behind.
I'm really bummed
I can't go to Canada.
Nothing seems to be working
in my favor at this point.
For the rest of you, you're
headed straight to the airport.
Have fun, guys.
I'll see you soon.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
Never been to Toronto before,
so this is a really exciting
experience for me.
And to actually meet
the Defiance makeup artist,
there's nothing
better than that.
- This place is awesome.
- I know, man. It's sick.
Frickin' crazy.
It's just so cool to be here
on the set ofDefiance.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity.
- Hello.
- How's it going?
Good. Welcome to defiance.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Stephanie.
I play Irisa, and I'm an
Irathient alien, as you can see.
We're very feral
and quite wild,
and we talk
when we need to talk,
but otherwise
we're not interested
in having a chitchat,
so you're very lucky
today, guys.
Is that a silicone piece?
Yeah, yeah, you can probably
see, like, it's all...
Oh, yeah.
So you guys
should go and meet Allan.
He's the guy that put
all my prosthetic on.
And I'll see you later.
I've got a scene to shoot.
I'm so excited
to meet with Allan Cooke.
I can't wait to ask him secrets.
Hopefully he tells me.
Today we're gonna glue on an
Irathient makeup to Lauren here.
Awesome.
Special effects
is, you know, a dream of mine,
and the makeup
of all these characters
and getting a chance
to see them come to life
is truly inspiring.
So you normally
do pre-painting?
As much as you can do, so
there's less time in the chair.
We'll call that done.
- It looks fantastic.
- Yeah, it's amazing.
- Thanks.
- Great job.
- Mark.
- Action.
There's Stephanie.
- We're gonna drink a toast.
- You want me to drink this?
Then we're gonna
talk about your uncle Eddie.
It was really co
and inspiring to see everything.
It'd be a dream come true
to work on this set.
Can't wait to get back
in the shop and get creative.
I know.
We're back in LA,
and we're all jazzed up
and ready to start
the Defiance challenge
and create an alien offspring.
We pick our models,
and we start sketching.
The two species that I have
are Bioman and Mutant.
I want to use
the bulk of the Bioman,
gonna make him really buff,
also gonna keep the glowing
green eyes and teeth
because I figured the Mutant
would spoil the perfect gene
from the Bioman,
which would just make him
a huge monster.
My concept is basically
mixing the Liberata
with the Mutant,
making a Mutant Liberata.
Gonna be taking the main
structure from the Liberata.
He has, like, a gorilla-shaped
head, rolls on his neck,
and also has a nose
that looks like a baboon.
It's a very grumpy character,
and from the Mutant,
I'm just going to make it
very grotesque,
give him a hump, and make things
very asymmetrical.
I look at the Liberata
and the Bioman,
how I'm gonna
breed these two together.
The Liberata is basically naked,
and the Bioman
is all muscle with
these little, spandex shorts.
So it's like,
oh, here we go again
with another
full-body creature suit.
I'm gonna incorporate a lot of
characteristics of the Bioman.
The Liberata
has texture down the nose,
so I want
that element in there.
And the Liberata's face
is a little bit wider
than the Bioman.
So I'm gonna widen
the alien's face out.
Hopefully, if I have time,
I can lay some hair in there.
It's really weird to take
something so big
like the Sensoth
and combine it with the 99er,
which is actually a very skinny,
mechanical creature.
I keep coming up with this
big, sasquatch-looking thing
with a little bit
more bulkier mechanics.
I can't stand my concept.
So I'm just gonna
sculpt a Sensoth,
put machine parts on it,
and see what I come up with.
What I really wanna do
is get the face blacked in
as well as black in
the whole torso piece and cowl.
I'm working with wood clay
because I can add
a lot of bulk real quick.
I definitely want
to get the face sculpted,
so I want to spend
more time on it
to really get
the expression that I want.
We all really want
to impress the judges,
so we're all going big.
Everyone's sculpting
these massive pieces
because no one's
gonna play it safe.
Wow.
Kris's Mutant's really cool.
It's right up my alley.
But I'm stuck
with the aliens that I got,
and I'm not really
getting into it.
This is ridiculous, isn't it?
I got freakin' Harry And
The Henderson meets Robocop.
You know?
I'm just like, shit.
Yeah.
Definitely not
my first selection.
I'm feeling completely lost.
It's not a good thing.
Especially
with that clock ticking.
I think this is probably
the first time any of us
are seeing Eric Fox
a little worried
and unhappy with his concept.
I'm really
just getting bummed out.
I already know that
I'm in a world of hurt
for this competition.
Fuck.
Coming up...
I only have
half my body molded.
Holy shit.
Gotta go to plan B.
He had a major blowout.
Mine is probably
the weakest character up there.
Going into the finale,
this is inexcusable.
It's really weird to take
something so big
like the Sensoth
and combine it with the 99er,
which is actually a very skinny,
mechanical creature.
So at this point, I don't know
if I can pull this off,
but I'm gonna try.
There's only three artists
in the finale,
and I really need to get
one of those spots.
- Looks good.
- Thanks, bro.
- Hey, guys.
- Hello.
We're gonna
do a little walkthrough,
see how you're doing.
All right, so which two aliens
did you pick?
I picked the Liberata
and the Mutant.
How exactly are you
going to utilize both of them?
He's gonna have the hunchback,
and his face and head
are gonna be deformed.
Are his legs larger,
to the point where you need
- maybe an oversized pant?
- Didn't really think of that.
Wrap it in some foam,
but then use an oversized pant
to give that heftiness
to the body.
- You chose...
- Liberata.
Bioman and Liberata.
I'm trying to marry the two
to try to keep
the lip area and the nose.
Similar to what Liberata is,
where it's very wide
in the lip and the chin area,
then also bring in
the human element.
With the chest here
and the muscles in the neck,
really make them big enough.
Think of that
when you're doing the chest.
Taking your shoulder muscles
all the way out
to the end of your shoulders.
Okay.
I have the cross
between the Mutant and Bioman.
So he's a big monster.
I think the fun thing is
is I can have a little bit
of freedom with the anatomy,
since the Mutant is so strange
and nothing has
to really match up.
When you finally
get this out in rubber...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...this is going to be a problem,
- so tear out...
- Mm-hmm.
About three lines
from the inside,
- and that allows him to do...
- Have some movement.
Gives him
a little bit more freedom.
Freedom.
That's a great idea.
He has the 99er, Sensoth.
I'm using the size of him
with the mechanics of him.
Figured that would be
the best way
to incorporate
these two characters.
Are you going
to bring hair down to the legs?
I'm bringing hair
down the stomach.
But I definitely want
to tie in a beard.
- Well, keep going.
- Thank you, guys.
I'm really bummed I'm stuck
making Harry And The Hendersons.
But I think this is definitely
a good opportunity
because I can show the judges
cleaner character makeup
without all the gags and getups.
All right, guys.
We're heading out.
Buh-bye.
The upper body
is close to finished,
so when I come in the next day,
I can sculpt the face mold
and try to get him ready
for foam latex.
Luckily, I only need to sculpt
a small face piece
and not a whole neck piece
'cause that's on the bodysuit.
Oh, cool.
I got a lot done today, but I
still got a lot more to do.
That's time, guys.
But by the end of the day,
I have had a revelation.
I'm actually
really liking my piece.
Yeah! Whoo!
So it's day two.
We have ten hours.
My biggest priority right now is
to get the sculpture finished.
That way, by the end of the day,
I can run foam in it.
Trying to give him that
really big neck in the back.
- Awesome, dude.
- Yeah.
Get a good look at you.
I'm going to bounce back and
forth from the body to the face.
I know that I got
a lot of work ahead of me,
but I'm gonna
do the best I can.
Awesome.
Just trying to make it
as gross as I possibly can.
Yeah, it looks good.
There's a lot at stake.
I'm doing this for my family,
to repay them
for everything they've done.
It's something
that I know is obtainable,
but I can't take that
for granted.
I just gotta do the best I can
and hopefully
get to the finale.
Just so much clay.
Hard to believe
that we're applying this shit
tomorrow morning, huh?
Here we go.
I don't want to let
my wife and kids down.
$100,000
would change our lives.
So it's imperative
that I get these molds done.
'Cause I can't be doing any of
that stuff on application day.
I really want to manage
my time efficiently,
so I decide to call
the sculpture finished
and start molding.
The sculpt
is going pretty well.
Just trying to bring the Bioman
and Liberata together.
It's taking me
longer than I expected.
I start to spray my body
sculpture with crystal clear.
I want to let that really dry up
so it de-molds a lot easier.
If you molded something without
putting any of the spray on,
it would stick inside that mold
like you wouldn't believe.
We have, like, two hours
left in the shop.
I really, really have to
start molding this.
If I can't
get this mold finished,
I'm gonna be screwed.
Everybody else is doing
these giant creature suits
with arms, torsos,
backs, and cowls,
all into one piece,
and some of the other artists
still haven't started
molding their characters yet.
_
So I feel a lot more at ease
than the rest of the guys.
_
The clock is ticking faster
than I've ever seen it tick.
I'm running really behind.
Oh, man.
It's really important
that I get these molds done up
because the foam
has to bake overnight,
and I don't want to have
to run it in polyfoam.
It's gonna kill the movement
and not be as comfortable
on the actor.
I gotta get this in foam latex.
Everybody's scrambling
to get their molds done,
and I'm struggling
to get my piece open.
Yo, Kris, can I get a hand?
Oh, jeez, man.
Luckily, Kris helps me,
and I'm able to open it.
Thanks a lot.
Thank you, dude.
And now I have
to really clean it out
and get it ready for foam.
But time is definitely
a factor here.
- How many minutes?
- Not enough.
God.
If I can't
get this mold finished
and run it for foam, I'm--
I'm gonna be screwed
'cause I'm gonna have
to run it in polyfoam.
It's gonna suck to have a shit.
That's something that could
ultimately send me home.
It's impossible.
This is the final four.
One person has to leave.
I really don't want
to be sent home tomorrow.
Fucking sucks.
Everybody is pretty
quiet in the lab.
And then you hear...
Eric Fox.
He's a maniac.
Mine's gonna come out
with a freaking beard.
His laugh is so unique...
When he laughs,
you start laughing.
And you're crying
and laughing because
you're laughing
at him laughing.
Yeah, buddy.
It's day two.
I'm molding, but it's taking me
longer than I expected.
I know I'm definitely
not gonna be able
to get the molds finished
in time for the foam latex.
I'm not happy about that
'cause I'm gonna have to run it
in polyfoam tomorrow.
And that's the last thing
I want to do
because the movement
on polyfoam is very limited.
I'm really stressed out
at this point.
I only have one half
of my body molded,
and the stuff takes, like,
half an hour to even set up.
There's no way
I can get these molds
completed in time
for foam latex.
This is a hernia right here.
These molds are really heavy.
Holy shit.
The clay is stuck
inside the mold.
I thought the clay was just
gonna peel right out of there,
but I'm sadly mistaken.
It's gonna take a long time
to get it all cleaned out.
And just like Wayne and Eric,
I'm not gonna be able
to run it in foam latex.
Gotta go to plan B.
Latex and polyfoam.
I'm disappointed.
It's just not gonna have
the same quality
of movement as foam latex.
This is the first time
I fucked up.
- Gonna have a polyfoam party.
- Come on.
How's your mold coming,
Anthony?
Fine.
I nearly got the core out.
The clay's all stuck
in the back of the mold,
as well as on the core.
I take him outside, get as much
clay out as I possibly can.
In the last second,
I'm able to finish it.
That's time!
- Damn it.
- Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Anthony is the only one
that made the deadline.
Me, Wayne, and Kris
get to have a polyfoam party.
In the morning.
What a day, man.
Whoo! Fun times.
This is not a party
I wanted to be invited to.
But I RSVPed that one.
Whoo-hoo!
It's application day.
We got four hours in the shop
and one hour at last looks
at the stage.
Three of us are gonna
walk into the finale,
and one of us is gonna go home.
So we gotta do
whatever we gotta do.
My foam pieces
came out beautifully.
And that's a great thing
because I have all the time
I need to paint before I
start applying and assembling.
- How you doing?
- Hey.
That's the face
that you're gonna be wearing.
You have
this real powerful neck.
Cool.
But I'm still
working on the body,
so I'll be a little bit,
so just relax, and I'll be back.
Okay, cool.
Eric and Wayne and I
have to run our suit molds
out of latex and polyfoam.
I'm worried
'cause I've probably got the
biggest piece out of 'em all.
Yeah, I'm gonna get you
going here in a second.
I still gotta clean clay
out of my mold,
brush latex, foam it,
seam it up, paint it.
This is really cutting
into my four-hour application.
I think all three of us
are feeling the pressure
on this one.
I'm running pieces
on application day.
That's not where I want to be.
I'm painting
based on what the judges said
about the last challenge
with my spattering.
They said I overdid it, so I'm
gonna hold back a little bit
to create a more cohesive look.
So now it's time
to de-mold
the polyfoam from the mold,
and I'm having a hell of a time
getting this thing opened.
It's a very large piece.
I'm trying to pull it apart,
and I'm just
sweating everywhere.
I'm hitting it, breaking it,
just ripping the mold apart.
I finally get the piece
out of the mold, and actually,
it looks really nice.
_
As I'm opening my mold,
I see that my appliance
is ripping right in half.
Oh, man, what a mess.
I need to fix this,
or I'm going home.
Oh, wow.
The thing
that's going through my mind
is how lucky I am not to be
in that polyfoam party.
I am definitely
in a much better spot
than I feel
the rest of the guys are.
How's it coming, Anthony?
Good. I'm just about
to start applying.
How's yours?
It come off okay?
I can't complain about it.
I got it out.
How's everybody else's?
Kris's ripped pretty bad.
He's patching it
and stuff, so...
Oh, really?
I'm panicking.
My suit ripped in half.
I've got major rips
on the seams.
I've gotta
make something of this.
So I take dental dam.
I start barging it
on the inside of the appliance
to keep everything together.
I have to do it.
I have no other choice.
- Final four.
- Yeah.
Everybody goes crazy.
How much time do we have?
An hour and 56 minutes.
Oh, my God.
It's really important
that this piece turns out
because it is
the main part of my makeup.
I'm just really nervous.
Luckily, my piece
comes out very easy.
That's at least some good news.
I'm just gonna get
a base coat on here real fast.
Just keep your eyes closed.
Time is running out,
and I'm taking a lot of time
applying all the pieces.
So I look around,
and everybody has at least some
type of paint on their model.
I'm pissed off at myself,
because once again, I'm gonna
be painting at last looks.
What's the time?
Ten minutes, guys!
I'm running out of time,
but I still have to do
some sparse hair work
while keeping
most of him very fleshy
and very grotesque,
just like the mutant is.
Time's up, guys!
I pulled through. I actually
got the suit on the guy.
I've got everything patched up,
so I have something to start
with once I get to last looks.
Coming up...
Oh, my God.
Just stressing out.
It's anatomically atrocious.
I think
it's a bitchin' character.
Who is the winner
of this challenge
and the first person
to make it to the finale?
We're in last looks,
and we have an hour left.
I need to do
the whole entire paint job.
If it's not finished
and the judges know that,
then they're gonna
send me home.
The atmosphere is pretty crazy.
Basically, the other guys don't
have anything fully painted,
so they're rushing
to get it done.
I got one hour
to finish this thing.
It's just gonna be
paint, paint, paint.
There's a lot more seaming
that has to be done
than what I thought.
I'm just aggravated at myself
because I have a weakness,
and that's time management
and getting pieces
finished and pre-painted.
Oh, my God, dude.
This is probably one of the most
difficult challenges I've had.
Just stressing out.
It's a madhouse.
Time, time.
30 minutes!
It's a nightmare
right now for me
because I have 30 minutes left
to paint everything.
Once again, I just
grab a 5-inch chip brush,
and I start painting
as fast as I can.
Gotta paint you like a house.
At this point, I'm pretty sure
that I'm gonna be going home.
Damn.
Come on.
You'll have dirt
on your hands too.
The beard on this piece
is very important
because it's gonna be
covering the neck seam.
It's very important that I
at least get something up there
before time's up.
Time's up, brushes down!
All right, well,
that's what we got.
This is the worst situation
I could be in.
There's only one person
getting eliminated,
and three are going
to the finale.
I'm kinda worried because I
don't have a finished paint job.
Oh, well.
Welcome
to theFace Offreveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
And three of you
will move on to our finale.
Say hello to your judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
- Hey, Glenn.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
- Gentlemen.
- Hello.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
- Hello.
- Hi.
And joining
our panel this week,
he's a highly accomplished
producer and director,
whose work includes CSI,
Caprica,
and Battlestar Galactica.
He's also producer
and director of Defiance.
Please welcome Michael Nankin.
It's just really cool to have
somebody so close to the project
looking at our characters
to see if we did them justice.
Michael, thank you so much
for being here tonight.
Thank you for having me.
I can't wait to see
what you guys have.
This week,
your spotlight challenge
was to choose
two unique alien races
from the Defiance universe
and create
their potential offspring.
Wayne, you're up first.
I was really worried
about my alien baby.
But now he's looking
so powerful,
and I could really
see his expression
emoting through the makeup,
so I'm feeling pretty good.
I did everything, pretty much,
that I wanted to do
with this character.
One thing I really
wanted to make sure
is that the chest and the body
really read from far away,
especially with the paint job.
Actually looks really cool.
It's intimidating looking
at the presence and
the silhouette of my character.
It's got no neck,
it's all muscle,
and his arms are humongous.
You've got elements
from the Bioman and the Mutant.
He's a big, mutated monster.
I love it.
When my character
comes out onstage,
I'm actually
pretty happy with it.
I think it looks really good.
It has a lot of the elements
that I was going for.
It's a pretty cool piece.
Judges, why don't you
take a closer look?
It evokes much more Liberata
than Bioman, I think.
- In the height--
- Well, I think it's
the overall physique of him
that sort of...
- Right.
- ...emulates Bioman.
The judges go in
for their close look,
and I'm dreading this
'cause I still think mine is
the weakest character up there.
Can you give us
some facial expressions?
This nose, and that lip...
Just those two pieces
kind of bring it to life.
Could we see the back?
I kind of dig that divot.
The paint job on this,
again, is--
this looks like they're putting
it on with a chip brush only.
Or a baseball bat.
I'm already
mentally preparing myself
to be sent home on this one.
It's unfortunate,
but I really don't think
my alien's as good
as the other three.
The paint job on this...
This looks like they're putting
it on with a chip brush only.
I'm already
mentally preparing myself
to be sent home on this one
'cause I think mine is
the weakest character up there.
See, this head shape
is correct for the Liberata.
A sort of pointed skull.
That's accurate.
Looks like a Mutant Liberata,
doesn't it?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
I'm hoping the judges
like what they see,
the tiny details and the
grotesqueness of this character.
The green teeth
and the green eyes
distract me from everything.
Come all the way
around to the back.
He had a major blowout.
Going into the finale,
this is inexcusable.
I'm definitely gonna take
some lumps from the judges.
I don't know if I'm gonna
be a finalist or not.
I think
it's anyone's game right now.
- This is really shoddy here.
- The hair work's rough.
I'm tired of being nervous.
At the end of the day, it comes
down to whether or not I'm happy
with something that I put
out there on the stage or not.
He's definitely sculpted the
most out of everyone tonight.
The judges will now
speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Wayne, please step up.
Tell us
about your design, please.
My design came from picking
the Liberata and the Bioman.
I wanted to bring
the Bioman's essence into it
by keeping the face more human
and then bringing
the Liberata into it
with the nose piece
that comes down
and bumping the forehead out.
I definitely give you credit
for the lip and the nose.
Thank you.
You have successfully
bridged this large,
elongated skull
into the shoulders.
But I wish you put
more of you into this makeup.
It's so mediocre,
and a lot of that is the paint.
Wayne, overall, I really kind
of like the whole character.
I think the back
was quite well done.
I think he's a pretty
cohesive-looking character,
and I think you did
a pretty great job.
Thank you.
From afar, it's hard to tell
what you did on the face.
But when you get up close,
there's some really nice
detailing going on.
I found your proportions
very pleasing to my eye.
And the bulge
in the back of the head
doesn't exist on a Liberata,
and it doesn't exist on Bioman.
It's a creation of yours,
and yet, it helps
make it all sort of work.
- Thanks.
- Wayne, you can step back.
Thanks.
Anthony.
Hi, Anthony. Would you tell us
about your creation, please?
My character is basically
a Mutant Liberata.
I used forms of the Liberata,
such as the rolls in the neck,
the shape of the head,
and just Mutated 'em.
I also added
grotesqueness into it.
I think you've really
been successful with this.
I think he looks actually
like a Mutated Liberata.
I like your paint scheme,
I love the fact that you did add
those little tufts of hair,
which really brings
the Liberata's furry texture
into the makeup,
which was nice.
Thanks.
You've got the Liberata,
and you've got the Mutant,
and they go together
in a very believable way.
- It's a really nice job.
- Thank you.
I think that
the face sculpture is fantastic.
There's just so much character.
- I'm quite impressed.
- Thank you.
- Anthony, please step back.
- Thanks, guys.
Kris, you're next.
Kris, tell us
about the concept, please.
I chose the Bioman
and Mutant combination.
What happens is the Mutant's
genes spoil the perfect Bioman.
I think, head to toe,
there's a cool vibe
to the character here.
I like that his head
didn't get huge.
He's scary, off-putting,
and from that standpoint,
the design feels
very appropriate.
The Mutant character
is a really hard one
because he's sort of
a generic zombie.
Having said that, I think
his face is really scary.
Makes me feel bad
for the Bioman.
It's anatomically
quite atrocious.
I think you know that.
I like the idea, though.
I think that the sense
of proportion is very nice.
There's something quite
redeemable about the makeup.
Okay, so he's
anatomically not correct.
Blah, blah, blah.
Guys, come on, he's a Mutant.
Give him a break.
I think he's awesome.
He's scary,
he's got green glowing eyes,
and I think it's
a bitchin' character, so there.
Thank you.
- Kris, you can step back.
- Thank you.
Eric,
please step to the center.
So, Eric, tell me
about your creature here.
Basically,
a hardworking miner 99er
got together with one of the
cute, cuddly, little Sensoths,
and this is the offspring.
It-- it disturbs me.
But it disturbs me
in the right way.
Having said that, I wish
it had been more of a blend.
What comes across is,
rather than a genetic mush,
you've got sort of a patchwork.
He's all Sensoth in one part,
and he's all 99er in the other.
I actually quite like it.
You've given him this wardrobe,
and he tells a story.
I think it succeeds in that.
Yeah.
I think you took
a big stride forward
personally
as an artist this week.
Thank you.
I love you,
I think you're adorable,
and you've done
some really funky stuff.
But, dude,
this is not one of 'em.
The hair is just so funky.
It just takes me
out of the whole moment.
I think particularly
at a distance,
it's got a really
well-done quality about it.
You've elevated yourself
to where there's
an element of sophistication
that you're starting
to impart into your makeup,
so that's wonderful.
- Eric, you can step back.
- Thank you, guys.
Okay, the judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they make their decisions
on who will move on
to the finale.
All right, guys, let's talk
about tonight's looks.
Why don't we start with Wayne?
His sculpting
has been shocking.
The speed with which
he approaches is mind-numbing.
Yeah.
He had the sculpture that was
most appealing at a glance.
I think Wayne
has a lot of talent.
I think he's really gonna
go far in our business.
Okay, let's move on to Anthony.
It is the one that has
the best morph
of the two characters.
It looks like
a Mutant Liberata.
And it has the best
paint job of all of them.
The primary forms of
the sculpture are really solid.
I think he also
satisfies the equation
of combining
the by-product of their union,
and this one felt
the most complete.
Anthony created something that
lived in the world of the show.
Let's move on to Kris.
He took on so much
that there was
too much surface area
to actually
design and sculpt for him.
He somehow managed to succeed
in bringing out
this mutant character.
If he would've
put a torn-up,
horrible, filthy shirt
on this guy
and given a little bit
more attention
- to the paint job on the face...
- Yes.
I think this
probably would've been
one of my favorite makeups
tonight.
On one side, I felt like, you
know, of these creature designs,
the Mutant is the most generic.
They need to rise above that.
All right, and last
but not least, Eric.
It's one of the nicest makeups
he's done.
For him, it's extremely subtle.
For once,
we don't have muscles,
and we don't
have blood all over everything.
Are these supposed to be
that simian?
Sensoth is-- is simian.
So the ape that he brought
to the makeup is correct.
Yes, it is.
You know, the thing that just
killed me was the hair.
Well, and, you know,
in a funny kind of way,
it's probably the one that's
closest to being a character.
The face seems more specific
than the other ones.
Although it's
not really a hybrid.
It's a shoulder of one
and a stomach of another
and an arm of one.
Ultimately, what three
get to go on to the finale?
And that's tough
because these guys
all deserve to be here.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- Yeah, we have.
- I think so.
Okay, let's bring 'em back out.
All right, Glenn, who is
the winner of this challenge
and the first person
to make it to the finale?
All right, Glenn, who is
the winner of this challenge
and the first person
to make it to the finale?
Anthony.
You did a great job
handling the hybridization
of your two aliens.
And we particularly loved
all of the character
that you put into the face.
Congratulations.
Thank you, guys, so much.
Thank you.
Anthony, congratulations.
You've made it to the finale.
Thanks.
It just feels so good
to come back and win
another spotlight challenge.
It's so surreal
and humbling every time.
That never gets old.
Now, as the winner
of this challenge,
you have also
won the opportunity
to shadow the special effects
makeup department
- on SyFy's new series Defiance.
- Oh, wow.
Congratulations.
- Oh, my God. Thank you, guys.
- Good job.
To have that added education
on top of this,
it's just the coolest thing
in the world.
All right, Glenn,
who is the next person
to make it to the finale?
Kris.
We were a bit conflicted
about your makeup tonight,
but the essence of him
really came through,
and you've been
a strong competitor all season.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you so much.
Wow.
I'm really excited about this.
Being in the finale was my goal
when I got
into this competition.
Thank you.
I feel like a winner already.
We have two artists and only
one spot left in the finale.
My dream has always been
to make it to the finale
and show everybody
what I can do.
I want this so bad
because I don't
want to let my family down.
Glenn, who gets the last spot
in our finale?
The last spot
in the finale goes to...
Wayne.
Once again, your sculpture is
the strongest part of your work.
There are
some really nice moments
on both the face and the back.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm gonna be in the finale.
I'm just blown away.
But at the same time,
it's bittersweet
because Eric Fox
isn't gonna be there,
and he deserved
to be in the finale
as much as the three of us.
Wayne, you have
our last finale spot.
Unfortunately, that means, Eric,
you will be leaving us tonight.
Okay.
Eric, you're a very colorful
character, and I love that.
You've really evolved
on the show by leaps and bounds.
And I really am excited
to see some of your work
that will be coming
from you in the future.
Thank you.
Eric, it really has been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Okay.
- Love you guys.
- Chin up, man. Good luck.
Yes.
Three of you have done an
incredible job to get this far.
Congratulations.
Go celebrate tonight,
and I will see you soon
for your final
spotlight challenge.
- Good luck, guys.
- Good luck, gentlemen.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, man.
Damn, dude.
Oh, that's cool.
Love you, bro.
Love you too, man.
Congrats.
I'm really happy
for Anthony, Wayne, and Kris.
They definitely deserve
to be in the finale.
They've worked really hard,
just as hard as I have.
I learned so much from you.
You pushed us all
to go farther and bigger.
Absolutely.
It's all good.
I accomplished what I wanted
to accomplish by coming here.
I'm proud
of everything I've done
and had a blast doing it.
Good luck, man.
I think
the most difficult thing
about not making it
to the finale
is I didn't want
to let my wife and kids down.
I just wanted them
to be proud of me.
It's been a great experience,
and I wouldn't change anything.
This has been awesome.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net