Welcome to the season finale
of Face Off.
Tonight, we're headed
to Las Vegas
and reaching epic new heights.
Three artists remain,
but only one will win it all.
I really wanna win
that $100,000.
- Anthony.
- He's absolutely amazing.
My family's been
very supportive of me.
I wanna show them
that everything
that they've sacrificed
has not been in vain.
Wayne.
His sculpting is genius.
WinningFace Offwould just
make my dreams come true,
to have my own shop.
Kris.
He's really, really good.
I'm a married man.
I got two kids.
If I win,
it'll changed my life.
And dreams turn to nightmares
as the pressure takes its toll.
You're gonna re-sculpt
the face?
I'm terrified.
That's a lot of time
that I don't have.
Just not feeling it.
I'm just worried
it might not be enough.
Oh, my God.
If my makeup falls apart,
I'm finished.
Oh, my God.
It all comes down
to one spectacular
and death-defying performance.
In the end, only one
will win the opportunity
to be a guest lecturer
at Make Up For Ever's academies
in New York and Paris,
the all-new 2013 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Welcome to Face Off!
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Oh, my God.
My arms are killing me,
my hands are completely swollen.
Now, it's down
to the last three.
I can't believe
we made it to the finals.
- It's already here.
- It's crazy.
It's a very surreal feeling
being here.
The house is so quiet now.
It's definitely
an emotional roller coaster.
So I go into the kitchen,
and my wife is on Skype.
My love!
I can't believe
I'm staring at you right now.
I love you so much,
and I'm so proud of you.
Hey, mom.
Hi, dad.
Hi, Anthony.
Hey, it's so good to see you.
Being here has
been really hard,
because when I've fallen,
my parents aren't there
to help pick me back up.
How are you?
Hi!
You having fun?
Yeah, it's a lot of stress.
- Hey, daddy.
- Hi, daddy.
Seeing my wife and kids
for the first time
in almost two months,
it just really makes me
wanna come home.
But I'm here for them,
and I'm gonna stick it out.
God, I miss you guys so much.
- I love you.
- Where are you?
Where are you?
I'm so happy
that you made it this far.
I'm so proud of you.
I just love you so much.
Seeing my wife reminds me
why I'm here.
This could be a life-changer
for both of us.
This has been
the most exciting,
most amazing experience.
_
Thank you.
It's definitely a treat,
especially
going into the finale,
having a chance
to have talked to them.
Daddy, did you knock
their socks off?
Keep your head up.
Being in the finale is
something special.
I'm a married guy
with two kids.
And if I win,
my life will change.
Let's do it.
I don't want to let them down.
Well, well, well.
All I keep telling myself
is it's one more time around,
do the best that I can
and hopefully win.
Congratulations,
and welcome to the finale.
- Surreal.
- Unbelievable.
Your final spotlight challenge
will take place
on our biggest stage yet
in Las Vegas.
You'll each be creating makeups
for the most spectacular show
in town,
Le Reve, The Dream
at the Wynn Resort.
Now, before I give you
all the details,
please welcome
the artistic director
of Le Reve, The Dream
James Santos.
James, what can you
tell these guys about it?
Le Reve, The Dream
is an aquatic show
with over 90 artists, acrobats,
and Olympic athletes.
There's no other show like it
in the world.
Le Reve, The Dream.
Wow.
All right,
for your final challenge,
you'll be focusing
on characters
that come to life
only in the depths
of the subconscious.
Dream thieves.
The dream thieves collect
dreams that are in the water.
They are adrenaline junkies
who cannot get enough danger
in their world.
Each of you will create
two fantasy makeups
that will be featured
in this aerial
and acrobatic performance
in front of a live audience
at the Wynn Theater.
I might be smiling
on the outside,
but on the inside
I'm terrified.
Now, one of your characters
must be a dream thief,
and the other their victim
who has something
the thief wants to steal.
Since your characters
will exist in the subconscious,
you'll each pick
one of these dream themes
to help guide your looks.
Anthony, you're up first.
I go straight for sinister.
I feel that I can come up
with something mischievous,
evil, but whimsical.
Just that alone,
I can get a lot of really
cool character into a face.
Wayne.
Supernatural
is really cool to me,
'cause it's the unexplained.
It's really wide open
for interpretation.
Kris.
I gravitate
to the ethereal category.
It's very celestial.
I think this will fit in
the Le Reve, The Dream show.
Vegas, baby.
Now, there's one huge element
that we haven't discussed yet,
and that is the water factor.
Le Reve, The Dream features
a 1 million gallon water tank
throughout the show.
So... your makeups
will need to be
100% waterproof.
It's terrifying knowing
that the makeups
that we're gonna be doing
have to withstand water.
It's something
I've never done before.
To win this finale,
you're gonna need some help.
Guys?
Hi!
You'll each get to choose
two of your former competitors
to join your team.
Wayne, you're got first pick.
Well, I have to go with Fox.
Yeah.
- Kris.
- Let's go PowerHouse.
Thank you.
- Anthony.
- Eric.
Meagan.
Alam.
- Autumn.
- Awesome.
Welcome back.
Okay, it is time
for you to get started.
All right, gang, here we go.
I picked ethereal.
So I go water celestial
like a space God,
slick and streamlined,
where there's smooth areas
on these characters.
So they're
just perfect looking.
Something Vegas-y.
A lot of that's gonna be
in the coloring.
Yeah.
Some silvers would be nice.
I think that'll be cool.
I really like my team,
and I trust them.
There's, like,
so many different elements...
That you have to consider
and bring into it
to make it work.
I've never had to do
waterproof makeup.
Ever.
You just can't sculpt--
But I think
if you keep different pieces
and not sculpt the suit,
you're fine.
Oh, no, no.
I'm not gonna sculpt
a full suit, I can't.
This is the biggest stage ever
in Face Off history,
which is really cool.
And I'm gonna be a part of it.
But we have two makeups to do,
and I can't even finish
one makeup.
The demon's after her
to steal her wings,
'cause usually
they get cast out of heaven.
- So he can fly back.
- That's right.
- That's cool.
- So he's trying to, uh--
- Yeah, I like that.
- I like that a lot.
My concept is
the dreamer is an angel.
She's growing these wings
and her dream
is to make it to heaven.
The dream thief wants to steal
that from her
and get his own set of wings.
This is a hard one.
No, you've got this.
Um, let's get ready
to start sculpting.
The thing with this challenge
is to keep it very minimal
and not have anything
restrictive on their bodies.
I decide to keep it
to a cowl face
and a minor chestpiece.
My concept
is a sinister dream thief,
and the soul embedded
in his chest was torn out.
He's trying to lure
this princess character
and steal her soul.
I'm sculpting
the facial prosthetics,
Eric Z starts working
on the chestpieces,
and Autumn starts
blocking in the cowls.
- Follow-- follow the structure.
- You like that? Okay.
- That's beautiful.
- You like that structure?
- I love it.
- Okay.
That's what I wanna hear.
Just start sculpting it.
We'll just make it work.
For the angel,
I'm having Eric get started
on the face appliance.
And Meagan's working
on the angel's wings
that are growing out
of her back.
Then for the demon, we're going
with a face appliance,
a cowl, and a chestpiece.
The prosthetic is actually gonna
stop right around his nose,
so that way
I don't have to worry
about trying to glue just around
the inside of the nostril.
Because if water gets in there,
that whole thing's coming off.
One of the bigger pieces
that need to be made
is the dream thief's
chest and back.
So I have House jump on that.
I know he's gonna be able
to get it banged out
by the end of the day.
I'm working on this face,
and Alam's gonna start sculpting
the female's chestpiece.
I'm just watching you
sculpt boobs, that's all.
Kinda distracting.
Cover it up.
We got 30 seconds.
That's time, everybody.
I think I have a great team,
and everyone's bringing in it.
Feeling pretty good
about day one.
So it's day two, ten hours.
All that's going through my mind
is get these pieces done
so that we have
time to run 'em in foam.
That looks nice.
I wanna try to mold everything
that we possibly can.
But I'm scrambling for ideas
right now.
Fuck. I hate this challenge.
I love this challenge.
I don't.
For a water challenge
like this, we're limited.
Everything's got to
be streamlined and thin.
Can't cover the ears,
the eyes, or the mouth.
Now, I have to rethink
everything
as far as designing
prosthetics.
I know this is the finale
and there's a lot of money
on the line.
Mm, just not feeling it.
And I'm more than concerned.
I'm really worried what
I'm doing might not be enough.
Coming up...
You're gonna re-sculpt
the face?
I'm terrified.
That's a lot of wasted time.
Oh, my God.
If my makeup falls apart,
I'm finished.
The winner of Face Off is...
Fuck. I hate this challenge.
For a water challenge like this,
we're limited.
Everything's got to
be streamlined and thin.
Can't cover the ears,
the eyes, or the mouth.
I'm really worried
what I'm doing
might not be enough.
Mm, just not feeling it.
So I have to rethink everything
going into this finale
as far as designing
prosthetics.
This is a big deal,
and I need to
make this thing shine.
Hey, everybody.
- Hello.
- Here for a final walk-through.
So it's Mr. Westmore's
last time
checking out our work
in the lab.
It's kind of a sad thing,
because he has been
a mentor of ours
and given us a lot of advice.
- I chose sinister.
- Mm-hmm.
I figured I could do some cool
storytelling with that,
especially with characteristics
in the face.
So we're basically doing
a prosthetic facepiece
and we're gonna be working
to the cowl,
tie it in texturally
and aesthetically.
And then for
our female character,
it's gonna be the same species
but a lot softer.
Do you think it's a smart idea
not to put the cowl
on the female?
I really like the cowl idea.
It's just--
really glue it down.
Because if there's one spot
the water can get into
it's going to turn
into a sponge.
I'm so much more confident
knowing
that Mr. Westmore said
you gotta go with the cowl.
- I love Mr. Westmore, dude.
- Yeah, he's so cool.
He's somewhat of a demon,
and he's after our angel.
She's developing these wings,
and they're growing out
of her back.
So it's underneath the skin.
As far as the dream thief goes,
there's a cowlpiece
and it stops here.
So we're not putting anything
on the neck area.
He has a facepiece.
It'll be blended over the cowl.
And he'll also have tattoos
that'll be black
that go around his shoulders.
What are you gonna use
for paint to do the tattoos?
Probably alcohol inks.
Is that what you've been doing?
- I'm their test subject.
- I love it!
- Ah!
- We're the Guinea pigs.
We have all
the different paints.
- Have you put it in water?
- Not yet.
- Use warm water.
- Okay.
Yes.
Because the tank they're going
into is gonna be warm.
Oh, okay.
I'm bummed out
that Mr. Westmore won't be there
for the rest of my life
to tell me
how to have
good time management.
It's kind of, like,
an aquatic, celestial
kind of look to the whole thing.
So it's sleek, Vegas-y.
The colors will be bold.
It's definitely a challenge.
And water is my biggest fear
on this one.
Probably the most important
thing is getting it sealed in.
Right.
I don't know, maybe,
what you think about this
- but the zinc oxide powder...
- Yep.
...on the edges
to really get a good bond.
That'll actually give it
a better bond.
It's been amazing having him
as a mentor in the shop.
I can't thank him enough for all
the great advice he's given us.
All right, everybody.
We're heading out.
We'll see you in Vegas.
- Bye!
- Bye. Thank you.
- Waterproof.
- Good luck, guys.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
What's the time?
Eight minutes.
Yeah, I like that.
Time's up!
Let's go home!
Thanks, guys.
For day three,
I'm gonna have to finish
sculpting the demon's chest.
But we're behind
because I really needed
all those pieces completed
by day three to pre-paint.
So... I'm kind bummed out that
it's not gonna happen that way.
It's day three,
I'm sculpting the five pieces
for the male model,
and House is gonna finish up
some arm pieces
for the female model.
We'll just be playing
with the paints today.
'Cause I want these pieces
pre-painted.
Her face is
pretty bad up here, man.
Oh, man.
The female face
second-skinned,
which means there's air pockets
underneath the surface
of the foam.
I might've been able
to get away with it,
but this being the finale,
I need to make sure
that face is perfect.
So all I can do
is run it in foam again.
But I can't re-run it,
because the mold is destroyed.
So all I can do now is spend
the time and re-sculpt this.
You're gonna re-sculpt
the face?
Because of this?
- Yeah.
- Patch it.
But look at all the--
I mean, the details there.
And look how thick
the seam is over here.
Oh, that is really thick.
Oh, my God.
I'm terrified.
That's a lot of time
that I don't have.
So I have Autumn mold
the chestpiece
while I start re-sculpting the
face as fast as I possibly can.
_
This is gonna be cool.
I'm just looking
for a nice complimentary color
to the orange.
- I know yellow is probably...
- Yellow.
- ...the most...
- Yup.
...suggested.
I really want the judges to see
what I can do with paint.
So I wanna come up with
a unique color scheme.
Let's think of a design
for the girl
that has the orange color,
the turquoise color,
and yellow.
Center around those colors.
Not gonna pry more
underneath the paint stick.
_
Shit.
I see Autumn and Eric
really struggling
to open Anthony's chestpiece.
I think Anthony's in trouble
on this one
because the only way
to get that off
is to break the mannequin.
But then you don't have
a core piece for the mold.
I notice Eric and Autumn
attempting to open this mold,
and it's not opening.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's locked around the neck.
It's way too far back.
It's way too far up the jaw.
What else can possibly go wrong
in the last moments
of shop time?
The one mold
I ask Autumn to make,
she... locks.
Wow!
Eric Fox is hosing me down!
Turn your arm around.
I wanna be able to get it
from different angles.
But your spraying me!
I'm sorry. Here, here, yeah.
I'll go from this angle.
We're making sure that
the prosthetic will stay on,
we're also testing, um,
colors *.
Wow! That hurt! You're spraying
like high doses of water.
They're jumping 30 feet
into a pool, man!
I think it's a great
test if it showed us how
far we can go protecting
the appliance.
Yea, that's *.
I notice Eric and Autumn
attempting to open this mold,
and it's not opening.
Shit.
The one mold I ask her to make,
she... locks.
_
I did lock a mold.
It's the first thing I've done,
so I'm feeling
like a jerk right now.
I don't wanna let Anthony down
in any way.
- Oop! There she goes.
- Oh, geez!
Oh, man.
- And look.
- Sorry about that.
She has her head on.
Luckily, the piece comes off.
There's a little damage
to the mold,
little damage to the skull.
Make me an elastic, like...
choker thing.
But nothing that can't be
worked with.
This is gonna take two hours
just to seal this.
My biggest concern is how
to make these makeups work.
I know this one's more
about application and painting,
so I'm stressed out about it.
I'll just get a gallon bucket.
You can dip your braid into it.
Our female has long hair.
So Alam is braiding in fabrics
into her hair
and leaving them kind of loose.
Because trying to put
all that hair into a bald cap
isn't gonna work out
for this challenge.
All right, house, check it out.
Yeah.
- I love it!
- I think that'll look cool.
Good.
At the end of day three,
I think nerves
are definitely still there.
But I feel a lot more at ease
that we got everything done
that we needed to get done.
That's time, everybody.
Whoo!
- Let's go to Vegas.
- Yeah!
I am glad today is over.
Now, it's just one more day
in Vegas.
I'll have to bring it
with my team,
because I totally want
to win this.
We're pulling up
to the wynn in Las Vegas.
It's beautiful.
Definitely a surreal feeling.
I never thought
that I would make it this far.
This finale is gonna be
unbelievable.
Oh, my God.
- Wow.
- Oh, my God.
We're walking in the suite
that Kris and Wayne
and I are gonna be staying,
and it's just the craziest place
I've ever been in.
Holy geez.
This suite's pretty sweet.
Oh, no way!
A pool table, man!
Dude, this is freakin' killer!
Damn!
I never been in
something so nice before.
Each one of the rooms
is bigger
than a normal hotel room,
with big screen TVs
and a beautiful view.
It's just crazy.
- This is insane, man.
- This is nuts.
It starts setting in
that this is gonna be
the last challenge.
Oh, yeah.
It's been such
a great experience.
But in the end,
may the best man win.
- To the final three.
- Final three, man.
Cheers.
It's application day,
and we're finally
at the Wynn Theater.
We have four hours
for application,
and then one hour
for last looks.
I immediately start sealing
the appliances.
It's very important
to make sure
that these pieces
are sealed properly
because if they absorb water,
they're just gonna fly off.
I'm scared as hell.
We're getting into
some water acrobatic stuff.
I'm worried about
the pieces not holding up.
I'm Wayne.
Our models are actually
performers from the show.
- Nice to meet you.
These guys are so conditioned
for this acrobatic performance.
But they've never
had makeup like this
applied to them before.
This is your headpiece.
My biggest concern
is making sure
everything gets on in one piece
and also keeping my teammates
on track.
You good?
- It's real sticky.
- Yeah, it is.
While Alam's sealing
some of the other pieces,
House and I are putting
the appliances on the male
because he's got more
than a female.
I have to sew it in first.
Meagan's getting
her hairpiece in.
And then once that's finished,
then we start applying pieces
as fast as we can.
We're a little bit behind.
I was hoping that my team and I
could have
all the appliances done
within the first two hours,
but that's not gonna happen.
So there's still quite
a bit to go
before we even start painting.
See how this fits.
Don't pull that tight.
I feel like I'm pretty far
behind at this point
'cause a lot of people
have already started painting,
and they've got a lot
of their pieces on already.
So... seeing that,
I'm thinking, oh, my gosh,
I have no idea
where the time's going.
_
Hey, guys!
- Hi.
- This is last looks.
You have one hour left
and it starts now.
- Oh! Geez.
- All right.
- Good luck!
- Let's keep going.
It's really about putting
our butts in gear
and just getting this done.
Give him a good powdering
all the way down his head,
everything.
- Get her-- her chest done.
- Okay.
Make sure you paint
his fingertips.
Got it.
Can't believe
this is already last looks.
I'm detailing the male model,
adding some metallic
blue colors to him.
House and Alam finish
the body painting.
I could never do this
all by myself.
Get her costume ready.
- This is it?
- Yeah, that's it right there.
I was on track.
Then one thing after another
started happening
and I'm falling right back
into not having
anything painted.
Yeah, so we got
so much painting to do.
- Oh, my God.
- 15 minutes left, guys!
Fucking unbelievable.
Keep your head
really still for me.
I'm gonna paint these horns
as fast as I can.
God.
And I don't even know
if I have time
to paint the horns
that are on the chest.
That's time, everybody.
- We did it.
- Aw.
I wanna win, but there's
two other artists here
equally as good as I am.
It's looking good.
Dude.
Honestly, I feel great.
You know, my team
really came through for me.
And I know I'm gonna have
something up there
that I'm proud of.
This is very intimidating.
The huge audience, you know,
looking at your work.
If my makeup falls apart,
I'm finished.
Coming up...
Well, that was just
the beginning.
Oh, God, here it goes.
It's one of the coolest things
I've ever seen.
Who is the winner ofFace Off?
Please welcome your host
McKenzie Westmore.
Welcome to
the beautiful Wynn Las Vegas
and the Face Off season finale.
Tonight, you will witness
an incredible performance
from one of the most
amazing shows in the world,
Le Reve, The Dream.
For their final
spotlight challenge,
we asked
each of our contestants
to create two original
fantasy makeups.
The first is a dream thief,
and the second their victim
with something
that the thief wants to steal.
Now, each of our finalists
also chose a dream theme
to help guide their work
and their characters
will participate
in tonight's performance.
So needless to say,
you guys are in
for an amazing treat tonight.
With that,
I'd like to introduce you
to our judges.
First, we have owner of Optic
Nerve Makeup Effects Studio
Glenn Hetrick.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
Tonight's first creations
are from Kris,
and he chose "ethereal"
as his theme.
So let's take a look.
Whoo!
I think my characters are cool
under all these lights.
And having this metallic
silver paint,
it just reflects off of 'em,
it's changing.
He just looks so God-like.
I'm definitely ready for this.
I'm satisfied with my makeups
and proud of my team
for what we accomplished.
And now, whatever happens
in the water
is gonna happen in the water.
There's a huge audience
looking at your work.
It's very intimidating.
From a distance,
they look great.
But when the judges
take a close-up look,
I'm just gonna be dreading it,
because there's just something
missing about it to me.
All right,
before we see the performance,
judges... why don't you come
take a closer look?
Can you tilt down so we can see
how it blends in your forehead?
Can you turn around for us...
if you don't mind?
There's some nice
little detail throughout.
I get it.
It's a simple aquatic approach.
- All right.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
It's really great
metallic color.
Let's get a good look
at your head.
Everything's blended.
Look, we don't have any hard,
horrible edges or anything.
Yeah, this is pretty fantastic.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
So this is all prosthetic,
this whole thing.
This is, by far,
my absolute favorite profile.
Because
it's so natural looking.
Yeah, it is.
I can believe
this thing exists somewhere.
- Yes.
- Mm-hmm.
He looks like he's made
out of stone almost.
- Yeah.
- Which is really cool.
- Gargoyle.
- Yeah.
- They're clearly related.
We'll hear their back story.
But you look at all the details
of this.
Yeah.
The cheeks,
the shape of the head.
The shape of the head is
what really pulls it together.
I do love this paint job
up-close.
Yeah, absolutely.
Thank you.
Are your eyes a bit compressed
from the piece?
It seems like you're having
a little bit of a hard time.
- I can't lift my eyebrows.
- All the way up, yeah.
Can you turn around and take
a look at these things?
The back is my favorite part.
Thanks.
This is really interesting,
this makeup.
- Yeah.
- Surprising!
The level of detail
to the sculpture
is so much greater
than when it--
Yeah, it's really kinda cool.
Can you turn
all the way around?
These actually go back--
they return into the head.
Which is very strange.
Instead of mak--
Even if the tips kind of came up
and out a little.
That doesn't bother me.
I think
it's kind of interesting.
- You do?
- Yeah, I do.
This is the biggest challenge
I've ever done,
which I'm excited about.
But I'm also terrified.
Because I may have
a nice piece on stage,
but once the performers
go in the water,
my makeup could
become a big mess.
Well, that was just
the beginning.
Now, it's time to put them
all to the test.
I present to you
Le Reve, The Dream.
Oh, God, here it goes.
Well, that was just
the beginning.
Now, it's time to put them
all to the test.
I present to you
Le Reve, The Dream.
- Whoo! - Oh, my God!
- Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my God, this is so amazing.
All my fears are gone
with the makeups
'cause they're holding,
and it just looks
so amazing out there.
It's the most beautiful thing
I think I've ever seen
in my life.
All right, well,
to our studio audience,
you've all helped make this
a fantastic evening.
Thank you so much
to everyone for being here.
Have a great night.
So, judges, what do you think
about what
you've seen here tonight?
It's one of the coolest things
I've ever seen.
Congratulations.
Everything stayed on.
And the makeups looked as good
when they came out of the water
as they did when they went in.
I gotta get tips
when this is over.
It was a phenomenal job,
all of you.
Thank you.
Well, the judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Kris, please step forward.
Begin by explaining
your concept.
I went with water celestials.
The male doesn't dream,
but the female
has beautiful dreams
and he's there to steal them.
I wanted to do something
that I haven't done before--
bold colors of silver
clashing with yellow and orange.
I thought that the silver color
was a great choice
to encapsulate
the ethereal concept.
But what you did on her
compared to what you did on him
seemed disconnected.
But it definitely stood out
as uniquely yours.
Thank you.
I thought your sculpting
was terrific.
Everything was very clean.
I loved your silver guy.
And when the lights hit him,
oh, my God, it was fabulous.
The sculpture--
particularly on the face--
was that perfect balance
of hard and soft
and really looked so beautiful.
Thank you so much.
Appreciate it.
Kris, you can step back.
Anthony.
Would you tell us
your concept of your characters?
I had sinister.
The male character
is the dream thief,
and he had his identity and soul
ripped out of his chest.
So he's trying to steal
the princess'.
I wanted to go
as two opposite ends
of similar characters.
The female being very soft
and round features
compared to the male's jagged
and angular features.
I think you did an amazing job.
Thank you.
The characters looked like
they belonged together.
I love the coloring
on both of them.
I especially liked
your dream thief,
because the paint job
was absolutely gorgeous.
Thank you.
The profile of the princess
was, for me, perfect.
That head shape
was so beautifully balanced.
She's still
a very female character.
And she's beautiful
in an alien way.
And to be accomplishing that
at your level
is truly impressive.
Thank you, guys.
Anthony, thank you very much.
Wayne, please step forward.
Hi, Wayne.
Tell us about your concept.
I picked supernatural.
I wanted to go with an angel
and a demon theme.
On her back,
I wanted to sculpt these wings
that were in development
of growth.
As far as the dream thief goes,
his goal is to
steal these wings from her.
They're a great team
as characters.
They felt like they
were related to one another.
I could definitely tell
your sculpting.
Beautiful stuff going on
with the head.
Great detailing.
It was one of the first times
I saw some wrinkles and aging
that felt organic
and realistic.
I concur.
I feel that most
of your successes tonight--
and there were quite a few--
can be found
on your demon character.
I loved the back
of the female as well.
It was both original
and well-executed sculpturally.
I, too, thought your characters
were very well-suited
for each other.
It was obvious that they also
were from the same world.
And I really enjoyed the way
that you had the horns
going back into his skull,
which was really inventive.
- I love that idea.
- Thank you.
Thank you, Wayne.
You can head back.
Well, the judges have heard
what you have to say,
and it's time for them
to decide who will become
this season's champion.
If you'll please head backstage
while they make their decisions.
Yeah!
Let's talk about each one
of our contestants tonight.
Let's start with Kris.
Beautifully done.
And I have a lot of respect
for the originality
that he infused
into the challenge.
I could look up
- and immediately identify...
- You knew.
- ...both of Kris' characters.
- Absolutely.
Which you could not do
with anyone else's.
You had to hunt 'em down.
He was the only one
that went bold with the colors,
albeit, I think
it was kind of an odd choice
to use orange with ethereal.
But his dream thief--
when he came out
with that silver makeup on
and those lights hit him,
- oh, my God, it was spectacular.
- Beautiful.
The water celestial character.
Even though the paint job
camouflaged it,
the sculpture underneath
was really quite good.
Yeah.
All right,
let's move on to Anthony.
I love the fact
that the female had no hair,
and she still looked
really uniquely beautiful.
It was just the actual subtlety
of the sculpture
and the way that it swept back.
And she really looked amazing.
It looks natural.
The proportions
have been reined in
and thought about so well.
That is a culmination
of listening
to so many of the notes
that we have all given him.
These designs
are absolutely usable.
It's also sinister.
It's what
it was supposed to be.
All right,
let's move on to Wayne.
- He is such a good sculptor.
- Yes.
And not just, like,
the surface of the sculpting,
but the ideas of the big forms.
He's definitely improved
his paint skills
since he came here.
That decision to vein
that guy up--
what a huge step!
I really thought
that it was a coup
that he put those horns
on that demon
and embedded them in his head.
He wanted to get those horns
on the demon,
and he figured out
a way to do it.
And he made some really
interesting choices
with some
of the structural things
on the demon's face.
While that's incredible, "A,"
and "B," we've never seen it.
Mm-hmm.
In our collective knowledge
of character design,
that's a difficult thing
in and of itself,
to come up with something that's
truly unique and original.
All right, judges.
Have you chosen a winner?
- It was a close one, but...
- It really was.
- Yeah.
- We're there.
All right,
let's bring them back out.
One of you will become
the winner of Face Off.
Glenn, why don't you tell us
about tonight's makeups?
Kris, we were delighted
with your silver character.
And we really appreciate
that you stepped
outside of the box tonight.
Anthony.
There was an immediately
recognizable harmony
between your characters,
and the profiles
were quite striking.
Thank you.
And Wayne.
As always,
there were some truly original
ideas in your sculpting,
and your characters were very
clearly from the same world.
Glenn, who is the winner
ofFace Off?
The winner ofFace Offis...
Glenn, who is the winner
ofFace Off?
The winner ofFace Offis...
Anthony.
Anthony, congratulations!
You are the winner of Face Off!
Congratulations, man!
You did it, man.
How does it feel?
Oh, my God, it's amazing!
Oh, my God!
To be the Face Off season four
champion is awesome.
Oh, my God.
Words can't describe
what I'm feeling right now.
Congratulations.
It's just so surreal.
I'm so thankful.
I'm Face Off
season four champion.
Yeah!
Here are the keys
to your new Fiat 500.
Anthony!
Whoo!
Oh, my God.
Thank you guys so much.
I feel like
I'm trapped in a dream.
This is awesome.
Oh, my God.
I'm honored
to have been part of the finale
with Wayne and Anthony.
This has been
the best experience.
This competition
has meant a lot to me,
because I showed myself
that I was able to do things
that I thought
that I couldn't do.
I'm not giving up makeup.
I'm gonna stick to it.
We all worked really hard,
so for me to come out on top
against such amazing artists
is truly an honor,
and it just makes me
even more proud
to be with all them.
This has definitely been
an experience
I will never, ever forget.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net