Previously on Face Off...
The artists created
confectionary delights.
Kris's candy corn demon
broke Anthony's winning streak.
Thank you so much.
And Alex was sent home.
Now, ten artists remain.
Tonight,
they'll face
a gargantuan challenge
and be judged
by a movie industry titan.
Bryan Singer.
Oh, my God!
- In the lab...
- I hope this works.
The pressure
reaches an all-time high.
I can't do this by myself.
This is crazy.
If we don't pull it off,
it's the biggest failure,
literally.
From the ankles up,
it's fabulous.
I think it's the biggest makeup
we've ever seen on the show.
It's a hot mess,
and it's embarrassing.
It's hard to critique
because I don't want
to kick you while you're down.
I'm incredibly impressed.
I'm-- actually,
I'm actually blown away.
In the end, only one will win
the opportunity
to be a guest lecturer
at Make Up For Ever's academies
in New York and Paris,
the all-new 2013 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
Good morning.
I think we're all relieved
that someone else won
besides Anthony.
His winning streak is broken.
It's definitely
a confidence booster for me
and for everyone,
but I think we're at a point now
where we really
have to take chances.
So into the van
and onto the next challenge.
It's very important to me
not to be in bottom looks again,
so to be noticed
for having top looks
or to win would be really,
really nice.
We wind up at Magic Mountain.
This place is so cool.
We're all running around,
acting like children.
We're at an amusement park,
so of course,
we're gonna have fun.
We're checking out
all the cool sites,
and then, we see
this giant redwood tree,
and just past the tree
stands McKenzie.
Welcome
to Six Flags Magic Mountain.
This has been a popular location
for dozens of films
and features
more roller coasters
than any other theme park
on the planet,
but I bet you're wondering
why the heck you're here today.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Well, I take it you did notice
the giant redwood tree
right behind me.
- Yup.
- Good.
Because that's why you're here.
You're all headed
to the land of giants.
Ah, knew it.
This week's challenge
is giants.
That's kind of a monster,
and that's kind of cool.
The adventurous tale
of Jack The Giant Killer
recalls Jack, a farmer's son
who rid the land
of all evil giants.
That is the basis for
this week's spotlight challenge.
To create
an original giant character
that Jack might have slain
on his adventures.
I have never made a giant
before, and I'm thinking
it's gonna be a lot of work.
Now, I'd like to introduce you
to the director and producer
of award-winning
and extremely popular films,
including The Usual Suspects,
X-Men, Valkyrie,
and of course, the upcoming
Jack The Giant Slayer.
He's also producer and director
of the TV show House.
Please welcome Bryan Singer.
Wow!
I'm starstruck.
It's Bryan Singer,
which is insane.
Oh, my God.
I'm a huge Bryan Singer fan.
He's awesome.
How are you?
Thank you so much
for being here.
Oh, my pleasure.
Thanks for having me.
As a producer who has brought
such amazing characters
to life,
such as Keyser Soze,
Magneto,
Wolverine,
what makes a compelling
character on-screen?
Well, I think
it's when you find a way
to translate
the actor's personality,
whoever's playing the role,
and infuse that
into the character.
I think whenever you do that,
you believe it more.
Now, there's something
that we haven't told you
about Jack's adventures
in the original tale.
Jack encounters several giants.
And some of them
have multiple heads.
With that in mind,
your giants must have
at least two heads.
- Nice.
- Okay.
Creating a giant with one head
is difficult enough.
Creating it
with two or three or more
is going to be
extremely difficult.
This is a team challenge.
Your randomly selected teams
of two are...
Alam and Eric Z.
Kris and Eric F.
- Oh!
- Oh, that's an awesome team.
Meagan and Jenna.
I know Meagan's worried
about the tumor in my hand,
which causes my fingers
to be completely numb,
so I know it's going
to be rough.
Wayne and House.
Autumn and Anthony.
Anthony's
a four-time winner,
so I don't even have to worry.
I feel like I'm on friggin'
vacation this challenge.
Now, please stand
with your new teammate.
- Awesome.
- Ah, that's great.
By the way, Bryan is also
going to be joining us
on our reveal stage
to see your makeups.
This is rad!
It's an honor to be able
to, uh, you know,
try to show off for this guy.
Bryan, what are you
going to be looking for
in their final creations?
Obviously, something original,
something
we've never seen before,
but also something
that brings out a bit
of the personality
in the models that they choose,
so we really feel
the characters come to life.
Okay, I want you guys
to stay here
for just a little bit
and get started
on your designs.
When you're done, I want you
to head back to the lab,
choose your models,
and get started.
Good luck.
See you tomorrow.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Let the actor
show through, right?
Right.
And that's the dwarf's head.
Yeah, this is
the actor's real head.
Oh, yeah, I know
what you're talking about.
Okay.
Eric is the mastermind.
I put my complete faith in him.
Our concept is
to take our big guy,
and turn him into Jack,
and have two giants
towering over him.
It feels really good
that Kris is willing
to take the risk.
If we can pull this off, it's
going to be something great.
Eye movement?
House comes up with a concept
right off the bat.
He's fired up about it.
Three heads
because I'm thinking everybody's
doing two heads.
Two heads are easy.
Actor's wearing makeup,
dummy head, dummy head,
and he's operating
both of them, la la la.
We're seeing the redwood tree,
and our giant lives
out in the woods,
so let's incorporate that.
The feet are going
to be giant roots,
and he's going to have
tree limbs popping off.
I really think
those kind of details
help create
a more iconic character.
I mean, it could be
any kind of giant.
It could be a bird giant,
it could be a horse giant.
You know?
I think we need
to keep things minimal.
I know that Jenna wants
to do huge things,
and she wants to go
out of the box.
You know, make this a fake arm,
and the other one a puppet,
so that mouth will move.
She wants to do these puppets
with the head,
but I don't think
we're capable of doing that.
What if we build up
from the shoulder?
His face is here, and there's
just a fake one above him.
We figured out that we can do
a head on top of a head.
It will look like our giant
has taken in a human being
and has transformed it
into the cartoon world.
That's time.
Let's rock this.
So we get back to the lab,
and it's time
to choose our models,
different models
than what we've used before.
They're actually
really big guys.
They're all, like,
6'6", 6'5", 6'4".
I'm trying to stay away
from every idea
that I think everybody else
is going to gravitate towards.
So our concept is
to have this contorted giant
with a twisted body,
heads kind of growing
out of him
as if they were
genetic mutations.
I start blocking in the chest
and the back pieces.
Autumn starts working
on the face.
Let's make sure we get
some good movement in the mouth.
Everything I do
has movement in the mouth.
I'm a little concerned
because I know Autumn
is a strong player,
and I feel
I'm a strong player too.
But I don't want his head
to be flat
'cause I already
got shitted on for that.
So when you put
two leaders together,
they clash.
I think
we can go more stronger,
like, on the chin.
Okay.
The concept for our giant is,
he slays other giants,
and as punishment,
he's chopped off their heads
and attached them to his feet.
We're also playing
with the idea that,
when your feet are tired,
you complain,
and that these heads
on the feet
will always be complaining
and talking back to the giant.
Do you like the way
this is coming, by the way?
Mm-hmm, I like it.
It's awesome
having Alam as a partner.
She doesn't get stressed out,
which is awesome,
and she always has
really fun, fresh, new ideas.
We only have
a limited amount of time
to create this giant makeup.
Let's get this thing sculpted,
priority number one.
So both of us do something
that we've never done before.
We're working
on the sculpture together.
We're not splitting up chores,
rather,
we're combining our styles
to create this makeup
as quickly as possible.
Symmetry is going
to be key on this.
Like, taper the sculpt
like that.
Yeah, and out.
So that as it goes on,
it just, like, bloop.
I'm feeling really good,
at this point,
working with Meagan.
I think we're communicating
really well.
I'm having a lot of issues
with my hand,
but I keep trying
to put it out of my mind.
I don't want it
to take up my time.
I need to focus
on what I'm doing.
So we get six hours today
at the lab.
We start cutting up
pieces of styrofoam
for our two giant heads,
just to get a rough shape,
and then we'll take
some ultracal and some hemp,
coat those over to get
about an inch thickness.
And once they're all set up,
we're ready to sculpt.
Point the nose that way.
- That way?
- Yeah, to keep the flow.
I thought it would
be crooked than this way, like--
You know, in any makeup,
the face is always
the most important element,
and this is the first time
that I'm stepping back
and letting somebody else
do the face
so that I can tackle
the chest and the back.
To give up that responsibility
is a little nerve-racking.
Kris and I want to execute
the biggest character
as possible,
so I grab a piece of chalk,
and I'm using the lab floor
as a giant doodle pad
to get our concept
and proportion chart done.
Now I can physically see
the amount of area
that needs to get covered.
Look how big that thing is.
Fox is a madman.
Gonna be 10 foot tall!
- That's 10 foot tall?
- 10 foot, yes.
How tall--
the dude's, like, 6'4"?
Yeah.
Right there, that's his head.
To create this giant,
I know that Eric wants
to push the envelope
as much as possible,
and I have
a lot of respect for that.
Looking at the sheer size
of their giant,
right away, I'm thinking,
"what is that mold
going to look like?"
Are they going to be able
to get it off the piece
and clean it out
and cast it in time?
- This is crazy.
- They said make a giant.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Laid out,
our giant is a lot bigger
than I thought
it was going to be.
I'm getting worried.
Will we finish this project?
I know we don't have
a lot of time to pull this off,
so every minute
has to be accounted for.
If we don't pull it off,
it's going to be
the biggest failure
in Face Off history.
Literally.
Coming up...
I can't do this shit.
Please don't give up right now.
It's not looking good.
Man, we are burnt.
There's a stunning lack
of originality
in this design.
Well, this is certainly
the most ambitious effort.
The dude's, like, 6'4"?
Yeah.
Right there, that's his head.
That's massive, dude.
Laid out,
our giant is a lot bigger
than I thought
it was going to be.
Hold those corners real quick?
I never worked
on a giant monster before,
but I trust Eric.
He wanted to make
the biggest monster,
so we're doing it.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Please touch it while I'm gone.
Oh, please touch it.
With a teammate like Autumn,
I think the way
to approach this is
to let her think
she has more control
than she really does.
I'm afraid, if I push too much,
then her personality's
going to get bigger
and may not be able
to be contained.
I, like, go and potty,
come back to something new.
You said touch it.
These guys are doing three.
Anthony's doing three.
The feet are three,
technically.
By the end of the day,
I'm looking around the shop,
and it seems like
almost everyone is
doing some kind
of three-headed creature.
- Let's do two.
- Let's do that.
- Bring it down a little bit.
- Yeah.
So we decide
to loop off one of the heads
and just make it
a two-headed giant.
It saves some work
for the actor,
and it saves some work for us.
Time's up, guys.
I think our sculpts
look beautiful,
and I'm especially proud
of my face sculpt.
I just hope Anthony doesn't
get credit for all of it.
- Whoo!
Day two begins.
We have a lot of work to do.
We have a chest to make,
a side shoulder piece,
we have to make a pair
of tree feet,
and we have to make a head
that our model can puppeteer.
We already done one head
and almost done two,
and we need one more.
So now I'm trying to sculpt
the left foot.
For our concept,
we're incorporating
a lot of tree elements,
and on the chest,
I'm incorporating
an oak tree-type texture
of bark,
so it's organic-looking.
Hey, guys.
We're here for our walk-through.
- Hi, everybody.
- Hey, hey!
Ready?
Michael Westmore--
he is
my mentor for the season,
and I really couldn't ask
for anything better than that
because it really
gives us a chance
to shape things
before it's too late.
We just kick-started these.
Obviously very root.
Almost like the tree root
itself-- the feet.
And the redwood was actually
the big inspiration for us.
Glad to see you've got
a lot of deep grooving to it
'cause the root
actually grows like this.
- Yeah.
- I want you to promise me
you're not gonna make it muddy.
Keep your browns
and your greens separate,
because they start
getting together,
and you lose
all your wonderful sculpture.
That's right.
We decided to focus
on a little more simple
and really concentrate
on the paint job.
Be careful of it because you
really have a lot of edges here.
And as the competition's
getting stronger,
getting rid of edges is gonna be
very, very important.
We have a plan for that.
Vines coming out of his mouth.
Smart thinking.
I love the idea
of the cleft lip.
You get this on,
really glue those lips down,
- so they don't flap on you.
- Yeah.
- It's gonna be neat.
- Yeah. Thanks.
Painting is gonna be important.
What are you thinking about,
color-wise?
We want to do some blue washes
and have some parts of him
have loss of pigment.
I think it's a good idea,
because you go dark,
you're gonna start losing
your detail.
Mr. Westmore loved the idea
of doing the blue color scheme.
And if there's one challenge
I'm going to go all out,
do some crazy colors,
it should be the giant.
We're go turn Jack
into a little dwarf.
He's a little guy
with a complex.
And the heads are
gonna be... puppets.
Okay...
Eric, I know last week,
you had some problems
completing everything,
so is anything happening here
that's going to come up
and bite you again,
or you really have it
thought out this time?
Really have it thought out.
We're tackling
all the sculptures.
We're kinda putting both
of our ideas into everything.
So we're just
splitting everything
right down the middle.
You know, this all
has to be molded today.
- Oh, yeah.
Mr. Westmore's concern is,
will we have time
to complete our giant makeup?
I won't lie.
I'm a little nervous too.
All right, everybody,
we're heading out,
- but it's looking good.
- Thank you.
When the sculpture is finished,
it's time to make a mold.
Wayne and I are
molding like crazy.
We're molding everything
together at once.
There's a lot to do,
and we're doing it.
Jenna is molding
in the spray booth,
and you just don't mold
in the spray booth.
You use that
for spraying stuff.
- Jenna!
- What?
I just wanna get this
properly done.
Do you wanna clean this,
and I'll do that?
Okay, go.
I'm starting to feel
a little frustrated
at this point
because I feel like
I'm not getting the opportunity
to do things the way
I would do them.
That's the trouble
with working with a partner
because we each have our
different way of doing things.
No, Jenna, no.
She does things one way,
I do things another way.
And sometimes it doesn't matter
how you do them,
just as long as you get
the end result
that you wanna get.
What did she do?
Jenna, you took the cowl
off of it?
I didn't take it off.
We gotta build it back up,
otherwise it's not
gonna go on his head.
I'm panicking.
There's no cowl here,
so there's no way for it
to stay on the actor.
So we have to block this out
really quick.
No, no, no, no.
That's fine, that's fine.
It's this, under here.
I can tell Meagan
doubts my ability to do things,
and I know she does not
wanna go home.
But I do wish that she
had a little more faith in me,
that I do know
how to do some things.
I hope this works.
Here we go.
Anytime you got a mold
this big to do,
it works a lot better
if you can do it as a team.
This thing is like
trying to plaster a hot tub.
I mean, it is massive.
- It's Bigfoot.
- Bigfoot!
Ooh, nice.
We've got an hour and a half.
Okay.
Did you put pry points?
There's one down here,
and there's one down here.
Jenna's responsibility
was to just
make that big mold,
and I can't open it.
There's not good pry points.
This is completely fucked.
I'm very frustrated
with our situation.
It's not looking good.
We're cracking it in,
and if it breaks, it breaks.
I'm trying to just get it done,
but it's a disaster.
We gotta get this mold open,
and I'm very concerned.
- Where's it stuck?
- Where is it stuck?
- Oh, right here.
- Where?
Right here?
I'm watching these poor girls
rolling around the floor,
struggling with a mold.
I can't take it no more.
I'm gonna have to step in
and help 'em get this mold out.
Watch out, move.
Thank you.
So we got the mold open,
but there's still a lot
of cleaning we have to do.
The time's ticking, man.
It's stressing me out.
- It's not on there.
- Oh, my God.
Once I finally
got the mold cleaned out,
I put it together, and it
doesn't close, there's a gap.
Which means if the mold
doesn't close properly,
then anything you fill in there
will leak or not cure.
So Jenna and I are running
high-risk right now.
Time's up!
Man, we are burnt.
We got our heads foamed,
but we still got
a hand to mold
on application day.
We'll get it done--
I hope.
All right.
It's application day.
We have four hours to complete
our giant makeup.
We know we have
a lot of work to do.
We're in the mold room,
pulling pieces out of mold,
running polyfoam.
I'm a little concerned.
I'm a worrywart anyway.
This whole thing came out.
Our piece is, like,
all messed up.
The whole edge
is completely ripped.
The nose piece has, like,
a bunch of lumps.
The seams are huge.
It looks really in bad shape.
It's still wet.
The foam piece is not cured
all the way,
so it's collapsing on itself.
I think
in the finished product,
we can either cover it
or hide it somehow.
I'm still optimistic
at this point
that something will work.
Ooh.
Yeah, it's ugly.
There are a few bad tears
in the prosthetic,
but I feel really confident
that Autumn and I are gonna
be able to pull this off.
We'll make that scarring.
We have a whole new set
of models.
They're all giant men,
6'3"-plus, bodybuilders.
How you doing, buddy?
And we're gonna
make a cool giant.
Slip your hand up in here,
and it's basically a puppet
like this.
Okay.
We're worried about
piecing everything together,
painting,
and then fitting it on him.
There's a lot to do
besides a makeup application.
When you're walking,
big, giant steps.
- Like--
- Like, big steps.
Yeah, there you go.
That's it.
All right, that's perfect.
Keep pulling.
We open up the molds,
and we see
a perfectly ran foot.
We got our feet,
and we're ready to go.
We're so excited.
You wanna blow foam
in that real fast?
- Yeah, hittin' it right now.
- Awesome!
We're in the mold room
still fabricating things.
Our model has been
sitting for a while
before we even get a chance
to go over
and say hello to him.
The clock's ticking.
I hope I didn't get me and Kris
in over our heads
with this wacky scheme.
Just start working
on a wardrobe.
I'm gonna start working
on the wardrobe, I got to.
Anthony
is pre-painting everything
'cause he is Mr. Illustrator.
And I will be
building the costumes
because he is scared shitless
of the sewing machine.
I need scissors.
Do you want me
to start mixing paint up
and getting, I'm gonna start
spraying the feet?
I'm feeling pretty good.
House is feeling pretty good.
We just can't wait
to see this thing
all just come together.
Is it gonna fall?
We go to put the cowl
on our actor...
It's not gonna stay up.
And it's not gonna work.
The whole inside of it
is gummy,
and I'd rather
put it somewhere else.
What I suggest
is we cut it open
and put it
coming through his shirt.
It looks really bad.
Like, it looks bad.
Cut it straight down the middle
so that we have
the front face of it.
I know Meagan
is furious with me
and aggravated with me
and frustrated with me.
You just gonna
put that wig on him?
- No.
- No?
Jenna's really--
she--
I could tell, mentally,
she's worn down.
Safety pin the head
to the cheesecloth.
- To this?
- Yeah.
And we'll wrap it
around his body.
Fuck, I can't do this shit.
Jenna, please don't give up
right now.
Please.
I can't feel my fucking hand.
I know that,
but please--
I-I can't do this
by myself.
Meagan's getting
kinda frustrated.
The time's ticking away,
and it's very stressful
when things start to go wrong.
You know, I just hope
they get this thing knocked out.
What time is it?
Five minutes.
Oh.
Lookin' handsome.
Scissors, scissors, scissors.
It's okay.
It's gonna work out.
That's time.
It's a disaster.
I feel like, regardless
if it's on me or her,
it's crumbling.
It's coming down.
And I just wanna get it
to a good place,
so it's not embarrassing.
Coming up...
We don't have much to do,
other than assemble a giant.
Honestly, it didn't
go the way you wanted.
It does look like hell.
Well, this is certainly
the most ambitious effort.
Last looks is always intense.
The last looks
on this challenge,
maybe the most intense.
Can you open the mouth?
Lower? Higher?
Uh, higher.
We don't have much to do,
other than assemble a giant.
I'm a little freaked out
about this.
- All righty.
- We didn't have any clothes.
We had to make that
all last-minute.
I start frantically
cutting up leather
and gluing it on.
Just kinda keep your hands
like that.
I don't want to let Alam down.
I wanna get this thing done.
I have to have a finished piece
up there for the both of us.
Hey, guys, we got
30 more minutes left.
Thank you.
Everything that possibly
could go wrong is going wrong.
We're sinking,
but we're trying.
Cut a hole
that will go over this.
Meagan has an idea
of how it needs to work.
- Do you understand what I mean?
- No, I don't.
She's thinking, I'm sure,
"what, is she stupid?"
His face is all jacked up.
Just take it off.
We can't just
send him out there
with one head,
he's gotta have two.
If you think it needs
to get off, then take it off.
It's time, guys!
Put your brushes down.
I'm gonna cry.
Look at that, fucking
awesome, man!
His other shoe's not on.
It's a hot mess,
and it's embarrassing.
And I am scared I'm going home.
Welcome
to the Face Off reveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
Say hello to your judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve
Makeup Effects Studio
- Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
Evening.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
A very big hello to you
this evening.
Hello.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
A giant hello to you
this evening.
Oh, copycat.
And with us again tonight
is writer,
producer, and director
Bryan Singer.
Hey.
Thanks.
Bryan, thank you so much
for being here.
Glad to be here.
This week
your spotlight challenge
was to create a giant character
with at least two heads
that Jack might have slain
on his adventures in the book
Jack The Giant Killer.
Let's see
what you've all come up with.
I like our giant.
He's the character
that Alam and I wanted to make.
On elimination day,
all that you can really ask for
is that you're happy
with your character.
This thing is impressive.
It's filling up half the stage.
And the looks
on the judges' faces is amazing.
I don't even wanna look at it.
And I'm thinking,
"I'm going home.
There's no way I'm gonna
make it through this."
I'm ready to win this one,
at least be in top looks.
I mean, we have
really clean makeup.
It looks really nice.
This is probably
the most excited I've been
since I've been here.
You know,
it is very nerve-racking
seeing, not only the judges,
sitting there,
but also Bryan Singer looking
with a magnifying glass
over our work.
Judges, why don't you
take a closer look?
Wow, that's bizarre.
It's just
such a strange choice.
Our giant doesn't have
as great of a presence
compared to the others,
and that worries me.
What the hell happened to you?
Tall, looks like polyfoam.
This is so great.
Look, he's stabbing his hand.
Oh, neat.
This is so fun.
It feels so great.
We pulled off
a last-minute miracle.
This thing is so huge,
so impressive,
but funny.
Your mouth doesn't move
in the makeup?
Open your mouth
as was you can, please.
Oh, they're just really stiff.
- Yeah.
- Interesting choices here,
form-wise,
that I just don't understand.
Is that edge coming up
down there?
Yeah, it is.
I am so embarrassed
that's onstage.
There's no doubt
one of us is going home.
Oh, my God.
Watch our new web series
Face Off Redemption tonight
to see this season's
eliminated contestants
compete to win a spot
on our next season of Face Off.
Interesting choices here form-wise,
that I just don't understand.
I'm so embarrassed
that that's on stage.
There's no doubt
one of us is going home.
Some neat broad strokes
happening.
I like the way they did this.
- This is clever.
- And it works.
I like there's a wood knot
in the palm.
Oh, yeah, that's great.
That's really cool.
I love that.
I love it.
It's really cool up close.
Yeah, and the wetness
of the tongue and the eyeball.
Yeah, it's really good.
- He's the saddest giant.
- He really is.
Like, he's encumbered
by these other characters.
Let's see the back.
Please show me.
Oh, this head's good too.
- Wow, man.
- These are good.
Bryan, you gave
some great advice
to these guys the other day.
So how do you think they did?
I'm incredibly impressed.
I'm--
actually,
I'm absolutely blown away.
Great.
The judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Wayne and House,
please step forward.
Guys, tell me
about the concept.
Well, it's two heads,
and we wanted the actor
to be the puppeteer
of the second head,
as well as using
the redwood tree
as an inspiration.
Overall, I like this a lot.
I think that I'm struggling
a bit with the proportions.
He's gotten so wide this way,
that's it's managed
to make him shorter.
Shorter, yes.
I love the color
that you chose to paint him
because it's not, like,
a typical bark color.
He looks like a stone statue
that has great animal qualities
to it as well.
It's very successful.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
There's some really great
sculpting going on,
particularly in the body,
with the bark.
I admire the fact
that yours is the only one
that the two heads can interact
and have personality
and be more
than just a giant
that happens to have two heads.
I thought it was
a really awesome piece.
- I really liked it.
- Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Please step back.
Autumn and Anthony.
So tell me the story
behind your giant.
He's kind of a backseat driver.
So the one in the back
is the one
whispering in his ear
to control the beast.
From far away,
I wasn't that impressed.
But when I got up close,
I really liked this a lot.
How long did it take you
to do the three-eye paint job?
I'd probably say
about five minutes apiece.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- That's quite impressive.
- Thank you so much.
What sporting goods store
did he get those gloves?
No, but the overwhelming
entirety of it obscures them.
I only noticed that
upon close examination.
But great work, really awesome.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you, guys.
Anthony, Autumn,
please step back.
Alam and Eric Z.
Start by explaining
your concept.
We took
a folktale approach to it.
The idea is he has this axe,
and he slays other giants,
and he attached these two
giants' heads to his feet.
They're forever tortured
as they walk.
They complain, like,
complaining, tired feet.
The head-on-feet thing is
such an absolutely
dreadful decision
that I'm having a hard time
even looking at anything else.
And it's disappointing.
It's too bad those heads
weren't somewhere else,
because from the ankles up,
he's fabulous.
- Thank you.
It's hard to get up
to looking at his makeup
because the feet
are so wretched.
They look too playful,
so it kills it.
- Okay.
- Eric, Alam, please step back.
- Thank you, thanks.
- Thank you so much, buddy.
Kris and Eric F.
Well, this is certainly
the most ambitious effort.
What's the whole concept?
The little guy
taking on the world, basically.
I think this would
definitely be a makeup
that my kids would like to see.
I really admire the fact
that you've taken
the tallest model
of all the actors up there
and yet made him
into the smallest person.
- That was really clever.
- Thank you.
You guys should definitely
be impressed with yourselves
in terms of how much work
you've pulled off.
I think it's the biggest makeup
we've ever seen on this show.
- Yes!
- That was one of our goals.
So--
Who came up with the idea
to have this giant
holding the actor?
Eric masterminded
the whole thing.
You not only pulled it off,
but it's a great idea.
Thank you so much.
Means the world.
Eric, kris,
thank you very much.
Please step back.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
You're awesome.
Success, man, success.
Meagan and Jenna, you're up.
Tell us about the concept.
What inspired this giant?
The idea behind him was
that Jack was just
an ordinary guy,
and this giant started
to take over his body.
This was originally
supposed to be up here.
- It was a cowl.
- Yeah, it was--
But it was a mess.
Who was responsible
for what aspect of this?
We both pretty much
took the load I would say.
It was definitely
a stressful grouping.
It was.
It became--
this breaks my heart
to say this.
It became very evident that,
with my hands like this,
I can't sculpt
the way I need to,
the way I want to.
And I feel terrible
about hindering
someone else's performance
because they're trying
to make up
for my lack of ability
to do it.
You know, it's hard to critique
because I don't wanna kick you
while you're down.
I mean, there's not
a lot of good.
It didn't go
the way you wanted.
And that is the net result
of what we get to look at.
There's a stunning lack
of originality in this design.
Whatever it was that forced you
to take the head off,
it was a horrible decision.
Meagan, Jenna,
please step back.
- Thank you.
- You okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, the judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they make
their decisions.
All right, guys,
so why don't we talk
about the looks that
you liked the most tonight?
Why don't we start
with Wayne and House?
I like the idea
that it was the one
interactive giant,
the two heads.
I think the sculpting on it
was so beautiful,
and the paint job was terrific.
I really like it a lot.
All right, let's move on
to Anthony and Autumn.
The paint job was spectacular.
For the amount of time
and the amount of sculpting
that they did, my God,
they did an amazing job.
It was
an interesting reveal too,
the fact that first you see
a head there,
and you're like,
"what?"
And then turns around--
suddenly, "oh!"
And then faces us again
and pulls back the outfit,
and you can see more
of the, you know, structure.
Yeah, that was amazing.
- The chest was beautiful.
- Yeah.
Let's move on
to Kris and Eric F.
That silhouette,
when it first came out
and the lights went on,
and you see
this little, tiny person
being held,
such a great concept.
I think that was really
a clever thing that they did.
It was a very clever way
to get some fun and humor
into a challenge that's
very difficult to do that.
Let's move on to the looks
you didn't like so much
this week.
Let's start
with Meagan and Jenna.
It was so bad.
It was inexcusable.
There was nothing
on that makeup that was good.
There's so many problems
right from the start
with this makeup,
it really didn't have
a chance to succeed.
And I know
that Jenna's hands are hurting,
and that is very unfortunate.
All right, guys, let's move on
to Alam and Eric Z.
It's so overly obvious
how poor the concept was
of having feet grab onto heads
and walk around with them.
There was no point
along the way
that they went,
"aah, this totally sucking.
Let's try something else."
I would've taken the heads off,
closed the eyes,
strapped them to a chain
to each one of my ankles,
and pulled them around.
Yeah, that's a way to treat it.
- That would've been my remedy.
- Yeah.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- Yep.
- Yeah.
- I think so.
Let's bring 'em back out.
Glenn, tell us
about the top looks tonight.
Wayne and House,
it was really cool
how you brought tree bark
into your design.
And the puppeteering aspect
was also
a really nice touch.
Anthony and Autumn,
your sympathetic character
was very successful,
and we loved the paint job.
Kris and Eric F,
it was a massive amount of work.
The profile was
extremely interesting as well.
Okay, which team
came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Okay, which team
came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Kris and Eric F.
You guys took on
so much this week,
and you delivered
some serious wow factor.
Congratulations.
- Thank you so much, guys.
- That's fantastic.
Eric F and Kris,
great job, guys.
But we can only have
one winner.
Glenn?
The winner is...
- Eric F.
- Yeah!
- Ahh.
- Whoo!
Thank you.
Aww.
In the end, it came down
to concept for us.
And as kris put it,
that was all Eric.
To hear my name as the winner,
it is amazing
because I've worked
so hard for this.
Thank you, guys.
- Eric!
- Good job.
Eric F, congratulations.
You and Kris can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you, guys.
- Thank you.
Wayne and House,
Anthony and Autumn,
you guys are also safe.
Please head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, guys.
Unfortunately,
that means the rest of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Meagan and Jenna,
this makeup was a problem
from its inception.
And honestly, your technical
and application issues
just compounded everything.
Alam and Eric Z,
there were some issues
with the head in the feet.
It just felt like a cheat.
So who's going home tonight?
The person
leaving tonight is...
Jenna.
Unfortunately,
there just wasn't anything
about your work this week
that's indicative of the fact
that you're going to be able
to continue getting better
while you're here on the show.
Jenna, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
The rest of you are safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you, judges.
Jenna, we're so sorry
that you've been struggling
with these injuries.
And we really hope you have
a speedy recovery, honey.
And please don't
let this get you down.
I think this is the best thing,
as much as it breaks my heart.
Jenna, it has truly been great
having you here with us.
Please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you all very much.
- Good night, honey.
- Good night.
I'm going home, guys.
This has been the greatest
experience of my life,
and I'm just sorry
that it has to end here.
I just wish
I could've shown the world
what I can really do.
If I could get my hands fixed
and get back to where I was,
I'd give anything
for a second chance
in this competition.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.tvsubtitles.net