Previously on Face Off...
Eric F's two-headed giant
gave him the win.
Yeah, boy.
And Jenna was sent home.
Now, nine artists remain.
Tonight, things take on
a whole new proportion
with the creepiest
creatures yet.
There's just one little detail
that I left out.
No way!
The halves
are not going together.
Oh, shit!
Meagan can't leave
the wings alone.
It's, like,
whatever could go wrong
is going wrong.
This makes me want to die.
It's awful.
What were you thinking?
If you ran out of time
and it looks like hell,
don't put it on.
There's no excuse for it.
I'm not happy at all.
I want to cry.
I think you knocked this
out of the park.
I don't know what the heck
you were trying to do.
In the end, only one will win
the opportunity to be
a guest lecturer
Make Up For Ever's academies
in New York and Paris,
the all-new 2013
Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
It really sucks
that Jenna's not here anymore.
You know?
I'm kind of emotionally
drained, you know.
After the disaster
that happened
with Jenna and I last week,
I'm questioning everything.
So I need to regroup
and figure out
what I'm strong in
and have confidence again.
I wonder who's gonna be next?
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
I'd like you to meet
today's special guest judge.
She has an incredibly
varied portfolio,
having worked with stars like
Ashley Greene from Twilight
and the cast of Mad Men.
Please welcome
the Head Makeup Artist
for Make Up For Ever,
Lijha Stewart.
Hi, guys.
It's cool that Lijha's here,
but she probably wants to see
some beauty makeup.
Not my strong point.
With recent movies like
Snow White And The Huntsman,
Mirror Mirror, Red Riding Hood,
it seems that Hollywood
has become obsessed
with the classics.
But these aren't the stories
that you were told as a child.
Each one of them
has an iconic female character
that has been completely
reinvented.
That is the basis for
today's foundation challenge.
Reinventing an iconic
female storybook character.
Using the storybook character
makes it
a little more challenging
because I think most of us
are used to monsters
and grotesque creatures.
Why don't you tell
these guys exactly
what's at stake here today?
The winner of this challenge
will not only receive immunity,
but a very special prize
as well.
To tell you more about it,
here's a message
from the creator
and the Artistic Director of
Make Up For Ever, Dany Sanz.
_
- I'm very excited.
- Good luck.
I can't wait to see your
amazing creation.
I love Make Up For Ever.
Okay, that prize is worth
thousands of dollars.
- I'm going for this one.
- I want this.
As a makeup artist,
you're always
spending money on your kit.
Having this would be
amazing for any of us.
All right.
Let's bring out your models.
Each model is holding
a classic fairy tale
featuring
an iconic female character.
Wayne, you get to choose first.
Little Miss Muffet.
Belle from
Beauty And The Beast.
Little Red Riding Hood.
- Snow White.
- Hansel and Gretel.
- Cinderella.
- Sleeping Beauty.
- Rapunzel.
- Little Bo Peep.
There's just one little detail
that I left out.
Your challenge is to take
the classic good girls
and turn them into bad girls.
- Oh, yeah.
- Sweet.
So, Lijha, you have any
last-minute advice for these guys?
Try and find something
in the story
to help drive
your transformation.
All right,
Make Up For Ever has stocked
the lab with everything that
you could possibly need today.
You have two hours
to complete your challenge.
Good luck, guys,
because your time starts now.
- Whoo!
- Okay, go, get working.
All right.
Where's the red box
of pre-mades?
I actually run over and ravage
the generic prosthetics pile.
Move this under there
'cause it's about
to become a war zone.
My plan is to "Frankenstein"
the whole piece together.
She's gonna be a victim
of a werewolf attack
in mid transformation.
Okay, don't move.
I'm so excited.
Right away, I know
that I can make
my Belle character
into a badass.
I want to do
a lot of scratches,
some sun damage,
some really subtle things.
I get Rapunzel.
And on the shelf
I see Make Up For Ever's
white eyelashes.
They're very long,
they're white.
And that really sets
the basis for my makeup.
So, it's not
just about the hair,
but her face
will be a ghostly white.
I'm not going
to use prosthetics
in this one at all.
I'm going strictly beauty.
I'm going to make Gretel
a badass, yet beautiful.
_
All right.
My concept is Cinderella
had her skin burned off
because she's been working
the cinders,
and now it's all hard embers.
I go immediately
to the third-degree silicone
and begin building it up
on top of her skin.
I have Sleeping Beauty
and I'm gonna age her
because she's been sleeping
a hundred years.
I'm gonna do the forehead
and under the eyes.
I really want that immunity.
I don't know much
about Little Bo Peep,
and I just think
of a sweet girl.
My vision for this is create
the strong brow line
in a way that makes her look
a little more evil
and mysterious.
I picked Little Miss Muffet,
and I'm gonna make her
into a spider.
I made these out of propoxy,
and these are her fangs
that will come up
out of the face.
I find a nose piece
and I use the nostrils
as pieces
where the fangs come out of.
You got ten minutes left.
Her heart has turned to ice.
And now she searches the lands
for beating warm hearts
of princes.
Yeah, it's a little gross.
Five minutes, guys!
That's it.
Brushes down!
- Hi, Alam.
- Hi.
My story is prince
actually came
and he was disappointed
that she aged.
He left her,
and she's hunting him.
I definitely think
we could've blended
the prosthetics
a little bit better.
The under-eyes, especially.
The cheeks look good though.
I wish you would have done
a little more
on the beauty aspect
and a little more
on the body and the hands.
She basically has been
attacked by the wolf
and is in mid transformation.
I think you did
a really good job
creating a character
and a story,
and I could tell exactly
what it was.
- Yeah.
- For a two-hour makeup,
- I think you did pretty good.
- Thank you.
When the spider
was coming down,
he actually dropped venom
in her porridge.
Years later,
she actually transformed
into a spider from the venom.
I think she's beautifully evil.
I love the fangs.
It's a very impactful element.
I do wish she had a little bit
more eye makeup on.
I really would like
to win this one.
Not only do you win immunity,
you're gonna win, like,
a couple grand
worth of products,
which is crazy.
And it's
Make Up For Ever stuff,
which their products
are excellent.
For an artist, to have a kit
that's loaded like this is huge.
All right, Lijha.
Which looks
were your favorites?
Eric F,
I was so impressed
by the makeshift prosthetics
that you did
as well the overall character
that you were able to create.
Thank you so much.
And, Wayne,
I really was impressed
by the fangs that you did.
I wouldn't want to cross her
in a dark alleyway.
Thank you.
Okay, Lijha.
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner of
this challenge is...
Eric f.
Yes!
No way!
Ahh!
I'm really excited
not only with this immunity,
but I'm a broke artist
that can't afford
a nice makeup kit.
So this could definitely
help out my business.
Okay, guys.
I will see you tomorrow
for your next
spotlight challenge.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
I have no idea
what we have in store.
But I got immunity.
So I can get as crazy as I want
- and have no fear.
- Good job, Eric.
Eric!
- Oh. Oh, wow.
- What is that?
- Oh, yeah.
- What is this?
This looks cool.
Walking into the lab today,
McKenzie's actually
standing there
with a bunch of monitors.
Makeup effects artists
are constantly searching
for new sources of inspiration.
This creative spark can
come from almost anywhere,
including
these abstract photographs,
which will serve
as an inspiration
for this week's
spotlight challenge.
Now, before I tell you more,
you're each going to need
to choose one.
I'm nervous.
We have no idea
what these shapes
are going to mean to us
as far as our next challenge.
- Meagan, first pick.
- Ooh.
There's one image
that I really like.
It has, like, a peacock look.
A lot of colors,
and I love how it pops.
Alam.
I choose my picture
because it has
really fun textures
and lots of color.
It looks the sea anemone.
Now that you've each chosen
a photograph,
let's take a look
at what these really are.
Coming up...
All that's going
through my mind
is just finishing something.
They look crazy.
I'm standing on the edge
of disaster.
I absolutely loved this.
I don't know what the heck
you were trying to do.
Now that you've each chosen
a photograph,
let's take a look
at what these really are.
- Oh.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my--
The images you chose
where actually scanned electron
microscope photos of bugs.
So your spotlight challenge
this week
is to create an original
bug hybrid character
inspired by
your microscopic photos.
Now let's find out
what each of you chose.
Meagan, you chose
the sunset moth.
Oh, it's a moth.
Alam, you have grasshopper.
- Anthony, you picked an ant.
- Beginning of my name.
There you go.
Kris, you chose
the blue morpho butterfly.
House, you have the honeybee.
Wayne, you picked the firefly.
Autumn, you picked the beetle.
- Eric Z, you have a mosquito.
- Mosquito.
Eric F, you have
the desert wolf spider.
So, the judges
will be expecting
to see your microscopic photos
reflected in your makeups
this week.
So go ahead and get started.
We gotta start sketching.
The downfall of the butterfly
is that now I have to make
these giant set of wings
to watch the size
of the human head
that I'm going to be
working on.
I'm concerned that they'll
probably end up being heavy.
I picked a mosquito,
which is exciting to me.
They're scary in a way.
You know, they suck blood.
I don't think I'm gonna
be using these colors
throughout
this particular piece,
but I definitely want to
incorporate them somehow.
I decided to do a chest piece
and have the arms coming out
of the midsection of the torso,
but sort of curled up.
I chose this photo
because I love
all the different textures,
the colors.
There's a lot to play with.
But when it came up as a moth,
I'm a little apprehensive
because I've never made wings.
I'm basically sticking with
the actual image of the moth.
So I was thinking
of polyfoam for this part,
and then just
one simple face piece.
I'm actually scared that
it may look like
a butterfly in the end.
I read a description
on how hairy a moth is.
That's definitely gonna be
something incorporated.
In the five hours
that I have today,
I definitely need to nail
the face sculpture
and get that molded out.
That's priority.
My concept is a scientist
and his DNA mixes
with the honeybee.
So, kind of half face infected
- with the bubbling of the disease.
- Yeah.
- Half face more of a bee style.
And then bursting out
of his back
is the formation
of the bee body.
- Right, that's really cool.
- You think?
Oh, yeah. I love it.
I have the firefly.
If you look at a firefly,
the eyes are really large.
And the head is almost
1/3 of the entire body.
And probably one of the most
important things about it
is having
this glowing abdomen area.
And that's something
that I'll have to figure out.
I'm gonna make this have
a silhouette of a firefly,
but when you get closer,
you're gonna see human elements
really come to life.
That's so freaking cool.
I love all that right there
underneath the nose.
And then those
big feelers come out.
And then the fly sucker
will come through
his, like, throat
and then come up.
- I love it.
- Thanks, man.
Even though I had last pick,
I'm actually very, very happy.
I've always really wanted to do
a cool spider hybrid creature.
So I'm taking a female,
and I'm having spider appendages
busting through certain areas.
Gonna really twist up
the human form.
I'm gonna do the fabrication
with PVC pipe, and, like,
a latex and foam skin.
What's wrong?
Hmm?
I'm thinking.
My bug is a grasshopper.
And I used to catch them
when I was a child,
and like, fry them
and eat them.
It sounds weird, but yeah.
It's kind of good.
It's crunchy.
I've never seen the grasshopper
this colorful.
It has a lot of color
that I can play with.
So I'm just really focusing
on making the texture
because that's the most
important part
of this challenge.
I think I'm going to do the silicone.
You are?
Why, for the translucency
and stuff?
_
Thank God I didn't get
a flipping butterfly.
I get a cool-ass beetle bug.
I'm gonna cover her face
in mandibles
and have the eyes on top
of the head
to make sure I get
the right profile.
I love the colors.
You know, with the green
palette, I really like it.
Maybe bring some Japanese
beetle purple hues
into it if I can.
It's really cool,
kind of gross little monster.
So hopefully, I can do something
a little bit gnarly.
I'm gonna have a lot of fun
with this one.
Does that book have any ants
in it, do you know?
Mine is the ant.
I have probably the simplest one
up there.
It's already very minimal,
that there's not much to add
to give it any oomph.
It's probably gonna be
a lot of pieces.
Back, chest, the head, the face,
the big abdomen, arms.
I just find myself adding clay
and ripping it off,
and then going to the head
and adding clay,
ripping that off.
And nothing is really
coming together.
For the first time
in this competition,
I can't see what this
is gonna look like at the end,
and that I think scares me
more than anything.
I already know,
two days from now,
I will be on the bottom.
My sculpt is * a
great exciting start.
I start sculpting my
thorax section
which is basically a
female butt*
that is kinda morphed
into a... you know,
- a spider butt.
- Eric!
What?
- It's a thorax!
- *.
It's a little bizarre, but
since I do have immunity,
I figured I can kinda
go out on a limb.
So, just to create
an insect human hybrid
in less than 20 hours
over the course
of 3 days is a huge task.
But it seems like everybody is
already off to a better start.
Very cool.
I know I don't have
any more time
to conceptualize.
I still feel lost.
And all that's going
through my mind
is just finishing something.
I like this, but I love this.
Don't shoot yourself
in the foot.
That's what I'm thinking.
I'm really hoping
I can get it molded
and ready for foam
before the night is over.
40 minutes left.
- 40?
- 40.
It's getting really crazy
in the mold room.
Everyone's rushing and trying
to get their piece out.
I get the face molded.
Done.
Plenty more to do on day two.
This is a big challenge
for all of us.
Time!
- Let's get out of here.
- Let's go, guys.
This is a really huge makeup.
I still have to make
the chest and back piece
with a cowl, wings, an abdomen
that glows, feet, and arms.
Tomorrow, it's gonna be crazy.
Let's go!
Day two in the lab,
I need to open my mold,
clean it out,
create my chest piece
and back piece
as well as an abdomen
and mandible.
It's just a lot of pieces
that have to be created.
Hey, guys.
Michael Westmore
and McKenzie come in.
And I'm definitely gonna
take advantage
of any suggestions he gives
because I'm still a little bit
knocked down
from the last challenge.
So, tell us about your moth.
I have the face piece,
and then I have some hair done.
And that's gonna be
incorporated in the chest piece.
Now, what about your paint job?
I'm gonna try to stick
with these colors.
Once you put the fur on though,
- it's all one color.
- Yeah, I'm spraying it brown.
You might even neutralize it
painting it either
a light yellow
or a white or something
on it first,
and then painting
your color over.
Because I know if you try
painting blue or green
or something over
the top of this,
you're not gonna get true color
out of it.
Okay.
What do you have in mind now?
I was trying to put
this texture
as much as I can
in the character.
Mm-hmm.
Colors in the costume?
These are all my colors.
It's gonna be really colorful.
It's very pretty,
but don't complicate your life
with too many colors.
Michael Westmore is worried
about my colors,
but I think I'm gonna
go with it.
It's gonna be more like
a humanoid type firefly.
But from a distance,
all you see
is a silhouette of a firefly.
So, the way
I'm gonna incorporate
the texture from the photo,
I'm gonna make them
come out of here
and then whip up.
You've got a lot to do,
you know, to stay on track.
Yeah, I'll pull it off.
- I have the ant.
- How are you doing with this?
- I'm struggling a little bit.
- Why?
Not a lot of interesting
things going on in the face.
So I'm really trying to just
really work on the profile,
so the silhouette
is very strong.
I'm glad to see you're making
the head larger, you know,
because when the individual
comes out
in front of the judges,
- they have to know what it is.
- Right.
After winning
the first three challenges,
I feel like I'm under
a microscope,
and that freaks me out
more than anything.
All right, guys.
We're heading out.
- But it's looking good.
- Thank you.
- See you guys.
- Good luck.
How am I gonna make
these giant set of wings
and how am I gonna attach it
to my model?
I'm concerned that
they'll end up being heavy.
So I'm going to use a foam core
because it's a lot lighter.
Kris, do you want to see
what I'm doing?
Just because our characters
are so similar,
I want to do something
totally different.
Mine are-- are yours--
I'm doing four.
You're doing four?
I'm just connecting them
in one half.
So that's just makes it simple.
So instead
of making one big wing
like Kris is doing,
I'm gonna do
two separate things.
And I also textured my wings
with actual hair,
because you read about them,
it's just hair.
I'm doing all of my pieces
with silicone
because I can color them
when I pour it.
So it looks more translucent
and still has the colors in it.
My silicone looks amazing,
but it's really scary
that I have a lot to do
on application day.
Time's up, everybody!
I have to make the body
of the grasshopper
and the wings and the legs.
And I don't know
how it's gonna work.
Today's application day.
We have four hours in the lab
and one hour at the stage
for last looks.
- How's it going, man?
- Hello.
Gonna be the bug man.
You'll have, like, a third leg
kind of growing out.
Here's what it's pretty much
gonna be like.
Something like that.
My first goal is to finish
those wings off.
I can do that
within maybe a half-hour.
Cool.
Next step
is pre-painting those pieces.
I feel pretty confident
I'm gonna get everything done.
Everybody else has
all these pieces
already ran in foam.
I still have to run my chest
and back in polyfoam.
As I'm putting the polyfoam in
and trying to close the mold,
the halves are not going
together properly.
I sit on this thing
and finally it clamps together.
All I can do is wait 45 minutes
and hope I have a piece
that is actually usable.
I'm running out of time,
so I'm just gonna make
the wings.
And I still have to incorporate
the texture from the photo.
So I take some dense foam,
and then I'm gonna make it
look like just like
the texture.
And then I'm sticking them
on the back
where they'll be coming out
of the spine.
- Snug as a bug.
- Yeah.
I'm not
necessarily sitting pretty.
And no one really is
at this point.
I see Meagan's piece.
Meagan can't leave
the wings alone.
I keep painting these wings,
and it's tough.
I don't know where I should stop
with the paint.
Finally I'm to a point
where I can open those molds.
There's at least something here
I can work with.
But all I can do now
is glue those on at last looks.
- Turn this way, please.
- What's the time?
6 and a half minutes.
- Coming up behind you.
- You're following me.
Oh, shit!
I'm just nervous
because they look crazy.
There's, like,
a hundred colors on them.
They don't look like wings.
I went overboard
with the paint.
It's time!
I'm standing on the edge
of disaster.
Coming up...
Whatever could go wrong
is going wrong.
This is the worst feeling
in the world.
If you run out of time
and it looks like hell,
don't put it on.
I think you did
a beautiful job.
- Whoa.
- We get to last looks.
And I realize
I forgot the elements
from the photo at the shop.
So, at this point
I'm freaking out.
It's, like,
whatever could go wrong
is going wrong.
This is the worst feeling
in the world.
I still have to apply
literally everything.
And I'm really stressed.
30 minutes left!
I'm always,
always running out of time.
I still have to put
the facial prosthetic on,
and color the body.
And her bald cap
is tearing off.
That's not good.
I need to get
those wings going.
Go all the way in.
I'm in a hurry,
and I don't love the wings.
Your palms are supposed
to be on it.
At this point,
everything's going downhill.
- It's time, everybody!
- Love it.
My character looks like hell.
I'm not happy at all.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you will be
eliminated.
Say hello to your judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio,
- Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
- Hello.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist
- Ve Neill.
- Hi, everybody.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
- Hi, guys.
- Hi.
This week,
your spotlight challenge was
to create a bug creature
or a character
incorporating
details and textures
seen only under a microscope.
So, let's see
what you've come up with.
It's nice, but it's not
extraordinary.
And I think in this stage
of the game,
if you're not doing
something extraordinary,
you may wind up going home.
I'm pretty terrified,
because to me,
it still feels unfinished.
I like it.
It's not as bad as I thought.
But I'm worrying
about the edges.
I'm worried now.
My makeup is more of a mask,
which is something
that I told myself
I wasn't going to do.
It still is not something
I'm proud of.
But it is recognizable
as an ant.
Mine stands out
just for the sheer size
of the wings.
But I really don't know
where I stand.
I'm really happy
with this makeup.
And if this is the makeup
that sends me home,
so be it.
I think she's beautiful.
She's got the provocative,
but I think very classy
old-school pinup style.
This might be something
the judges can appreciate.
I want to cry.
She looks like Chewbacca
and the moth made a baby.
I'm ready to go home.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look?
Would you look at this hand?
I don't understand the texture.
Hmm.
Great attention to detail.
Look how he lit up the tail.
It's really clever.
From the inside.
Open your mouth, please.
I like the way the thing works
when he just wiggles his chin.
- Mm-hmm.
- It's cool.
- Oh, silicone.
- Why?
- Can you turn around?
- Turn back around.
Those are wings, I'm assuming.
Makes me want to die.
It's awful.
The back is just wretched.
I'm worried because
I didn't finish my makeup.
I just want to be safe.
We want to know what you think
of tonight's transformations.
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
- Oh, silicone.
- It's awful.
- Can you turn around?
- My goodness.
This is...
makes me wanna die.
I'm worried because
I didn't finish my makeup.
I just want to be safe.
I like that this is rough,
and I like all
of these wrinkles.
There's a lot going on.
This shape complimenting
that shape
is just absolutely beautiful.
The shapes align.
Oh, my God.
Just look this Teenage
Mutant Ninja Turtle texture.
- It's just ridiculous.
- He's shaking his hand.
That's cool.
Very action figure.
It's a different approach.
It's stylized.
- It's a great shape.
- Yeah.
There's some neat things
happening sculpturally too.
_
- This looks like pop art.
- Woof.
Right now I'm on the bottom.
So, at this point, all I can do
is just admit how bad it looks.
The judges have scored
your creations.
Let's find out
what they thought.
Meagan...
Kris...
Alam...
Wayne...
Anthony...
You were the best
and the worst this week.
The rest of you are safe and can
head back to the makeup room.
The judges would like to speak
with each of you now
to learn more about your work.
Meagan.
Tell us about your decisions
and what drove your design
this week, please.
I chose a moth.
And for inspiration,
I read about moths and how much
hair they had.
So I think I went a little
too crazy with the hair, but--
- I've studied insects,
and I don't think
you were that far off
with the amount of fur.
Really, it's the colors
that are killing this.
Quite honestly, it looks
like you lobbed paint at it
from across the room.
It's a hodgepodge
of different colors
smashed into whatever the wings
are made out of.
Very disappointed.
You've done better.
Looking at the picture
of the moth,
I see the blue,
and I see the orange in there.
But other than the fact
that you used
those two colors
and quite poorly,
you really didn't
follow any design.
Meagan, please step back.
Kris.
What was your inspiration
from the photo?
For the microscopic picture
is all the top of the head.
But the reference books that we
had never really got close up
to a butterfly's chest,
so I made it up.
I think you did a beautiful
job of making it up.
The colors in the chest piece
are also the colors
that were in
that microscopic photograph,
which is a really good choice.
And I just think aesthetically,
it's very pleasing to look at.
I really appreciate that.
I absolutely loved this.
I think that the head
is a super cool shape.
The sculpture on the chest,
I love that it's not
the exact anatomy.
It's putting yourself
as an artist into the makeup.
- So, great job.
- Thank you so much.
Kris, please step back.
Alam.
Yeah.
Tell us about the inspiration
for color and texture.
I didn't know grasshopper
can be, you know, very colorful.
But the picture
has orange and yellow
and black and purple.
So I wanted to use
all those colors.
There's just
a whole bunch of stuff
that destroy this design.
The thing that's tied together
on her back--
they are not wings.
I just ran out of time.
If you run out of time,
and it looks like hell,
don't put it on.
When you go, "I want to put
a lot of color in something,"
you have to figure out
how those colors
are going to flow
from one to the other.
By the way,
why is that silicone?
Um...
Right.
That's a problem.
If you're going
to use silicone,
you must retain
the translucency of it.
That's the point to silicone.
The piece on the back,
unfortunately
you didn't paint
the inside of the piece.
I don't know what the heck
you were trying to do.
I mean, it's just kind of
a mish-mosh this week, honey.
Alam, thank you.
Please step back.
Wayne, you're up.
Begin by explaining
what your design was.
- It's a firefly.
- Mm-hmm.
But I wanted to have
this nice silhouette
to where you can see
the big eyes
and the very long
fly-like wings,
and then have
the vacuum-formed plastic
in the back with the light.
I think you knocked this out
of the park.
The fact that his mouth movement
is so integrated
into the makeup
that it facilitates
this cool move,
that's incredible.
And the way that you hid
the eyes
by putting them in plain sight
is ingenious.
Thank you.
The profile of his sternum
in particular
just gives him so much character
in the silhouette.
It was a really beautiful thing
that you did.
I like the color scheme.
It's very neutral.
And then you have this beautiful
green, glowing tail.
Can you tell me where you
integrated the photo?
There's no excuse for it.
But I forgot the pieces
at the shop.
- Oh.
- Oh, too bad.
Wayne, please step back.
Good job.
Anthony.
So, tell me about
your creation.
He's an army ant.
Based on the texture
that was in the picture,
I put a little bit of the
texture in the top of the head
and a little in the back.
It just doesn't look
like an ant to me
for some reason.
Do you have the antennae made
out of something
other than those foam tubes?
I had intended to.
But just to get something
up here, I did this.
There are so many things
about this
that are really bizarre to me.
Having this sash knit-sweater
thing underneath plates.
And then this tacked-on
turtle shell thing on the back.
It's really bizarre.
I'm not happy with the paint.
I'm not happy
with the sculpture.
with your overall design.
Nothing's working
on this one for me.
I agree.
You shouldn't have been
so good at the beginning,
'cause now we were waiting for
you to do something fantastic
- every single time.
- On the next one.
If there's a next one.
Anthony, please step back.
It's rough.
The judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they make
their decisions.
All right, guys,
let's talk about the looks
you liked the most tonight.
Why don't we start with Kris?
The sculpture on the chest
and the head is so beautiful.
The proportions are great.
When you don't have a ton
of reference around you,
to just come up
with all those shapes,
that says a lot
about his skill.
The paint job was very pretty.
And the colors
were really gorgeous.
Let's move on to Wayne.
Wayne's firefly
is absolutely amazing.
The way the little tail
lights up
and that whole silhouette
with that big sweeping
back end.
He spent his time
in all the right places.
The head is
very well proportioned
to the rest of the body.
The genius, dare I say,
of putting the antennae
on his cheekbones,
knowing that those
are going to be things
that the actor's going to drive
and animate.
Well, we do have a problem
'cause unfortunately,
he did not incorporate
that close up
and did not complete
the challenge.
Let's move on to
the bottom looks this week.
Let's start with Meagan.
She is trying to take
the notes into the account.
She's still not at the level
where she needs to be,
and which is why
she is in the bottom.
I don't know
that I can conjure an image
of any makeup where
the paint is done
quite that badly.
It looks psychedelic vomit.
Let's move on to Alam.
The pink, plastic wings
with a bunched-up thing
at the top.
If you're gonna do wings,
make sure you understand
- how they at least work.
- Right.
And the punctuation
of her makeup
in terms of these bad choices
- was glitter flip-flops.
- Glitter flip-flops.
- Leaves, crystal-- what?
- What the heck?
And she can't even describe
what it is she's doing.
Let's move on to Anthony.
It's the worst that he's done.
The chest for what it was
should have been fabricated
because he got nothing out
of all the time
that he spent sculpting it.
I'm confused about his
decision-making on this one.
To throw in those antennae--
- Oh, dear God.
- Oh, yeah.
He could have glued on a sock
and it would have
had the same effect.
It was so disappointing.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- Yeah, I believe we have.
- Yep.
Let's bring them back out then.
Glenn, tell us about
the top looks.
Kris, you had some really
great shapes
in your design.
And it was one of the few
that we thought looked great
close up and far away.
And, Wayne, really loved
the chest sculpture.
And you did some really
clever work
with the articulation
of the face.
So, who is the winner
of this challenge?
Actually, we have a situation
which has never before
occurred.
So, who is the winner
of this challenge?
Actually, we have a situation
which has never before
occurred.
Wayne, your makeup was amazing
and it would have been
our winner,
but you didn't include
your microscopic image.
So that means, Kris,
you are the winner
of this challenge.
You created
a great cohesive makeup.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you so much.
Wayne really won
this competition,
but he forgot one element.
It did fall in my lap.
I'm cool with that.
- Kris, congratulations.
- Thank you.
You and Wayne can head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Unfortunately,
that means the rest of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Meagan.
The textual divide
between the body and the wings
combined with a very bad
paint job
resulted in
an overall confused makeup.
Anthony, it was clear
that you struggled
with your concept.
And a few pieces
of the makeup felt
as though they were
sort of tacked on.
Alam, your makeup was littered
with very strange
design choices.
And you have to learn
how to make better decisions
regarding your time management.
So, who is going home tonight?
The person
going home tonight is...
Alam.
Oh, my God.
Not only did we not understand
some of your choices,
but you didn't either.
And that's a huge problem.
Alam, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
That means, Anthony, Meagan,
you are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Alam, you have a memorable
and very distinct vision.
And that's a good thing.
- We'll miss you.
- Thank you.
Alam, it has been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you, guys.
- Good luck.
- Good-bye, Alam.
- It's really sad.
But I made it through
six challenges.
- It's crazy.
- Oh, my God.
I've learned a lot.
I've changed a lot.
I'll open the wine.
I'm glad that I started
my career here.
I'm gonna practice and practice
and I'm never gonna give up.
I love this.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.tvsubtitles.net