RuPaul: Previously
on All Stars...
This season, each of you
will vote for the bottom queen
you think deserves the chop.
Everybody gets a vote?
Everybody?
You're two-faced, and I don't
fuck with two-faced people.
There's only one person
I don't get along with,
-and it's India Ferrah.
-[sighs]
RuPaul: Welcome to
the Werq The World extravaganza!
India Ferrah.
I have one word for you:
hairography.
-Yes.
Ahh. That was explosive, baby.
RuPaul: Derrick Barry.
Cher. You called me
after Madonna?
Fuck you.
The impersonations
were not great.
RuPaul: Mayhem Miller.
I was so excited
about where it was gonna go,
and then when it went there,
I thought, "Oh,
can we go back
to where we were?"
RuPaul: Ongina.
It kind of didn't go anywhere.
Carson: It stalled a little bit.
I wish I could have done better.
I've been in my head
all fucking week.
But, like, an All Star
believes in themselves.
I literally did not.
Ferrah, con-drag-ulations.
You are the top All Star
of the week.
[applause]
You will lip sync against
a secret lip sync assassin.
[cheers and applause]
Yay!
Yvie Oddly, con-drag-ulations.
You're the winner, baby.
The $10.000
will roll over
to next week's tip.
Oh, my God.
Yvie holds the lipstick
of the queen that the group
has voted to get the chop.
Derrick Barry.
Derrick, sashay away.new act?
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, Miss Thing, that was insane.
Bitch, no. I can't.
Bitch, you gonna get those off?
You deserve to rest your digits.
I am so gagged.
The first time
I won a challenge,
you bring out Yvie?
Ru had got me.
That's a huge deal
to have Yvie Oddly
as the first lip sync assassin.
But you know what?
If I have to lose to anyone,
at least
it was to that bitch.
The lip sync assassin situation.
Can we talk about Yvie Oddly?
When that screen rose up...
That really changes
everything now.
-It does.
-Everything.
You were the first winner
and the pressure of getting
that $10.000 tip--
Bitch, I wanted it so bad.
Ooh, that would have
a lot of nice things.
I tried. I tried.
-You did an amazing job.
-Thank you.
But I can't say that I'm mad
at it going into
the escrow account.
-I can't either.
-I'm not mad either.
'Cause I can't wait
till next week.
-Oh!
-Ooh!
-Yes!
She's, like,
I'm in the game now.
Do you know
how many things I can get
for $20.000?
Hold on. If I put $20.000
in an IRA Roth,
do you know
how much money that is?
$20.000 in an IRA Roth.
You guys,
it was the scariest feeling.
I know.
I flubbed this one
because of my nerves.
Like, I'm ready
to kick your asses.
[all laugh]
-Bring it, bitch.
-Bring it.
Mayhem, how do you feel?
-I'm here.
-Yeah.
Y'all love me.
You really love me.
Yeah, you're here
by our vote.
You all each got a vote, but--
Yeah, 'cause we--
okay, look.
When it went to Yvie,
I was, like, okay,
this is gonna be a true test
of my friendships right now.
[all laugh]
But you know what?
Honestly,
with a clear conscience,
I voted for you
to continue on with the show.
I know that you have
so much more to offer.
I just didn't think
that Derrick had as much range
to continue on with the show.
Did anyone vote
for Mayhem to go home?
I voted for you to go home.
-Are you serious?
-Yes, I am.
-You're joking, right?
-I am not joking.
Oh, so you...
Oh, so...
For real?
I've known Juju forever.
Worked with her,
been friends with her.
So I am gagged.
Gagged.
You've known me for years,
so you know my range of talent
and what I'm capable of.
And I would have thought
that you have been, like,
you know, I do know Mayhem
and I know she has the potential
to stay here and do well.
If we want
to decipher the performances,
I liked your performance.
I just...I laughed more
at Derrick's.
It's not personal, girl.
No, that's personal. [laughs]
That sounds completely personal.
I think she said
it's not personal,
and I think
she gave a reason why.
I don't think it is.
-It's cool.
-But it didn't affect you.
It's cool.
No, it didn't,
because obviously
everyone else saw
what it should have been.
Your feelings are very valid,
you know,
and I acknowledge that.
And if--
That's not a real apology.
I'm sorry that I hurt you.
We're all predators,
and the crown is the prey.
And somebody's feelings
gonna get hurt.
They're gonna
take it personally.
But I am hungry for this crown.
I'm here to slay and filet
and slice and dice
these bitches.
Ooh, I'm gonna eat you up, ho's.
I'm gonna eat you ho's up.
[slurps]
RuPaul: The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race All Stars
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics
a coveted spot
in the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize of $100.000.
With extra-special guest judges
Madison Beer
and Tessa Thompson.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪end act
She's a super queen.
Girl, yes.
-Yes.
-Another day, another dollar.
Oh, yesterday
was such a long day.
Oh! My legs.
-Oh.
-Uh.
"Show up and show out.
"Heart, Derrick Barry.
I love you, Jujubee."
-I love you, too.
-Aw, look at that.
That was a nice way of saying
I'm not saying goodbye
to India, okay?
[all laugh]
Derrick's message, it was short,
I don't think it was that sweet,
and I just want
to get it off the mirror.
I just want to spray it,
wipe it away,
get it out of here.
Girls, you all got a vote.
How does that feel?
Yeah, for the first time ever.
[sighs] I was up all night
because my decision...
I don't know
if I did the right thing.
Do you think you voted
for the wrong person?
I feel I should have
brought in some Wite-Out.
Because Ongina...
Derrick, and Mayhem,
they believed
that they could do it.
And you didn't believe
in yourself.
And that's an All Star thing.
Uh, where did that come from?
Cracker wants to put my name
on the lipstick with Wite-Out?
Okay, first of all,
you're not BenDeLaCreme
and you wish you were.
And second, you're not a judge,
so slow your roll.
And third, like,
there's no third
because just
shut the fuck up already.
You are an All Star and you
have to believe in yourself,
and that's something
you can switch right now.
I do believe in myself.
I think everyone's
looking at that from you.
I do get that All Stars
is another type of game,
but are we playing
mental warfare here?
I don't know if Miz Cracker's
trying to get in
to Miss Ongina's head,
but that seems
a little shady to me.
I literally was up all night.
I was, like,
should I have done that?
So now--help me sleep.
Go to bed.
[all laugh]
[alarm]
-Ooh, girl.
-Here we go.
She done already
done had herses.
Dear diary, I've got a crush.
[giggles]
He's rich, famous,
and he has
one big huge...
heart.
So should I slide
into his DMs
or just...
slip him the tongue?
Wait a minute.
I have an idea.
I'm gonna write a song.
[laughs]
Hello, hello, hello.
[cheers and applause]
-Yes.
-Mother.
Good morning, All Stars.
-Good morning.
For this week's maxi-challenge,
you'll be debuting
the newest All Stars smash hit:
I'm In Love.
-Ooh.
-Yes.
Working in groups,
each of you
will write and record
your own love sickening verse
to the celebrity man crush
of your choice.
Then you'll create a group look
and choreography.
#AllStars5.
You wanna know
who my celebrity crush is?
-Yes.
Ed O'Neill when he was on
Married With Children.
-Oh, my God.
[laughs] Yes.
There. I said it.
Now, India Ferrah.
As last week's top All Star,
I'm gonna put you on the spot.
Okay.
Who are your
two biggest competitors?
Ooh.
Ho-ho-ho.
Shea...
and...
Blair.
Shea I understand, but Blair?
Oh!
Okay.
India, Shea,
and Blair St. Clair,
you are this week's
team captains.
[all laugh]
Oh, my God.
I fucked the whole thing up.
Now, as captains,
you get to choose
your own group members.
Starting with India,
who do you choose first?
Jujubee.
Oh.
Come on up here.
Blair, you're next.
I'm gonna go with Cracker.
Mariah.
My Season 3 sister Alexis Mateo.
Mayhem Coors Light,
come on over, girl.
That means
you're stuck with me, Shea.
[laugh] You all think
that you're picking me last,
but this is working out
to my favor
because I get to be on a team
with Mariah and Shea.
Yay.
All Stars, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
Come on. Let's do this.
-Who's your celebrity crush?
-John Stamos.
-Oh, from Full House.
-Uncle Jesse.
I want my house filled.
Filled. [laughs]
Cool.
And who is yours?
My celebrity crush
is Daddy Yankee.
Oh, yeah, I see that.
Daddy Yankee has it.
The way that he just stand there
and grab the microphone,
baby, grab me like that.
What I had was,
'cause mine
was gonna be, like,
♪ I'm in love with my fiance ♪
♪ His name is RJ,
and nothing can take him away ♪
India, you ain't dating
no celebrity.
We all know that.
You are in love with RJ.
Yeah.
But India is a character
on All Stars.
Yes.
-I know you miss this man.
-Right.
But, like, girl,
you are so hilarious.
No.
You are, though.
You gotta believe in yourself.
-You're just saying that.
-Ju's right.
So I would dig into that
and be, like, super campy.
Okay.
I know India
is an amazing entertainer.
She can lip sync,
do a great drag show,
and she ain't afraid
of cosmetics.
But this one
is a girl group challenge,
and when she's surrounded
by other girls,
personalities overshine.
I want my celebrity crush
to be silly.
So who are you gonna choose?
I have Hannibal Lecter
written down.
Blair, coming from you,
that's, like, so crazy.
I know.
[silent stammer]
This bitch
is into eating people,
and she's that skinny?
What about you?
I'm thinking Mr. Rogers.
I love that.
I really believe in us
as a team.
Obviously, I think
I know the two of you the best
out of all the competitors
right here in the competition.
And I think that the three of us
already have
a great working relationship.
I absolutely agree.
However,
we have to turn it out.
I've competed with Cracker
before.
Something happened
with a pickle.
-There you go.
-[whimpers]
It just was overshadowed
by Dr. Dill.
Mayhem, sashay away.
I'm not taking no chances
with Cracker this time around.
I gotta make sure
that I do my job and shine.
The sweater's warm and fuzzy.
Um, okay.
♪ Oh, that sweater's so cozy
when it's pouring rain ♪
Uh...
Come to my neighborhood and I
could ride your trolley train.
I ain't saying
that I'm a songwriter,
but I do know how
to make stuff rhyme.
But somebody--hmm--
wants it her way.
[sighs] You guys seen
Shakespeare In Love?
'Cause I'm, like,
really good at writing.
I'm so good at writing.
[laughs]
Okay.
It's not the Cracker show.
What do you think
the other girls are doing?
See, I feel like Blair
is gonna have a lot on her hands
with such strong personalities
like Cracker.subtitle
I'm still thinking about
what happened this morning.
with Cracker and the Wite-Out.
I felt like to her,
I'm not good enough to be here.
But I'm goddamn good enough
to be here.
I just was in my head.
You know what I mean?
-Which happen to the best of us.
-All of us.
If this is the game
Cracker wants to play,
then so be it.
But shadiness
does not make a winner.
Or--wait.
Does not a winner make, right?
Okay.SUBTITLE
-Well, I want you to be here.
-Thank you.
And I think
you deserve to be here.
[laughs]
Let's go make some magic.
-Yay.
-Good luck, ladies.
-Thanks.
Good luck, Blair.
Good luck, Mayhem.
I caught what you were
throwing over there, Miss Ma'am.
Oh, did I miss someone?
[laughs]
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Welcome.
-Hi. How are you guys?
It's time to record our
I'm In Love girl group lyrics.
I feel like there's
so much weight on my shoulders
to really deliver well.
Because everyone knows
that I'm a singer
and that I know
how to record music.
My name's Leland,
this is Freddy.
We put together
this song for you,
and we can't wait
to see what you do with it.
All right, team captain.
Blair, you ready?
Who did you pick?
I picked Hannibal Lecter.
So this is not gonna be
the Katy Perry Teenage Dream
verse of the song?
-Probably not.
-Here we go.
♪ He'll look at me
with hunger in his eyes ♪
♪ I'm the whole damn smack,
just serve my-- ♪
Err.
We're pitchy.
Did I hear that right?
Don't she do music?
Why don't we do
some, like deep, breathing.
Let's all do some
breathing exercises together.
-[inhales]
-'Cause I wanna enjoy this.
-Through your diaphragm.
-This is fun for me.
This is what I love doing.
Well, you gotta breathe.
Let's breathe.
Let's breathe together.
I feel like for me,
specifically for me as a person,
like, I get in my head
and I freak myself out
and I know I can do it.
Less talking, more breathing.
Here we go.
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
Relax.
Blair is nervous boots.
Pinocchio's wooden joints
are shaking.
Give me, like,
if Hannibal Lecter
walked into
Beauty and the Beast.
♪ He'll look at me
with hunger in his eyes ♪
♪ And I'll take my pie
to the first place prize ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm in love ♪
-There. That's all we needed.
-Yeah.
Much better.
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love ♪
♪ I'm in love
with Sylvester Stallone ♪
♪ He played a boxer, so he moves
around the ring just fine ♪
♪ When things get Rocky ♪
♪ I'm, like,
please release that Rocky IX ♪
And Cracker has arrived.
This is your Broadway moment.
Sylvester Stallone.
Who's your crush?
My crush is Mr. Rogers.
-Famed sex icon.
-Sexy as hell.
All right. Well,
let's go ahead and go for it.
I'm excited to hear your verse.
All right.
♪ Well, those sweaters
look so warm and fuzzy ♪
♪ Be my puppet, babe ♪
Aw, shit.
I fucked it up.subtitle
Let's grab it again.
♪ Be your puppet, babe,
forget about the Muppets ♪
Oh. ♪ Duh-duh-duh, blah blah ♪
I think the opening
is way better,
so let's just bring it up.
It also made sense.
"Be your puppet."
-Yeah.
-That was great.
Here come Cracker again,
piping up about something.
Why she talking so much?
You... [sighs]
Bitch, it's my turn.
♪ Do, re, mi, fa, sol,
la, ti, do ♪
Oh, shit.
All those letters.
Or you can say
whatever you want.
♪ Do, re, mi,
fa, so, latte ♪
♪ Venti, coffee ♪
I love it. That sounds great.
Let's get started.
♪ Daddy Yankee,
he's my man, he's my papi ♪
♪ When he sings reggaeton,
he makes me really happy ♪
♪ Every time I see him,
I get sassy ♪
♪ Got me nervous
and really gassy ♪
[laughs]
Yes.
[applause]
Ooh, Alexis.
This sounds so good.
If Daddy Yankee
doesn't call Alexis,
Daddy Yankee, you crazy.
Tell me about your love
for John Stamos.
Oh, my. Well,
who doesn't love John Stamos?
Right. America
loves John Stamos.
The world.
John Stamos.
[inhales] Oh...
Greek yogurt.
♪ He's Uncle Jesse,
and I need him, need him ♪
♪ Taking off my blouse ♪
♪ Please fill up my house,
'cause... ♪
Great.
♪ Justin Timberlake ♪
♪ He's bringing sexy back ♪
♪ I sent that Britney back ♪
♪ 'Cause I felt very attacked ♪
The first two lines are good,
but I'm a little bored.
Give me more.
♪ He's bringing sexy back ♪
♪ I follow in his tracks ♪
Hills and valleys.
Give me moments.
♪ He's bringing sexy back ♪
♪ I follow in his tracks ♪
I'm worried,
because India's energy
has to match
me and Jujubee's energy.
One girl in our group
fuck up,
we gonna have to go solo.
♪ Chadwick Boseman ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, girl, he's my boo ♪
♪ The mother-tucking Black
Panther, what you gonna do? ♪
♪ He's the king
and I'm the queen ♪
♪ I'm dreaming about
what kind of life we'll lead ♪
[applause]
That was so great.
But were you surprised?
[laughs]
♪ I'm in love,
I'm in love with-- ♪
Oh, my God,
it didn't even come out. Sorry.
It sounds like you're
going through something vocally.
Tell me what's going on.
I don't know what it is,
but I lost my voice
over the last week.
This is, like,
the worst thing for me
because I'm so not a singer
and then this has to be the day
that I, like, sing.
It's okay. It doesn't matter
if you're a singer or not.
It's all about your delivery.
Let's grab it again.
-Ahh-ahh. Okay, ready.
-Here we go.
♪ Henry Cavill,
he's my superhero man ♪
♪ And-- ♪
Why don't you give me
some pblblblblbl?
Pblblblblbl.
[voice breaks]
♪ Henry Cavill, Henry Cavill ♪
Pblblblblbl.
Uh...uh...pblblbl.
♪ Henry Cavill ♪
Does that need to be faster?
Yeah, I'm not sure
the rhythm of your verse.
From the Henry Cavill,
it goes right into
the ♪ Henry Cavill ♪
♪ He is my Superman ♪
There shouldn't be
too much of it.
Okay. Okay, I got it.
♪ Henry Cavil,
he's my Superman ♪
♪ We flyin', flyin' ♪
♪ And when we touch down ♪
♪ I'll be ridin', ridin' ♪
Girl, what was that?
I was, like, is she doing
the Finding Dory whale call?
Whoooooah.
I was, like, bitch, oh, no.
♪ I'm in love with Jason Momoa ♪
♪ Yes, I'm that bitch,
yes, I'm-- ♪
Uh!
Let's grab it again.
♪ Yes, I'm that bitch,
Yes, I'm his-- ♪
Uh!
♪ I'm in love with Jason Momoa ♪
♪ He is my Superman ♪
Uh!
Uh, Jason Momoa
I think played Aquaman.
Oh, shit.
I am looking
at both of my teammates
and how they've done so far,
and all I can think is, Shea,
you in danger, girl.
Ooh, main stage.
Yes.
Girl, it's time to rehearse
for our I'm In Love
girl group challenge.
Y'all go ahead
and take a seat.
-Break a leg.
-Thank you.
I brought a pillow so I could
sleep through your performance.
Ha.
Alexis, you have a little
more experience in choreography.
-Uh-huh.
-Okay.
So if you will
take the lead on that
and help out with the group,
I would love that
and appreciate that.
I made the executive decision
to hand over control to Alexis,
because Alexis has that power
to get me and Juju
to really, all right,
five, six, seven, eight.
Can you all do
the switch boots thing?
Or that's too much to ask?
Oof. Right, left,
repeat, repeat.
[clears throat]
How you feeling?
I would give it a five out of...
-That's hideous.
-Okay.
We got no time for fives.
This is All Stars 5.
[all laugh]
If he's bringing sexy back,
shouldn't we bring sexy back?
Yeah.
I don't know, because
your sexy is not that sexy.
I'm very sexy.
-Give it to me.
-Mmm!
[all laugh]
Five, six--
Mayhem's laughing at me.
I don't even know
why I'm the choreographer.
I didn't sign up for this,
you know.
Touch all the way down
to the leg.
How far are we going down?
I don't want you
to pull a hamstring.
-I love ham and I love strings.
-Okay.
Somebody better call my manager
right now.
-We doing Beyoncé.
-Oh, yeah.
[laughs]
Okay, okay, okay, I got it.
And then how do I transition--
It'll be a circle.
Okay. So it's... wow.
Then by the time they sing
the first verse, we should pose.
Oh, my God!
[applause]
That was a big opening.
Thank you, thank you.
Okay, it's your guys' time now.
I'm not feeling
totally confident
about how we did
recording the songs,
so we have to make up for it
with this choreo.
-So I'm here. Mm-hmm.
-She's in the center.
We gotta make this shit
look flawless.
Five, six, seven, eight, boom.
♪ I'm Cinderella
and my friend's Johnny ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love ♪
♪ I'm in love,
love, love, love ♪
Team Shea. Not a surprise,
coming right out the gate.
Ahh, ahh.
-And then--
-Yes, that would be perfect.
I want to be on her team.
One, two, three.
This is the highest altitude
I've ever been at
without actually being
enclosed in an airplane.
Okay.
Wow.
As soon as that,
then I can just...
-Right.
-We're cohesive.
We have our concepts.
We're gonna create little waves,
so he is my Aquaman.
Aquaman.
We're working great together.
Right? Yes.
Bitch, we winning.
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love,
I'm in love with him ♪
[applause]
Okay.
-Yay.
Shea, how'd I do?
Shea's team is like, a-one
and two and three and four
and five, six, seven, eight.
I'm like, oh, God.
I'm gonna hit center here,
and then the two of you need
to be on either side.
Yeah, and we should open up
a little bit.
So we're here, and we're
doing the one, two,
I'm coming down and up.
So remember, we're doing--
the words are--
I wanna cook for him,
-I wanna cook for him.
-Yeah.
-So that--
-Right foot again.
Can we do hung-ry?
Hung-ry.
As a team leader,
it's my job
to keep everyone on track.
We just need to be unified
as a team.
And that's our transition
to Cracker.
-Okay.
-So I think we--
And I'm gonna get rid of her.
-I'll take it from you.
-I can just...
But I feel like Cracker's
main focus right now is Cracker.
-Hung-ry.
I'm holding it weird. Okay.
We can simplify
if it'll make it cleaner.
No, no, it's still cool.
No, it just would
make it cleaner. So I'm in--
We have a time limit.
Did I pick the wrong team?
We're back!
♪ Ooh ♪
Today we're getting ready
for our I'm in Love
girl group performance.
Teamwork makes the dream work.
It does make the dream work.
-It really does.
-Dreamworks, Inc.
Oh, my team is way over there.
Hey, I'm gonna put my shit
right here.
Blair and Cracker are on
the other side of the room,
which is a good thing.
Because there's been
some tension.
Let me ask you, how
do y'all think about our team?
I feel like it's a little bit
of tension there.
There was a lot of stress there.
Yeah, all I was getting
was a lot of frustration.
I think it's just
personalities.
It was very difficult,
because you know
when working with a group
there has to be
some kind of compromise.
And I felt very much
that Cracker was not budging.
You know, that she likes her
way, and that's
the only way.
I can see that.
She did try to rewrite my verse.
-Mm-hmm.
-Which I was, like--
-No, are you serious?
-Oh, baby.
No, bitch, I gag.
And it's like--
and I think, okay, so--
And you didn't went
completely ballistic?
Girl, you know,
I tried-- [laughs]
Yesterday, when she was, like,
she wanted to Wite-Out--
Girl.
Like, heat just, like,
went whew all the way.
And I think, like,
smoke came out of my ears.
It was like,
where'd that come from?
Like, I want it behind me,
especially
with the challenge today.
Right.
[sighs]
I love you,
but you can be difficult.
How am I difficult?
-You're egotistical.
-Yeah.
Oh, that's garbage.
-Really?
-Why?
Because I all the time say
I'm worried about this,
I'm worried about that,
and blah, blah, blah.
I never hear that.
Oh, God.
I have a Pavlovian response
to the word "difficult."
I was like... [panting]
because I get that all the time,
and I feel like I'm a loving
person trapped in this cage,
and people can only see
the cage.
Honestly, to be real,
I can't connect with people.
I don't--nobody
seems to understand
where I'm coming from.
I can't get people
to understand me.
It's why I have, like,
very few friends.
I wanna be that person
like Blair
that everyone thinks of as nice.
I haven't made a friend in years
because in my head, I'm,
like, don't get used to this.
There will come a day when they
don't wanna talk to you anymore.
If I knew why people
thought I was difficult,
I could fix it.
My time in drag is my only time
that's peaceful for me.
Even if people
don't understand me or like me,
I put on a pretty dress,
and the judges say I'm good.
They love you.
No, I can't cry because I have,
like, all this face on.
You'd need feelings to cry,
darling.
Girl.
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
♪ Cover girl ♪
And what?
[applause]
Welcome to the main stage of
RuPaul's Drag Race All Stars.
Love of my life,
Michelle Visage.
You still haven't signed
that prenup, doll.
Oh. Tomorrow, me and the boys
at Jacoby & Meyers.
Okay. [laughs]
Style superstar Carson Kressley.
Why do birds suddenly appear
every time you're near?
Oh, I think they're just
looking to flock.
Oh.
[Michelle laughs]
Music sensation Madison Beer.
How are you, darling?
I'm amazing, Ru,
but can I confess something?
I'm in love with you.
Oh! [laughs]
I think that would make
a really good song.
And the fabulous Tessa Thompson.
Welcome.
Thank you so much for having me.
I'm really gagged.
You know, I'm such a fan.
[all laugh]
You do that like a pro.
[laughs]
I've been watching.
This week,
we challenged our All Stars
to sing and dance
in the name of hot romance.
All Stars, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
♪ Love, love ♪
♪ He's so perfect,
and he makes me crazy ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love,
I'm in lo-lo-lo-love ♪
♪ I really wanna
handcuff him to me ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love,
I'm in love with-- ♪
♪ Daddy Yankee ♪
♪ He's my man, he's my papi ♪
♪ When he sing reggaeton,
I get really happy ♪
♪ Every time I see him,
I get sassy ♪
♪ Got me nervous
and really gassy ♪
♪ In my dreams,
he say, Oye, mami ♪
♪ Because
he's my daddy, daddy ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love,
I'm in love with-- ♪
♪ John Stamos ♪
♪ He's Uncle Jesse,
and I need him, I need him ♪
♪ His pants are sexy,
and I see it, see it ♪
♪ Taking off my blouse,
please fill up my house ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm in love, I'm
in love, I'm in love with-- ♪
♪ Justin Timberlake ♪
♪ He's bringing sexy back,
I follow in his tracks ♪
♪ I sent that Britney back ♪
♪ 'Cause
I felt very attacked ♪
♪ I'll give him all my love ♪
♪ My hugs, my kisses,
he's my drug, 'cause-- ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love,
I'm in love with him ♪
♪ I'll do anything
to make him want me ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love,
I'm in lo-lo-lo-love ♪
♪ I cook him dinner,
because I bet he's hung-ry ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love,
I'm in love with-- ♪
♪ Sylvester Stallone ♪
♪ He played a boxer ♪
♪ So he moves around
my ring just fine ♪
♪ When things get Rocky ♪
♪ I'm like, please release
the Rocky IX ♪
♪ Let me pick the speed,
the man is my Creed ♪
♪ Make me wanna play Rambo
till I can't pick my feet up ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love,
I'm in love with-- ♪
♪ With Mr. Rogers ♪
♪ Ooh, those sweaters
look so warm and fuzzy ♪
♪ Be your puppet,
forget about those Muppets ♪
♪ Tall and nerdy
with big brains ♪
♪ Be my neighbor
on this train ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love,
I'm in love with-- ♪
♪ Hannibal Lecter ♪
♪ He'll look at me
with hunger in his eyes ♪
♪ I'm the whole damn snack ♪
♪ Just serve my heart with
a side of fries, super-size ♪
♪ I'm beefing up ♪
♪ And I'll take this pie to the
first-place prize, 'cause-- ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love,
I'm in love with him ♪
♪ I'm his Cinderella,
he's Prince Charming ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love,
I'm in lo-lo-lo-love ♪
♪ To keep him from me,
it would take an army ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love,
I'm in love with-- ♪
♪ Henry Cavill ♪
♪ He's my Superman,
and we flyin', flyin' ♪
♪ And when we touch down,
I'll be ridin', ridin' ♪
♪ He makes me weak
with those blue eyes ♪
♪ Like kryptonite
between my thighs ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love,
I'm in love with-- ♪
♪ I'm in love
with Jason Momoa ♪
♪ He is my Aquaman,
I take his trident how I can ♪
♪ He'll have me bent,
I'll have him sent ♪
♪ Yes, I'm that bitch,
yes, I'm that bitch ♪
♪ He'll filet me,
he will slay me ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love,
I'm in love with-- ♪
♪ Chadwick Boseman ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, girl, he's my boo ♪
♪ The mother-tucking Black
Panther, what you gonna do? ♪
♪ He's tall, dark,
long, and lean ♪
♪ And he rocks my kitty world
like you never seen ♪
♪ He's the king
and I'm his queen ♪
♪ I'm dreaming about what
kind of life we'll lead ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love,
I'm in love with him ♪
♪ Didn't know
he even knew my name ♪
♪ Until the court
told me stay ♪
♪ At least 30 feet away ♪
♪ It's so cute
how he plays hard to get ♪
♪ But on this page,
they forgot ♪
♪ To blur out
his home address ♪
♪ Love, love ♪
♪ I'm in love with him ♪
[all saying their crush names]
[laughter and applause]
♪ Everyone can be someone ♪
Category is
Love The Skin You're In.
First up, India Ferrah.
Carson: Oh, I see one,
two, three, four skins.
[all laugh]
Tessa: I love how she wears
her heart on her...hip?
[RuPaul laughs]
India: My runway look
is racial unity.
I wanna celebrate
all the beautiful skin tones
that are out there,
connected with a red-beaded
and rhinestone heart.
It's just a gorgeous message
I wanna spread.
Michelle: Send me nudes.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Up next, Jujubee.
Carson: That's a latte body
she's showing.
-Mm-hmm.
-Jujubeast!
Jujubee: I'm serving you
Asian Mae West,
with a nice updo.
Oh, I own everything.
I'm looking sickening.
My body is ripe.
My goodness,
I would fuck me.
RuPaul: Ooh, she puts
the motion in the Laotian.
Oh, my God.
[all laugh]
Alexis Mateo.
Look at the layers
on those lips.
Michelle: Which ones?
Alexis: I'm walking the runway
in this self-made gown
in complete leather
in my skin tone,
and I'm so proud to be seen
as a Puerto Rican, baby.
RuPaul: She's ribbed
for your pleasure.
Blair St. Clair, I declare!
Michelle: Someone forgot
their sunscreen.
[RuPaul laughs]
RuPaul: Now that's the worst
case of pinkeye I've ever seen.
[all laugh]
Blair: I am loving
the skin that I'm in,
and I wanted to go
outside of the box.
Because I think that I am more
than what people see
on the outside,
and I'm giving them
exactly what I feel like
on the inside:
pink.
Carson: We're all pink
on the inside.
RuPaul: That's true.
Ding!
RuPaul: Miz Cracker.
Carson: This would be great
at a salad bar.
Madison: Yes, the sneeze guard.
[all laugh]
Cracker:
You want Jewish princess,
I am giving it to you.
It's time for me to show
my roots, literally.
You wanna fiddle around
on the roof,
this whore is ready, darling.
Carson:
Look how long her tulle is.
Tessa: Ooh, I've heard.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Mayhem Miller.
Michelle:
Somebody have a towel?
Carson:
You really can't bead it.
[all laugh]
Mayhem: My gown today
is lovely, honey.
She is dripping.
And when I say dripping, she's
like really oozing glamour.
Do I love the skin I'm in?
Ha ha!
Look at it.
Mmm. Chocolaty.
RuPaul: Melts in your mouth,
not in your hands.
Shea Couleé.
Ooh.
Michelle: Now I know
where my implants went.
[all laugh]
Shea: Oh, yes, mama,
I'm serving up some
Nubian goddess realness.
Mama just stepped out
of the Nile River
drip-drip-dripping
in Swarovski stones,
and I feel gorgeous
and expensive.
Carson:
That's some serious vajazzling.
RuPaul: It certainly is.
Come on, Josephine Baker.
Madison: Come on, Grace Jones.
Michelle: Come on, Pam Grier.
RuPaul: Up next, Ongina.
Michelle: Hey, girl, hey.
[all laugh]
Ongina: My dress is a take
on a traditional
Filipino costume.
The feathers is inspired
by a legendary mythical bird.
And I just love wearing this,
because I'm very proud of being
a Filipino-American immigrant.
Tessa: This look
really ruffles my feathers.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Mariah Paris Balenciaga.
Carson:
She mer-made it herself.
-Yeah.
-She did.
Mariah:
I am floating down the runway.
I am feeling like
butterscotch and caramel
mixed with a kiss
of brown sugar, baby.
RuPaul: She's got
a very glamorous headache.
[Michelle laughs]
The best kind.
I told y'all
I didn't come to play.
-Ru.
-What?
Michelle:
Is the train still running?
[all laugh]
Welcome, All Stars.
Based on your performances
and runway presentations,
I've made some decisions.
When I call your name,
please step forward.
Alexis Mateo.
Miz Cracker.
Mayhem Miller.
You are safe.
[exhales]
Safe queens,
you may leave the stage.
Thank you.
Now, the rest of you
represent the tops
and bottoms of the week.
It's time
for the judges' critiques.
First up, India Ferrah.
Tonight on the runway, I think
you looked really beautiful.
Thank you.
It's very like
Dancing with the Stars,
mother of the bar mitzvah lady.
It's a certain look,
but it's done really well.
Your celebrity crush
was Justin Timberlake.
You did, like, a Laganja moment,
"feeling very attacked,"
which made no sense to me
with the Britney moment
and then the Justin moment.
It was kind of disjointed,
and I kind of lost you
a little bit in your group.
I will say
during the performance,
I did kind of find myself
wandering to other people
a little bit.
All right, up next, Jujubee.
You chose John Stamos.
Your lyrics were one of
my favorites of the night.
You said, "Taking off my blouse,
please fill up my house."
Yes, ma'am,
I wanna go to that church.
[all laugh]
I actually got help from India
for that lyric.
Well, India, you gave her
your good material.
Your runway, just your walk
is so unbothered.
Your hair is a confection.
You look like
a walking champagne flute.
You're just so beautiful.
Up next, Blair St. Clair.
I do declare.
I love the whole look
from top to bottom.
It is delectable.
I just don't understand
how it's skin.
I don't mind the pink at all.
The latex
is kind of skin-tight
and like a second skin.
I think it's really artistic
and super fun.
I'm obsessed with you.
When the song started,
I immediately was staring at you
the entire time.
And you were just
having fun with it.
Then you stepped onto the runway
and blew me away with this.
I get it,
and I think it's amazing.
Thank you so much.
Up next, Shea Couleé.
Hi, y'all.
I literally gagged when you
came out for runway tonight.
I was like... [gasps]
And then your jaw was open
for a really long time.
It happens.
[all laugh]
I was impressed.
It's beautiful, it's fun,
it's campy, it's glamorous.
It's what drag should be.
You came out here
for the challenge,
and you looked so cute.
I loved the little
Afropuffs you had,
and your lyrics were spot-on,
and you were in it.
My note there
was "professional."
Because you were living it.
You weren't just
going through the moves.
You were totally
commanding the stage.
I can't stop looking
at your nipples.
[all laugh]
Ooh.
I wish I could, too,
but I can't look down.
[laughs]
Thank you.
Up next, Ongina.
Tonight on the runway,
I actually dig this.
But because you're so tiny,
your neck
is completely lost in that.
This runway look
is one of my favorites.
I have to agree
with Michelle, though.
The execution
just needs some tweaks.
It's like a little egg
in a nest up there.
-Okay.
-Tonight in the performance,
while I don't think
that Henry Cavill
is the most inventive choice,
I feel like
the way that you approached
singing his praises
was inventive.
In your performance, there
were moments that I lost you,
and it's really difficult
on these stages,
with all these animals.
So you gotta fight
for every moment that you get.
All right, up next,
Mariah Paris Balenciaga.
Hello.
This look tonight
is so stunning.
The construction of this gown,
I mean, the pavé bustier
that's peeking out
through that neckline
is, like, ridiculously good.
I thought the performance
was good.
I liked your look
probably more
than I liked your performance.
I did sort of,
when I would look at you,
I felt like
you were a little bored
or you, like, weren't really
that in your character.
You're a quiet one,
so you need to make sure
that you continue to get seen.
As you know,
this is All Stars,
and we are splitting hairs here.
But there will be tops
and there will be bottoms.
That's what she said.
[all laugh]
Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
Based on the judges'
glowing critiques,
I've made some decisions.
Shea Couleé.
Con-drag-ulations.
You are the top All Star
of the week.
[applause]
You've won a six-night,
all-inclusive trip for two
to Puerto Vallarta
at the Almar LGBT Resort.
Mm.
Jujubee.
Blair St. Clair.
You are safe.
[mouths words]
India Ferrah.
Ongina.
Mariah Paris Balenciaga.
You are the bottom three
All Stars of the week.
Shea Couleé, you need to decide
which of the bottom queens
you will eliminate
if you win the lip sync
against this week's
lip sync assassin.
And the rest of you
will cast your vote
for which of the bottom queens
you think should get the chop.
Thank you, ladies.
You may leave the stage.
Oh, my God, the girls are here.
-Ladies!
-Come on in.
I am riding
on such a high right now,
but I come back to reality,
and I realize that
there is a bottom three,
and my team makes up
two-thirds of that.
So let it out.
Shea won!
-Shea!
-Yay!
-Congratulations.
-Thanks.
Are you in the top?
No, not at all.
I'm actually
in the bottom three
with India and Mariah.
-Moi.
-[gasps]
First of all,
let's take a moment.
Accentuate the positive.
Shea, how do you feel?
Honestly, it feels
really bittersweet,
because my teammates make up
two-thirds of the bottom three.
And as a team leader,
that makes me feel
like I didn't do my job.
Well, you should not
feel that way,
because you were just
that freaking great.
And Ru was even saying
that it's very hard for her,
especially this week,
to try and decide
who were gonna be the bottom.
-Yeah.
-So it makes it--it's hard.
Well, I guess we have to start
doing these deliberations, so--
Actually, before that,
can I say something?
Yeah.
I prepared for All Stars.
I was like, oh, my God,
I'm so fucking excited.
Like, this is my chance
and my opportunity.
And I came here
and I was a little bit rocky.
Like, my reading challenge
wasn't the best.
My talent,
I was almost on the bottom.
And now I'm on the bottom three.
I have so much more to give,
and I wanna give it,
and I know I have the hunger,
I have the drive.
I wanna be here so bad.
But you don't have to
deliberate with me,
because these two do not deserve
to go home at all tonight.
This is not me giving up.
This is the fairest thing to do.
[sighs] Oh, God.
The giggity-gag is that I said
Ongina didn't have the heart
for the competition,
and then Ongina says
she doesn't have the heart
for the competition.
But I can see that Ongina
is hurting.
A lot of winners started out
in the bottom multiple times.
And it's not fair for anyone
to say that it means
you don't have what it takes.
And I made your morning
difficult a while ago,
and it was stupid.
This is how that morning
could have gone.
Like, "Are you guys
excited about today?"
"Yeah." Me.
Did I mean what I said?
Absolutely.
But does it help me
to make Ongina feel bad?
And does it help Ongina
to feel bad?
No. That's the mistake.
How you feeling?
Um, I'm in a little disbelief
that I'm in the bottom three.
Didn't see that one coming.
No, I didn't.
But honestly, I wouldn't
have changed anything
except for having more attitude.
I know that I have the diversity
and the range
to be here and to stay here,
and I want everybody
to see more.
And right now, I'm very proud
of what I've done.
And I just wanna keep going hard
and keep showing all the
different facets of my growth.
Yeah.
It really sucks that
we're in this position,
because I feel very responsible
for you and Ongina.
You guys were right there,
helping me shine,
and so it, like,
doesn't feel fun.
It doesn't feel right
that I have to be the person
to decide somebody's fate.
There is some kind of solace
in knowing that me and Ongina
were on the winner's team,
because she might go ahead
and throw us a bone
and just vote India off.
So, hey.
How you feeling, girl?
I am a mess,
because I feel like
I didn't do that bad.
You didn't.
-This sucks.
-Yeah.
Because y'all
are like my friends.
Well, I want you to know
I'm not giving up.
I'm not gonna back down.
I came more than prepared.
I wanna be at the top.
That may be bad for some people,
because that may be threatening.
But I'm not gonna sit here
and be like, "I can't do this."
I was moved by what you said
over there on the couch
with the other girls, truly.
But I just wanna know.
In the event that I do decide
to choose one of the other two
for any reason,
can you please
just, like, promise me
that, like, you won't give up?
No, I'll fight, you know,
whatever that means.
Ongina's down on herself,
but I saw her battle
so much adversity
in this last challenge,
I'm just wondering
if perhaps another chance
might help breathe
some life into her
and give her the last push that
she needs to make this work.
I hope you know
how bad I wanna be here.
I absolutely do, 100%.
I know we don't know each other
that well,
and I know how hard it is,
because the other two
on the bottom are on your team.
Yeah, it does make it
tough for me,
because you wanna feel
a sense of loyalty
to your teammates, you know.
And I consider myself
a very loyal person.
And both of those girls
really put a lot of trust in me,
which is not easy
in a competition.
But you were an incredible
team captain as well.
I know Shea has such
a tough decision to make.
But Ongina just pled to us that
she no longer wanted to be here.
I refuse to sit there and say
to anyone, "Send me home."
Why would I do that?
Well, I hope
that I can continue.
-Mariah?
-Yes, my love.
What's up?
I just wanna show you all more.
I just wanna keep giving more
in every challenge,
and I know that
it's not my time to go.
Who should go home?
Oh, my God.
Ongina was on my team,
and I know the heart
and the passion
and the want that she had
for it to push through.
And India,
she's a fierce entertainer.
You can't dispute it.
Wow, this is, like, the worst,
because I really love Ongina.
And I also share my Season 3
common bond with you and India.
Do you think that Ongina
saying that is her giving up?
Remember, too,
if Shea wins this lip sync,
and not the assassin,
our vote doesn't matter.
Gosh, I need to have sex.
[all laugh]
I see my name front and center,
and that is
a crude wake-up call.
To go home now, I can't.
I need to prove it to myself
that I'm able to compete
against the best.
It just tells you how hard
All Stars really is.
Because Ongina has wanted
to be here for so long,
and now she's gonna bow out?
[sighs]
I am furious
about you giving up so fast
in the competition.
I cannot let it go.
So my vote
is for you to go home.
Honestly, this decision
is not an easy one.
There's so many things that
are going through my head.
Who do I think wants this?
Who do I think is the best
out of the three?
And who do I think
deserves another chance?
This is only week two,
and this is excruciating,
but I feel like I know what
decision I need to make.
Welcome back, ladies.
Shea Couleé, it's time to
lip sync for your legacy.
Would you like to meet
your opponent?
Sure.
[all laugh]
The time has come
to present this week's
[echoing]
lip sync assassin.
Oh, my God, who is it?
Oh, there is so much pressure,
because, damn, I gotta
go up against some bitch
whose one purpose
is to come in here
and stop me
from winning this lip sync.
-Who is this?
-Oh.
[echoing] Ru-veal yourself!
-Trinity?
-Oh, it could be Trinity.
Wait, that's Kameron.
[cheers and applause]
Child, hmm.
[muttering]
[laughs]
None other than
the dancing queen herself,
Miss Alyssa Edwards.
So I'm a little skurred
right now.
I'm back, back, back,
back, back again,
giving y'all a dose
of assassin-eers.
Oh!
[all laugh]
Now, ladies,
Alyssa holds the lipstick
of the queen that the group
has voted to go home.
Now, if Alyssa wins,
that queen gets the chop.
Two queens stand before me.
Shea Couleé, this is your chance
to impress me,
win $20.000,
and earn the power
to give one of the bottom queens
the chop.
The time has come...
[thunder]
to lip sync...
[echoing] for your legacy.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
[music plays]
♪ I don't wanna take it
anymore ♪
♪ I'll just stay here
locked behind the door ♪
♪ Ooh-hoo ♪
-Yeah!
-Come on, Shea!
♪ Someone stole
my brand-new Chevrolet ♪
♪ And the rent is due,
I got no place to stay ♪
♪ Whoo, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ And it's hard to say ♪
♪ Just how
some things never change ♪
♪ And it's hard to find ♪
♪ Any strength
to draw the line ♪
♪ Oh, I'm just burning,
doing the neutron dance ♪
♪ I'm just burning,
Oh, girl.
Oh, my gosh, this lip sync.
Whoa, I'm excited.
♪ Yeah, and it's hard to say ♪
♪ Just how some things
never change ♪
♪ And it's hard to find ♪
♪ Any strength
to draw the line ♪
♪ Oh, I'm just burning,
doing the neutron dance ♪
♪ Oh, I'm so happy,
♪ And I'm just burning,
doing the neutron dance ♪
♪ Well, well, well, well,
ooh, ooh ♪
[laughs]
[cheers and applause]
Wow.
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Shea Couleé...
you're a winner, baby.
[cheers and applause]
You've earned a cash tip
of $20.000.
Oh!
[applause]
Alyssa Edwards,
you may slay another day.
At the house.
Always and forever
a runner-up...
proudly. [tongue pop]
[all laugh]
Now, excuse me, did Mama Ru
just call my name
over Alyssa Edwards?
Girl, I mean... [laughs]
Will the bottom three queens
please step forward?
Shea Couleé, with great power
comes great responsibility.
Which queen have you chosen...
to get the chop?
I thought a lot about this,
and I think that you
are all unbelievably amazing
and so talented.
The queen that I've chosen...
is Ongina.
You are a giant.
I don't ever wanna hear
anything different.
As it is written,
so it shall be done.
Ongina, you are and will
always be an All Star.
11 years ago,
you changed my life, Ru,
and I just wanna say
thank you so much.
And you're changing
my life again,
and I cannot thank you enough.
Ongina, 11 years ago
you changed my life.
Now sashay away.
I'm disappointed that
my time here is so short,
but this is not the last
that you'll see of me,
I promise you that.
I will haunt you in your dreams,
and my legacy
will live on forever
and ever and ever.
Celebrate your life,
because life is a celebration.
Goodbye, all.
[applause]
Con-drag-ulations, ladies.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get a "amen" up in here?
-Amen!
All right,
now let the music play.
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪vote
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪
RuPaul: Next time
on All Stars...
You need to design and present
your own signature suite
worthy of a five-star hotel.
I'm very delicate.
-Lift with your legs.
-Oh, my God.
[grunts]
There is no butch queen
on this team.
[elephant trumpets]
-Come inside.
-Come on in.
I've said that before.
To indulge yourself
in our girthy meats and cheeses.
I love girthy meat.
Everybody wants to be
a celebrity.
-Rich.
So you don't respect me?
Is that
what you're trying to say?
-Listen, sweetheart--
-Don't "sweetheart" me,
because I'm not
"sweethearting" you.
I am not ready
for the Alexis shark attack.
You know what?
I'm done with Miz Cracker.
RuPaul: Ru-veal yourself!
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪
♪ Am-Am-Am-Am-American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪