RuPaul:
Previously on All Stars...
For this week's maxi-challenge,
we're gonna be playing
the Snatch Game of Love.
[cheers and applause]
I'm gay!
[all laugh]
[purrs]
Flavor Flav!
[all laugh]
Open up my thighs,
show you the surprise.
-He don't want it.
-[laughs]
Oh, India.
There was no Jeffree
in your Jeffree.
It was definitely a miss for me.
Shea Couleé, con-drag-ulations.
You're the top All Star
of the week.
Oh, my God. [laughs] Oh!
Starting today,
if you're not the top All Star,
you are in the bottom.
What?
Remember when you were in
the bottom with me and Mariah?
Alexis and Mayhem came to me
and asked me
to put your lipstick in.
Plotting? Against me?
I did not. I did not.
You're lying.
I'm not lying, girl.
Is Alexis the villain?
When I did that vote,
it was in my heart.
I just wanna know
why I should pick somebody
else's lipstick
over yours.
Ru-veal yourself!
Aah!
[all shouting]
Shea Couleé,
you're a winner, baby.
[applause]
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
I thought long and hard
about this.
India.
India Ferrah, sashay away.end
recap
Ooh, wow.
Home sweet home.
Back into ye olde werkroom.
India has gone home,
and there is
only five of us left.
And I can see the top four
upon the horizon,
and I can see myself there
so bad.
I just got to keep pushing.
Well, Shea, congratulations.
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Yes! Girl, you turned it.
How are you ladies feeling?
Well, that was just,
like, a lot.
I'm still just, like,
really kind of confused.
Yeah.
What's going through
your mind right now?
I'm embarrassed
about the whole situation.
[crying] It hurts me,
because India was my friend.
And this was,
like, a desperate moment
for her to stay
in the competition.
Um...
I got really close--
really close
to picking your lipstick.
I'm not gonna lie.
This imagery that India
created in my head
of you going to all the girls,
like, in secret,
telling them to pick my name,
it just, like, really shook me.
But even though
there were doubts,
there wasn't reason enough
for me to send you home.
Shea, did I think
you were competition? Yes.
Did I campaign against you? No.
I know how voting works.
If I wanted you to go home,
I needed to talk to all of you.
Did I talk to you
or any one of you?
Never.
Should we look at the group?
I mean, yeah, I don't
even wanna talk about it.
I just wanna look at the box.
Yeah, I just kind of wanna
look at every vote.
So, India.
India.
Alexis.
I thank you guys
for believing in me.
You know, I see it.
I feel like the right person
went home tonight.
India was in the bottom
four times in a row.
Ooh.
But, like, with
the India/Alexis drama,
no one really knows
who to believe.
But Alexis is still here,
and it's hard,
because you wanna trust her.
But that doesn't mean
I'm not watching from afar.
Always watching.
One thing growing up that
my dad always, always said:
Whatever is done in the dark
will come out to the light.
-Thank you.
-Always.
And if there were
shady dealings,
if there was stuff going on,
it will eventually come out.
It's not real.
I can tell you that.
You live to fight another day.
To live another day.
You mean to die another day.
[laughs] Stupid.
[all laugh]
All right, who wants
to take their titties off?
Oh, me!
After this stunt, nothing
is sure for me any longer.
This feels like
when nobody wants to play
with you in the playground,
and they all pick up their toys
and they don't let you use them.
Sisters.
I'm kind of worried that the
competition is ruined for me.
And now I have to be perfection,
because the girls
are gonna vote me out
as soon
as they have the chance.
Hands down.
It's a scary place to be
right now.
RuPaul: The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race All Stars
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
a coveted spot
in the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize of $100.000.
With extra-special guest judge
Bebe Rexha.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪end opener
Oh.
-We are back.
-♪ Back, back, back again ♪
I am in the top five!
Oh, I do know
what this feels like...twice.
Oh, this is a long one.
Drag-stoevsky.
"Thank you all for showing me
kindness still exists.
"The truth shall set you free.
"XOXO India Ferrah,
humble, heart, happy, honest."
Checkmarks.
-Checkmarks.
-Yeah, checkmarks on each one.
On each one.
Ugh. More shenanigans.
This mirror message
is very pointed,
and I think we all know
who it's pointed at.
India has left the competition,
and we still talking about her.
Smart girl, India.
We still talking about you,
bitch.
-Top five.
-Wow.
This feels so good.
It does.
-And it's a fierce five.
-It really is.
This is a fierce five,
and very diverse, too.
I feel like
we all deserve to be here.
What you thinking, Cracker?
Because you very quiet, bitch.
Oh, I'm, like,
I'm gonna shut the fuck up,
because we're about to vote
on the top four,
so I'm not gonna put my foot
anywhere it doesn't belong.
[alarm]
Oh! There we go.
What are we doing today?
She done already
done had herses.
Hey, All Stars.
I got all my sisters with me,
plus aunties, nieces,
and several many play cousins.
So go on and fix you a plate,
Corneshia.
Y'all hungry?
[laughs] Yes, I am.
What's a "Corneshia?"
That's my cousin.
Don't act brand-new.
Hello, hello, hello!
-Hello!
-Hi!
Ladies, in all my travels
across the country
and around the world,
the most important thing
I've learned is this:
Happiness
is in your own backyard.
So for this week's
maxi-challenge,
my sisters Rozy and Renae and I
are throwing
a Charles family backyard ball.
-Ooh!
-Oh!
And you're all invited!
[all laugh]
-I love barbeque.
-
Now, y'all need to serve up
two fresh looks.
First look,
tapping into my family's
colorful Louisiana roots,
country cousin realness.
You'll create an original
play cousin persona
and crash the party
with a comedic back story.
Second look,
starting from scratch,
y'all need to whip up
some high fashion
worthy of the main stage.
-But there's a twist.
-Of course.
Michelle, tell them what
materials they'll be using!
[game show music plays]
Ru, the All Stars
will be using items
you find in your own backyard.
-Like tablecloths...
-"Audience": Ahh!
-lawn chairs...
-Ooh!
-picnic blanket...
-Ahh!
-hammocks...
-Ohh!
-barbeque sauce...
-Ah!
-and more.
-Oh!
The total value of this
Charles family ball showcase
is... priceless.
["audience" applause]
[all laugh]
Thanks, Michelle.
Now, you can use your own hair,
heels, and underpants,
plus materials
from the FandS Fabrics wall.
So y'all better fire up
your charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent,
because company's coming.
[applause]
All Stars, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
Successful shopping trip.
Ooh, this was fun.
[grunts]
What the fuck
is "backyard eleganza?"
I don't have a backyard.
I live in Boston.
Hey, I have a poem.
Who could sew,
who loves hot glue,
my name is Juju.
Oh, wow.
No, but for real, who could sew?
My major in school
was theater costume design,
so I'm not a stranger
to a sewing machine.
I sew, like, half of my stuff
that I wear.
I sew a little,
and I also use
a lot of hot glue.
How about ju, Jujubee?
I'm so-so with sewing.
[laughs]
I'm so excited about
this sewing experience.
I know what I like, and I know
what silhouettes I like,
and this is definitely
like high fashion,
so I'm excited for that.
I think I have
a great eye for fashion,
so I feel like this challenge
is, like,
the Blair St. Clair challenge.
This feels like
it could finally be my win.
Also, this is my wheelhouse
because my family
likes to get together
and make stuff
out of weird materials.
Since I was a little kid,
I have been making stuff
with trash.
My mom took us to the museum
to look at costumes from around
the world and throughout time,
and said,
"Pick your favorite one."
"We're gonna go home
and make it out of garbage."
This challenge is a way for me
to show the judges who I am,
that I can do it all.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no!
What happened?
I made a mathematical error
just now.
Oh.
Wow, okay.
But if I don't nail it,
then they'll fail it.
And we do not need that
this late in the game.
Aah!
It's fine.end act
Today's maxi-challenge
is the Charles backyard ball.
You know what?
I am so confident
in this challenge, I'm--
ooh, I'm gonna take this.
Bitch, I am lying,
because I'm scared.
I am going to poop myself,
because this is terrifying.
That's the honest truth.
This is hard. This is hard.
I hate this challenge.
This other side
is the right side of it.
-And then you have all these--
-Well, how do you know
that it's the right side
and the wrong side?
See how you can see those,
like, lines running through it
from where it's been woven?
You're kind of seeing all that
and how it's smooth
on this side?
Yes.
And can you tell
this is the right side.
When you look over
at cute little Jujubee,
and, like, "Help me,"
I am just not the kind of person
that can be like, "No, bitch,
this is a competition."
Like, of course
I'm gonna help her.
I know that you're not
necessarily trained
in sewing and building costumes.
But the same type of, like,
energy and creativity
that you apply
to your performances,
-apply to this.
-Thank you.
You got it.
Don't do this to me!
Girl, that moment
when the material you chose
is not going through
the machine.
What's T?
It's just I'm having
to figure out
how this material
is gonna go through the machine,
because she's giving me
a little trouble right now.
Tension is tight, so you
might wanna loosen this up.
Okay.
And then your length
is super short,
so that's also making it--
So maybe like two and a half,
three.
Yeah, okay.
-Shea.
-Yes?
You never told a lie.
I never told a lie.
It's working perfectly.
Bam.
I really like this challenge,
because this is like what we do
in real drag, right?
Oh, yeah, girl.
When you ain't got money.
-Right?
-Yes.
This challenge
is perfect for me
because I do everything I wear.
What's your concept?
What you going for, mama?
I am going to do what I do best
is gowns, you know.
Mm-hmm.
I'm a pageant queen.
Yes.
And I'm gonna keep it very me.
But you also have to use
all the materials
that scream "Hello,
I'm a cookout material."
Right.
I want the gown to feature
everything that a barbeque has:
cups, plates, napkins, forks,
and even a kiddie pool, bitch.
Yeah, I was thinking in my head.
I said if I get invited to
RuPaul's barbeque in real life,
what would I wear?
And I said, the most.
[all laugh]
Yeah, I think this might be
your challenge, girl.
Now, is this barbeque
like a July Fourth celebration?
It's family, so you know
you have to show up
and show them that you're
employed and everything.
I love a barbeque.
Guys, India left me, like,
a letter, but also a gift.
Oh.
"Thank you so much for being
so sweet and showing me
"that there are still
wonderful people out there.
"I can't wait
to work with you soon.
"Keep slaying, so proud of you.
XOXO, India."
Wait, she didn't
give me nothin'.
You didn't get one?
Not even part of one.
Maybe she ran outta ink.
-Shea, you got one?
-I did.
Mine says, "Shea,
I'm so honored and blessed
"to have gotten to know you
and work with you.
"You are such an amazing person
and kind spirit.
"Love you so much.
"Keep turning it.
P.S.: I've got you."
-Wow.
-Did anybody else get a note?
I got one, I think,
but I don't wanna read it.
You don't wanna read it?
No, because it's not
important to me right now.
For real this bitch
didn't give me a letter?
I'm not gonna lose sleep
over India not writing me
a fucking note,
but she wrote a note for Alexis.
Did you wanna read my note,
Jujubee?
No, I'll just read mine.
Yeah, I'll read it.
Don't read it to me.
I don't wanna know.
Just read it to yourself.
You don't want me
to read it out loud?
No.
"Alexis, you are such a bitch.
I can't believe you're
still in the competition."
Girl.
"I can't stand you."
[laughs]
"You are the potato salad
with raisins
that nobody eats at a barbeque."
[laughs]
I am.
Do you want me to actually
tell you what it actually says?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
It says,
"Alexis, I still love you.
"Hugs and kisses, India.
Open your heart."
Wait. It doesn't say I'm a liar
or something like that?
No.
"Open your heart."
What do you think this means?
I don't know.
"Alexis, I still love you."
You don't love me, bitch.
Girl, bye.
This whole drama with India,
I feel like Alexis wants it
to all be done and over with
and for us
to stop talking about it.
But even though
I'm obviously looking
at Alexis Mateo differently,
I feel like everybody else
should be watching
their backs, too.end act
Today we're getting ready
for the Charles
Backyard Barbeque Ball.
Oh, damn,
this is in centimeters?
Centimeters.
So 2.54 centimeters is one inch.
I remember that from math class.
Hey, y'all!
-Hey, mama.
-Hey.
Who's making the potato salad?
-I ate the potatoes.
-[laughs]
Alexis Mateo.
Hey, RuPaul.
Does your family have barbeques?
-All the time.
-Really?
It's not all, like, barbeque,
but it's more like
all you can eat.
Is it in Puerto Rico
or in Florida?
In Puerto Rico.
All my family's in Puerto Rico.
I don't have nobody
in the United States.
Well, you have Vanjie.
Vanjie, my drag daughter
who doesn't cook.
She was here last week
as the lip sync assassin.
It was interesting.
I looked over at you,
and you had a sort of a--
I don't know, it was
a weird look on your face.
Were you happy to see her?
I was very excited
to see Vanjie.
It just--
it was a lot going on.
Yeah.
And when I saw Vanjie,
all I thought in my head
was, like,
you don't wanna go home
in front of your daughter.
Yeah. Yeah.
So let's talk about
this challenge.
I feel more at home
than any other challenge.
-Really?
-Let's put it this way.
Because this is literally
what I do normally.
You know how to sew, you know
how to put things together.
I can defend myself.
[laughs]
-You have it mapped out.
-I think so.
I'm gonna stay true to Alexis.
Good. You should.
You're an All Star.
-Yes.
-[laughs]
All right, Alexis,
I'll see you at the picnic.
I'm so ready to eat.
[both laugh]
Shea Butter Couleé.
Hey, Ru.
On your season,
you won the ball challenge.
I did. The gayest ball ever.
I love creating looks.
As a little kid, I used to
take my dad's dress socks
and cut them up and sew gowns
for my sister's Barbies.
Ooh.
Yeah, I started pretty young.
-Yes.
-And here we are.
And here we are. Wow.
And talking about family,
I remember
that when you were
on this competition before,
you had experienced
some bad news.
My dad, he had been battling
cancer for about five years,
and he had been in remission
and he was fine.
But while I was here
during filming,
went into the hospital,
and two days before the cast
for Season 9 got announced,
he passed away.
And, um...
It was really tough.
Because my dream
for RuPaul's Drag Race
was wrapped in the idea of him
getting to watch and see me,
because I know
he would have been proud.
And for me, the imagery
of having this Christian,
military, Black father
sitting in that audience
rooting for his son
was all I'd ever wanted.
When I felt like
I was coming to terms with that,
a month later to the day
my oldest sister passed away
from breast cancer.
And she was the one
that showed me
Supermodel Of The World.
Her and I used to strut around
that living room.
-Your soul sister.
-Yeah.
She encouraged me to be
the person that I am today,
and I felt really lost,
because I felt like
my two biggest cheerleaders
were now gone.
Though I miss them both
every single day,
I feel them with me.
My dad is half of who I am.
I carry him with me
everywhere I go,
and I know
that he's proud of me.
I know that.
Well, you can honor him
by living your best life.
Yeah.
Thank you. I will.
-Thanks, Shea.
-Thanks, Ru.
-Hi, Jujubee.
-Hi, Mama.
[laughs] You're making
something here.
-Do you sew?
-No.
[laughs]
I've done it before.
So here we are in the
Charles Family Backyard Ball.
Yes.
I know that there was some
back story with your family.
That your mother
had left the family.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
I was 15 and Dad died,
so it was me and my two sisters.
And six months afterwards,
she kind of had a meltdown
and left with some man.
And it was me
and my two sisters,
we became basically
wards of the state.
I was very lucky.
I got to live with my aunt,
but my two sisters
were put into foster homes.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Oh, my goodness.
And how long were they in there?
We disconnected
for about five years,
and then got back together.
So how have you created family
in your adult life?
I've had to let go of a lot
of the people in my past,
because
it wasn't healthy for me.
So most of my friends now
are my friends
that I meet at my meetings,
because we share
the same spirituality.
-We're all broken inside.
-Yeah.
But we're working on
becoming better human beings.
A couple years ago,
I made some decisions
that would affect my life.
I broke up with my fiancée
of 12 years,
and I also
made a conscious decision
to stop using drugs
and drinking.
And that has been
very impactful for me
not only as a human being,
but as a drag queen.
I'm not completely found,
but I'm not as lost
as I used to be.
If that makes any sense to you.
Ooh, that sounds like
a gospel song.
I wanna hear Albertina Walker
sing that song.
And you stick with those friends
in those places
that you and I both know about.
Because I think
what you're gonna find
is they will help you.
[sniffles]
Because I wouldn't be here today
without those friends.
[both sniffle]
I wouldn't be here.
It's a beautiful moment for me,
because I needed this meeting.
I needed this, and I'm so happy
that there's somebody here
that I can relate to with this.
And it just so happens
to be the person
that I look up to the most.
It's a real, real gift.
Thank you.
And you can honor that gift
by shining and sewing
and cooking.
I'll bring my potato salad.
Is that your signature dish?
With raisins and MSG.
[laughs]
You can leave out the MSG now.
No, my campaign
is Jujubee for MSG.
[laughs]
Vote for me.
Okay, yeah, okay, yeah.
Well, you got my vote.
I'm gonna let you get to work.
It looks like
you got a piece of fabric here
that you have not cut,
you have not patterned,
you have not done
a damn thing to.
I folded it in half.
You folded it in half.
[both laugh]
So I'm gonna let you get to it.
-Thank you, mama.
-Thank you so much.
-I'll see you out there.
-Yes, ma'am.
[exhales]end act
Runway day!
Oh, it's my favorite day.
Oh, God.
Today we're getting ready
for the Charles
Backyard Barbeque Ball.
Girl, I still have
so much work to do, though.
Oh, I have so much to do. Ugh.
We have to present
the country cousin character,
and a high fashion
eleganza look
made from backyard
barbeque materials.
-So what's your eleganza here?
-Eleganza?
Well, whenever I show up
to a family function,
everyone always
points out my clothes,
and everyone around
is, like, what is that?
But also, like, "Oh, my gosh."
You know, like,
that's just my family.
So I wanted to do something,
like--
Extra. Extra St. Clair.
So all these items
are used in different ways
that are repurposed,
but you're not necessarily
gonna see all them,
because I'm trying
to give this high fashion look.
Right.
Okay, Blair.
We know.
You're so good, Blair.
Well, you better be,
because you have not won
a challenge yet, bitch.
Oh, this is looking good.
Oh, you know, it's still
in a million pieces,
because, you know--
Still, girl?
Yeah, because making this
out of dinner napkins was...
-a choice.
-It's a choice.
Because it's been unraveling.
But I also have not had a time
to, like, fit it on myself.
It looks nice, though.
I love the pants.
I would wear the pants.
Okay.
What to say about Alexis Mateo?
I'm still trying
to figure her out.
No, really. I'm really
trying to figure her out,
because I don't think that
she's giving us the true T.
Are you freaking out
or are you okay?
I'm freaking out a little bit,
just because if you don't win,
you're in the bottom.
There's only five of us left,
and Alexis Mateo is still here.
So that means
I am in danger of going home
if I wind up in the bottom,
you know what I'm saying?
So... [laughs]
I gotta carry this one out.
We also have to get ready,
and I still have, like,
a ton of sewing to do.
So I'm just gonna
keep breathing.
Let go and let God,
and watch Juju eat her
watermelon slices over there.
You so fake over there,
eating your fake watermelon.
Everyone at home could tell
that that watermelon ain't real.
Well, everybody at home can see
through y'all two bitches,
because I know
you're conspiring against me.
Uh, no, that dress
is conspiring against you.
What?
It's campaigning, honey.
Get it right.
Can I ask you guys a question?
Yeah, sure.
At this point, we have all
got strikes against us
and things going for us.
So how is everyone
gonna vote today?
You know what?
I'm gonna vote with my heart.
Okay.
[laughs] I have no idea
what that means.
Voting with your heart
probably means
I'm gonna vote the way that
I wanna vote at that second
during that moment
for this specific vote.
So there's literally
no criteria, bitch.
I'm gonna vote
with my heart, too.
[all laugh]
Girl, what is done in the dark
shall come to light.
Girl, y'all keep pulling it.
It didn't happen.
Let it go.
Oh, wow, why she so mad?
I feel like the girls
are trying to be
as accommodating as they can be,
but I know
it's a lot of mixed feelings,
and I don't know how long
they're gonna hold this grudge.
So in this challenge
I have to be fucking perfect,
or I'm gonna be
the next one home.end act
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
♪ Cover girl ♪
-And what?
-Whoo!
Welcome to the main stage of
RuPaul's Drag Race All Stars.
She's the ketchup to my mustard,
Michelle Visage.
Ru, always be safe
and use your condiments.
[all laugh]
Style superstar Carson Kressley,
Now, have you ever
played cornhole?
Oh, gosh, I love cornhole.
I was just playing it
last night.
You play that lawn game where
they throw beanbags at night?
Oh, no, they do it differently
in West Hollywood.
Oh.
And the beautiful Bebe Rexha.
Now, do you have a favorite dish
you like to bring to a barbeque?
Potato salad and gossip, Ru.
[all laugh]
This week
we challenged our All Stars
to create two sizzling looks
for the Charles Family
Backyard Ball.
And joining us on the runway
are my sisters, niece, nephew,
and some new relatives
I just met through a DNA test.
Hey.
All Stars, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
Get it, girl.
Well, hey, cysts.
Hey, y'all remember
back in the day
when I performed in drag
at the Charles family reunion?
Absolutely.
[all laugh]
Well, this is the remix.
Y'all know who this is.
Category is
Country Cousin Realness.
Hyuk.
[horse whinnies]
Up first, Miz Cracker.
Cracker: Hello!
I'm RuPaul's second cousin
twice removed...
by court order.
I'm joking...mostly.
My name is Jocelyn Opal Rose,
but the family just calls me
"She's got a lotta nerve
showing her face around here
after all these years."
Ooh, for the backyard fish fry,
I brought my world-famous
"things I could find
at the gas station."
Today I'm planning
to spill a little secret.
My doctor told me that Ru
isn't just my second cousin,
she's my perfect match,
and I could really use
a kidney right now.
[hacking cough]
Michelle: Stevie Hick.
RuPaul: Jujubee.
Jujubee: Sorry I'm late.
I didn't wanna come.
[laughs]
I'm RuPaul's Asian bestie,
'cause once you go Asian,
that's all you be cravin'.
My name is Ping, but everybody
in my family calls me "Amber."
I hope you like my outfit.
For the backyard fish fry,
I brought my famous
potato salad with raisins,
which I made with potatoes
and raisins
and my secret ingredient:
MSG.
Mmm.
Today I'm planning
on spilling a family secret.
RuPaul isn't just my bestie,
she's my psychological
mommy dearest.
[laughs] Bye.
Carson: She has hat it.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Blair St. Clair.
Blair: I'm RuPaul's first cousin
twice removed
and then added again
for federal tax reasons,
from Indianapolis, Indiana.
My name is Darlene,
but everybody in my family
calls me "Stinky"
because I sure can
gas up a room real good.
[belch]
For this year's
backyard barbeque,
I brought my signature
Indiana surprise,
made with baby food
and amoxicillin.
The secret is to let it gel
for 30 minutes in the fridge
at 30 degrees Fahrenheit.
Today, I'm planning
on spilling a family secret.
Now, don't tell nobody,
but RuPaul isn't just
my first cousin twice removed.
Considering the paternity
of my newborn son,
RuPaul, you are the father!
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Those boots
were made for incarceration.
Shea Couleé.
Shea: Oh, hey, y'all.
It's me, RuPaul's
baby niece Sheaquita,
but everybody calls me
Lil Ki-Ki.
I'm wearing a one-of-a-kind
airbrushed T-shirt
by my cousin Pookie
in loving memory
of my Big Mama.
Today I was running
a little bit late,
so all I was able to bring
was the bag of "She
already done had her chips."
That was in
my glove compartment.
But my family secret
is that not only
is RuPaul my great auntie,
but she also my best friend.
For real, though, Auntie Ru.
Now, make sure y'all save me
some potato salad,
'cause I'm gonna be
right back.
Carson: Well, she left
the tags on this.
Michelle: She did.
RuPaul: Alexis Mateo.
Alexis: ¡Rrr!  ¡Hola y saludos!
I'm RuPaul's ex-housekeeper,
and my name is Carmencita.
But everyone in the family
calls me Carcita.
I'm going to hair school
on the weekdays,
but on the weekends,
I am the queen of salsa
in every bar, baby.
I'm bringing coquito
to the barbeque
because it's the best
Puerto Rican drink
in any party.
Today I want everybody to know
that RuPaul still owe me money
from back when
I was his housekeeper,
and I better get it back.
Michelle:
Wearing lime ain't no crime.
Category is
Backyard Ball Eleganza.
First, Miz Cracker.
Good girl gone badminton.
[all laugh]
Carson:
Hey, what's all the racquet?
Cracker:
Ladies, I am ready to serve.
I'm bringing Fifth Avenue
to the backyard,
and I'm bringing it to you
with a fascinator made out
of a racquet and a wiffleball.
I have wiffleball earrings,
I have a shuttlecock
on my throat,
on my shoes,
and I have a shuttlecock
under my skirt.
RuPaul: You know,
it's strange to see her alone.
She's usually with a net.
Michelle: Oh, my God.
RuPaul: Jujubee.
Carson:
Look at the melons on her!
Michelle:
Now, do you spit or swallow?
Oh, my--
The seeds, the seeds, guys!
RuPaul:
The seeds, the seeds.
Jujubee:
Ooh, girl, I am giving you
the only Laffy Taffy
Miss Taffy USA mama.
Mm. [tongue pop]
I'm wearing watermelons,
my favorite fruit.
My hair is just absolutely
perfect and coiffed.
Nobody's touching this.
I'm the watermelon lady.
Michelle:
She's got a peel.
[all snicker]
RuPaul:
I declare, Blair St. Clair.
Come on, Leg.
Carson:
It's curtains for her.
[all laugh]
Blair: My runway look
is giving you
high-fashion couture glamour.
There are pleated
ruche moments.
I'm giving you color blocking
and pattern blocking.
I have tassel moments going on,
and I am living for my
slicked-back, wet hair moment.
Feel the fantasy.
This is all real.
RuPaul: Fresh from the pool,
she's ready for Adult Swim.
[all laugh]
Shea Couleé.
Bebe: Oh, marry.
RuPaul: Who invited Grace Jones
to the picnic?
Michelle: Here comes the bride
all dressed in assless chaps.
Shea: I am serving you
backyard bridal realness.
I've got my jumpsuit
with my chaps
and my beautiful
mosquito net veil,
and all my family and friends
are here to see me
tie the knot.
Carson: She's putting the "ass"
back in "Kansas."
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Alexis Mateo.
Carson:
Is she wearing a cup?
Michelle:
She's performing a Solo act.
Darn it, I had that!
[all laugh]
Alexis: My runway look
is Alexis Mateo
the house down boots.
And I'm serving barbeque
extravaganza eleganza.
Michelle: Oh, she brought
her own flotation device.
Bam. I'm bringing
the kiddie pool, bitch,
and it's always wet
between my legs.
Carson: I like the way
this pools at the hem.
[all laugh]end act
Welcome, All Stars.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques,
starting with Miz Cracker.
Hello.
-Hello, Miss Jocelyn Opal Rose.
-That's right.
AKA "She's got a lotta nerve
showing up here after all that."
[all laugh]
It looked like you had 47 cats
and may live in your car,
but it was really fun.
It was messy,
it was--it just--
we knew exactly
who this person was.
I thought
you were really into it.
It was hilarious.
Overall tonight,
from the barbeque monologue
to both of the outfits,
you're actually my favorite.
I love this dress, by the way.
What is the top made out of?
It's some kind of seatbelt
material for hauling cars
or some kind of rope.
It seems like stuff
for straight people.
[laughs]
It looks really beautiful
and it looks really fashion
and your makeup is gorgeous.
All the way down
to the details
of the shuttlecocks
on your feet,
it's really, really thoughtful.
Since the drag gods
are watching,
I should say one thing.
Some of the support that I got
and someone that was
a cheerleader for the people
in the room was Shea.
-Thank you, Miz Cracker.
-Thank you.
Up next, Jujubee.
♪ Hello ♪
-♪ Hello ♪
-♪ Ahh ♪
The first line of your monologue
was hilarious,
because that's basically
my life.
"Sorry I'm late,
I didn't wanna come."
That's--it was hilarious.
The character that you wrote
was really funny,
and the outfit
matched the character.
The hat was ridiculous.
Where do you find a hat
with a brim--
See, there's this guy
that I kind of hang out with,
and he had the hat,
and I borrowed it.
-Aha.
-I think he got it from Italy.
-Came in a huge box.
It sure did.
Nice melons, by the way.
[all laugh]
Let's talk about the dress,
though.
This is tablecloth.
All the melons that you see
came from this mat.
I think this is very pretty,
but the seam details
on both sides
are a little bit wonky.
When you turned on the runway,
that was kind of
a little bit of a giveaway.
I hate this challenge.
[all laugh]
But I'm very proud of myself,
because I actually made a dress,
and I also received help
from Shea,
and I'm very grateful.
So thank you, Shea.
Oh, love you. Thanks.
-Thank you, Juju.
-Thank you, Ru.
I declare, it's Blair St. Clair.
-Hi, Darlene.
-Hi. How are you?
So your character, I appreciated
the Gay-tona 500 moment.
Your look was really great,
but for me, all in all,
it wasn't a knee-slapper.
I wasn't dying of laughter.
I felt a lot of lulls
in the room.
It needed to be trashier for me.
Didn't really sell
the character.
This runway look,
I do see that you put that--
was that, like,
a lawn chair webbing
that you have on the hem?
To give it some movement,
but also, like, weigh it down.
It's looking
a little messy to me.
I can tell when you were walking
that something
was undoing back here,
because you were
kind of holding it in.
And if you're gonna do
that hair, I say go for it.
I think it needs
either some gloss or, like,
just make it look either slick
or make it look dry.
It's kind of in between.
I actually love
the Debbie Harry vibes,
like the Blondie vibes.
I just think
you're so beautiful,
and, like,
I really love your makeup.
Like, I would love
for you to do my makeup.
Call me.
-Thank you, Blair.
-Thank you.
Up next, Shea Couleé.
Hello, uh, Sheaquita.
Was that your alter-ego?
Yes, but you can call me
Lil Ki-Ki.
-Lil Ki-Ki.
-[tongue pop]
I thought your play cousin
couture moment was really great.
Immediately, we had
something to relate to
with the Grandrea from
your season, from 90210.
I thought that was genius.
Loved your monologue.
It was hilarious.
You had a bag of chips,
and you ate one of the chips.
Like, I couldn't stop
watching you.
Tonight on the runway,
you took a different approach
to the picnic attire.
I think it's fun,
I think it's different.
I think it's really fresh,
because it has a story to it.
Like, I would wear this.
Like, I think it's dope.
Those are the shuttlecocks
across the sweetheart neckline?
Mm-hmm, and I just found out
that y'all call these
"shuttlecocks."
-Uh-huh.
-Yeah.
I grew up
in a Christian household.
We called them "birdies."
We weren't playing with no cocks
up on our backyard.
[laughs]
The only thing, maybe,
there's a lot going on.
Maybe I would have made it
a tiny bit less busy,
but it's still really cool.
All right, thank you.
Obviously, you are one of
the seamstresses of the bunch.
Yeah.
Because it sounds like
you had enough time
to not only make
a couture garment,
but also to help everybody else.
Why not?
I just think
it's really important
that as, like, queer people,
that we all act as family.
I understand that
this is a competition,
but if one of us looks good,
all of us look good.
Thank you, Shea.
Bam. Alexis Mateo.
Hi-ee.
I loved this look tonight,
because when you came out here,
I knew right away
those were Solo cups.
And the hair is very you,
and then of course
the big reveal.
I've never seen a dress with
a kiddie pool built into it.
Like, I wasn't expecting it
to happen,
and then when it happened,
I was, like,
that's the best thing ever.
Like, I screamed.
I would say that this look
really floods
both your basement and mine.
[laughs]
But I don't love
the way this mermaid
kind of hemline is working,
because it's really
cutting off your lower half
into another half.
So the proportion
is a little wonky for me.
The character in the beginning,
I know how funny you are,
and I felt
a little let down by her.
The dress was plain
and bright green,
and then the reveal,
the hair was really small.
I just felt like
it was kind of flat.
I wish you would have
kept the pink wig on.
I didn't like the red wig.
I just liked the pink wig.
I thought that
it was a great idea,
but then there wasn't
quite enough there
for me to sink my teeth into.
Thank you, ladies.
I think I've heard enough.
We are at the point
in the competition
that if you're not the top,
you're in the bottom.
Now, based on
the judges' critiques,
I've made some decisions.
Miz Cracker.
Con-drag-ulations.
You're the top All Star
of the week.
[applause]
You've won
a five-night stay for two,
plus airfare, at The Lalit
London in London, England.
My favorite place in the world.
Juju, Blair, Shea, Alexis,
you are the bottom All Stars
of the week.
[sighs]
Miz Cracker, you need to decide
which bottom queen to send home
if you win the lip sync
against this week's
lip sync assassin.
The rest of you need to vote
for which bottom queen
you think deserves the chop.
Thank you, ladies.
You may leave the stage.end act
[sighs]
Suddenly I'm a top four girl.
[imitates explosion]
-Oh, my God.
-Oh, my goodness.
I'm trying to appear calm,
but inside, I'm like,
looka back, looka back,
looka back at it, looka back.
Congratulations, Cracks.
-Thank you.
-Yes, Cracker.
-You worked really hard on this.
-Congratulations, Miz Cracker.
Girl.
And congratulations on top four.
Thank you. That's
what means the most to me.
How'd you feel about
the judges' critiques?
I was really crushed,
I'm not gonna lie.
I'm really frustrated right now,
because they weren't
loving this,
and I understand
and I respect opinions.
I'm not gonna stand here
and be like, "No, it's right,
and you should say it's right
because you're wrong."
That's not me,
and you guys know that.
Well, we're all in the bottom
if you're not Miz Cracker
this week.
Yeah, right. However, for me,
based on the report card,
we have two ladies
that have won challenges,
one of them twice.
And if I'm gonna go
by the report card,
it would have to be Alexis
and Blair in the bottom.
Oh, so that's the game
we're playing.
You're just gonna throw
your friend under the bus.
If I was questioning my
friendship with Cracker before,
I'm absolutely questioning
my friendship with her now.
This is not an easy one.
And because you guys
are very equal,
I wanna take each of you aside
and talk to you
so I can get that gut feeling.
I think that's just gas.
Oh, is that what that is?
[Shea laughs]
This is exactly
what I was afraid of,
because I knew that in order
to remain in the competition,
I really
had to win the challenge.
So this dream turned
into a nightmare real fast.
I'm gonna plead my case,
and I'm gonna do it quickly
and clear, okay?
Even though me and Blair
have done a great job,
and pretty much neck to neck,
I just want you all to know
that it means everything to me
to stay,
and I think that
I do deserve to continue.
I don't wanna cry because
I feel horrible doing it.
No, don't feel horrible
about your feelings.
Yeah, because I feel like,
you know, drag is joyful.
Join the party.
This is really hard,
and I'm very emotional.
I know. My stomach is,
like, literally in knots.
[sighs]
How do you unregister to vote?
[all laugh]
I just cannot go home.
I entered the werkroom, day one
I won the reading challenge,
and I've never
landed on the bottom
until we started having
a group bottom.
And I don't think it's fair
to go home yet.
I have put so much dedication,
fire, emphasis,
love into this, passion.
Yeah.
We've had differences
this competition.
Yeah.
I hope that we've
put them all aside, you know.
I hope you're hearing this
as a friend,
because I do value
your friendship.
I want you to know that whatever
the decision that I make is,
I'm not looking at
who's my best friend.
I'm looking at
who's a powerhouse.
Mm-hmm.
Who's gonna go out there
and be an inspiration.
Well, just remember I love you.
I respect your decision because
it's your decision to make.
I just cannot go home.
Cracker was my friend
coming into this competition,
but Cracker's not stupid,
and I think Cracker sees me
as some competition.
And I'm afraid that she might
find this as an opportunity
to say, well, Blair,
you had weak critiques,
and you're a threat
in my mind.
Chop.
I know you and Blair has a great
bond, you know what I mean?
Yeah, mm-hmm.
And I realize that because this
nonsense drama that happened,
that probably
in everybody else head,
I am also a choice.
But I did a great job,
you know what I mean?
-Yeah. I mean, you have.
-And I think I deserve to stay.
You've been so consistently
up there, girl.
So true.
I just want this to be an
inspiration for everybody else,
that you can still do what you
love to do when you're my age,
and continue to be there.
Yeah.
So follow your heart.
I just wanna say to you, Blair,
I could not be
more proud of you
and what you've done here.
You really do inspire me.
But do you agree
that you and Alexis
were the weakest this week?
[sighs] I mean, I agree
that we had the weakest
two critiques of the week,
but I think as a whole
in this competition
I have consistently stayed safe
or have risen to the top
every week,
and have grown and grown
and grown and grown and grown.
And, like,
I have so much more fire,
so much more passion,
determination,
talent left to show.
In your opinion,
who do you think remaining here
is the weakest?
Didn't have to say a word.
I have no idea
how the group is gonna vote.
Juju and Alexis have a lot
of history with each other,
and I know Shea
isn't Alexis' biggest fan.
But that doesn't mean
that she's necessarily
just gonna vote for her.
And I sure as hell don't know
how Cracker's gonna vote,
either.
It's scary to think that
this could be my last day.
There's one crown.
[sighs]
Fuck.
I want to win this.
I'm going to be there.
Who else
is gonna be there with me?
Oh, I'm so sorry,
I'm so sorry.
I think that you're fabulous,
extremely talented,
and I know that you're going
to go very far after this.
I love you,
but I know you can still grow,
so that's my vote.
Looking at these lipsticks,
I feel the weight
of what I'm about to do.
I could end someone's dream
tonight and it hurts,
but we can't afford to feel
those feelings right now.
My gut has already told me
what to do,
but I'm like
is there any other choice?
Do I have another option?
Can you imagine?
You want me to do it.
You, like,
secretly want me to do it.
I got it. I get it.end act
Welcome back, ladies.
Miz Cracker, would you like
to meet your opponent?
I wanna meet my opponent, Ru.
The time has come...
To present this week's
lip sync assassin.
Oh, it's gonna be
Trinity Taylor.
Ru-veal yourself!
Trinity. Nobody else
can afford feathers.
Has to be at least
$65 worth of feathers.
-Oh!
-Yes!
Bitch, it is
Miss Thick and Juicy,
Roxxxy Andrews.
I've gone to her show
in Fort Lauderdale.
Roxxxy turns the party, y'all,
and everybody in the room,
even the folks
in the back, back corner,
still feel everything
that she's serving.
Roxxxy Andrews,
welcome back, my dear.
Hi, Ru.
Is there anything
you'd like to say to me?
I'm Roxxxy Andrews,
and I'm here to make it clear
I know you love me, baby.
That's why
you brought me here...again.
[laughter and applause]
Look at you,
spittin' them rhymes.
[record scratches]
Ladies, Roxxxy Andrews
holds the lipstick
of the queen that the group
has voted to go home.
Now, if Roxxxy wins,
the queen on her lipstick
gets the chop.
-Y'all ready to slay?
-Yeah, ma'am.
I'm wearing a Spandex leo.
Two queens stand before me.
Miz Cracker, this is your chance
to impress me,
win $10.000, and earn the power
to give one of the bottom queens
the chop.
The time has come...
[thunder]
to lip sync...
[echoing] for your legacy!
Ooh-ah!
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
♪ I was a liar ♪
♪ I gave into the fire ♪
♪ I know
I should've fought it ♪
♪ At least I'm being honest ♪
♪ Feel like a failure ♪
♪ 'Cause I know
that I failed you ♪
♪ I should've done you better ♪
♪ 'Cause you don't want
a liar ♪
♪ I don't care
if you got her in your heart ♪
♪ All I really care
is you wake up in my arms ♪
♪ One last time ♪
♪ I need to be the one
who takes you home ♪
♪ I don't deserve it,
I know I don't deserve it ♪
♪ But stay with me
till morning ♪
Whoa!
[cheering]
♪ And I know and I know ♪
♪ And I know
that you got everything ♪
♪ But I got nothing here
without you, baby ♪
♪ So one last time ♪
♪ I need to be the one
who takes you home ♪
♪ One more time ♪
♪ I promise after that,
I'll let you go ♪
♪ I know
I should have fought it ♪
♪ At least
I'm being honest, baby ♪
♪ Stay with me a minute ♪
♪ I swear I'll make it
worth it for you ♪
[cheers and applause]
Bitch, you betta shake that,
Roxxxy, yes!
♪ Be the one
who takes you home ♪
♪ One more time ♪
♪ I promise after this
I'll let you go ♪
I caught it.
♪ Baby, I don't care
if you got her in your heart ♪
♪ All I really care
is you wake up in my arms ♪
♪ One last time ♪
♪ I need to be the one
who takes you home ♪
[laughter and applause]
Yes, ladies, yes!
Oh, yes!
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Roxxxy Andrews,
you are a winner, baby.
Yes!
[laughter and applause]
So thick and juicy!
The $10.000 will roll over
into next week's tip.
Miz Cracker, you are safe,
and you may step
to the back of the stage.
Okay.
Will the bottom queens
please step forward?
With great power
comes great responsibility.
Roxxxy Andrews, which queen
has the group chosen
to get the chop?
The group has spoken,
and the queen that they have
chosen to get the chop...
Alexis.
As it is written,
so it shall be done.
Alexis, you are and will
always be an All Star.
Now sashay away.
I'm disappointed,
because I really wanted
to bring that crown
to Puerto Rico.
But I will have to say
thank you to RuPaul
for a life-changing opportunity.
Not once, twice, three times.
Let me walk out of here
with style.
[laughs]
[applause]
This is a new beginning
and a new chance for me.
I am ready
to conquer the world, honey.
There's a lot of Alexis Mateo
on the way for you.
I came here with a bam,
and I still look sickening, no?
[laughter and applause]
Yes!
Con-drag-ulations, ladies,
and please remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
are you going to what?
Love somebody else.
Can I get a "amen" up in here?
-Amen!
Now let the music play.
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪vote
♪ Just like you, too ♪
RuPaul:
Next time on All Stars...
For this week's maxi-challenge,
you'll face off
in a stand-up comedy smackdown.
Miz Cracker,
you get to choose
the order in which
the queens appear.
Woof.
Nobody's getting a good spot.
I want to try to fuck
you guys up as much as possible.
Ooh, shady.
[gasps]
-Say hi to Jane Krakowski.
-Oh, my gosh, hi.
You may know me
from the STDs that I gave you.
I wouldn't open with the STD.
Ross Mathews is so gay...
How gay is he?
The only thing higher than his
voice is his estrogen level.
-Ha!
-[belches]
Wow, I'm so nervous.
[laughs]
I was not able
to come up with any material.
-[belches]
-Oh, wow.
I'm completely freaking out.
Ru-veal yourself!
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪
♪ Am-Am-Am-Am-American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪