RuPaul:
Previously on All Stars...
One Shea.
Touché.
What in the what-what?
Shea, I voted for you.
The next vote for Shea was me.
For this week's maxi-challenge,
you'll be caught behaving badly
on the gossip show SheMZ.
Miz Cracker! Miz Cracker!
Oh! Miz Cracker!
One question!
You just came into my store,
and you took everything!
I'm addicted to licking.
It makes me feel good.
Lick it! Lick it!
That can't be safe.
It took a long time to get
where y'all were gonna go.
It was a little bit
of a one-note for me.
Miz Cracker, con-drag-ulations.
You are the top All Star
of the week.
[applause]
What matters to me
is what my peers think.
I'm happy
with whatever the outcome is.
Who is this Mayhem,
and why have you checked out?
Ru-veal yourself!
-Oh!
-Oh, sis!
[cheers and applause]
Morgan McMichaels,
you're a winner, baby.
Miz Cracker,
you are also a winner, baby.
Which queen has the group chosen
to get the chop?
Mayhem.
Miz Cracker,
which queen have you chosen?
I would like
to send Mayhem home.
Mayhem, sashay away.end recap
Let's have a seat
over here, darling.
Being in the werkroom
after Mayhem's gone feels weird.
Four girls have gotten chopped,
and it is a tight competition.
But no matter what, I got a win!
Congratulations
on your $20.000 win.
$20.000.
Girl, I feel like I am 35
after a four-minute club remix.
I was just exhausted.
How do you feel?
Uh, I am so glad
to still be here.
Thank you.
That could have been
a double elimination.
Like, gag.
That was insane to me.
Ooh, we were, like, arr?
Should we look in the box
and see the votes?
-You have the power.
-Oh, yeah, stretch it. Oh.
Girl, stretch those long arms.
Girl.
Mayhem.
Mayhem. Mayhem.
She voted for herself.
I feel like
if you vote for yourself,
what you also
should be voting for
is an ass-whipping
from the rest of the cast
for taking up a slot.
I did not come here
to give up, okay?
I can't even spell that.
Imma call my mama, and she
gonna come and whup yo ass.
You never give up
on your dreams.
Do you guys feel like anyone
is the clear winner
or top right now?
If we're going based off of,
like, performance,
it would probably be
frontrunner, second,
and I'm pulling up
right behind.
Juju, I think you are
the frontrunner right now.
No, I wouldn't--
I wouldn't say that.
What about
Miss Quiet over here, too?
No, she has been consistent
like me,
but, like, we haven't win yet.
Yeah, we haven't won yet.
But I am tired,
and I wanna get outta drag,
so good night.
Started from the top.
Now I'm in the bottom.
Three weeks in a row.
#PowerBottom.
It's just so fucking tight.
Ooh, it's so tight.
-It's knotted.
-Oh, my God.
Headed into this week,
I need to get crazy, get wild.
Pblblbl.
[laughs]
I really need to just let loose.
I could just barely
get my finger in it.
Ooh, I'm so excited
I wanna shake it a little.
Oh, it's so tight!
Shea, just do it!
I've still got a ton of tricks
up my sleeve and my pants leg.
RuPaul: The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race All Stars
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
a coveted spot
in the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize of $100.000.
With our extra-special
guest judges
Tommy Dorfman
and Jeffrey Bowyer-Chapman.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪end teaser
♪ Bam bam bam bam ♪
♪ Mm, mm, mm ♪
I'm walking into the werkroom
feeling like I am invincible,
because even if I bottom today,
y'all can't get rid of me.
I just won.
Roll footage from Season 10,
me getting eliminated
after winning.
-We survived another day.
-Oh, my goodness.
I am the queen!
-Girl.
-Aw.
"Short and simple,
just like me."
I love you, queen.
-I love you, queen!
-She's the queen!
-Queen girl!
-Queen of the party!
Party!
[alarm]
Oh!
RuPaul: Ooh, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
Here we go!
Roses are red,
violets are blue-ish.
I hope you meet a nice boy
as long as he's Jewish!
Yay!
So snatchmaker, snatchmaker,
make me a match,
and the crown
could be yours, bubbeleh.
Let's hope he's a mensch.
[laughter and applause]
-Yes! Make me a match!
-Yes!
I think we all know
what that means.
I think we know
what's happening.
Hello, hello, hello.
-Oh, hi!
-Hi, ladies!
Festive!
-It's so groovy!
-Nice shoes.
My babushkas, I'm kvelling!
Now, for this week's
maxi-challenge,
we're gonna be playing...
the Snatch Game of Love.
[cheers and applause]
#AllStars5.
So get ready to open your hearts
and bust out your funniest
celebrity impersonations.
And remember, if you do well
in Snatch Game,
everyone remembers.
And if you bomb,
they really remember.
No pressure.
All Stars, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[laughs]
-Yes!
Come on, All Stars 5.
Let's get snatch-ning.
-Snatch-ning!
-Yes!
Snatch Game
is the hardest thing
that any human being
will ever do.
But I'm excited
for the Snatch Game of Love,
because it's all about
what would your character do
to snatch some love.
I never got to do Snatch Game.
-Oh, you didn't?
-No.
It's not like "Michelle Visage
is so old that--"
and you're like, what would
Alice in Wonderland say
about Michelle Visage, you know.
I wanna know if I should wear
this black turban or...
this black turban?
I'm doing Eartha Kitt
for my Snatch Game of Love.
She was Catwoman, and I don't
know if you guys know this,
but my best friends
are my two cats.
Here's Pris. Here's Mister.
I know! [kisses]
Wait, didn't Valentina do that?
-She did.
How are you gonna beat that?
I'm going to play up
her movements
and her catlike... [purrs].
Eartha Kitt's been done
two times, girl.
By Chi Chi Devayne...
[all laugh]
And by Valentina.
Monotonous!
So I am going to stand out by
serving up this piece of pussy.
[cat yowls]
-Shea.
-Yes, ma'am?
Who are you doing?
Let's see if you can guess.
Oh, my God.
-Flavor Flav?
Yeah. [laughs]
-That is so great.
-Wow.
I mean, like, who else for
a dating show of love, right?
Any fears?
Oh, yes.
Look, I was safe
with Naomi Campbell,
but safe is not the way to go.
Flavor, what time is it?
Uh, my batteries are out.
Flavor Flav is drag.
Flavor Flav
is camp.
But it could be a risk,
playing a guy for Snatch Game,
and I'm skurt.end act
I'm nervous.
I'm not gonna lie.
It is a very difficult
challenge.
Today's maxi-challenge
is Snatch Game of Love.
I did not do Snatch Game
on my season,
so this has been the one
that I've been dreading.
You need to make RuPaul laugh.
A lot of pressure.
Hey, All Stars!
Hey!
It's time for me
to get an impression
of your impersonations.
-Oh, wow.
-All right.
Oh, really?
Alexis Mateo.
Hello, RuPaul.
Now, you ain't gotta tell me
who that hair is.
-I know whose hair that is.
-Who is it?
That's Walter Mercado, baby.
Yes, Walter Mercado.
Do you know about
Walter Mercado?
Are you kidding?
Walter Mercado is a superstar.
In Latin America, this is,
like, the iconic Liberace.
How will you make
Walter Mercado funny?
The fact that he relies so much
on horoscope, planets,
and energy.
So if I ask Walter Mercado
right now,
what did you have for breakfast,
Walter Mercado?
I really have Uranus
for breakfast.
-[laughs]
-How about that, Ru?
It's exaggerating
what he already is.
Yes, well, I can't wait
to see Walter Mercado out there.
And I am so excited for him
to read you your future.
All right.
See you in a minute.
Bye, Ru.
-Hello, India.
-Hi, Ru.
Now, you've never done
Snatch Game before.
I've never, and so I want
to take a risk, and--
-Oh, you're gonna take a risk.
-I'm taking a risk.
Oh, the girl who's been in
the bottom three weeks in a row
is taking a risk.
So I have chosen
Jeffree Star.
-Jeffree Star.
Wow.
Beauty icon, YouTube sensation,
which is a risk
because many people love him,
and many people hate him.
Kind of like my life story.
But, no, no, I think
that's a fabulous idea.
Just how you gonna
make him funny?
He's actually already, like,
funny with his quirky remarks,
and he's very, like,
girl, shook.
Like, can't relate.
It's very those little remarks.
You know, I always tell people,
you gotta have those one-liners
that are ridiculous
but always work.
I can always
answer someone with,
"I don't see how that's
any of your business."
Ask me a question.
What do you think
of the weather outside?
I don't see how
that's any of your business.
[all laugh]
-It's always funny.
-It is so good, yeah.
And so, you know,
have those prepared.
If I ask you a question,
like Jeffree Star,
what'd you have for breakfast
this morning?
Um, I had some fucking
marijuana,
and, yeah, that's
none of your business.
So, yeah, I've got
a lot of preparing to do.
All right, baby.
I'll see you out there.
Thank you so much.
Comedy?
Me? Yeah.
Oof.
Why, I declare, Blair St. Clair.
Hey, Ru, what's up?
I see a short little
bobbed wig over there.
Oh, okay, yeah,
I know who it is already.
You're gonna do Ellen.
Ellen DeGeneres.
Have you done Ellen before?
I haven't, but people told me
that they get Ellen from me.
So if you're Ellen,
I'm gonna ask you a question,
and you answer me
in your Ellen voice, okay?
Hey, Ellen, what'd you have
for breakfast?
Oh, I had a kid.
It's a baby goat.
I--I--I love baby goats.
Baby goats are my favorite.
You know,
I--I--I love baby goats.
Baby goats.
I think I'm a kid at heart.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Your Ellen
didn't make me laugh just now.
It was an interesting
character study,
but it didn't make me laugh.
-Okay.
-I want you to succeed.
I want all you kids to succeed.
I want you to make me laugh.
This is scary.
I know.
[mouthing words]
Maybe I should rethink this.
Yeah, mm.
RuPaul's not buying
Ellen DeGeneres,
but there is no option B for me.
It's A or nothing.
Make me friggin' laugh.
-I will.
-Okay. All right.
Ooh.
Ugh!end act
Michelle:
From the heart of Hollywood,
it's time to play
Snatch Game of Love.
And here's the snatchmaker
himself, RuPaul!
Welcome.
Love is in the air.
So let's meet
our celebrity snatchelorettes.
First up, Oscar, Grammy,
Golden Globe winner Lady Gaga.
Hello, Ru.
You know, there could be
a hundred people in a room,
and maybe 99 of them
don't believe in you.
But one of them has $100.000
to give away,
so I'm happy to be here.
Okay. Up next,
it's the legendary astrologer
Walter Mercado.
Thank you, divine,
for having me.
Now, do you see love
in your future?
I see many big things
in my future.
Oh, really, like what?
One of them is not love.
[laughs]
And next, we have makeup mogul
Jeffree Star is here.
Hi, how are ya?
Now, Jeffree, I wanna know.
What's the foundation
for a healthy relationship?
Oh, baby, the foundation
is all body fluids.
All body fluids.
It's a really strong foundation.
All right.
Lovers, are you ready
to play the Snatch Game of Love?
Ooh, I'm divine even.
Let's close that sugar wall.
All right.
Originally from the A-T-L,
our first snatchelor
is a real peach.
Welcome, Tommy Dorfman.
[cheers and applause]
-Hi, Tommy.
-Hi, Ru.
Look at that outfit.
That is so gorgeous.
Thank you.
Tommy, are you feeling the love?
Primarily from my gut down.
Oh, from your gut down.
That's a good sign.
But it might be because the belt
is cutting off my circulation.
[all laugh]
All right, now
here's how the game works.
You ask our celebrities
some very personal questions,
and they try to woo you
with their answers.
Now, when the buzzer goes off,
you choose your dream snatch.
All right, let's get started.
Okay, contestant number one,
finish this sentence.
Women are jealous of my blank.
My sense of smell.
Aw.
Is that too on the nose?
Perfect.
Contestant number two.
-Mm-hmm.
-Women are jealous of my blank.
Women are always jealous
about my sixth sense,
because I can
predict the future,
and I can see the present.
I bet you you have a belt
right now.
[laughs]
Wow, that's uncanny!
That is unbelievable.
Incredible.
Contestant number three.
Women are jealous
of my big pink vault.
Vault?
It holds many things.
Oh, like money and stuff.
And private belongings.
Oh, okay.
All right.
It's hard to watch.
Contestant number two,
based on what contestant
number one is wearing right now,
what would their fashion line
be called?
Well, I'm looking here,
and I think the fashion line
could be called
A Star is Born Into Poverty.
It was my question, dumb bitch.
[all laugh]
But you didn't see
that one coming!
I did.
Well, do you wanna answer?
Yes. It looks like
purple toilet paper.
That's all.
All right,
contestant number three,
gently blow
into contestant two's face.
[blows]
Contestant two,
what does contestant three's
breath smell like?
It smells like confusion.
[all laugh]
And lots of regrets.
But I could have tell you that
without even smelling
her breath,
because I am a psychic,
and I can tell.
She's confused
and she regrets being here.
[all laugh]
Contestant three,
what does contestant
number two's breath smell like?
Whew. Smells like a cheap wig,
cheap dollar-store cosmetics,
vodka, with a splash of regret.
-Mm.
-Whew.
You didn't see
that one coming.
Mm-mm. Neither did you.
[all laugh]
Oh!
Contestant number one,
what flavor of ice cream
best describes you,
and convince me
why I should lick you.
Well, as an Italian New Yorker
who's a New Yorker
with an Italian background,
I don't think I'm an ice cream,
I'm more of a gelato.
And if you wanna know about
my flavor, I can't remember.
I forgotto.
[all laugh]
Can't relate.
I thought I was
an American horror story.
Ooh-hoo-hoo.
The Star is Unborn.
Jeffree Star
is unborn right now.
I keep it very simple, you know.
Just like my hair,
I'm gonna say vanilla,
because everybody loves
fucking vanilla, man.
Pick me.
[all laugh]
It doesn't take
a sixth sense, baby.
[all laugh]
I'm gonna space.
Contestant number three.
Well, I wrote a little
something for you, okay?
I'll give you Dairy Queen,
pink dreams,
tongue all on your ice cream.
Open up my thighs,
show you the surprise.
Oh, wow.
Ahh.
I didn't see that one coming.
Nope.
It was dark.
To cool that down.
-Contestant number three.
-Mm-hmm?
If you could possess
one superpower,
what would it be
and how would you use it on me?
Probably to fly, so we can
get up outta this bitch,
I can grab you, we can fly,
and I can feed you
this ice cream sandwich
between these legs.
He don't want it.
-[laughs]
-He don't want it.
I can see it in your future.
Did you see that in the stars?
It's in the universe now.
[all laugh]
[buzzer]
Oh, there's our buzzer.
Time's up, Tommy.
Who do you choose?
Will it be
snatchelorette number one,
number two, or number three?
I'm gonna have to go
with contestant number two.
[cheers and applause]
Oh, I saw that coming.
I am psychic.
But before you meet
snatchelorette number two,
let's meet
who you didn't choose.
Tommy, meet Lady Gaga.
Whoa!
Such a pleasure.
Oh, my goodness. Mwah.
Tommy, say hello
to Jeffree Star.
Hi, how are you?
-Good. How are you?
-Good.
Call me.
He's not a real psychic.
He'll never see it coming.
[all laugh]
All right, Tommy, a sugar wall
stands between you
and your dream snatch.
-Whew.
-Move that wall!
Tommy, it's Walter Mercado!
-Tommy, little Tommy!
-Wow.
Come here.
Give a hug.
Gimme a hug.
You smell good.
I was looking in my future,
and I saw you coming.
Yes.
[all laugh]
Well, there you have it.
Another snatch made in heaven.
[cheers and applause]
Don't go anywhere.
We'll be right back
with more Snatch Game of Love
after this.
After you!
Good luck, you two.
Have fun.end act
Welcome back
to the Snatch Game of Love.
Let's meet our next batch
of celebrity snatchelorettes.
First up, it's America's
sweetheart,
Ellen DeGeneres.
How are you, Ru?
Now, Ellen,
when it comes to romance,
how important
is a sense of humor?
Romance?
I already have a wife at home.
You do, don't you?
Yeah, what am I doing here?
All right,
she's back, back, back again.
It's the legendary Eartha Kitt.
[purrs] Hello, kitty girl.
Yes. Now, Eartha,
does love have nine lives?
-Love has many lives, like cats.
-Yes.
And I know Ellen
likes pussy, too.
[all laugh]
The godfather
of reality dating shows,
it's Flavor Flav.
Flavor Flav!
What's up, my boy Ru?
Hey, Flav.
I'm so excited to be here,
I'm on cloud nine.
I feel like my feet
can't touch the floor.
Look at 'em!
RuPaul, she scares me.
Is it she?
Gender is a construct, man.
Tear it apart.
I'm stranger than fiction,
but better than art!
You know what I'm saying?
Whoo!
Oh, this is gonna be good.
All right, are you all ready
to snatch a snatchelor tonight?
Never been readier.
I love a good snatch. Whoo!
Close the sugar wall!
Our next snatchelor hails
from the Great White North,
but why it gotta be white?
Please welcome
Jeffrey Bowyer-Chapman.
Hi, Jeffrey.
Hi. It's been a while.
You look good.
Thank you.
So you're single again, I see.
Looking for love.
Wait. Wait a minute.
Is that the shirt I bought you?
It still smells like you.
[record scratch]
[exhales]
Okay. Let's play
the Snatch Game of Love.
All right, let's do this.
Contestant number one,
finish this sentence.
When people meet me, the first
thing they notice is blank.
I'm gay!
[all laugh]
And you know,
it's working out for me now.
No complaints and not many
symptoms these days.
All right, contestant
number two, same question.
The first thing somebody notices
about me is my big, wet smile.
[all laugh]
-[purrs]
-Contestant number three.
What they normally notice
is my big, fat, 14-inch clock.
You know what time it is?
No, really, I'm asking.
My clock's been stuck on 4:20
since 1985.
[all laugh]
Whoo!
[purrs]
Contestant number two,
I'm originally from Canada,
so if we went up there
for a winter visit,
how would you
keep me warm at night?
I would sensually
walk to the thermostat...
and turn up the thermostat
to a sensible 74.
[all laugh]
I need a woman like you
in my life.
If this shit don't work out,
we should bang
in the parking lot.
[all laugh]
Juju and Shea
are doing so great,
I should feel terrible.
But I'm laughing too hard
to worry about that.
This is a masterpiece.
Contestant number three,
same question.
The best way to keep warm
is to pile in a bed
with six other bitches.
And by bitches,
I mean teacup Pomeranians.
Them dogs are so cute.
[all laugh]
They're all fuzzy and shit.
And contestant number one.
Well, you know, I'd have to
bring the necessities with me.
I'd have to bring
my butler Batu,
my gardener Rosa,
and my housekeeper Jennifer,
and we'd all pile up together
like penguins
and squawk to keep warm.
[squawks]
All right.
[crickets]
White people, right?
Back in my day,
we called this "white noise."
[all laugh]
Contestant number three,
starting with the line
"roses are red,"
recite a romantic poem
about why I should pick you.
[clears throat]
Roses are red, buses is yellow,
I just realized...
that you are a fellow.
[all laugh]
Yeah, boy!
And contestant number two.
Roses are red, violets are blue,
pick me 'cause I love you.
[all laugh]
That was mad creative.
You know, you remind me
a lot of my mama.
She was baldheaded, too.
[all laugh]
Contestant number one,
pretend that you're a frog
and I'm a prince,
and convince me to kiss you.
I don't think
I could seduce you.
I think I'll have to
pass it on to the next one.
All right.
Contestant number two,
same question.
Ribbit, ribbit.
I am a lady frog,
and you are a sweet prince.
I am convincing you.
[all laugh]
Oh, shit,
there goes my gold-plated ring.
You know how many child support
checks I didn't turn in
just so I could get
this shit?
[buzzer]
Oh, Jeffrey,
that means time is up.
It's time to decide
who snatched your heart.
Is it snatchelorette
number one,
number two, or number three?
Contestant number three.
Contestant
number three.
Flavor Flav, yeah!
[laughs]
That's what's up!
That's my boy!
Whoo!
All right, Jeffrey,
let's meet
the two snatchelorettes
you didn't choose.
Say hello to Ellen DeGeneres.
-Hi, there.
-Howdy! I'm Ellen.
-Good to meet you, Ellen.
-Let's take a selfie.
[all laugh]
-Adios.
-That's amazing.
Arrivederci, avocado!
[all laugh]
Jeffrey, say hello
to the great Eartha Kitt.
[purrs]
You're lost, my darling.
[all laugh]
Jeffrey, only
a thin, pink sugar wall
stands between you
and the snatch of your dreams.
Say hello to Flavor Flav!
Yeah, boy, what's up, what's up?
Aow, aow, aow, aow, aow, aow!
So what, we going
to Red Lobster or what?
Yeah, you got it.
All right. Biscuits on you!
And maybe later on me! Aow!
[all laugh]
Till next time,
everybody say, love.
-Love!
Everybody say, Jeffrey,
why didn't you call me back?
Oh, Ru, you had me
at hello, hello, hello.
-What?
-Yeah.
[cheers and applause]
Way to go, RuPaula!
[cries]end act
Girl, yes!
Oh, my camel toe's
pretty loud, though.
Love that moose knuckle.
She's calling me.
I'm feeling pretty secure
about my performance yesterday.
I thought my Snatch Game
was amazing,
and I think I could win.
[kisses]
Send it to the universe.
[laughs]
You killed it.
I was surprised.
As I was doing it,
I was, like, oh, my God.
I loved your character, too.
-I think you did a good job.
-Eartha Kitt?
I know, third time's the charm.
That's right.
[both laugh]
If I have to say
f somebody is in trouble,
it might be India, right?
Here's the thing.
If she's in the bottom again,
then what do we do?
Because this would be,
what, her fourth time?
Her fourth time.
That is crazy.
India is my Season 3 sister,
so of course there's
more connection there
than the other girls.
I don't wanna see her
going home,
but I might be worried
for my sister.
How are you feeling, India?
I'm feeling good.
I mean, I've never done
Snatch Game before.
I'm sure
I could have made it funnier.
But you know what?
I did it. It's over with.
You feel proud?
Yeah.
-Hey, Walter Mercado.
-Huh?
Can you predict
who you think is in the top
and who you think
is in the bottom?
What do you see for us?
Yeah, we wanna know.
If you wanna know the results,
you have to call
my psychic line.
[all laugh]
It's $400 a minute.
[laughs]
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
Take your time, bitch!
Yes!
[all laugh]
♪ Cover girl ♪
And what?
Welcome to the main stage of
RuPaul's Drag Race All Stars.
Come on, Michelle Visage,
do you believe in love?
Well, I got something
to say about it,
but I won't continue, because
it'll cost us royalties, so...
[all laugh]
The hilarious Ross Mathews.
Now, how far do you go
on the first date?
About eight,
eight and a half inches.
I thought
you were gonna say "Pacoima."
[all laugh]
I would never go to Pacoima.
And the talented
Tommy Dorfman.
Now, have you ever dated
a drag queen?
Actually,
Violet Chachki and I dated
when we were in high school.
I bet you've got
the stories to tell, don't you?
Oh, I do, but I think
I'll keep those private.
[all laugh]
And Jeffrey Bowyer-Chapman,
thanks for coming back.
You know, people crazily think
that we have some type
of sexual tension between us.
-That's totally crazy, Ru.
-Crazy!
[laughs]
[dramatic music plays]
[meows]
[chomp]
Wait, I don't get it.
I don't get it, either.
Yeah.
This week,
we challenged our queens
to make us fall in love
with their best
celebrity impersonations.
And tonight on the runway,
category is Prom Queen Fantasy.
Hey, you guys wanna see
my prom photo?
Here it is.
Uh, that's me on the left.
-[gasps]
-Aw!
[all laugh]
Stunning.
I'm really looking forward
to my 10th high school reunion
this year.
[all laugh]
I don't get what's so funny.
All Stars, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
♪ Everyone can be someone ♪
Category is Prom Queen Fantasy.
First up, Miz Cracker.
Michelle:
She's a proactive drag queen.
[all laugh]
Cracker: In my prom dress
with my acne,
I am everything
that I wanna be:
funny, pretty, stupid.
Ross: Be right back-ne.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Alexis Mateo.
Jeffrey: Cha-cha-cha!
Alexis: My prom queen look
is very quinceañera.
And I'm not wearing no corsage
because I am single and ready
to mingle at my prom, baby.
[laughs]
RuPaul:
Wham, glam, thank you, bam.
[all laugh]
India Ferrah.
She's the kind of girl
who will spike the punch.
-With actual spikes.
-Yeah.
India: I am giving you
full-on Morticia Addams
goes to the prom.
Gothic, tears down my eyes.
I am living the dark fantasy.
Ross: When will they finally
invent waterproof mascara?
RuPaul: I do declare,
it's Blair St. Clair.
You know, tuxedo rentals
have really improved
since I was in high school.
Blair: Today on the runway,
I am giving you
gender-bent illusion.
I am the prom queen and king.
-Aw.
-Oh.
Tommy: Oh, put
a mother-tucking crown on it.
RuPaul: Jujubee.
Tommy: Betsey Johnson fantasy.
Jujubee: My prom queen
fantasy look
is giving you eighties.
I'm giving you crimped hair,
don't care.
Yes, mama.
RuPaul: Don't crimp her style.
Shea Couleé.
Everything's coming down roses.
[all laugh]
Shea: I'm serving you Carrie
meets my Season 9 elimination.
There is a crown
that is pouring out
this cascade of rose petals,
and I am living.
Ross: But she's still got
a rosy outlook.
She does, she does.end act
Welcome, ladies.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
Starting with Miz Cracker.
Hello, Mama.
Tonight on the runway,
I think the dress
is kind of not as prommy
as it is showgirly or saloony.
It's not
some glamour prom moment,
it's a hilarious
prom zit nightmare.
That's such a great,
funny concept.
The Snatch Game performance,
I am never, ever bored
with whatever Gaga gives me,
-and I was bored.
-Yeah.
I just felt like Cracker
was being Cracker
doing some Lady Gaga lines.
I see that almost
surgical Cracker
who is overthinking it again.
You're a control bitch, and
you wanna control everything.
And it's all in your head.
Use your gut.
Let go, and, uh...
let God-- [laughs]
-I was not gonna say that.
-Who are you?
-Let go and let God.
-Really?
Michelle, write that down.
I think that's good.
[all laugh]
I think it's really good.
Yeah. Thank you, Miz Cracker.
Thank you all.
Up next, Alexis Mateo, girl.
I love this look.
It's perfect.
I wouldn't change
a single thing.
I loved not just a peek of leg,
but the full leg.
When we watched
the Snatch Game and I saw you,
I knew exactly who you were
because I grew up
watching Walter Mercado.
You were so funny
and so in the moment.
I mean, truly,
the definition of "yes, and."
You did for me
what I want every queen
to do for me in a Snatch Game.
You edu-tainted me--
or edu-taint--
you taught me something,
and you made me laugh.
I had no reference
for Walter Mercado,
but after watching
your performance,
I know exactly
who Walter Mercado is.
What were you saying
about taint?
[all laugh]
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
-India Ferrah.
-Hi.
I love your runway.
I feel like we would have
been friends in high school.
I don't know that I get
the prom, necessarily,
but if a girl showed up
to my prom looking like that,
I would tell her
how great she looked.
Now let's talk...oh...
about Snatch Game of Love.
Oh, India, there was no Jeffree
in your Jeffree.
Jeffree is such a character,
there's so much
you can do with him.
It was definitely a miss for me.
Blair St. Clair.
Yes.
The gender-fuckery of it all,
the top hat,
the reveal with the crown,
I wish I could have looked
like this at my own prom.
You look beautiful.
You know, my husband and I
do an impersonation of you
walking down the runway.
Because on your season,
she had on a fur coat,
and she walked to the end
of the runway, and she went ooh!
Shh.
[all laugh]
She's cold.
Don't tell anybody she's cold.
It's a secret!
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit,
I'm gonna pop something.
[all laugh]
Oh, my God. Oh.
The Snatch Game,
I felt that
you were kind of giving me
the same note throughout.
You know, relying
solely on lesbian jokes.
I mean, I'm gay, but not
every joke that I make
is about, like,
hot dogs and eggplants.
You get a big A for effort,
because it was really good.
It just wasn't that funny.
Thank you, Blair.
Shh.
Thank you so much.
-Up next, Jujubee.
-Hi.
Hey, you didn't choose me.
[all laugh]
What was I thinking?
You weren't.
Con-drag-ulations on serving
the best Eartha Kitt
that I've ever seen
on this show.
-Yes.
-Okay.
Wow.
If any other queen
ever wants to do Eartha Kitt
again in Snatch Game,
they gotta come to you
and you gotta give 'em
an Eartha Kitt kit.
This look tonight, Juju,
I just wanna eat you up.
You're just like
a little lavender lollipop.
You're the only one to really do
an eighties spin on prom.
And it brought me back
to my youth.
No, Michelle, I mean the 1980s.
[all laugh]
All right, thank you, Juju.
Thank you, Ru.
Up next, Shea Butter Couleé.
Hey.
So I have this thing
with doing cis male hetero
characters on Snatch Game,
because, you know,
this is a drag show,
and if you're gonna do that,
it needs to be a huge
personality like Flavor MF Flav.
[all laugh]
You hit it out of the park.
I think that will go down
as one of the best Snatch Game
performances in history.
No one's ever done Flavor Flav,
and it's about time.
[all laugh]
When I go home tonight,
this is the look
that I'm going to remember.
You look incredible.
We're getting kind of
a Carrie-meets-Sasha Velour
at the finale.
Yeah, that's right on.
I just wanted to base a look
around a moment
where I thought I was
gonna be queen of the prom,
and it didn't turn out
like that for me.
And for, like, the next year
at meet-and-greets,
fans would take off their hats
and rose petals would fall out.
Because I was the butt
of this joke,
and I wanted to find an
opportunity to reclaim my rose.
I find it interesting that you
felt like the butt of some joke.
You know, I would never
think of you as a joke.
Um...
I was really devastated.
I'm not gonna lie.
And it took me being surrounded
with people who loved me
and kept me inspired
and pushed me to keep going,
because those...
those are the very people
that are responsible
for me standing here right now.
Well, count us amongst them.
Thank you.
Love you.
I love you, too.
-Thank you, Shea.
-Thank you.
Thank you, ladies.
Now, based on
the judges' critiques,
I've made some decisions.
Shea Couleé, con-drag-ulations.
You are the top All Star
of the week.
[applause]
Oh, my God. [laughs]
Oh, thank you guys so much.
You've won a seven-night stay
at a luxury apartment
in Paris, France,
airfare included,
courtesy of misterb&b.
Holy shit.
I'm just trying to think of
something real cute to say,
but that's a cute prize.
Thank you.
Now, ladies, starting today,
there will be
no more safe queens.
What?
If you're not the top All Star,
you are in the bottom.
This is crazy.
I did so well in the
Snatch Game and in this runway,
and I can go home tonight.
Shea Couleé, you need to decide
which of the bottom queens
to send home...
if you win the lip sync
against this week's
lip sync assassin.
The rest of you need to vote
for which bottom queen
you think deserves el choppo.
[stifled laughter]
So while you queens deliberate
in the werkroom
on Objects furniture,
the judges and I
will be writing poetry.
You may leave the stage.end act
Ooh, yes.
This is how you elegantly
walk into a room, ladies.
Show the children
how to walk, mama.
It wouldn't be All Stars 5
without another twist.
[laughs]
-Baby.
-Ru tells us
if you're not in the top
from here on out,
you're in the bottom.
Thank God I'm in the top
this week. Ha!
-Congratulations.
How does it feel
to get a second win?
A second win is cool,
but this was Snatch Game.
To win such
an important challenge
was really validating for me.
Oh, my gosh, guys, are you
as gagged as I am right now?
Everyone's in the bottom
except for Shea.
Except for Shea.
I hate that.
I mean, honestly, it feels like
I'm in the clear bottom two
based on the critiques.
So you say bottom two.
Based on the critiques,
who do you think
is in the bottom with you?
I think India and I
are in the bottom together.
Alexis, how are you feeling?
This is the first time
of me in the bottom,
so it's strange. Yeah.
This is not fair that on a day
that I got good critiques,
RuPaul throw this twist on us.
What the fuck, man?
I'm not gonna lie.
There's been this lingering
thing in the back of my head
where I was just all, like,
Alexis Mateo tried to get me
out of this competition.
And I just wanna know why
I should pick somebody else's
lipstick over yours.
When I did that vote,
I was doing it
to sleep at night,
to keep friendships.
Nothing against you.
It was in my heart, and I knew
you were not going anywhere.
I would never do something
to none of you on purpose,
to anybody.
Now, that being said,
don't try to come for me
just because you might feel
like, oh, she voted against me.
If it's in your nature
and that's your truth
to send me home,
remember, everything you do,
every action has a consequence,
and you have to live with that.
Do you wanna talk one-on-one?
No, I feel like I have
everything that I need.
Can I request that I talk to you
one-on-one, if you don't mind?
Oh, yeah, sure.
No, I don't mind.
-Yeah, here, let's talk.
-I would like to.
I am hearing
complete bullshit.
I know the T,
and if I happen to leave
this competition tonight,
I'm not leaving
without letting Shea know
the juice
that I'm about to spill.
I can't sit there
hearing something
that is weighing on me.
Do you remember when you were in
the bottom with me and Mariah?
Mm-hmm.
Alexis and Mayhem came to me,
asking me to put your lipstick.
-What?
-Yes.
They came to me and asked me
to put your lipstick in.
Plotting? Against me?
I felt like there was
some shady shit going on,
and now all of a sudden
I have someone telling me
right to my face that there was.
I'm not asking you
to vote her out,
but I can tell you
I need to be here.
Yeah.
So I need you
to keep me here, please.
I need you to think about that.
I really appreciate
you telling me this.
-Yeah.
-I really appreciate that.
I'm not about this whole
"she said, she said" business.
So I wanna bring it up in front
of the rest of the girls
and see what really went down.
India and I had a conversation,
and she let me know
that when I was in the bottom,
you and Mayhem came up to her,
telling her that
she should choose my lipstick.
I did that to you, India?
-When?
-You and Mayhem both.
The night me, Mariah,
and her were all in the bottom,
said, "Are we doing it?
Did you get Shea's lipstick?"
And I said,
"No, I did Mariah's."
No, I didn't.
India is the queen of stunts.
She should have her own show
in Vegas called The Stunt Queen,
because this is
the biggest shenanigans
I ever heard in my life.
You said it wasn't personal,
but to campaign to get me out
of this competition
feels personal.
I did not. I did not.
You're lying.
I'm not lying, girl.
Did I campaign
with you guys?
No, I--not to us.
I did not say
"Let's get rid of Shea."
My vote, I did it
because I didn't wanna do that
to Mariah personally.
Lies, lies, lies.
Big lies.
Well, then why not vote
for India?
Because India,
I thought we were friends,
but now I realize
we're not.
My vote and my conscience
is clean.
You can really sit there
and say that?
I am. I am, because
you know what, that is--
-That shocks me.
-That's a lie.
I'm real.
I'm not here to play a game.
That's been weighing
on my shoulders.
-No, you're playing a game.
-I wanna be here.
Let me tell you
why you're playing the game.
I'm not playing the game.
Because you know
you are about to go home,
because you have been
in the bottom for so long.
And now you need a little plug
to save yourself.
I have never say anything
about getting rid
about nobody here.
I am so aggravated right now,
because I know Shea
is not 100% secure with me,
and also, this stunt
can cause the other girls
to vote against me,
and I can probably just go home
for something
that I didn't even do.
I can sit here
with a very clean conscience
-and look in your eyes...
-This is stupid.
and say that I am not
playing games.
This is not for me.
Why else would I pull you
to the side?
Maybe it's a little shady of me,
but I actually wanna see
if this is real,
because somebody here is lying.
This is the biggest stunt
in the history of All Stars.
Are you lying to me
or is she lying?
No, I'm not lying to nobody.
Because I trust you.
A lot.
You cannot do that, Juju,
because you know
I would never lie to you.
-For why would I lie to you?
-I know, I know.
I didn't vote for her because
I wanted to get rid of her.
I just didn't want Mariah
to feel bad.
I'm so confused right now.
I don't even know
what's real anymore.
Now I'm starting to feel like
there is this person
that is here in the competition
who's playing two games,
and that's where I'm starting
to become concerned,
because do I want to keep
that type of competitor around?
Shea, can we talk?
-Yeah, sure, girl.
-Please.
Yeah.
This whole setup
about you going home, girl,
if I was gonna campaign, it was
not gonna just be me and Mayhem.
-We needed everybody.
-Yeah.
For a campaign,
you gotta campaign.
Not with one or two.
You gotta campaign
with all the girls.
It doesn't work if the majority
of the votes are not in.
Hands down.
Politics.
What saddens me the most,
she's campaigning
on that sofa right now
for me to go home.
Why would she throw you
under the bus like that?
I don't know,
and she was my friend.
This competition can bring
the worst of everybody,
and now I understand
Derrick very well.
This was a very clear
fuck-you
in your face, Alexis, moment.
And even though India's makeup
and hair is pretty,
you got some ugly demons
inside you, girl.
India has
one of the worst report cards
in Drag Race history right now.
But she has made us
look very hard at Alexis.
Mayhem style.
You're a liar,
and this is why
Derrick don't like you.
I don't know what to feel.
I am so confused.
Oh, why not?
No, I'm kidding.
If India is lying,
she would have been
a better actor,
which means she would have been
better at Snatch Game.
Is it Alexis?
Is Alexis the villain?
Oh, my gosh.
The truth shall set you free.
Girl, stop acting a fool.
I came into this
wanting to judge these girls
based off their performance,
and India has been in the bottom
four times.
But I've been, like,
roped into some other game
where Alexis potentially
has campaigned to get rid of me.
[sighs] Oh, God.
I don't know if I can survive
allowing someone like that
to continue
competing against me.end act
Welcome back, All Stars.
Shea Couleé, are you ready
to meet your lip sync opponent?
Well, I guess so.
[all laugh]
The time has come...
to present this week's
lip sync assassin.
Is that Laganja?
Laganja?
I think it could be Trinity.
Ru-veal yourself!
That's a short heel for Laganja.
Somebody with little feet.
Aah!
[screaming and laughter]
[laughs]
You're damn right!
The lip sync assassin
is Vanessa Vanjie, my daughter.
I cannot even enjoy the moment
when I see
my drag daughter again,
because if she wins the lip sync
and she holding my lipstick,
it could be humiliating for me.
Vanessa Vanjie Mateo, welcome.
Thank you.
Ladies, Miss Vanjie
holds the lipstick
of the queen that the group
has voted to go home.
If Vanjie wins the lip sync,
the queen on her lipstick
gets the chop.
And the $10.000 will roll over
into next week's tip.
I don't get no fif--no--
-Uh-uh.
-[laughs]
Y'all ready to slay?
I was born to slay.
Two queens stand before me.
Shea, this is your chance
to impress me,
win $10.000,
and earn the power
to give one of the bottom queens
the chop.
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing] for your legacy!
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
[music plays]
♪ I see you on the street,
and you walk on by ♪
♪ You make me want to
hang my head down and cry ♪
♪ If you gave me half a chance
you'd see ♪
♪ My desire
burning inside of me ♪
♪ But you choose
to look the other way ♪
♪ I've had to work
much harder than this ♪
♪ For something I want,
don't try to resist me ♪
♪ Open your heart to me, baby ♪
♪ I hold the lock,
and you hold the key ♪
♪ Open your heart to me,
darlin' ♪
♪ I'll give you love if you,
you turn the key ♪
♪ I think that you're afraid
to look in my eyes ♪
♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ You look a little sad, boy,
I wonder why ♪
♪ Don't try to run,
I can keep up with you ♪
♪ Nothing can stop me
from trying ♪
♪ You've got to open
your heart to me, baby... ♪
Shea goes hard.
Splits, kicks, slams it.
What are you doing, Shea bitch?
♪ You hold the key ♪
♪ Open your heart to me,
darlin' ♪
♪ I'll give you love
if you, you turn the key ♪
♪ Open your heart,
I'll make you love me ♪
[cheers and applause]
Yes! Whoo!
Bitch, that was everything.
-Bitch!
-Yeah!
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Shea Couleé, con-drag-ulations.
You're a winner, baby.
[applause]
Whoo!
Ooh.
You've earned a cash tip
of $10.000.
Oh, God I normally love
more than just the tip,
but that'll do.
[all laugh]
Ooh, she is a nasty ho.
Vanessa Vanjie Mateo,
are you gonna say hi
to your drag mama?
Aw.
Aw, mother and daughter reunion.
-Bye, Vanjie.
Bye, Vanjie.
♪ Open your legs to me ♪
I shoulda did that.
I coulda won.
Oh, my God.
[laughter and applause]
Will the bottom queens
please step forward,
which would be everybody.
Shea, with great power
comes great responsibility.
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
At first, I felt like
I had my mind made up
about who I was going to pick
to send home.
But one of the bottom queens
revealed to me
that someone here may or may not
have been campaigning to
send me home a few weeks back.
[sighs] I thought
long and hard about this,
and the queen that I've chosen
to go home tonight is...
India.
As it is written,
so it shall be done.
India Ferrah, you are
and will always be an All Star.
Now sashay away.
Ladies, I want you
to remember the four Hs, okay?
I want you to live happy.
I want you to listen
to your heart, okay?
I want you to remain humble,
and most of all, be honest.
The old me would be
so disappointed in leaving.
Now I can leave
with my head held high
because I got to show all
the different sides of India.
I was not lying to you.
I'm not gonna be at home
sitting on my couch,
being, like,
"I wish I had done more."
Because I am
so fucking proud of myself.
Like... [exhales]
Mwah. See you soon!
She left off one of the Hs.
Be a ho.
Aow!
Con-drag-ulations, All Stars.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell are you
gonna love somebody else?
-Can I get an "amen" up in here?
-Amen!
All right,
now let the music play!
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪vote
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪
RuPaul: Next time
on All Stars...
It hurts me,
because India was my friend.
No one really knows
what happened.
Whatever is done in the dark,
it will come out to the light.
Mm-hmm.
For this week's maxi-challenge,
we're throwing
a Charles family backyard ball.
[all laugh]
What the fuck
is backyard eleganza?
My major in school
was theater costume design,
so I'm not a stranger
to a sewing machine.
I'm so-so with sewing.
-[laughs]
-No!
I felt really lost.
I wouldn't be here today
without those friends.
[sniffles]
I wouldn't be here.
Ru-veal yourself!
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪
♪ Am-Am-Am-Am-American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪