RuPaul: Previously
on All Stars...
You'll be debuting
the smash hit I'm in Love.
Oh, yeah!
Do you think that you voted
for the wrong person?
I should have brought in
some Wite-Out,
because Ongina,
you didn't believe in yourself.
Are we playing
mental warfare here?
I'm gonna get rid of her.
-I'll take it from you.
-I can just--
It's not the Cracker show.
We have a time limit.
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love ♪
♪ I'm in love with him ♪
♪ He's tall, dark,
long, and lean ♪
♪ And he rocks my kitty world
like you never seen ♪
I did kind of find myself
wandering to other people
a little bit.
I liked your look more than
I liked your performance.
On these stages,
with all these animals,
you've gotta fight
for every moment that you get.
You don't have to deliberate
with me,
because these two do not deserve
to go home at all tonight.
I made your morning difficult
a while ago, and it was stupid.
Ru-veal yourself!
[cheering]
Shea Couleé,
you're a winner, baby.
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
Ongina.
Ongina, sashay away.
What...a...day.
Two girls have gone home now,
and it's starting to get real.
This is going to happen
every single week.
It's gonna get tough.
Feelings will get hurt.
But I'm feeling $20.000 richer.
Congratulations, Shea.
Yes, bitch.
How you feel?
It feels good to be
in a position like this,
but also it was really hard
to send our girl Ongina home.
But, um, I felt like
it was her time.
Ongina was mentally checked out.
I want to make sure
that whoever I keep here
is hungry and capable
of handling all the challenges
that this competition
throws our way.
I'm curious to see--
How everyone voted?
Well, open it.
Okay.
All right,
let's lay 'em all out.
One for Ongina, two for Ongina.
Ongina, Ongina,
Ongina, Ongina.
Unanimous.
I am still angry with her,
because she just gave up.
She was, like, doing damage
control before it happened.
If I went home and found out
someone else gave up,
I'd be devastated.
This is an opportunity
of a lifetime,
and there are so many girls
that would love to be here.
If anyone else wants to give up,
speak now
or forever hold your peace.
Mariah, how are you feeling
right now?
I'm letting my lady parts
calm down.
I'm still vibrating from being
that close to being sent home.
It just took my breath away,
not in a good way.
-Mm-hmm.
-Yeah.
Ugh, yeah.
Oh, my gosh.
There is a little moment
of relief right now,
but with that relief
is a big old scoop of reality.
And I never wanna be
in the bottom again.
I know y'all spent the coin,
but I spent the mint, bitch.
[all laugh]
So y'all gonna have to shove,
kick me in the back of the head
with a high heel
to get me up outta here.
All right, girls,
let's take this off.
Let's take this--
Oh, God,
I could go for a corndog.
How do you feel
beating Alyssa Edwards?
I mean, bitch.
I'm like, what universe
am I living in?
Coming to the competition,
I thought Shea Couleé
was the queen to beat,
and she's in the top of the game
right now.
Alyssa Edwards?
-Girl, oh, my God.
-In a lip sync?
Girl, gag.
But I'm not scared
to compete with her.
I'm here to win the big prize,
not just a challenge.
And tomorrow
is a brand-new day, baby.
They better wake up and see me,
because I'm coming.
No one is safe.
Bam.
RuPaul: The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race All Stars
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
a coveted spot
in the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize of $100.000.
With our extra-special
guest judges
design superstar
Martyn Lawrence Bullard
and the hilarious Nicole Byer.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
-Hi.
-Whee!end teaser
Skip to m'Lou, my darlin'.
Another day.
Alive to survive.
Mr. Cameraman, show me my mark.
Into the werkroom
and the fantasy.
Hold my hand and guide me
gently--gently to my place.
I'll take my mark now.
-Oh!
"I can't wait for our
friendships to blossom more
"outside of this werkroom.
I love you, Ongina."
Aw, we love you, Ongina.
Oh, it's not going anywhere.
Nobody's ever gonna accuse you
of being a domestic.
Well, girl, with $20.000,
you won't never have to
clean a mirror again.
Can I borrow a 20?
When I get home
and see Ongina, I know her.
She gonna be like, "I really
shouldn't have quit, huh?"
"I really--I really should have
stayed, you guys, huh?"
[all laugh]
So, Cracker,
this is the real talk.
What was the purpose
of going in to Ongina
in the beginning of the morning?
Do you think that you voted
for the wrong person?
I should have brought in
some Wite-Out,
because Ongina,
you didn't believe in yourself.
Like, is this a "strag-edy"
you're trying to do
with everybody's mind?
My intention was to say,
"Ongina, I want you
to believe in yourself,
because I need to see that."
And I went about it wrong.
I should have said that,
not what I said.
And, uh...
Are you okay, Mayhem?
[laughs]
Girl, I don't believe
not none of this.
-I'm just gonna be real.
-Right.
I really don't believe
none of it.
Same.
I smell shenanigans, foolery,
and some tricks and shows.
Is this for real, or are you
just playing a game?
It's not feeling authentic, sis.
All I can do is apologize
and say that I was wrong.
She's not here any longer,
and now you're gonna say
you apologize?
It's done.
From now on, we all have
to really show who we are.
I wanna get to know everybody
for real,
because if I ever in a position
to send anybody home,
if I don't trust you,
I'm gonna go against you.
Alexis wants you to be real,
she wants to be clear
about things,
she wants to trust you,
she wants to know who you are.
I think you're playing
head games, Miss Alexis,
and it's working on
some of these bitches.
I made one mistake, and--
It was not a mistake.
It was just a situation.
Okay.
[alarm]
-Baby!
Ru done saved the day.
Saved by the bell.subtitle
RuPaul: Ooh, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
Hey, All Stars,
welcome to the Ru-mada Inn.
You want room service?
Well, bitch,
here's a wake-up call.
Ain't nobody got time
for your baggage.
Ooh!
So who doesn't have time
for my baggage?
I love two-star hotels!
Hello, hello, hello, ladies!
-Hi!
Ooh! There you are.
Come on, resort wear.
[laughs]
Now, ladies, as All Stars,
you know firsthand that
VIP travelers these days
don't just want a room,
they want
an unforgettable experience.
I know I do.
In this week's maxi-challenge,
you'll be starring in the
hottest new hotel design show,
Shantay Enjoy Your Stay!
Now, working in teams,
you need to design and present
your own signature suite
worthy of a five-star
Ru-tique hotel.
[applause]
#AllStars5.
Feel free to use materials
from the F&S Fabrics wall
and Objects furniture.
Now, we did
a random drawing earlier,
and the teams are Miz Cracker,
Mariah Paris Balenciaga,
and Shea Couleé.
-Oh!
-Okay!
The next team is Jujubee,
India Ferrah, and Alexis Mateo.
And last but not least, Mayhem
Miller and Blair St. Clair.
All Stars, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
-Yeah!
-Yeah!end act
♪ Together again ♪
We are always together
on everything.
Today's maxi-challenge
has got to be
one of the most difficult
in RuPaul's Drag Race history,
because there are so many parts.
What are the things
that you like about
when you're staying
in a hotel?
Glamour and glitter.
I like glamour.
All right.
Not only do we have to create
a hotel suite,
we have to create a welcome
basket, a signature nightcap,
we have to give a room tour.
But most importantly,
we have got to sell this suite.
We can make everything,
like, gold, like, all golden.
Okay. Gold is rich.
-Gold is rich.
-It's exclusive.
Oh, my gosh,
okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
♪ The ideas ♪
Me and Blair
are teammates again. Ha-ha!
Hopefully we will be able
to vibe a little bit better
without Cracker.
We gonna win this week.
I can feel it.
I'm really kind of disappointed
that you guys had
"say something" hat day today,
and didn't tell me about it.
[all laugh]
So we need to pick a theme,
clearly.
Does anyone have any ideas, or--
-I think--
-Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh!
Wild Alaska. The room
is just all Alaska-themed.
There would be, like,
a river with salmon,
there would be, like, snow,
an Alaskan pipeline underneath.
Yeah, I don't wanna stay there.
This is really, really difficult
for me to admit,
but it's my third time here and
I've never won a main challenge.
I have to change that.
I really want something
kind of, like, tropical.
But this is a design challenge,
and I'm paired with two bitches
with questionable taste.
What are we gonna do,
like, a jungle or something
that is outside--
I actually really like
the whole jungle idea.
Let's be real. My taste
is questionable, too.
I shouldn't be here talking
shit about my teammates.shit
[laughs]
Write it out, bitch.
So we need to have
a clear concept.
Right, and one of my favorite
shows in the whole entire world
is The Golden Girls.
Baby, I can watch that
over and over and over again
on reruns.
I think, like, nostalgia
is a very powerful thing.
The Golden Gals,
the Golden Gals' Palace, the--
[gasps]
The Golden Gals' Palace.
My closest friend on Season 10
was anxiety,
and after the drama
this morning, she's back.
Beachy, eighties Miami.
-Miami.
-Right.
Okay. Right, okay.
The girls are not happy
with Cracker.
They think that
I am scheming and shady,
and I'm starting to spiral.
I think, honestly, the most
iconic bedroom is Blanche's,
with that banana-leaf wallpaper.
Yeah, that kind of thing.
Everybody knows a banana leaf.
Yeah. I think in Season 10,
I would have been like,
"I'm gonna fall apart right now.
It's happening. Here we go.
Aah!"
But do I wanna be in
the midst of a mental breakdown
when I go out
to perform for RuPaul?
Nerp.
Picture it. 1923, Sicily.
[laughs]
Ooh.
Oh, wow.
This is a big space.
It's time to design our suite,
and I see paintbrushes,
goggles, smocks.
I'm just, like, okay, I hope
they don't expect me to do it.
Now, I'm not used to doing,
like, labors.
I'm not that girl.
Ru's picture's right here.
The bed's right here,
the bar's right here,
the couch is right here.
Do you wanna see
how the couch looks?
And then--
Or--I mean--
I'm very delicate.
I'm more delicate.
There is no butch queen
on this team.
Please be light.
-Lift with your legs.
-Oh, my God.
[grunts]
You guys, I can't find Blair.
[laughs]
The goal for our luxury suite
is to make it look expensive.
Oh, look at all this opulence.
We have a lot of rich stuff.
This gonna be Versailles,
this gonna be a palace.
This gonna be real fancy.
This gonna be the Gottis' house.
Should we take a step back
and look at this again?
No, trust our gut.
Juju, girl, what the hell?
That's how your makeup looks
the way it does.
Have you ever fucking
painted a room, bitch?bleep
Yes.
Now I got a clue who hasn't.
Oh, my God,
we are gonna be garbage.
I cannot help
this process at all.
Do we have a ladder?
Golden Gals.
I'm with you, girl.
I'm gonna put a seagull.
Yes! [laughs]
Fly the seagull
into that sunset.
Look. Already looks like
a winning room to me.
I'm on a team with Shea Couleé
on a bad day, which is great.
We have chemistry, and it makes
everything so much easier.
She's putting the "sis" back
in "Sistine Chapel," girl.
[laughs]
I'm gonna paint a beautiful
sunset in my Golden Gals' room,
where my spirit lives right now.
As long as the rattan furniture
has been Pledge-scrubbed,
everything's okay.
Oh, you guys,
this is super cute.
I could definitely see Shrek
loving this place.
So what's y'all's color palette,
like just like brown and green?
Yeah, like your foundation.
This is nice.
-Oh!
-Oh, really!
This is real nice.
These bitches, you know,
sometimes it gets annoying.
It's like being in a daycare.
Don't touch me,
because I got paint.
I'm just gonna let them bark.
I will put
the dogs to sleep later.
You're Xed outta this place.
Please continue walking
this way.
That green is drying
a lot darker than I imagined.
Yeah, and I love it.
This is an exclusive
motherfucking wild ridem-fucking
to the other side.
A one-of-a-kind experience.
Well, this is one of a kind.end
act
Runway day, runway day.
Today we're getting ready
to present our hotel suites.
Oh, yeah, that definitely smells
like a freakin' trouser snake.
I'm not completely confident
with what we're doing,
but I'm still
gonna sell this damn room.
I know you guys
are not very good into,
like, designing interiors,
but this is not just that.
It's also about
who we are as a group.
Right, it's also us being
exaggerated versions
of ourselves.
Right.
Our personalities need to shine.
I'm a little worried,
because I gotta present
a luxury hotel suite
with two very strong
personalities,
and stand out on my own.
I need to shave my face.
Do you guys
need help shaving your backs?
Why we don't leave
our backs hairy?
So it's really a 4D experience.
That's true.
But please make sure
you shave all your chins.
Girl, I could not sleep
last night.
This challenge is so hard, so--
But the more that
we work together on this,
the more I'm feeling more sound.
I mean, we had some challenges
in the last challenge,
and we pushed through that.
Because, like, I was
so thrown off by Cracker.
But I think, like, we got
each other in this challenge.
At this point
in the competition,
everything's
a little nerve-wracking.
But with Cracker not being
involved in this challenge,
Mayhem and I are doing
really great together.
I think what Cracker's
missing out on
is taking ownership
of her behavior,
and the things that she does
and the things that she says.
Instead of having an explanation
about everything,
just be like,
"You know what? I'm sorry."
And I just don't feel
the sincerity, unfortunately.
-Right.
-I don't.
That Miami sunset color palette,
you turnt it.
You picked the perfect colors.
We created a view, y'all.
I could sit there
and look at that sunset,
my little glass of sherry.
And some piping hot tea.
Oh, bitch, you--oh, we're
gonna be pouring it later.
My group is playing characters
inspired by The Golden Girls.
Shea's gonna be Shea D. Arthur,
Cracker is gonna be Rosebud,
and, of course, I'm gonna be
Balenciaga Devereaux,
kind of like the cheeky, slutty,
always flirting with the help
kind of girl.
It's right up my alley.
So, Cracker,
it was a little bit rough
at the table yesterday
with everyone.
I feel like people
are not happy with me,
and I took it
to a place in my head
where I was like, "I'm bad.
I'm bad Cracker." You know?
Right. [laughs]
And then it took me
a little while
and working with you guys
and seeing our success
to be like, "You know what?
Not bad Cracker."
Just, like, bad situation.
Well, I've definitely enjoyed
working with you this week.
I think it's all about
chemistry.
Yeah, definitely.
Like, the people that I respect
are Shea and Mariah and Juju
and those people
that I really look up to,
and those are people
that I am working well with.
So everything else, I will learn
and work on and get there.
So you don't respect me?
Is that
what you're trying to say?
what you heard from that?
Yeah.
[hiss]
Fuck!
I said I'm working with people
that I respect.
Yeah.
Girl, I am not ready
for the Alexis shark attack,
and she is going in
for the kill.
Listen, sweetheart, you're
trying to make a conflict--
Don't "sweetheart" me, because
I'm not sweethearting you.
I'm not deaf, so I can hear you.
I was saying that I am working
well with people that I respect,
and that makes me feel better,
and that the rest
is a learning curve.
And the reason why
yesterday morning
was so, like, intense for you
was because of me,
and I'm still waiting for you
to come to talk to me.
But it's easier for you
to just talk there.
I honestly don't think
that that is the T.
You know, I had asked her
just how she was feeling.
And her comment about working
with people that she respects,
I don't think that
that was, like, any shade.
Bitch, who was talking to you?
No one
was even talking about you.
We were having a tender moment
over here as a team,
talking about
how much fun we had,
and then you have to pipe up
and try and get into
my teammate's head.
You told me,
"Girl, you've gotta watch
the way you interact
with people."
And I walked away with that
to this group,
and I was, like,
I am going to make sure
that I am the best me
for this group.
So I really listened
to what you said.
At least you're aware
of what is happening in my head.
Does that make sense?
Many moments and years,
I have trouble communicating,
because this is not
my first language.
Second language, my ass.
I could be an asshole
and just say, you know what?
I'm done with Miz Cracker.
I don't wanna get to know her.
You know,
I don't wanna be that diva.
How the fuck this bitch say
this is her second language,fuck
and she been going for hours?
[laughs]
A lot of girls talk about you
behind your back.
Oh, I could be one of them
and just go behind your back
and tell everybody how we gonna
get rid of you, but I'm not.
I know.
I'm not.
And I hear everything
that you're saying.
I think people
are piling on Cracker
because people
are threatened by Cracker.
They know that
she's tough competition,
and I feel like they actually
are getting in Cracker's head.
And I'm like,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Hold up. Wait a minute.
Don't go there,
because I ain't with it.
That's my teammate, and we've
got a challenge to focus on.
I can't wait to see
how this turns out.end act
RuPaul: Pack your drag.
It's time to put the "T"
in "travel"
with Shantay Enjoy Your Stay!,
the show that takes you
inside sickening suites
designed by the world's
draggiest design divas.
Tonight, the queensgraphic
are turning up
the turn-down service
for extra-special guests
Michelle Visage, Ross Mathews,
design superstar
Martyn Lawrence Bullard,
and Nicole Byer.
First up, sissy that walker
over to the Golden Gals'
Palace & Resort.
You're just in time
for the early bird special.
Why, hello and welcome.
I'm Balenciaga Devereaux.
I'm Shea D. Arthur.
I'm Rosebud.
And welcome...
[all] To the Golden Gals'
Palace & Resort.
Come on in.
The Golden Gals' Palace & Resort
is designed to make you feel
warm, welcome, and comfortable.
Picture it. Floor to ceiling
plate-glass windows
giving you a lovely scenic view
of the Miami sunset.
We feature reclaimed
rattan furniture,
which is also real fancy
for "used wicker."
We have a gorgeous armchair
with a heated afghan.
-Ooh.
-Mm.
Every other hotel in the world
has wifi
and Internet accessibility,
but we have a landline
with free local calls.
So you could remind
your grandchildren
it's been a while
since they've seen you.
[disconnect signal]
Hello?
First, we're gonna hope
that you indulge yourself
in our complimentary
gift basket,
featuring an assortment
of girthy meats and cheeses.
I love girthy meats.
[doorbell]
What was that?
I think we have some company.
Well, let's not be rude.
Let's go welcome our guests.
-Oh, welcome!
-Oh!
Hi, hi, hi!
Some of the people
who've had their final rest here
include Frank Sinatra,
Bob Hope.
Oh, but there's
a waiting list, too.
We have the Lady Bunny
and the Bianca Del Rio.
Now, they expect to come by
very soon.
There is no Golden Gals' evening
complete
without a sinfully delicious
piece of cream cheese pie.
Cream cheese pie,
Rosebud?
-Oh, I'm sorry.
-Cheesecake!
Yeah, there ya go.
Any time you need a little
extra assistance late at night,
we have a full-time gentleman
caller butler service.
All you have to do is hit
this emergency alert button...
[alarm]
and some dear gentlemen callers
will be with you right away.
Can I have that button?
-Full service.
-I could never.
Thank you so much
for visiting us here.
Make sure to tip the boys,
but just the tip.
And don't hesitate to tell
everyone you know about us.
Now, thanks for coming, and...
[all] Thank you
for being a friend.
[laughs]
Where'd the cheesecake go?
RuPaul: Your RuPaul-iday
continues.
Next stop, let's get wild
in the Glamazone
with Alexis Mateo,
India Ferrah, and Jujubee.
Bienvenidos
to a wild adventure at the...
[all] Glamazone.
[all purr]
Come inside.
I've said that before.
It smells just like a jungle.
Lots of animals,
ah-ah-ah-ah,
and everything in the wild.
[growls]
We're wearing
leopard print dresses.
Mm-hmm.
[snarls]
Right here in our rhino room
you're gonna feel right at home.
Here I am, sitting on a chair
that my grandma made.
She made this
with her two bare hands.
I sat on her lap.
Oh, she was chewing tobacco.
All the stories I heard.
Didn't understand a word.
This is the P-P bar.
Party-Party bar, everybody.
My grandma
also made this chair.
Ahh. Ooh, your grandma
might wanna reinforce that.
Oh, don't talk
about my grandma, bitch.
We have our very own
golden showerhead,
and it's gonna leave you
with a warm sensation of joy.
[moans]
[all moan]
And this is where
all the magic happens.
These sheets are infused
with 15-karat Laotian gold,
and there is a mosquito net
to protect you from the live
mosquitoes we've released.
[buzzing]
But not to worry,
because in our welcoming basket
we have mosquito Ru-pellent.
-Ooh, yes.
-Ooh.
And of course we include the
most exotic fruit we can find.
What the hell just happened?
Bananas, oranges,
apples, and grapes.
[all growl]
-[hiss]
-Hi, ladies.
All: Welcome to The Glamazone.
Mmm. Smells like bananas.
You're just in time
for our signature nightcap.
-Yes!
-I love a drink!
Oye, oye.
There goes our butler.
-Oh!
Our signature nightcap
is a mix of natural flavors,
and, of course, a mysterious
ingredient to help you relax.
Ooh!
It's the ultimate place to stay
if you're excited
about the jungle.
Not only can you pet the pets,
but they pet you back.
Wow, that is wild.
This only happens at...
[all] The Glamazone.
[all growl]
[hiss]
Come on, lay with me.
Did your grandmother
make this, too?
-Oh, yes, girl.
-Oh, boy.
You know how long
it took her to make this?
-No, how long?
-Now lay down.
-Okay.
-Do you see the stars?
Oh! I see the stars.
You guys are gonna be protected.
It's like a giant condom.
-Oh, look at that!
-Oh, thank you!
Night-night!
-Night-night.
-Have sweet dreams.
Oh, my God, they are ready
for bed, everybody.
So come see us soon here at...
-The Glamazone.
[soft growls]
RuPaul: For our last Ru-sort,
we're going for the gold
in the 24-karat Experience,
presented by Blair St. Clair
and Lamé.
Oh, hi there.
I'm Blair St. Clair.
And I'm Lamé.
Have you ever wondered
what it would be like
to vacation
like an A-list celebrity?
Everybody wants to be
a celebrity.
Here in the 24 Karat room,
you can do just that.
So let's take a look
in our fullest of fantasies.
Mm-hmm.
The 24 Karat room is luxury.
-Rich.
-How rich?
Very rich.
So rich.
Daddy rich.
We offer you
your very own selfie chaise.
Just look and click.
[whispers] Expensive.
-Rich.
You wanna know who else
has been here, Blair?
Tell me.
The Kardashians.
All of them?
-Even Rob.
-[gasps]
Can you name all the Jacksons?
All of them?
Even Rebbie.
Boo. A magic mirror.
Mirror, mirror, on the wall,
who is the fairest
and the goldest of them all?
It's you, bitch.
You are fierce as hell.
You can slay
the house down boots.
Yes, God, okurr?
I feel rich!
[whispers] Expensive.
Rich.
[whispers] Expensive rich.
In our gift basket, our guests
will receive Golden Mist.
It smells like what?
-Success.
-Oh!
And this,
a golden bath bomb nugget,
made from pixie dust
and pirate lust.
I love gold bath bombs.
Lamé, do you hear that?
Ooh, I just hear
the money coming.
-Hello. Welcome.
-Hello.
Welcome to the 24 Karat room.
The glamour
is almost unbearable.
Can't you feel the power?
[whispers] You smell rich.
We are rich, darling.
Golden God?
Of course we have
a signature nightcap,
a golden elixir that is made
from leprechaun tears
and infused with
golden goose juice.
Shaken, not stirred.
-Ooh.
-What do you taste?
I taste money.
-I taste dividends.
-Mmm.
[whispers]
It tastes like chicken.
Now we must put you to bed,
because I'm sure
you're exhausted.
-Yes, we are. Yes, yes.
-So exhausted.
Beyond.
Oh, okay, I'll go over here.
Well, thank you.
These sheets!
-How does it feel?
-[gasps]
They feel like gold.
Do you feel...
-Rich?
Ooh, very.
How rich?
The richest.
You should book your stay
in the 24 Karat room today.
Actually, we're all booked up.
Oh!
-Shh.
-Don't let the goldbugs bite.
Those are also expensive.
They cost us a lot of money.
RuPaul: Thanks for joining us
on Shantay Enjoy Your Stay!
And remember, nobody
tucks you in like a queen.end
act
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
♪ Cover girl ♪
And what?
[applause]
Welcome to the main stage of
RuPaul's Drag Race All Stars.
She puts the "ho" in "hotel,"
Michelle Visage.
You know I'm the head manager
of the Whore Seasons.
[all laugh]
He puts the "mo" in "motel,"
the hilarious Ross Mathews.
Motel 96.
[all laugh]
Design superstar
Martyn Lawrence Bullard.
Now, should the carpet
match the drapes?
If you want, Ru.
But you know, I always prefer
a hardwood floor.
Oh, the English.
[all laugh]
And a woman who does not need
a wake-up call, Nicole Byer.
How do you like my dress?
Oh, my God,
I think you nailed it.
[all laugh]
This week,
we challenged our All Stars
to create their own Ru-tique
hotel experiences,
and tonight on the runway,
category is Three, Three,
Three Looks In One.
All Stars, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
♪ Everyone can be someone ♪
Up first, Blair St. Clair.
Oh, I do declare.
Blair: Today on the runway
I am giving you
a travel-through-time fantasy.
I'm starting off
in my 1950s Sunday best dress.
Nicole:
Yes, from the bed to the plane.
Next, I'm giving you
my 1960s Twiggy fantasy
in this yellow mod dress.
And girl, you could take this
on the go-go.
Ross:
I'll have some warm nuts.
-Ooh!
-Ooh, yes!
Nicole:
Straight to the disco!
I am finishing in my
Studio 54 inspired fantasy.
She is metallic, she is golden,
she is shifty.
Ross: Now boarding,
Studio 54.
RuPaul: Mayhem Miller.
-Ooh.
-Yes.
Mayhem: I am giving you
vintage, honey.
I'm looking expensive,
and I'm here not only
checking in to the hotel,
I'm gonna have cocktails,
and then I'm gonna say,
"It's hot in here,
I'm gonna go for a dip."
-Wapow!
-Ooh!
Martyn: Oh, my goodness.
Nicole:
Yes, don't get the wig wet.
Got that bathing cap on!
RuPaul: Uh-huh.
I am Dorothy Dandridge,
and I'm gonna put
my big old toe in the pool,
and they're gonna
have to drain it,
because I'm too sickening.
Nicole:
Ooh, with that fat ass,
she's going right
to the bottom of the ocean.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Alexis Mateo.
Ross: She looks like
a big top.
RuPaul: Yes.
Michelle:
That's not what I heard.
[all laugh]
Alexis: I love the circus,
so I am serving a three looks
in one circus theme.
I start in the tent.
-[gasps]
-Ooh!
Then I go to a ballerina.
Nicole: Now we know
what's under the big top.
Yes!
-A lime ballerina.
-Uh-huh.
[Martyn laughs]
-Ooh!
-Oh!
-Yes!
I finish in a trapeze artist.
And, ooh, I look good, bitch.
RuPaul: Send in the clowns.
India Ferrah.
Martyn: Oh, baby.
RuPaul: I think I'm getting
a herringboner.
[all laugh]
India: I'm serving three-in-one,
black-and-brown houndstooth
couture realness.
Nicole: I'll just leave this
right here.
-Yes.
-Uh-huh.
And I'm giving you reveal
after reveal after reveal.
-Oh!
RuPaul: From demure to whore
in seconds.
Michelle: Yes!
[all laugh]
This is 1990s
Vogue magazine cover,
and I feel stunning.
Michelle:
I love this pussy belt, mm.
RuPaul: Yes. This pussy's
under lock and key.
Jujubee.
-Yes!
-Ooh!
Ross: Can't decide if this
is a trick or a treat.
RuPaul: It's a trick.
[all laugh]
Jujubee: I am serving you
the sickest, witchiest witch.
She's the queen of Halloween.
-Oh!
Nicole:
I love this Mrs. Claus.
You know Santa's really
getting it every night.
And then I am giving you
a Santa baby.
She's a little slutty,
but she's still a good girl,
so she's not
on the naughty list.
-Oh!
Oh, my goodness, that's Jujubee!
The beaster bunny.
The truth is,
I really love Thanksgiving,
but I was not gonna come in
dressed like a pilgrim
because of
cultural appropriation.
I do not want a pilgrim
to be upset with me.
RuPaul:
A queen for all seasons.
Mariah Paris Balenciaga. Ooh.
Michelle:
Drag in virtual reality.
RuPaul: Yes.
Mariah: These looks
are inspired by New York City.
Once you leave the house,
you're out all day long.
First, I'm going to a party
with all of my girlfriends,
and I am completely feeling
my Susanne Bartsch fantasy.
RuPaul: Oh, okay, dark lady.
After that, me and my husband
are going to have cocktails
with the boss.
Here she is, fellas.
-Ooh.
-Oh, yes!
Ross: That LBD is a BFD.
[all laugh]
My third look is very elegant.
It was inspired by a gown
that JLo had worn
on the red carpet.
Michelle: These have always
brought me luck.
RuPaul: Mm-hmm.
Miz Cracker. Oh!
[Nicole laughs]
Ross: Feed me, Seymour!
[all laugh]
Cracker: My three-in-one runway
is quintessential Cracker.
It's glam, but it's silly.
-Oh!
RuPaul: She's really
coming out of her shell.
Michelle: She is.
Oh!
Yes.
RuPaul: What?
-Ooh.
-Oh.
RuPaul: Wait a minute now.
I'm telling the story
of Anastasia.
We have a Fabergé egg,
the princess herself,
and the princess on the run
after the Revolution.
RuPaul: Wow.
Nicole: I love it.
RuPaul: Shea Couleé.
[all laugh]
-Wow.
-Whoa.
Shea: My three-in-one look
is based off of
the rosy maple moth
mixed with
a Lisa Frank character.
RuPaul: You larvae it?
Michelle: I larvae it.
I'm trailing my gorgeous,
iridescent organza skirt,
and then I come out
of my chrysalis.
RuPaul: I'm getting Kate Moth.
[all laugh]
-Oh!
-Ooh!
I spread my wings, bitch,
and take flight,
because I know the judges
are living for this look.
Ross: Are those
two wings on your back,
or are you just happy
to see me?
[all laugh]end act
Welcome, All Stars.
Based on your performances
and runway presentations,
I've made some decisions.
My favorite suite
this week is...
The 24 Karat Gold Experience.
-Did she say that for real?
-Yeah.
Shut the fuck up. [laughs]fuck
You're lying.
But the best performance
of the week
was by a queen
from another group.
Jujubee, con-drag-ulations.
You're the top All Star
of the week.
All right.
-Thank you.
-Yes.
I've been waiting a really
long time to win something.
Thank you.
You want a carrot?
[all laugh]
You've won a seven-night stay
for two
in the penthouse suite
at the Grand Resort and Spa
in Fort Lauderdale, Florida.
-Ooh!
Thank you.
Jujubee, you need to choose
one of the bottom queens
to send home
if you win the lip sync
against this week's
secret lip sync assassin.
The rest of you need to vote
for which bottom queen
you think deserves the chop.
Jujubee, Blair, and Mayhem,
you may leave the stage.
Thank you.
Ladies, it's time
for the judges' critiques.
First up, Alexis Mateo. Bam.
Hello.
In the Glamazone,
I thought you had
some really funny moments.
You are a queen
that is effortlessly funny.
You can truly just,
like, blink at people
and to me, it's funny.
I thought your suite
was spectacular.
I loved the P-P Bar.
[all laugh]
Tonight on the runway,
your three-in-one looks,
you actually really did
three fully different looks,
and I appreciate that.
With that said,
they were a lot to look at.
Was this, like, a circus theme?
Yes.
Okay, well, particularly
the middle outfit
I just thought didn't work
in between the two.
India Ferrah.
Hi.
The three looks
were all very, very different,
but they were related.
They looked like they came
from the same planet.
The outfits were amazing.
I love the fabric.
By the way, when you're finished
with it, I wanna do a chair.
[all laugh]
Ooh.
In the hotel suite,
what did you bring to that?
The golden shower
was, like, the main thing
that I was, like,
supposed to, like, focus on
and really embrace.
You know, Martyn,
you have to pay a little extra
for the golden shower.
[all laugh]
Yeah, but it's worth it.
In the Glamazone zone,
between Alexis and Juju,
you were kind of the one
that fell back for me.
You just were kind of getting
lost in the background.
You always wanna be on a team
of strong people, right?
But then what can happen
is if you don't elbow
your way to the front,
you're suddenly in the shadows.
I'm sorry.
Mariah Paris Balenciaga.
Tonight on the runway,
I mean, you always
look beautiful, Mariah,
but I will say taking
a jacket off is not a look.
Okay.
So Golden Gals' Palace,
you three set yourself up
for a very big job,
because I am
a Golden Girls fanatic,
I know Ru's
I know Ross
is a Golden Girls fanatic.
And the thing that was missing
were jokes.
There were no jokes.
Your room, from the palm leaves
to the whole vibe, I loved it.
I thought the room
looked really great.
But the dodgy old bedsheets
and the weird pillow,
that didn't look like anything
I wanted to get into.
Miss Devereaux
is one of the greatest
characters ever written.
She was
the original Samantha Jones.
She just,
she owned her sexiness,
and I wanted more whore.
It's why I love Michelle Visage
so much.
[all laugh]
[French accent]
Miz Cracker.
Mademoiselle.
I was just so enthralled
by the entrance.
Each look was great.
Okay.
You were Rosebud.
There were a few things
that really made me laugh.
Hello?
But there was a lot
of fun moments and ideas
that just fell flat.
I thought you were really funny,
but, like, I think
you're missing a little bit
of being spontaneous
and in the moment.
[sighs]
Are you okay?
Yeah. It's been, like,
the wildest ride of my life.
And I think as Alexis will know,
sort of having a hard time
connecting with people.
Fuck that. Who cares?fuck
Don't listen to anybody.
You're you.
You are fabulous.
Be you. Who cares about
what anybody else is saying?
Thank you, Cracker.
Up next, Shea Couleé.
Hey!
[all laugh]
I love how colorful it is.
I love how bright it is.
But it is a little crafty.
It could be a little refined.
Your room, it really felt
like a Golden Girls set,
which I loved.
But I did feel that
your character was a little off.
Shea D. Arthur, Bea Arthur,
I think you had
her seriousness down.
She just wasn't funny.
You also, like, set up
some jokes that didn't pay off.
Like, the "picture this" moment
was super fun,
and then there was, like,
no more of that.
I mean, you were using Sophia's
catchphrases as Dorothy,
which I think--
I didn't read the whole bible,
but I don't think
you're allowed to do that.
[all laugh]
Everyone could have just
turned it up to a 10.
I feel like everyone
was playing it safe.
It turned into a hotel room
with just three elderly women.
Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
Now, based on
the judges' critiques,
I've made some decisions.
Alexis Mateo.
Miz Cracker.
You are safe.
India Ferrah.
Shea Couleé.
Mariah Paris Balenciaga.
You are the bottom All Stars
of the week...
and will be up for elimination
officially.
You may leave the stage.end act
-Hi!
Come on in.
Bone-jour.
Girl, I am gooped, gagged.
I am in the bottom three.
I could be going home tonight,
and I'm feeling so fragile.
Con-drag-ulations, Miss Winner.
Thank you.
I mean, I'm very grateful
and I'm very happy
and I'm very excited.
It was my first win.
-Yes. Con-drag-ulations.
-Thank you.
But I didn't get to be up there
to hear what happened.
I'm in the bottom three.
Yes, they're bottom three.
-Again?
-Oh, again.
India, myself, and Shea.
What?
They did not like my look.
They said that they did not
enjoy the experience.
Literally, they said that it was
a room full of three old ladies.
I personally think
that's a good time.
-I'm so confused.
-Oh, you're confused?
I keep providing good drag.
I keep providing India.
For once, for once
in my fucking life,fucking
I am proving who I am as India,
and I couldn't be happier.
But I did a challenge in between
two fucking amazing
queens,fucking
and now I have the chance
that I'm getting sent home
on something
I've waited eight years for.
And I don't wanna...
Right.
I don't.
Oh, wow.
These girls are so emotional.
Like, dang.
This is hard.
It's really hard.
Whew.
I guess I have to do
what I've gotta do, right?
Who--
I'll go.
-You wanna go first?
-Let's do it.
I am so frustrated.
Michelle's critique
about my runway look
is bullshit
with a bow wrapped around
it,bullshit
because I don't do
any half on anything.
Jujubee:
All right, girl.
And I just really didn't think
I was gonna be
in the bottom three.
You already know
that I love you.
This whole competition
is, uh--
-Full of surprises.
-Yes.
Mm-hmm.
Coming into this competition,
I came back,
wanted to push myself
and push my boundaries,
and have a good time doing it.
Do I need to work harder
on pushing my personality
out on camera?
Yes, but I'm light-years
ahead of where I was.
That doesn't make it easier
for me at all.
-No, it doesn't.
-No.
We came into this
knowing that we have to make
these tough decisions.
I know.
But, like, it sucks.
Anything worth doing
is not always easy.
I just wanna stay.
So this week was a miss for me.
I just hope that I've earned
your guys' respect enough.
Girl, you have a track record,
and an American track record--
But everyone gets to make
their decision for themselves.
This is what's great
about All Stars.
Nobody knows
what's going to happen.
You could fuck up every day
and land in the top four.fuck
You could slay it
and get manila-ed
because you are at the mercy
of other queens,
and queens are crazy.
We all know that Shea
is a powerhouse of a queen.
Absolutely.
But honestly, she got the worst
critiques on the runway.
Right. We all know that
she is a huge competitor.
Yeah.
So do we send the competitor
home tonight?
I wanna tell you
that I want to be here.
This is my dream.
And I'm just really hoping
that you see it in yourself
to give me a second chance.
The decision is so hard to make.
Mm-hmm.
It's easy to say, "Oh, well,
I'm gonna play fair."
I wanna beat
the best of the best.
But if you want that crown,
you're gonna play the game.
And Shea is in the bottom.
I could vote for Shea to leave.
Ooh, is this strategy, bitch?
I do hope
I make the right decision.
How do you feel?
Second week, bottom three.
I did not want to be
in this position again.
Sometimes it's not your day,
you know?
No, it's not, but sometimes
it might be my last day.
And hopefully,
that's not the case tonight.
And honestly, Cracker,
I didn't know
how I was gonna feel
being on a team with you,
because of the static
and tension that your group had
in last week's challenge.
And I must say, I really
thoroughly enjoyed myself,
and I wouldn't
have traded my group.
-I wouldn't.
-[sniffles]
It hurts being
in the bottom three again,
but I'm still proud.
You should be.
You always should be.
You're Mariah.
-Bitch.
-[laughs]
I'm gonna toast
to my motherfucking
self.m-fucking
[laughs]
If I go home tonight,
I will be absolutely devastated,
because I worked so hard
to get here.
And to have it end this way,
ugh, it would just be
so disappointing.
Coming from the top,
there's only one way
to come down.
[sighs] I just don't know
how I could even possibly fathom
making this decision.
World out there,
it's harder than you think.
Don't judge me for being sappy,
because this
really is difficult.
I'm sorry.
No matter who I pick,
Imma make someone mad.
Mariah's like my best friend
in this competition,
but I made a deal
with another girl.
I can't go back on my word.
And then we got the bitch
that's been doing good
that just had a bad week.
If I vote for her,
she might hate me.
But I'd rather have someone
go home that's a threat
than a friend,
because I need votes.
You're forever sickening, bitch.
This is All Stars.
Ain't nobody safe.
Do you wanna know
what's in my mind?
Because I know you wanna know.
I know you're asking.
What's going through
my mind right now is...
oh, I miss my cats.
They don't judge me.
They do, but they
have to live with me.
I feed them.
I also scoop their poops.
I feel like I would be a crazy
cat lady if I had one more cat,
but two is enough for now.
Meow, meow, bitches.end act
Welcome back, ladies.
Jujubee, are you ready
to meet your lip sync opponent?
Mm-hmm.
Good.
The time has come
to present this week's
lip sync assassin.
[thunder]
Whew.
Who is this?
Could this be the Babadook?
Oh, my God, who could that be?
Ru-veal yourself!
I live for the pop.
Like the boots.
Ooh, pretty.
[cheers and applause]
Ooh, a woman!
Yes, motherfucking
ma'am.m-fucking
Bitch, the lip sync assassin
is Monét X Change,
the All Stars 4 winner.
All right. Y'all good.
Come on, bitch!
Monét is a performer,
and she will lip sync
the fuck out of a song.fuck
Monét X Change.
Thank you for joining us
tonight.
Thank you for having me.
Ladies, Monét X Change
holds the lipstick
of the queen that the group
has voted to go home.
Now, if Monét wins the lip sync,
that queen gets the chop.
Y'all ready to slay?
Yeah.
Two queens stand before me.
Jujubee, this is your chance
to impress me,
win $10.000, and earn the power
to give one of the bottom queens
the chop.
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing] for your legacy!
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.fuck
[music plays]
♪ Mirror, mirror on the wall ♪
♪ Don't say it,
'cause I know I'm cute ♪
♪ Louis down to my drawers ♪
♪ LV all on my shoes ♪
♪ I be drippin' so much sauce ♪
♪ Got a bi' lookin' like Ragú ♪
♪ Lit up like a crystal ball ♪
♪ That's cool, baby,
so is you ♪
♪ That's how I roll ♪
♪ If I'm shinin',
everybody gonna shine ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm goals ♪
♪ I was born like this,
don't even gotta try ♪
♪ Now you know ♪
♪ I'm like chardonnay,
get better over time ♪
♪ So you know ♪
♪ Heard you say I'm not
the baddest, bitch, you lyin' ♪
♪ It ain't my fault that
I'm out here gettin' loose ♪
♪ Gotta blame it on the Goose ♪
♪ Gotta blame it
on my juice, baby ♪
♪ It ain't my fault that
I'm out here makin' news ♪
♪ I'm the pudding
in the proof ♪
♪ Blame it,
blame it on my juice ♪
♪ Ooh, baby,
no, I'm not a snack at all ♪
♪ Look, baby,
I'm the whole damn meal ♪
♪ David,
you ain't bein' slick ♪
♪ Don't dare
try to cop a feel ♪
♪ The juice
ain't worth the squeeze ♪
♪ If the juice
don't look like this ♪
♪ Hold up, please ♪
♪ Don't make me
have to take your bitch... ♪
Monét X Change.
♪ If I'm shinin',
everybody gonna shine... ♪
Bitch looks like a chocolate
dreamsicle dipped in velvet.
I am praying that she does not
have my lipstick in her hands.
♪ It ain't my fault that
I'm out here gettin' loose ♪
♪ Gotta blame it on the Goose ♪
♪ Gotta blame it
on my juice, baby ♪
♪ It ain't my fault that
I'm out here makin' news ♪
♪ I'm the pudding
in the proof ♪
♪ Gotta blame it on my juice ♪
♪ Ya-ya-ee ♪
♪ Ya-ya-ee, ya-ya-ee,
ya-ya-ee ♪
♪ Blame it on my juice ♪
♪ Blame it,
blame it on my juice ♪
♪ Ya-ya-ee ♪
♪ Ya-ya-ee, ya-ya-ee,
ya-ya-ee ♪
♪ Blame it on my juice ♪
♪ Blame it,
blame it on my juice, yeah ♪
[cheers and applause]
Whoo-ee!
-Yes, bitches.
-Juicy!
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Monét X Change.
Con-drag-ulations.
You're a winner, baby.
[applause]
The $10.000 will be added
to next week's tip.
Jujubee, you are safe,
and you may step
to the back of the stage.
[applause]
Will the bottom queens
please step forward?
With great power
comes great responsibility.
Monét, which queen has the group
chosen to get the chop?
Ru, the group has chosen,
and the queen that they have
picked to get the chop is...
Mariah.
As it is written,
so it shall be done.
Mariah, you are and you
will always be an All Star.
Now sashay away.
Thank you so much for another
opportunity to show my growth
and to display my talents.
And girls, good luck.
I love you.
Gimme a hug. I love you.
Keep on doing it, bitch.
Love you. Mm.
Don't shoot the messenger,
girl, okay?
I got a bag of marbles for you
in the back, bitch.
I feel good about what I've done
in this competition.
I can go with my head held high
and my heels still on
and twirl into another venture.
This Mariah
has grown exponentially,
and she's ready
to take on the world.
And forever and always,
in a room full of 10s,
I'm always gonna be grand prize.
Y'all, good luck.
Have a good time, bitch.
[applause]
You know what? Gimme
my fanny pack, I'm leaving.
I'm so sick.
This is too much.
Con-drag-ulations, All Stars.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an "amen" up in here?
-Amen!
All right.
Now let the music play.
♪ I am American, American,
American ♪vote
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white and blue ♪
♪ I am American, American,
American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪
RuPaul: Next time
on All Stars...
I'll be honest.
Shea, I voted for you.
The next vote for Shea was me.
I'm sorry, what--what--
what in the what-what?
For this week's maxi-challenge,
you'll be caught behaving badly
on the gossip show She MZ.
Alexis strongly suggested
you were discussing ways
to push me
out of this competition.
What?
She MZ!
I didn't steal any vases.
[gasps]
-Everything on me is real.
-Oh, really?
-Like this?
-Aah!
-Ooh!
-Mother!
I'm aroused.
Oh!
RuPaul: Ru-veal yourself!
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪
♪ Am-Am-Am-Am-American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪