[Female announcer]
Welcome to the grand finale
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Please welcome to the stage
the queens of Season 9.
♪ I am American,
American, American... ♪
[Female announcer]
The girl can't help it.
It's Jaymes Mansfield.
♪ The red, white,
and blue ♪
♪ American, American,
American... ♪
You'll never go back
once you go Kimora Blac.
♪ My, my, my... ♪
There's nothing
like a dame.
Give it up
for Charlie Hides.
♪ We are a family ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey,
despite what you think ♪
♪ This is who I am... ♪
We found her.
It's Eureka.
♪ Everybody came here
wanting to be free ♪
♪ New York to California ♪
♪ Sea to shining sea ♪
♪ Everybody... ♪
Hola, mis amores.
It's Cynthia Lee Fontaine.
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white
and blue... ♪
Brooklyn in the house.
It's Aja.
♪ I am American,
American ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪
What happens in Vegas
slays in Vegas.
It's Farrah Moan.
♪ Stand up for yourself,
we've just begun to fight ♪
♪ Ain't no way we're
going back in time... ♪
She's perfect,
she's beautiful,
she looks like a model.
She's Valentina.
♪ I am American, American,
American... ♪
She's back in town
to shut it down.
Nina Bo'nina Brown.
♪ I am American, American,
American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ Just like you, too... ♪
She's a Broadway baby.
It's Alexis Michelle.
♪ I am American,
American ♪
American... ♪
And now
our top four queens.
Put some pep in your step
for Peppermint.
♪ I am American,
American ♪
♪ The red, white and blue ♪
♪ I am American, American,
American ♪
♪ I am American,
American... ♪
She's arty and she turns
the party, it's Sasha Velour.
Shake a leg.
It's Shea Coulee.
And here comes the tuck.
It's Trinity Taylor.
♪ I am American,
American, American... ♪
Give it up one more time
for the queens of Season 9.
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪
[cheers and applause]
And now
our commander in chief,
but you can call her mother.
It's RuPaul.
[cheers and applause]
♪ Guess who's
back in the house ♪
♪ Heels
click-clackin' about ♪
♪ Fine, fresh, feminine,
style to eleven ♪
♪ I'm divine, so heavenly,
gentlemen sweatin' ♪
♪ It's dimes across the board
no doubt ♪
♪ Body like wow, pussy
'bout to end this drought ♪
♪ Titties so plentiful,
fish queen jezebel ♪
♪ Should be criminal ♪
♪ Don't make sense for
a bitch to be this endowed ♪
♪ North to the south,
what is that sound? ♪
♪ Watch me drop, drop, drop
into the ground ♪
♪ Wait for the four,
drop to the floor ♪
♪ Add up the tens
to get the score ♪
♪ I been that bitch,
yes, I love that drama ♪
♪ Fishy, feminine,
up-and-comer ♪
♪ From the Clintons
to the Obamas ♪
♪ I keep it tight,
now they call me mother ♪
♪ Jaded queen bitch,
I love that drama ♪
♪ Fishy, feminine,
up-and-comer ♪
♪ From the Clintons
to the Obamas ♪
♪ I keep it tight,
now they call... ♪
♪ Me... ♪
♪ Mother ♪
[cheers and applause]
Everybody say love.
Love!
Now take that
to your special prosecutor
and investigate it.
[cheers and applause]
Welcome
to the grand finale
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
[cheers and applause]
This season, the lip syncs
were on everybody's lips.
Valentina, you know
what I'm talking about, girl.
[cheering]
So tonight,
for the first time
in Drag Race herstory,
on this stage
our top four queens
are going to have to lip sync
for the crown.
[cheering]
Two by two
they'll face off,
and in the end,
one queen standing
will be crowned
America's next drag superstar.
As my high school dealer
Duane used to say,
that's some good shit,
right?
Now, before the competition
reignites,
I want to say hi
to my Judge Judys,
Michelle Visage,
Carson Kressley,
and Ross Mathews.
You gotta work.
You've gotta work
tonight, bitch.
Now to our top four.
[cheers and applause]
A little later tonight,
you're gonna find out
who's going to lip sync
against who.
So be ready to mop the floor
with your charisma, uniqueness,
nerve and talent.
But for now,
I just have one thing to say.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[cheers and applause]
The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia
Beverly Hills cosmetics
and $100,000.
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
[RuPaul laughs]
[cheers and applause]
[RuPaul]
Now, in a moment,
our top four queens
will face off
in an epic sudden death
lip sync smackdown.
Now let's get things popping
with our top four queens.
First, a groundbreaking queen
from New York City.
Take a look.
[Peppermint]
I am Peppermint,
and I am sweet and sassy.
[Carson]
The entire point of drag
is to give the middle finger
to rules of gender.
[RuPaul] Take it
to the runway, runway.
[Peppermint]
♪ Tippytoe, here you go ♪
♪ With the number one queen ♪
♪ It's P-E-P-P-E-R ♪
♪ Bitch,
you know the rest ♪
[all laugh]
[cheers and applause]
Hey, Peppermint.
Hey, Ru.
Now, we are all
looking forward
to some killer lip syncs
this evening.
Are you ready?
-Are you ready?
-Oh, yeah, I'm ready.
[laughs]
Now, you've been dubbed the
lip sync assassin this season.
What do you say to that?
I say just let me know
where to aim.
[laughs]
[cheers and applause]
Now, who's here
to support you tonight?
Well, I have
my beautiful mother
here to support me.
Hi, Mama Peppermint.
And one of
my closest girlfriends,
Ms. Trace Lysette
from Transparent.
Hey, girl.
So, Trace, what was
your favorite Peppermint moment
this season?
Her lip syncs,
because
there is no substitute
for stage presence
and talent.
-Ooh!
-Thank you, Trace.
Now, Peppermint,
we have a surprise message
from an old pal of yours.
Take a look.
Peppermint,
I am so proud of you, girl.
You have been my sister
for so many years,
and that has made it
that much sweeter
watching you shine,
showing the world that being
a proud transgender woman
is not incompatible
with being America's
next drag superstar.
You can have them both.
I love you, Peppermint.
I love you, Drag Race.
Shantay, you will
always stay in my heart.
Now, Peppermint,
a lot of people get confused
about how can you be
a proud transwoman
and be a drag queen.
What do you say
to those people?
Transwomen
have always contributed
to the wonderful art form
of drag
since the beginning of time.
This is not new,
and my contribution to drag
is as powerful
as any gay man.
One last question.
Now, since this season's
makeover challenge,
have you heard from
our cameraman Sarge?
Uh, I have not.
Unfortunately,
Sarge had another job,
but we did find Wintergreen
hanging out
in the parking lot
at the Waffle Hut
in Pacoima.
Please welcome back
Wintergreen.
[cheers and applause]
[laughs]
Oh!
Wintergreen,
you look marvelous.
This is all you, honey.
[all laugh]
Well, Peppermint,
thank you for giving us
Wintergreen
and for filling this season
with sass and class.
[applause]
Next, a queen
who blew our minds
with her beauty
and her brains.
Take a look.
[Sasha]
My name is Sasha Velour.
I am a fashiony,
artistic, weird queen.
[Russian accent] If you
were my mother's daughter,
she would drown you
in river.
There's something
extremely modern
about your style.
♪ If you wanna join
the revolution ♪
♪ Innovate,
that's my solution ♪
♪ Da da da da da da boom ♪
[cheers and applause]
Sasha Velour, welcome.
Now, you were never
in the bottom this season.
You never had to lip sync
for your life.
Are you ready to lip sync for
the crown tonight?
I mean, that's the thing.
If I actually do have
a regret about this season,
it's not getting to show
the passion
that I love getting
to express in the lip sync.
I'm thrilled.
I'm ready.
Good. Good.
[cheers and applause]
Sasha, this season
you helped teach the children
about our rich gay history.
Yeah, they say that
if you look into a mirror
and talk about sad things,
I appear behind you
to give you
a queer history lesson.
[laughs]
Drag queens
have always been the keepers
of our queer history.
We make it, we tell it,
we remember it,
we mis-remember it,
and we love it,
and I'm so glad
that I got to help
bring that tradition
onto the show
in my own little way.
[cheers and applause]
Okay, now are you ready
for a surprise message
from a big fan of yours?
-Sure.
-All right.
Hey, Sasha,
it's Katy Perry.
I'm so sorry
I can't be there.
I just want to say hello
and that I love you
and thank God for you.
[cheers and applause]
[RuPaul] Isn't that wonderful?
So, Sasha, who's here
rooting for you tonight?
Well, I have my dad,
Papa Velour.
[RuPaul] Well.
And my boyfriend
Johnny Velour.
Ahh. Now, what was it like
watching Sasha?
You did watch the show
on television, right?
We often did watch parties
at my house in Illinois.
I watched every show
and all the "Untuckeds"
sometimes more than once.
[cheers and applause]
Now, I've heard you,
Sasha, talk before
about how your late mother
inspired your drag.
What do you think she'd say
if she were here tonight?
She'd say, "Too much."
Seriously, I think
she would be so proud of me
for going from
a little boy
who wore dresses
in the living room
to a little boy who wore
dresses on this grand finale.
I love it.
[cheers and applause]
Okay, now,
what would it mean to you
to be crowned
America's next drag superstar?
It would be
a dream come true.
An honor.
I feel that
the drag I do
is a little bit different.
It pushes the boundaries
for what people might expect.
And I believe that
that is the future of drag,
and I am so honored
to represent that.
[cheers and applause]
Sasha Velour,
I want to thank you
for sharing your uniqueness
and elevating
this competition.
Now, in moments
our top four queens
will face off
in an epic lip sync smackdown
for the crown.
But first, our next queen
is a true triple threat.
She's funny,
she can lip sync,
and she looks good
with a hotdog on her head.
[Shea] My name's Shea Coulee,
and I didn't come to play.
I came to slay.
[all laugh]
[Michelle] She's a great
entertainer, she's a great dancer,
she's a great actress.
♪ To show 'em how,
these bitches ♪
♪ I own 'em, got that?
Supermodel switch ♪
♪ Ms. Coulee, she a real,
real bad bitch, uh ♪
[cheers and applause]
Shantay, Coulee.
What do you say?
Are you ready to lip sync
for the crown tonight?
-I was born ready, Ru.
-Ooh, all right.
[cheers and applause]
So tell me this.
Who would you not want
to lip sync against?
Sasha and I have
a really great friendship,
and I know it would be
super dramatic
if we had to lip sync
against one another.
Luckily I'm a messy bitch
who loves drama.
[laughs]
Now, I know
that you and your family
have had a really rough go
of it this past year.
Do you mind talking
a little bit about that?
Um...two days before
the cast was announced,
I lost my dad to cancer.
And...a month after that,
I lost my sister to cancer.
And my dad,
we had gone through such
an amazing journey together,
of him understanding me and
learning about who I was and...
[Shea]
I know that he watches me.
-Absolutely.
-And I feel him.
-Yeah.
-All the time.
-Sorry.
-[RuPaul] Yes. I feel that.
[cheers and applause]
Now, you told me
that your mother
is a minister.
[laughs] Yes. I mean,
she's a reverend now.
-She done come up.
-Oh.
Are you Reverend Coulee?
-Yes.
-Hello.
[applause]
Does Shea take after you
or her father?
His creativity
comes from his father.
His rhythm comes from me.
[laughter and applause]
All right.
Thank you, Reverend Coulee.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Now, Shea,
one of my favorite moments
is when you took
the character of Blac Chyna,
and I'm not the only one
who felt it was stellar.
Hey, Shea Coulee.
Honey,
you did not come to play.
You came to slay.
And yes,
you did steal the show,
I mean, 'cause
that's what Blac Chyna does.
Now make sure you go out there
and get that crown.
All right, I love you.
All right,
I'm out, I'm out, I'm out.
[cheers and applause]
Whoa!
That was a nice car.
-It certainly was.
-Yeah.
So what would it mean
to you
to become America's
next drag superstar?
It would be an era
of sickening
black drag queens
running this world
continued.
I love it.
Shea Coulee, thank you
for showing the children
how it is done.
[cheers and applause]
Up next, a queen
who is so much more
than just a tight tuck.
She's got a big,
juicy ass, too.
[Trinity]
The body is here, bitches.
[Michelle]
When this first started,
we just saw a pageant girl.
I call shade.
[Michelle]
You have done things
you didn't know
you had in you.
Children!
♪ Just bow down,
'cause I'm the new Miss Thing ♪
[cheers and applause]
[RuPaul]
Trinity, when you started the season,
your approval ratings
were low.
But you turned things
around.
How'd you do that?
And speak slow
because Donald Trump is watching
and he wants to know.
[cheers and laughter]
Honestly, I have
a resting bitch face.
It's just people hate me
until they get to know me
and they get to know
my humor,
and then apparently
America likes it, so...
-[laughter and applause]
-Carry on.
So who's here
supporting you tonight?
I have
my much older sister Ginger
and my sugar dad--
I mean,
my new boyfriend Leo.
[RuPaul] Oh.
How'd you two meet?
Well, I'm a good Southern
Baptist Christian lady,
-so church.
-[RuPaul] Oh, at church,
Also know as
an adult gay dating app.
[RuPaul] Oh.
[laughter and applause]
Leo, had you seen Trinity
on TV before?
Yes, I did.
And did you think
I'm gonna get some of that?
And I sure did
and then some.
[all laugh]
-Yes.
-[RuPaul] Oh, I love it.
Now, Trinity, your tuck got
a lot of attention this season,
especially from
the gorgeous Chris Pine
and the boys
at Saturday Night Live.
See that?
What was that like for you?
Girl, I just wanted
to drop to my knees
and climb him like a tree.
[cheers and laughter]
If you're watching,
please call me.
Uh-oh. All right.
Sorry, Leo.
[all laugh]
Well, here's
a little something extra
from a true fan.
Hey,
this is Bobby Moynihan
wishing Trinity Taylor
good luck.
Us pageant bitches
got to stick together.
Don't fuck it up.
Death drop!
[all laugh]
Yes.
Okay, Trinity,
are you nervous
about lip syncing tonight?
Absolutely not.
This is what I do.
I'm a performer.
So who would you not want
to lip sync against?
None of 'em, girl.
Bring 'em on, honey.
I'll lip sync to all of 'em.
Send 'em all packing, bitch.
[cheers and applause]
Ladies and gentlemen,
Trinity Taylor.
[cheers and applause]
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the stage
our top four.
[cheers and applause]
Tonight one of you
will become America's
next drag superstar.
But for the first time
in Drag Race herstory,
to win,
you will have to survive
a lip sync smackdown
for the crown.
To explain how it works,
here's our special
Drag Race correspondent
Ross Mathews.
Okay, tonight we'll start
with four queens
but only one queen
will take the crown.
First, a spin of the wheel
determines which two queens
will face off
in lip sync number one.
Then the remaining
two queens
will face off
in lip sync number two.
The winners
of those two lip syncs
will then go head to head
in the final
lip sync for the crown.
And the winner will become
America's
next drag superstar.
I'm so excited.
I'm gonna need to change.
Ru, back to you.
Thank you, Ross.
That sounds a lot like math.
Now, on this wheel
are the names
of our top four queens.
Wherever the wheel stops
will determine which queen
lip syncs first.
Ladies, are you ready?
[cheering]
All right, here we go.
"Big money."
[all laugh]
[cheering]
Well, Trinity,
the wheel has spoken.
And now you get to choose
who you will lip sync against.
Choose wisely.
I want a battle.
I choose Peppermint.
[cheers and applause]
That means Sasha and Shea,
you two will face off
in tonight's second lip sync
coming up next.
You may leave the stage.
Okay, Peppermint,
you get to choose
your lip sync song.
Oh, pit crew.
[cheers and applause]
Each of these boxes
contains one of my all-time
favorite lip sync songs.
Peppermint, do you choose
box number one
or box number two?
[audience shouts]
[cheering]
The crowd has spoken
with box number two.
All right.
Brice, open your box.
"Stronger"
by Britney Spears.
[cheers and applause]
Okay, ladies,
assume the position.
Two queens
stand behind me.
[laughter]
Ladies,
this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing]
for the crown!
[cheers and applause]
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
♪♪♪
♪ Hush, just stop ♪
♪ There's nothing
you can do or say ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ I've had enough ♪
♪ I'm not your property
as from today ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ You might think that
I won't make it on my own ♪
♪ But now I'm stronger
than yesterday ♪
♪ Now it's nothing
but my way ♪
♪ My loneliness
ain't killing me no more ♪
♪ I'm, I'm stronger ♪
♪ Here I go on my own ♪
♪ I don't need nobody,
not anybody ♪
♪ Here I go ♪
♪ Here I go, here I go ♪
♪ Stronger than yesterday ♪
♪ It's nothing but my way ♪
♪ My loneliness
ain't killing me no more ♪
♪ I'm, I'm stronger
than yesterday ♪
♪ It's nothing but my way ♪
♪ My loneliness
ain't killing me no more ♪
♪ No more ♪
♪ I'm stronger ♪
[cheers and applause]
Ladies,
I have made my decision.
The winner of tonight's
first lip sync,
the queen moving on
to the final lip sync
for the crown
will be...
Peppermint,
shantay you stay.
[cheers and applause]
Con-drag-ulations.
You're moving on
to the finals.
Go ahead and head backstage
and get ready for the lip sync
for the crown.
Trinity Taylor,
I'm sorry, my queen,
but this is not your time.
You are an amazing queen,
and thank you
for an amazing season.
Now sashay away.
[cheers and applause]
Now welcome back
to the stage
Sasha Velour
and Shea Coulee.
Bring back my girls.
[cheers and applause]
Sasha and Shea,
let's find out what song
you'll be lip syncing to.
Oh, pit crew.
Show us what you're packing.
Whitney Houston's
"So Emotional."
[cheers and applause]
Sasha, Shea,
assume the position.
Two queens stand behind me.
Ladies,
this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing]
for the crown!
Good luck
and don't fuck it up.
♪♪♪
♪ I don't know
why I like it ♪
♪ I just do ♪
♪ I've been hearing
your heartbeat ♪
♪ Inside of me ♪
♪ I keep your photograph
beside my bed ♪
♪ Living in a world
of fantasies ♪
♪ I can't get you
out of my head ♪
♪ I remember
the way that we touched ♪
♪ I wish I didn't like it
so much ♪
♪ I get so emotional,
baby ♪
♪ Every time
I think of you ♪
♪ I get so emotional,
baby ♪
♪ Ain't it shocking what ♪
♪ Love can do? ♪
♪ Ain't it shocking
what love can do? ♪
♪ Hey, I gotta watch you
walk in the room, baby ♪
♪ I gotta watch you
walk out ♪
♪ I like the animal way
you move ♪
♪ And when you talk,
I just watch your mouth ♪
♪ Oh, I remember
the way that we touched ♪
♪ I wish I didn't like it
so much ♪
♪ Oh, I get
so emotional, baby ♪
♪ Every time
I think of you ♪
♪ I get so emotional,
baby ♪
♪ Ain't it shocking what ♪
♪ Love can do? ♪
♪ I get so emotional,
baby ♪
♪ Every time
I think of you ♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby ♪
♪ I get so emotional,
baby ♪
♪ Ain't it shocking what ♪
♪ Love can do? ♪
[cheers and applause]
Ladies,
I have made my decision.
Sasha Velour,
shantay you stay.
[cheers and applause]
Con-drag-ulations.
You've made it
on to the finals.
Go get ready
for the lip sync for the crown.
[cheers and applause]
That means Shea Coulee,
I'm sorry, my dear,
this is not your time.
Thank you
for a fabulous season.
[cheers and applause]
Now sashay away.
[chanting]
Shea! Shea! Shea! Shea!
[cheering]
In just a few minutes,
Peppermint and Sasha Velour
will lip sync for the crown.
But first, a queen
who knows all about winning.
All hail America's reigning
drag superstar,
Bob the Drag Queen.
[cheers and applause]
Bob the Drag Queen,
welcome back.
It's time
to hand over the crown.
Uh, I'd like to keep it on,
please.
[cheers and laughter]
What part
of "hand over the crown"
do you not understand?
[cheers and laughter]
So, Bob,
what was it like
for you being America's
next drag superstar
this past year?
You get to travel
the world
and realize how many people
you've actually touched.
And let me tell you,
I've touched a lot of people.
[laughs]
So what's next for you?
Funny you should ask.
You can see
my stand-up comedy special,
Suspiciously Large Woman,
which will be airing
on LOGO TV
in the United States
of America.
Uh-huh.
And my cousin Tralana
will be selling bootlegs
in the parking lot.
Right. Good to know.
Thank you,
Bob the Drag Queen.
[cheers and applause]
To our squirrel friends
around the world,
I present
your top two queens.
[cheers and applause]
Peppermint...
[cheering]
and Sasha Velour.
Two queens stand behind me.
Prior to tonight,
you were asked to prepare
a lip sync performance
of "It's Not Right,
But It's Okay"
by Whitney Houston.
Ladies, this is
your last chance
to impress me
and prove to the world
that you are America's
next drag superstar.
[cheers and applause]
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing]
for the crown!
[cheers and applause]
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
♪♪♪
♪ I pack your bags so you
can leave town for a week ♪
♪ Yes, I am ♪
♪ The phone rings ♪
♪ And then you look at me ♪
♪ You said it was
one of your friends ♪
♪ Down on 54th Street, boy ♪
♪ So why did 213 ♪
♪ Show up
on your caller I.D. ♪
♪ It's not right,
but it's okay ♪
♪ I'm gonna make it
anyway ♪
♪ Pack your bags up
and leave ♪
♪ Don't you dare
come running back to me ♪
♪ Was it really worth
you going out like that? ♪
♪ See, I'm moving on ♪
♪ And I refuse
to turn back, yeah ♪
♪ See, all of this time ♪
♪ I thought I had
somebody down for me ♪
♪ It turns out ♪
♪ You were making
a fool of me ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ It's not right,
but it's okay ♪
♪ I'm gonna make it
anyway ♪
♪ Pack your bags up
and leave ♪
♪ Don't you dare
come running back to me ♪
♪ It's not right,
but it's okay ♪
♪ I'm gonna make it
anyway ♪
♪ Close the door behind you,
leave your key ♪
♪ Take care of my baby ♪
♪ I'd rather be alone
than unhappy ♪
♪ Oh ♪
[cheers and applause]
Ladies, in addition
to the title
of America's
next drag superstar,
the winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
will receive
a crown and scepter
provided by Shandar,
a one-year supply of Anastasia
Beverly Hills cosmetics,
and a cash prize
of $100,000.
[cheers and applause]
Now...
[thunder]
the time has come
to crown our queen.
Ladies,
I've made my decision.
The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race,
America's
next drag superstar is...
Sasha Velour.
[cheers and applause]
Is there anything
you'd like to say?
Let's change shit up.
[cheering]
Let's get inspired
by all this beauty,
all this beauty,
and change
the motherfucking world!
Now prance.
Prance, I said.
♪ If I dream
everything I wanna be ♪
all the possibilities ♪
♪ If you just believe
in your wildest dreams ♪
♪ They will come true,
they will come true ♪
Remember, if you can't
love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen
up in here?
[all]
Amen!
All right.
Now let the music play.
♪ If I dream
everything I wanna be ♪
all the possibilities ♪
♪ If you just believe
in your wildest dreams... ♪
Aah!
♪ They will come true ♪
♪ Yeah, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey ♪
♪ Hey, kitty girl ♪
♪ It's your world ♪
♪ When you walk the street
steppin' to the beat ♪
♪ Hey, kitty girl ♪
♪ Get your crown ♪
♪ In the disco heat ♪
♪ You're the boogie body
rockin' queen ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Kitty kitty,
Hey, here kitty kitty ♪
♪ Hey, kitty kitty, yeah ♪
♪ Ahh, yeah, whoa-oh-oh ♪