[RuPaul]
Sashay away.
Can I get an amen in here?
Good luck.
Sashay away.
Can I get an amen in here?
How the hell can you love
somebody else?
Can I get an amen in here?
And don't fuck it up.
Oh, my God.
Hey.
I am Peppermint,
and I am sweet and sassy.
Yes. I perform and host
in New York.
When you come
to a Peppermint show,
you're gonna see people
screaming and hollering,
money flying and
you're gonna feel special.
I look great. Perfect.
My braids are sitting just right.
I got it going on.
All right,
let's get to work.
Hello. It's me, Valentina.
Hola. ¿Qué tal?
Who am I? Valentina.
I'm 25 years old.
I'm from Echo Park, California.
Sass.
-Hey, beauty.
-Valentina.
-I'm Peppermint.
-Mucho gusto.
-Mwah.
My type of drag,
it's very dramatic,
very theatrical
and always very Latina.
I'm an undiscovered superstar.
I've always dreamed
of being in here,
and here we are, girlfriend.
Here we are, girl.
Oh, come on, give it up
for the big girl
serving pure catfish.
My name is Eureka,
and I am 25 years old.
People would categorize me
as a pageant queen,
but to me, my drag
is the genre of fabulous.
[laughs]
Hi, I'm Eureka.
-Where are you from?
-East Tennessee.
Girl, I'm country
as a biscuit, honey,
and I love eating 'em, too.
Your hair's hot.
-Thank you, girl.
-I love the baby hairs.
I'm a little natural around the way,
girl, you know.
That's my favorite shape
is round.
I can see.
I'll eat you.
[all laugh]
Hi, hi, hi.
It's about to get shady
up in here.
My name is Charlie Hides
and I'm [muffled] years old.
[door creaks]
-Hey!
Oh, my God,
Peppermint's here.
I'm known as a celebrity
impersonator.
My drag persona
is rude, crude,
socially unacceptable
and over the top.
Can I ask you,
with that dress,
why didn't you wear like
a big pair of earrings?
I really wanted to give you, like,
Walmart realness.
- I'm getting that, Eureka.
-Thank you.
[all laugh]
It's Christina Aguilera.
So this is what
it looks like.
[Eureka] She's naked.
My name is Farrah Moan,
and I'm from Las Vegas, Nevada.
Oh, my God, dirty.
My drag is inspired
by Vegas showgirls.
My wardrobe
shows a lot of skin
and there's usually
a feather or two
or five dead ostriches.
You never know with me.
-Hi.
-Hi, I'm Charlie.
-Charlie.
-What's your name?
Farrah. Farrah Moan.
Farrah Moan walks in.
She's a twig,
and she looks about 12.
I have underwear older than her.
Hi. I'm Eureka,
like the vacuum cleaner.
How are you?
I've never vacuumed before.
Well, I came
to clean house, girl.
[screaming] Aah!
What?
[coughs]
Oh, wow.
My name is Sasha Velour.
I am 29 years old.
I am a bald, fashiony,
artistic weird queen.
Hi, ladies.
I'm committed to being
uniquely Sasha all the time.
[Eureka] Tell us about yourself.
I'm a visual artist.
I love telling stories
with art and with drag.
What story are you telling
with this unibrow?
[laughs]
How do you like them egg rolls,
Mr. Charles?
I'm Alexis Michelle,
and I am New York City's
premier Broadway queen.
Holy shit.
Hello!
I went to school
for musical theater.
I think
the ultimate fantasy now
would be to be on Broadway
in drag.
-Girl.
-Come on, New York.
So the East Coast
is well represented.
I will say L.A., West Coast,
it's the center of the universe.
Sorry, New York.
She says forget
what you heard, apparently.
Memo taken.
My name is Shea Coulee,
and I didn't come to play.
I came to slay.
[contestant]
I love The Muppets.
I'm Shea Coulee,
and I'm 27 years old.
Shea Coulee is...
champagne lifestyle
on a lemonade budget.
Hey!
You're gonna get
a full-on production
when you see Shea Coulee.
Costumes, check.
Makeup, check.
Dance moves, she got 'em.
-Where are you from?
-I'm from Chicago.
Yes, Chicago.
[all laugh]
Chicago drag is the
motherfucking bomb-dot-com.
-Dot-com?
-Yes, bitch.
It's got its own domain.
[all laugh]
The body is here, bitches.
Oh, shit.
Girl, I'm Trinity Taylor.
Some people say I'm the look
and feel of real,
but my body speaks for itself.
Shut it down!
Trinity does not pad.
I love plastic surgery,
and I went from a pancake
to a Kardashian.
I do a lot of pageants,
but I don't like to use
the word pageant queen
because there's such
a stigmatism with pageant queen.
I can do anything,
from beautiful
to way outside the box.
Oh, my God. Lady!
Bitch, I'm just excited
to know somebody.
[Eureka] Me and Trinity know
each other from competing.
She, like, won the pageant
that I really wanted to win
so, of course, there's that, like,
bougie attitude from her.
I am the body girl.
I'm here
and I'm not padded.
She's gonna be competition.
Who are the pageant girls?
You're a pageant girl,
I'm a pageant girl,
you're a pageant girl.
Just to clear the air,
I promise I'm not
one of the mean ones.
[all laugh]
That is a lie.
-Oh.
-Ooh.
There's always been tension
with me and Eureka.
Maybe she has an issue
with the fact
that every pageant
that we've been in,
I beat her.
Is it me
or is it hot in here?
I'm Kimora Blac
from Las Vegas.
The queen is here.
Bow down, bitches.
Oh, you ain't
the only body, girl.
I love anything see-through
and anything
that shows my body.
Big tits, big ass,
irresistible.
Gay guys love me,
straight guys love me.
Kimora Blac is everyone's
sexual preference.
-Hey, girl.
-Oh, my God!
Oh!
Oh, my goodness.
That’s my Vegas sister.
Kimora's ass is famous.
That's what she's
gonna be known for.
That ass is gonna have
its own t-shirts.
I can see it all now.
Season 9, baby.
How long
you been doing drag?
Oh, my God, 10 long years.
-Brava.
-10 long years.
[Valentina] 10 months.
And you can go to hell.
[Valentina] My debut was 10 months ago
when I performed.
I can't. I can't.
I can't with her.
I'm fairly new to drag,
but I wouldn't consider myself
looking like
an amateur drag queen.
I carry myself like a winner
and a superstar.
-Come on, drag babies.
-[laughs]
Hi, shape-shifters.
I am Jaymes Mansfield,
I am 26 years old,
and I'm from
Milwaukee, Wisconsin.
I build puppets.
I'm a kooky, comedy queen
that has way more
up her sleeve than they know.
[contestant] All right.
Jaymes Mansfield looks...
scared and confused
when she walks in.
Like, am I
in the right room?
[puppet] Hi, honey.
-Oh, my goodness.
These are my
summer diamonds.
Some are diamonds
and some are not.
[all laugh]
Is this all fake
or is it real?
Um, I'd say the foot upward,
it's all fake.
I meant your personality.
[all] Ooh.
I'm Nina Bo'nina,
banana fo-fana,
Osama bin Laden, Brown,
boom, boom, boom, boom.
I am Nina Bo'nina Brown,
and I am back in town
to shut her down.
Well, no, I can't say
I'm back in town,
'cause I haven't even
been in town yet.
Yes, ma'am.
[Eureka]
She seems a little mousy.
Hey, sisters.
-Yay!
-Yes.
My drag consists of fantasy.
One minute I may be a zombie.
The next time I may be a nun.
I'm not cosplay.
Nobody does what I do.
What inspired your look?
Well, you know, my drag
is like universal, honey.
You never know
what you're gonna get.
So your drag's like STDs.
You never know
what you're gonna get.
Exactly.
[all] Ohh!
My name is Aja and I'm
from Brooklyn, New York.
Your edges
are officially snatched.
Yeah.
Aja is vangy.
Her drag style is very
the streets of Tokyo
meets the streets
of Brooklyn.
She's cute,
but she's dangerous.
Oh, my. I am so happy
to see you.
-I'm so happy.
-I love Aja.
She is the number one name
in Brooklyn
that people
are talking about right now.
Hi. Aja. Mwah, mwah.
Oh, you are so gorgeous
in blue.
Thank you, thank you.
So nice to meet you.
Aja's makeup is just really
rough around the edges,
but she comes off
as confident.
Does she know
what she looks like?
'Cause if not,
I need to tell her.
I feel like I'm at home
with so much talented girls.
-Yes!
-Oh!
Oh!
Bitch!
[Eureka] Yes, ma'am, honey.
That's a damn good
Lady Gaga impersonator.
-Oh, girl.
-Oh, my God.
So this is the Derek Barry
of the season.
[ contestant] Oh!
Yo, I'm Ronnie
and I'm from New Jersey.
I'm New Jersey's number one
Lady Gaga impersonator.
But what I'm really
excited about
is how long it takes
for these queens to figure out
that it's really me.
Is it time to go home?
[laughs]
[Eureka]
Wait a minute.
Mother Monster has arrived.
Wait a second.
[all screaming]
Holy fucking balls,
it's Lady Gaga.
Like, the real one.
Holy shit. I'm on
RuPaul's Drag Race, Season 9,
and Lady Gaga
is in the same room as me.
Aah!
[screaming]
Oh, my God.
I can't tell you,
I have been the closest to death
and you've pulled me out of it,
and you don't even realize
what you do for people
and how much you inspire people
like me and all of us.
And I just want to tell you,
you're so amazing,
and I never thought in the world
I would ever meet you.
And I think you're so incredible.
I'm so sorry.
I think you're so incredible.
Aw.
[applause]
You allow us to be who we are
as an artist. Thank you.
I have always really admired
the craftsmanship that
goes into what you all do.
Drag has for me
been an opportunity
to leave myself
when I didn't want to be me.
-Right.
-Yeah.
And felt so completely out of place
when I was in high school.
Drag has just been part
of my life for the longest time.
It's just really an honor
for me to be here,
to be with you all.
-No, it's an honor for us.
-Yes, Gaga.
[cheers and applause]
[door opens]
Hello, hello, hello!
[cheers and applause]
Oh, my Gaga!
[all laugh]
Gather round, ladies.
Oh, darling, mwah, mwah.
You look amazing.
Thank you, so do you.
Now you've had a chance
to meet my girls.
Do you have any advice
for them?
You know, when
you're having a bad day,
just remember
that I was nobody,
and then I became somebody
one day.
And it's the same right here.
-Ah!
-Yes.
Your lives are gonna
change forever today.
And I would also
remember something
that you taught me
a very long time ago.
Get the money up front?
Yes, and on the back.
[laughs]
Remember what
he always has said:
♪ You better work ♪
[in unison]
Turn to the left.
Work.
Now turn to the right.
Sashay, shantay.
[cheers and applause]
[RuPaul]
Now, as you can see,
this season is going to be
stuffed with more stars,
more stunts and more shenanigans
than ever before.
[contestant]
Yeah!
And on this premiere,
for the first time
in Drag Race herstory...
Uh-oh.
No one...
is going home.
[all] Oh!
- [gasps] Crack, crack,
crack, crack, crack, pshew!
Face on the floor.
- #OhMyGaga.
And ladies, to get
this episode started,
we're throwing a pageant.
[all] Oh.
Yes, Miss Thing,
the Miss Charisma Uniqueness,
Nerve & Talent Pageant.
[all laugh]
-Yes!
-Oh, my God!
I can do this.
I want to show these bitches
that I'm the one to look out for.
You'll be competing
in two categories.
First, you need to show us
where you're from
with a frock
inspired by your home city.
Second, as a salute
to our legendary guest star,
you need to strut your stuff
in your favorite
Lady Gaga drag.
So don't be a drag,
just be a queen.
[cheers and applause]
Lady Gaga,
would you do the honors?
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
-Whoo!
-Yes!
-Move, bitch.
-Oh, my God, up.
-Watch out now.
-Ow!
I'm right behind you,
honey. Sorry, guys.
Where am I gonna go?
This first challenge
is very important
because this is the first
impression that you make.
No one can afford to fuck
this shit up.
Bam, bam, bam.
Are they sure this wasn't
the challenge,
'cause I feel like I’m winded.
[Farrah] Is this already
a claimed work station?
Hello?
Am I missing something?
Can someone tell me
if there's another station somewhere
that I'm not seeing?
[sighs]
Farrah is awkwardly endearing
with the way that she whines.
So am I,
like, Matilda or something?
I call her
Blonde Benet Glamsey
'cause she whines like
a 6-year-old, so, huh.
[Farrah] I really want
a station of my own.
[Peppermint] So have you ever done
a Gaga look before?
Yeah, 'cause I've played her
a bunch of times in my video.
-Oh, yeah, in your videos.
-I make YouTube videos,
which I make by myself
in my living room.
I've been making fun of Lady Gaga
on YouTube for years.
I am always afraid that
when I impersonate people
that they're gonna watch
my videos.
Lana del Rey said I was
an asshole, apparently.
Lana del Rey
called you an asshole?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Charlie has a very on-the-edge
kind of sense of humor.
It's an acquired taste,
and I'm not sure if the judges
have acquired that taste.
[Aja] I'm wearing the rainbow
kimono that Gaga wore.
[contestant]
Yes, bitch.
-Coming through.
-It's V collar.
[contestant]
Oh, like it's the one.
[Aja] I was like, can I, like,
go through your archives
and, like, have stuff?
And he was like, yeah,
take whatever you want.
Aja is very New York.
"I'm from New York.
I did this."
"Oh, my God,
this guy made me this."
She talks about the costume
designers and all this jazz.
No one cares.
Touch it. It's Arctic fox
dyed with saffron.
- Oh. My hometown look
is a Georgia peach.
Girl, I said, how am I gonna go
from a damn mouse to a peach?
I haven't seen a lot of girls
who can get some paper
and some kind of glue
and create a new face.
I may not have
the best stuff,
but I work with what I got,
and I think that's
what makes me different.
I just need for people
to believe in me.
Ladies, who wants to win
the first challenge the most?
-Me!
-Come on, girl!
-Everybody.
Get in line, girl!
I'm about to storm
all you bitches.
Right. She gonna be
just like the candy.
She gonna dissolve.
Ha ha!
[Shea] The stakes are high
for this first challenge
because everyone is fighting
for that spotlight.
The true Gaga-rini,
that is what's about to go down.
I feel very prepared
and ready.
The only thing that I want
from this challenge
is to beat Trinity.
[applause]
Hello.
Welcome to
the Miss Charisma
Uniqueness,
Nerve & Talent Pageant.
Let's meet our distinguished
panel of judges.
Fourth runner-up in the Miss
South Plainfield, New Jersey
Popping, Dipping, Spinning
and Vogue-ing Pageant,
Michelle Visage is here.
Darling, I wear it with pride.
Thank you.
Style superstar,
Carson Kressley.
I love that this is
a scholarship pageant.
Great work.
And the hilarious Ross Mathews.
I have Vaseline on my teeth.
Ha ha!
And the one,
the only Lady Gaga.
Well, if you could do me a favor
and shoot me from the left
and put a filter on that camera,
would you?
All right, Ms. Streisand.
Now, to get
to know them better,
our contestants
will introduce themselves
wearing frocks that represent
their home cities.
Let the pageant begin.
[applause]
[RuPaul]
Category is...
First up, Peppermint.
[Carson] Check out
those big apples.
My name is Peppermint
from New York City,
home of Metro cards,
EBT cards and Lady Liberty.
[Lady Gaga]
That's a mint I'd like to bite into.
[RuPaul] Valentina.
[Carson] Olé, you stay.
I'm Valentina.
I'm from East L.A.
and I'm repping
Mariachi Plaza.
[RuPaul]
Oh, Mary-achi.
Next up, Eureka.
She's the forgotten
Mandrell sister.
[Carson] Right.
Howdy, y'all. I'm Eureka
and this is Mary Jo Beth.
I come to you
from East Tennessee,
and I'm representing
the redneck woman.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul]
Honky-tonk ba-donka-donk.
Charlie Hides.
Honey, she is Thanks-giving it
to you, darling.
[Ross] Yes, she is.
Hi. I'm Charlie
from Massachusetts,
the home of the pilgrims,
America's first drag queens.
[RuPaul]
She's a witch.
[Lady Gaga] Burn her!
[Michelle] Burn her at the stake!
[RuPaul] Up next, Farrah Moan.
Michelle] I can tell from here
she gives great head-dress.
Hi, my name's Farrah Moan.
I'm from Las Vegas, Nevada.
Are you feeling lucky?
What happens in Vegas
slays in Vegas.
-That's right.
-Yeah.
[RuPaul]
Next up, Sasha Velour.
She's crowning.
[all laugh]
Hi, I'm Sasha Velour
and I'm from New York City,
home of queer modern art,
Haring, Warhol, Basquiat.
[Michelle] Burger Queen.
She's got a Whopper.
We just can't see it.
[RuPaul] Alexis Michelle.
[Lady Gaga] These have always
brought me luck.
I'm Alexis Michelle,
a native New Yorker,
home of Broadway, bagels
and an epicenter
of civil rights.
Work that message, girl.
[Ross] Darn kids have tagged
my swimsuit again.
[Carson] See, it's the elder care
that I relate to.
[RuPaul] Shea Coulee.
[Ross] She-brew National.
[Carson] Don’t be fooled
by the brats that she got.
My name's Shea Coulee
and, bitch, I'm from Chicago!
[all laugh]
Nothing reminds me of home
more than a big wiener sandwiched
in between two buns.
[Ross] The other girls
better "catch up."
They "must-heard" about her.
I want you to "relish"
this moment.
[all laugh]
Somebody stop me.
[laughs]
[RuPaul] Trinity Taylor.
[Ross] You must be this tall, Ru,
to take that ride.
I'm Trinity Taylor
from Orlando, Florida,
the theme park capital
of the world.
Want to take a ride?
[Lady Gaga] I'd take a ride
on her disco trick.
[RuPaul] Uh-huh.
Kimora Blac.
[Ross] Blac lives matter, y'all.
Hello, my name is Kimora Blac
from the city of Las Vegas.
All the girls in Vegas
just know me
as the youngest, hottest,
skinniest queen.
And if you're feeling
a little frisky,
whatever you do to me
stays in Vegas.
This message has been brought
to you by penicillin.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul]
Up next, Jaymes Mansfield.
[Ross] Holy cow!
Hi, I'm Jaymes Mansfield.
I'm a tejano living
in Milwaukee, Wisconsin,
land of beer, cheese
and serial killers.
Shh.
[all chuckle]
[RuPaul]
She's a dairy queen.
Aja.
[Carson] Make America gay again.
-Yes.
My name is Aja
and I'm from New York,
where people are always angry
on the streets.
But it's okay 'cause
you could be yourself.
Lady Liberty has spoken.
I wonder how many immigrants
have gone through her.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul]
Nina Bo'nina Brown.
She's got Georgia
on her mind.
And her face.
I am Nina Bo'nina banana fo-nana
Osama bin Laden Brown.
Originally from
South Kakalaki,
you can now catch me
in Atlanta, Georgia.
Take a bite of this peach.
[Michelle] It looks like she's got
a touch of the Zika.
-[laughs]
-Oh, my, Michelle.
The last thing I thought would be
brought up today is Zika.
[RuPaul] Welcome back
to the Miss Charisma
Uniqueness,
Nerve & Talent Pageant.
In this next category,
our contestants
return to the stage
wearing their very best
Lady Gaga drag.
First up, Peppermint.
Grammy Awards 2016.
[Ross] If it ain't brocade,
don't fix it.
[Peppermint]
"Crowd control to Major Tom,"
giving you Gaga/Bowie
realness.
Because
the entire point of drag
is to give the middle finger
to rules of gender.
[Lady Gaga]
I have nothing to say.
I'm going to be speechless
this whole time.
[RuPaul] Wham, bam,
thank you, ma'am.
Next up, Valentina,
the CFDA Awards.
That was Mugler when
Nicola Formicetti was there.
[Valentina] I am wearing the look
she wore for the CFDA Awards.
I definitely see myself
a bit in Lady Gaga
because she carries herself
with grace and glamour,
but I always want to add
a Latina flair to what I do.
[Lady Gaga] I brought
my sister as my date,
and we were both
on the red carpet
like a bunch of pissed-off
New Yorkers.
[Michelle] Some things
never change, darling.
[RuPaul]
Paparazzi love her.
Next up, Eureka,
the "Telephone" video.
Yes.
[Eureka] Guilty as charged.
I decided to do
the "Telephone" look.
I just want to give them
something big and glamorous
and kind of risky couture.
Got my titties on my chin,
cinch, pull and tuck, honey,
that's the D.
[Lady Gaga]
Great choice, darling.
I believe that was
Jean de Castelbajac
who made that garment.
[Michelle] Oh, you say that
to all the queens.
[RuPaul] Next up, Charlie Hides,
Brit Awards 2010.
[Carson] That's a lace-front wig,
I believe.
[RuPaul] I believe it is.
[Carson] Yes.
I've chosen to wear the outfit
that Lady Gaga wore
for the 2010 Brit Awards.
I've done Lady Gaga
hundreds of times on YouTube,
and I think I’m pretty polished,
so I'm fairly confident.
Philip Treacy
made this for McQueen,
and he gave it to me because
I was doing a tribute to him.
[RuPaul] Don't be a drag,
be a McQueen.
Next up, Farrah Moan,
the "Alejandro" video.
Pray and slay.
[Michelle] Oh, my God,
look at her cross.
I look exactly like Lady Gaga
in my "Alejandro"
music video look,
and I'm rocking my real hair
and I really hope
that Lady Gaga lives for it.
That attitude and the face
is really good,
and the makeup is on point
because Steven Klein and I
had an argument about it.
I thought it was too much makeup
in this scene.
[Michelle]
Don't cross this queen.
[Ross] Everybody needs a virgin
to sacrifice.
[RuPaul]
Can I get an amen?
Next up, Sasha Velour,
the "Applause" video.
Do I have something
on my face?
[all laugh]
I'm wearing my favorite look
that she has ever done.
A Pierrot clown, high art,
Pat McGrath makeup.
It is the place
where art and pop meet.
[Lady Gaga] It's gonna be hard for this
not to be one of my favorites.
[Michelle] What do you live for, Gaga?
The applause.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul]
Painted for the Gaga.
[all laugh]
Alexis Michelle,
the Golden Globes.
Best actress realness.
[Alexis] When I saw Gaga
at the Golden Globes in this gown,
I said she's wearing
Alexis Michelle's body.
So here I am body, curve,
swerve and trophies.
Yay!
[Lady Gaga] Donatella Versace
made this for me.
That is not easy to
make that bodice that way.
Wonderful job, darling,
and thank you for bringing
my Globe with you.
[Carson] It's Ver-sayce.
[RuPaul]
Matching trophy.
Shea Coulee,
Monster Ball Tour.
Ross] Paws up, baby.
My Lady Gaga look,
it's ethereal, powerful,
yet gentle and serene,
and it mixes engineering
and fashion.
This reminds me of the film
that Nick Knight did
with the yellow electric
urine blonde.
Mmm.
[Carson] Urine blonde is
my screen name on Scruff.
[Lady Gaga] It is?
[Carson] Yes.
[Lady Gaga]
It's my password on Netflix.
[RuPaul] Trinity Taylor,
American Horror Story, Hotel.
[Lady Gaga] Yes, Countess.
[Carson] Yes.
[Trinity]
This look speaks to me
because I love darkness
and glamour and vampires.
And Lady Gaga
was so seductive and sexy
and brilliant in the show.
Trinity, a little club soda
will take that right out.
You know, they say
that if you use your own spit,
the enzymes
break down the blood, so...
[RuPaul] Good to know.
[Michelle] Thank you.
[RuPaul]
This competition is cutthroat.
Kimora Blac,
Lady Gaga "On The Go."
[Lady Gaga]
This is the Versace phase.
[Kimora] I'm giving a look that Gaga
wears to, like, the airport.
I think picking out what
she's done for red carpets
is so predictable
and it's so, like,
all right, done.
[Lady Gaga] Those boots,
they remind me of the pleasers
that I used to get
off of, um...
[Michelle]
Hollywood Boulevard, honey.
[Lady Gaga] Yep, yep.
[Carson]
No ifs, ands or butts about it.
-Uh-uh.
-No, ma'am.
[RuPaul] Jaymes Mansfield,
the cover of Vogue.
Oh.
I am serving you Gaga
on the cover of Vogue.
My drag is campy
and different,
so I'm giving you Lady Gaga
in slumberland.
I look amazing.
If they don't like this dress,
don't blame me,
blame Marc Jacobs.
[RuPaul]
Oh, she's a little sleepy.
[Carson] It's Marc Jacobs.
She's Marco-leptic.
[Lady Gaga] She's actually
not wrong, either,
because I was so tired
the day that we did that shoot
that that's probably what
I looked like in between shots.
[RuPaul] Cover girl,
put some gel in your hair.
Nina Bo'nina Brown,
VMAs 2009.
Oh, my God.
[Michelle]
Yes, McQueen, yes.
This was one of the biggest
nights of my life.
[Nina] I'm serving you
the black version of Lady Gaga.
Lot of hips, a lot of ass
and a lot of sass.
I can't see how Lady Gaga
is reacting
because I can't see anybody.
[Ross] I just love the expression
in her face
when she wears this outfit.
You know, you can tell
she's happy.
[RuPaul] Oh, no,
she's on the edge of whore-y.
Up next, Aja,
Commes des Garcons.
[Carson] Now, where did I
park my car?
[Aja] For my Lady Gaga look,
I'm wearing a remake of her
Commes des Garcons look
that she wore to show
that beauty has no shape.
[Lady Gaga]
You know, I wore this
because the media
was saying I was fat
and I knew this archive,
so I called Commes des Garcons
and I asked them
if we could wear it.
It's such an excellent choice.
[Ross] And very slimming.
[Lady Gaga]
It's all about the waist.
[Michelle] Oy, gevalt.
[all laugh]
Okay, judges,
we are looking for one winner
who has what it takes.
Let's start with Peppermint.
I think Peppermint
has a fun personality.
You could tell that she likes
to take the piss with her drag,
and I do like that.
I thought her Lady Liberty
was kind of basic to me.
Peppermint's David Bowie,
it would have been so great
to have the lightning bolt.
-On the face, yeah.
-Yeah.
I love when I see
the exact impression
and the detail in that,
but the adding
of the hoop earrings,
I didn't understand it.
Bowie wouldn't have
worn them that big.
-If he did, he would've worn one.
-One, exactly.
You know,
so I'm looking at detail.
[RuPaul] Valentina.
[Ross] That hometown look of hers
was my very favorite look
of anybody up there.
It was just
such a strong look,
and her Spanish sombrero,
East L.A. homage,
I thought it was super fun.
I thought she was beautiful
and I thought
the makeup was on point.
And then, the Lady Gaga look
was also super strong.
[Lady Gaga] Both of these looks
brought a tear to my eye.
Her walk was fantastic.
For me,
she was the best model.
[Michelle] Mm-hmm.
[RuPaul] Wow.
Eureka, that first outfit,
there was a little bit of
a used-up Tina Turner there.
Tina Turner away.
I was laughing and entertained
and that's part of this.
[Michelle]
As far as her Gaga look,
I thought it was fun,
it was detailed.
She's actually one of
my favorites of the night.
[RuPaul] Charlie Hides.
Her first look was the pilgrim.
I wasn't blown away
by the first look.
I felt like there was supposed
to be a rip-away moment
and it kind of just
sort of got a little mangled.
But the Gaga look might have
been one of my favorites.
[Lady Gaga] The detail of the way that
that lace sort of interlays,
it's beautifully done.
[RuPaul] Farrah Moan.
[Michelle] That first outfit
was definitely not Las Vegas.
I felt it was more like
a different version
of, like, Anna Karenina,
you know.
Anna Karenina
goes to Game of Thrones.
Well, she does
sort of look like
she's in the main showroom
of the Vatican.
-Yes.
-[laughs]
[Michelle] As far as her Gaga look,
being a smaller queen,
she chose something
that swallowed her up,
and that might not have been
the best idea for a Gaga look.
[Lady Gaga] I was hoping that there
was gonna be a tear-away.
-Yes.
-And there wasn't.
I do have to say
I was impressed by her poise.
I'm wearing Poise
right now, actually.
Sasha Velour.
One too many props
can spoil a good party.
She was kind of cumbersomely
standing up there
holding these things.
Hey, Michelle, it's only
episode one of season nine,
and I'm already
disagreeing with you.
-Okay.
-Okay?
-Go on.
-I like more is more.
I like that she brought
the props.
She didn't waste any time
showing us who she is.
Too much.
If you just lose the portrait,
this would've been
a perfect performance.
Look at Gaga finding middle ground
for Michelle and I.
[Michelle] And then, "Applause,"
I thought she did well
and even in
that kind of flowy thing,
-it changed her persona.
-Yes.
Yeah, I didn't know
who it was.
-Right.
-And that is great drag.
Yeah.
I don't think any other queen
told us exactly who she is
better than she did.
[RuPaul]
Alexis Michelle.
When you're gonna use things
like words on your body,
you have to be able
to read them.
Mm-hmm.
And the way they were
positioned on the bustier
and on the corset,
you couldn't read them.
The point was lost.
But her Gaga moment
was stunning.
-Yeah.
-That dress is amazing.
You could put Donald Trump
in that dress,
he's gonna look gorgeous.
-No.
-Now, that I don't agree.
The shape and the silhouette
that she achieved,
-this was really good.
-Mm-hmm.
This is someone to watch,
I think.
[RuPaul]
Shea Coulee.
What'd you think about
that first outfit?
[Carson] I thought that was really fun
and very memorable.
I mean, who doesn't like
a giant wiener on your head?
As long at it's girth-y.
And I thought
the Gaga look was great.
[RuPaul] That dress is just amazing.
The dress was actually made
by Jim Henson.
-Of The Muppets?
-Yes. The original dress
was made in very particularly
pleated origami,
and it was mechanical.
And I felt that
some of the other girls
went a little further
with the detail.
Let's talk Trinity Taylor,
no relation to Rip Taylor.
-Oh, damn it!
-Yeah.
I thought Trinity's Orlando outfit
was kind of nondescript.
You wouldn't know
where she was from.
Now, when she turned around,
it was the kind of anal sun.
Yeah.
And it was kind of like,
oh, okay.
But her Countess Lady Gaga
drag I loved.
[RuPaul] Phenomenal.
I loved it from top to bottom,
and everybody knows
I love a bottom.
[Lady Gaga] That hair that she did
for the Countess
is so difficult to do.
To get that type
of smoothness
and to get the lace to lay
that flat is very hard.
She fucking nailed it.
[RuPaul]
Let's move on to Kimora Blac.
[Michelle] I thought the first look
was not indicative of Vegas to me.
It was very cheap looking.
And the Gaga look, to me,
it just seemed like something
you'd see in a bar.
There's no pizzazz.
I think she needs a moment
to get comfortable.
[RuPaul] Jaymes Mansfield.
[Ross] I love whimsy.
[RuPaul] Yeah?
[Ross] I thought I was being served
a comedy queen.
I was left with a little
drag blue balls with her.
I didn't get what I thought
I was going to get.
Well, there's so much
you could get.
If you're from Milwaukee,
I mean, you could be
covered in cheese.
You could have a wig
that looks like an udder.
Like, you can't go halfway.
Right. Like,
take it to the next level.
Milk it. You milk it.
Milk it, honey, yeah.
What did you think
of her interpretation
of your Vogue cover?
The hair is not what it was.
My bigger issue
is I think she's hiding.
It's about her just letting
her true self shine through.
[RuPaul] All right. Let's talk
about Nina Bo'nina Brown.
[Ross] I was so excited
when she walked around
the corner.
It's whimsical,
but it's also fabulous.
That insane peach face
with the head.
It's so twisted,
and yet it's so beautiful.
And this choice
of the McQueen,
she makes a statement
with each piece.
[RuPaul] She has
a point of view, yeah.
She has a point of view
as an artist.
I see a star.
[RuPaul]
Let's move on to Aja.
[Carson] I wasn't blown away
by the Statue of Liberty moment.
It's okay.
Why do you hate America,
Carson?
[all laugh]
I did love
the Commes des Garcons look,
but the makeup was real bad.
I don't know
that she nailed it tonight,
but this girl,
she's gonna keep surprising you.
All right. Judges,
time to fill out your scorecards
and bring back my girls.
The Florida election committee
will be verifying these results.
[laughs]
Welcome back.
I've combined
the judges' scores,
divided them by five
and added a 20% tip.
[laughs]
When I call your name,
please step forward.
-Eureka.
-Ooh.
Sasha Velour.
Nina Bo'nina Brown.
[gasps] Oh.
I wish you could see
the expression on your face.
[laughs]
I wish I could see
the expression on your face.
Con-drag-ulations, ladies.
You are
our top three finalists.
Now, if for any reason
tonight's winner
cannot complete her reign,
the first and second runner-ups
will thumb wrestle
to determine
who takes her place.
[all laugh]
I hold in my hand
the name of Miss Charisma
Uniqueness, Nerve & Talent.
Ladies and gentlemen, the winner
of a fabulous weeklong getaway
to The Grand Resort and Spa,
Fort Lauderdale's premiere
gay men's spa resort...
[inhales]
And the title of Miss Charisma
Uniqueness, Nerve & Talent...
The winner is...
Nina Bo'nina Brown.
-Yes!
-[applause]
Come on, mama.
[Nina] For them to crown me,
it means a lot to me.
Girl, Lady Gaga
bought my drag.
She bought it.
She didn't rent it
from the Netflix.
She bought it.
Validation complete.
Is there anything
you'd like to say?
I know that this is
just the beginning,
but to get you guys' approval
for this means a lot to me.
Thank y'all so much for this.
I truly appreciate it
from my heart.
Well, my queen, go ahead
and serve your public, honey.
Yeah. Come on, baby.
Yes.
Congratulations, darling.
[RuPaul]
Nina Bo'nina Brown!
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Stop the music, please.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have to apologize.
This is not a Steve Harvey
moment.
Nina, you are still our winner.
You are still our winner,
honey, but...
The real competition
is just about to begin.
I'm introducing...
a 14th queen into the race.
[Michelle gasps]
[Ross] What?
Who?
Fuck! Oh!
Breathe.
Please welcome back
to the race...
the 14th contestant
in the 9th season
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
-[screams]
-Yeah!
Bitch!
Ru, are you punking us?
Oh, my God.
No fucking way.
What?
♪ Yeah, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ Hey, kitty girl ♪
♪ It's your world ♪
♪ When you walk the street
steppin' to the beat ♪
♪ Hey, kitty girl ♪
♪ Get your crown ♪
♪ In the disco heat
you're the boogie night rockin' queen ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Kitty kitty,
Hey, here kitty kitty ♪
♪ Hey, kitty kitty, yeah ♪
♪ Ahh, yeah, whoa-oh-oh ♪