Megan's like Conor's little maid.
Megan, you are our winner.
The person going home is Jo.
Now, only seven remain.
And tonight on "Face Off"...
This challenge is vile.
I love it.
Your next Spotlight Challenge... zombies.
But there's something that you should know.
Are you kidding me?
Once I saw the wrinkles come to life,
I was, like, "This is cool."
The blood is just so heavy on the face.
It's a stunning makeup.
To make it to the top,
they'll have to impress
our award-winning panel of judges
Ve Neill, legendary makeup artist,
whose work includes
"Edward Scissorhands",
"Beetlejuice", and the
"Pirates Of The Caribbean"films.
Glenn Hetrick, cutting-edge
makeup effects artist on"Heroes",
"Legion", and "Buffy The Vampire Slayer".
And Patrick Tatopoulus,
visionary creature designer
for "Independence day", "Godzilla",
and director of
" Underworld: Rise Of The Lycans".
Who will be the next great
name in movie magic
and earn $100,000 dollars
and a year's worth of
makeup from Alcone?
Get ready for "Face Off".
Sync by YYeTs
Corrected by ThreeSixes
www.addic7ed.com
What's up, guys?
Want some breakfast?
The loft is super empty without Jo.
I miss her.
But ever since Jo left,
we've created a truce.
So what do you guys feel?
There's more positivity
between the two lofts?
Honestly, I feel like a
weight's been lifted.
So I walk into the lab,
and as soon as I round the corner
I see there's a piece of glass, a t-shirt,
a bucket and a brush,
or some kind of weird challenge.
Welcome to your next
Foundation Challenge.
As you know, the winner of
the Foundation Challenge
will earn an advantage
going into the Spotlight Challenge.
Today, you are at the scene of a crime.
The only thing missing is the blood.
One of the first things that
we do as makeup artists,
you learn how to get blood right.
You will have exactly one hour
to create a gallon of blood
using the various supplies
that we have provided you with,
such as chocolate syrup, chicken guts,
ultra slime, laundry detergent,
tomato soup, acrylic paints, food coloring,
and hand sanitizer.
Every effects artist I know
has a recipe for blood.
doesn't share that recipe.
So let me introduce you to
your guest judge for the day.
He's a former LAPD detective,
where he worked everything
from Homicide to Vice,
and now he's a private investigator.
Please welcome Bob Jakucs.
Hey, Bob. How are you?
Hello, McKenzie. How are you?
Good. Thank you so much for being here.
Thanks for having me.
After your hour is up,
you will each participate
in a blood splatter test.
So, Bob, what will you
be looking for today?
The color, the texture,
and especially the quantity.
Was it blunt force trauma?
Are they thinking it's
a gunshot wound?
My grandfather was a cop for 37 years.
And I know those guys are always saying,
"Oh, that's movie blood.
That's not real."
That makes this a tough competition.
Your clock starts now.
Now we look like psychotic scientists.
I start grabbing the chicken guts
because I love the splat
sound that it makes.
This challenge is gross,
disgusting, vile.
I love it.
Real chicken guts? I don't like it.
I certainly wouldn't use it on a film set.
When I make blood,
I like it to be edible and safe.
I use corn starch to add opacity,
corn syrup for some thickening,
and I went for the laundry detergent
because laundry detergent
can keep from beading up
on your skin and looking fake.
All I kept thinking was my grandfather
would have to believe this is real blood.
What I'm doing here is
making sure it doesn't get too translucent.
If it starts to look see-through,
and then it looks like
syrup, not like blood.
It's kind of cool.
It stinks over here.
I think it's Meg.
Megan breaks out the blender
and starts pureeing chicken guts.
I swear to God,
it smelled like it was
Elizabeth, New Jersey,
it was so bad.
It is your 10-minute warning.
Aah!
Time is up. Grab your blood and
please come over to the walls.
I want you to all fling your blood at once.
Go!
What we're supposed to do is throw
blood up against the glass,
the t-shirt, and the wooden panel.
My technique is to spatter
it on there with my fingers.
I know that, realistically,
blood does not cover the walls.
When he said crime scene,
I was, like, "I'm going all out."
Gage created blood lake.
I was half tempted to throw my
whole bucket against the wall.
Time is up.
- Hey, Tate. - Hey.
Bob, what do you think?
This is good here, where you've got
tissue or even brain.
This area is good.
It's a little excessive over here,
and also up on the glass.
This would be good for a gunshot wound.
You could have put that more
down where the wounds were.
These drops wouldn't be as big.
They would be more along these
lines here down at the bottom.
This is a 2x4 to the head, repeatedly.
Your spattering here is good.
Less is best.
- Wow.
- How's it going?
Good. What happened?
It was a really deep gash
decapitating the head,
as well as a very deep stomach wound
basically bleeding out.
Bleeding out all depends on gravity.
So if they decapitated them
and the body and the head went down,
yeah, you would have a lot of bleeding.
I think it may be a little more excessive
than we needed to do.
I figured that if a bullet
is going straight through someone's head
that the back is going to burst open.
Megan, your puddling is good.
I like that.
As we move up, blood really
wouldn't look as watery as yours.
There would be more of a
thicker element to it.
So, Bob, who do you think nailed it?
Tate, your creative use
of tissue was very good...
the aspect of skin or brain
in a really traumatic
injury was really good
in the way you up it up there.
All right, thank you.
Tom, the spray portion,
the spatter portion,
looked very, very good.
Who's the winner of this challenge?
The winner is...
Tom.
I'm super happy to get the win,
because I did take this challenge
thinking that this is a cop,
I know what he wants to see.
The reason I chose Tom
was that less in this situation was better.
Best spatter pattern that you
would normally see in a
situation like this.
Tom.
Thank you.
You have won an advantage
going into the Spotlight Challenge.
Sweet.
All right, Bob, it was great
having you here with us today.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, McKenzie.
All right, guys, let's talk about
your next Spotlight Challenge.
This one is an all-time classic makeup.
Zombies.
Yes!
McKenzie announces zombies.
All of us collectively were, like, "Yes!"
For this challenge, you
will need to create your
own original zombie.
And the stakes are higher than ever
because this week two of
you will be eliminated.
When McKenzie dropped the bomb
that two of us would be going home,
I could feel everyone really
get intense about it.
So, Tom, as the winner of
the Foundation Challenge,
you get to pick your model first.
The rest of you will
choose your models in
randomly selected order.
I have an idea,
so I pick my model based on the fact
that he has a super-chiseled jaw.
All right, guys, your time starts now.
I want to do kind of a
classic '80s style zombie
who is now just a dried-out husk,
kind of falling apart, all leathery.
My concept is a shark
attack zombie in a wetsuit,
big shark bites on his torso.
He's blue in the face.
Right away, I just started
jumping into the sculpture.
I'm going to sculpt the face out
of clay on top of the lifecast,
and then I'll use my
sculpture to make a mold.
I'm making a zombie hooker.
I'm sure there's been a
zombie hooker somewhere
in one movie somewhere along the line,
but not as cool as this.
The title of it would
be called "I love L.A".
This woman's going to have a lot
of botched plastic surgery.
She didn't pay her bills on time.
It's a home invasion zombie.
Its guts spill everywhere,
and it's a freshly torn open human being.
So there has to be blood everywhere.
What's yours, Gage?
A World War II veteran who was killed.
I want to put shrapnel in him
and I want him to be really messed up.
He's going to be maybe three days dead.
Most of the classic zombies
are thin people that they
try to make look thinner.
So I thought, "You know what?
"Let's build up in order to subtract."
Two hours into everybody's designs
people are sculpting like
mad and full-steam ahead,
because, finally, zombies.
Hey, guys, if I could have
you please gather around?
I'm thinking McKenzie's just
coming around to say hi.
No. No, she just doesn't
pop in just to say hi.
There's something that you should know.
Sometimes in the real world,
a director will change a
scene at the last minute.
This is one of those cases.
sometimes in the real world,
a director will change a
scene at the last minute.
This is one of those cases.
What do you know?
There's going to be a twist.
I'm thinking "They're
going to pull our models."
"I sculpted boobs on this".
"If they give me a guy, I'm screwed."
This week, your models are all...
Dancers.
And your zombies will now be performing
a choreographed dance
routine on the reveal stage
in front of the judges.
So, that means the judges are
going to be looking very closely
to make sure that your makeup holds up.
So please rethink your
makeups accordingly, okay?
- Good luck.
- You got it.
I was like, "Are you kidding me?"
- All right.
- That's awesome.
What's your character?
It's a zombie.
McKenzie tells us the zombies
are going to be dancing now.
Well, it kind of helped make up my...
it threw...
I'm...
The thing is, I was going to do
this shark attack zombie in a wetsuit,
and I've worn a wetsuit.
They're not maneuverable.
So I'm trying to think of a different idea
other than a wetsuit right now.
No intestines hanging out?
I think they might trip now.
I had planned originally for
this really cinematic entrance.
I wanted 10-15 feet of
intestines dangling out of her,
dragging on the floor behind her.
It was going to be gross.
I need a wardrobe change.
I just crapped my pants.
I have to change my medium.
I was going to cast originally in silicone.
Oh, no.
But not if they're going to be moving.
The whole dance twist
hasn't really changed
any part of my design,
except, forget silicone.
I'm running on foam.
Definitely no silicone or gelatin.
They're going to be
sweating their asses off.
I was considering it... full foam.
I'm going foam with this.
Yeah, this is all foam now.
Gelatin breaks down with sweat huge.
It will melt right off of you.
Silicone would be way too heavy.
So a lot of people have had
to resort to foam latex,
which to me is appropriate
for zombie work anyway
because they can be more opaque.
If you make zombies look too translucent,
they look fake.
Tate's doing this insane...
he's doing a Tate piece.
Dude, that is one sick-looking face!
Me!
Yeah, I'm going the ground hamburger route.
Man, you.
Are you done with your sculpt already?
The body, yeah.
No ? Wow.
I went with zombie prostitute
because prostitutes are
scary enough as it is.
I think what the judges are
definitely going to be looking for
is pieces falling off.
That is not happening to me.
Now that they're dancing...
kind of threw some people for a loop.
Some other people just went with it.
It didn't slow me down at all.
That looks awesome.
It's supposed to be plastic surgery.
I'm going to have saline
underneath, like, fake water.
I dig it.
My plan of attack today
is to sculpt and mold the breasts,
add detail,
and then focus on the face tomorrow,
because to me the face is
the most important thing.
- How's it going, Tom?
- It's going.
I love the fact that you do
anything you want to a zombie
but it won't die unless you
take off its head or burn them.
This is going to be a zombie
that has been run over.
So he's going to have a squished stomach
with a huge tire mark across it.
Delicious.
I'm really going to try to create
the optical illusion that he's missing
a good chunk of his stomach.
If I can pull that off,
I think this is going to look really cool.
Do you like it?
Are you just saying that?
No.
I'm doing face, neck, arms, and hands
because I don't want to deliver something
that's going to be similar
in style or fashion
to what someone else is doing.
After five hours of sculpting,
looking at the chest, looking at the face,
I feel like they really go together nicely.
I really like this belly.
I like how you blended
it out on the hip bone.
That's going to look really good.
Conor's design looks typical,
which isn't going to give
him the creative points.
Of course, Conor looks amazing, as usual.
I... his... his work looks amazing.
That's it everybody.
Tools down. Let's go home.
So day two in the shop. I'm really excited.
My goal for the end of the day
is to mold my face sculpture.
Then I'm going to sculpt both
ears and start the chest.
Are you going big on the face?
Are you going to do, like, the zombie brow?
I'm leaving her mouth,
but everything's kind of torn away
kind of like in the middle
of getting a facelift.
My goal for today
is to sculpt the muscle
underneath the skin.
So I break out the
"Gray's Anatomy" book
and I am seeing all the
muscles and everything.
Once my sculpture is finished,
I'll cover it in a
substance like wet cement
that hardens around it to make a mold.
When my mold is ready, I'll clean it out
and then I'll fill it with foam latex.
Just doing some more pieces.
Nice.
So, like he was all chomped on and stuff.
Then I'm going to make some sharp metal.
I'm really taking the
ball and running with it.
I'm seeing the whole picture and loving it
because as an artist if you
can see that whole picture,
you can go for it.
Hey, guys.
- Hello.
- How are y'all doing?
Patrick and I are here to
take a look at your works.
How are you doing here?
Unfortunately, I have
very little to show you.
It's almost an '80s-style zombie.
Got you.
I decided to go with zombie prostitute.
Cool concept.
What I'm trying to incorporate
is the anatomy underneath the skin.
I want the skin to look
like it's been peeled away
to look like it's been in
the middle of surgery.
Mm-hmm.
Having McKenzie and
Patrick look at our work,
it kind of makes you question
your whole artistic skills
and whether you're going
to impress them or not.
Did the dancing challenge change anything?
My only concern was the arm appliances.
I didn't want to do silicone
because it's too heavy.
I decided to go with foam on those.
- Excellent.
- Good work.
- Thank you.
Well, interesting.
Some of them are actually quite
traditional in their designs.
And you got some very
original ideas as well.
Megan, for example, has a
very interesting concept.
What do you think about Tom's?
I think he went for something
more detailed in the sculpt.
He wanted to show maybe more
that he can actually deliver the goods.
When it comes to Anthony,
I'm a little worried that he decided
to paint on some of the internal organs
rather than sculpt them
into the prosthetics.
We'll see how it turns out.
Good old Tate is going crazy.
He used wet clay,
which was clever.
With a prosthetic that big,
it allowed him to sculpt a
lot of detail very fast.
All right, Patrick. Thank you.
My pleasure.
All right, everybody,
keep up the good work.
- Thank you, guys.
- Thank you.
Bye. Take care.
Five minutes, y'all!
The character's developing
right before my eyes.
I have the wig, I got the outfit.
I'm not worried about my zombie at all.
In this challenge,
there are some that are
stronger than others.
From what I can see, Megan's is
weaker than everyone else's.
Everybody's looks awesome.
I didn't expect my stuff to be
as amazing as Conor's or Tate's,
but I'm actually getting pretty worried.
I'm wondering now, "Well, shoot,
does a zombie mean a tribute
to "Dawn Of The Dead?"
"Or anything else we've seen?"
Because mine is kind of
like "Hellraiser"looking.
"Two people going home" keeps
repeating over and over,
and I feel like my time is ending.
I'm really scared.
Today is application day.
Now that the prosthetic is set up,
it can be removed from the mold
and then applied to the
model's face and painted.
- How'd your pieces come out?
- Very nice.
The Application Day
is when people's characters
start coming together.
That's when I start
to get a little scared.
I start to second-guess myself
or I start to give myself false confidence.
This fits you like a glove.
This is going to be completely disgusting.
I will continue to choose
Deb whenever I can,
because she is like one of the dudes.
You're going to owe me a drink after this.
Yeah, right.
Joy is a good sport.
I think she has one concern
about the fat suit,
and that is limiting her motion.
Otherwise, she's in it to win it.
Slide on in.
Hello.
Diana comes over.
She's actually really excited
because the last time we worked together
it was the alien challenge, which I won.
This is all going to be kind of torn open
so we can see all the carnage.
Oh, amazing. Okay. I'm excited.
I... I... that's a really nice breast.
Oh, wow.
Today two people have to go home.
- Oh. Really?
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Every competition, the judges
have criticized my paint job,
because I never have enough time
to paint it the way I want it.
I'm not going to let that happen this time.
Painting is one of my strongest points
and I need them to know that.
I'm in trouble because of time management.
I got so caught up in the paint
that I didn't get a chance to
do everything I wanted to do.
Tom what's that clock say?
- 30 minutes. - Thank you.
Once I put the first coat of the wash
and I saw the wrinkles come to life,
I was, like, "Holy crap".
"I've got something good here."
Gage's is looking pretty cool.
Tate's looks incredible.
- Conor.
- Lift your head up, please.
He is a talented, trained artist.
There's some not so impressive stuff.
Anthony is body-painting
organs, which could hurt him.
I mean, we're going in
front of zombie experts.
I did glance over at
Megan's a couple times.
Little concerned about what
she's got going on in the face.
It's very bloody.
There is this fine line
between utilizing blood
and using blood to cover things up.
Tom's is a pretty cool idea,
but he isn't going in the right
direction with his wrinkle lines.
We're just freaking out
because we all know a group
elimination is coming.
It definitely raised the bar.
So we're backstage and its last looks time.
I think the majority of worry
that I have is about Joy's arm
because there's a distinct line
between prosthetic and hand
and that's really bothering me.
You look disgusting.
I'm worried a little bit about the tongue.
If she does the caterpillar or something,
it could bend straight
up and be in her face.
- Time, please!
- 12 minutes.
I wanted mine to look bloody,
but not actually be bloody.
Because if they are bloody and
they're rolling on the floor
and jumping up and down, they're
going to fling blood everywhere
and stick to everything.
I'm really worried because I think
I overdid it with the blood.
You cover stuff with blood,
you usually get ridiculed.
I mean, the lights...
that's just going to shine
out red like a candy apple.
Welcome to the "Face Off" reveal stage.
Tonight, two of you will be eliminated.
Say, hello to your judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening, guys.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
Hi, everybody.
Creature designer and director
Patrick Tatopoulos.
- Hello, everyone.
- Hi, Patrick.
And your guest judge this week
is a special effects legend
who's worked on everything
from "Transformers",
to "Sin City", to "The
Chronicles Of Narnia",
and "The Walking Dead".
Please welcome two-time Emmy
Award-winner Greg Nicotero.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi, Greg.
Our judge this week
is Greg Nicotero.
He's such a legend in the effects
community and well-respected.
I'm so nervous right now.
So this week your Spotlight Challenge
was to create an original zombie makeup.
Then we threw a twist at you.
Not only does your zombie
need to look amazing,
but they must also survive
a full-on dance routine.
Now before we see the performance,
let's check out your zombies.
I'm really happy with
everything that I created
concerning my character,
right down the background.
Because it's really important.
These judges, they want to
see a complete package.
I feel like I've delivered that very well.
I'm feeling pretty good.
I think she looks very
stylish and very cool.
It's pretty much what I envisioned.
I had a zombie hooker...
face falling off, sliding
all over the place.
I had a whole character behind my zombie.
The big difference with this
Spotlight Challenge is
that two people go home.
So I'm starting to get a little scared.
I love my zombie. He's cool.
The paint came out exactly
how I wanted it to.
He looks like shoe leather.
Joy's outfit is hilarious.
In a roomful of drab zombies,
she really does stand out.
But it's the arms that I'm worried about.
Didn't have the coloration that I wanted.
It was just rushed.
I feel that I covered too much
of my sculpture with blood.
Deb's a nutjob.
Deb takes the ball that I hand her
and then she just runs downfield with it.
The piece fits her perfectly.
She has sold every makeup I've put on her.
I couldn't be happier.
So now let's see if they can stay intact.
This dance was choreographed
by the hot young duo Craig and Lindsay,
fittingly put to the song "Zombie"
by recording artist Natalia Kills.
Let's bring on the zombies.
The lights drop and all of
the zombies fall into place
and I'm terrified that that
tongue is going to hit the floor
and bend some odd direction.
Coming up...
You see the undead come
to life and then boogie.
It's the coolest thing.
I would shoot that tomorrow.
Great.
Don't put things over their mouth.
It's a stunning makeup.
Everything needs to hold
up to this dance routine,
that is the challenge.
So my fingers are crossed.
That was great.
I'm looking, everything
seems to be in place,
the tongue is intact,
guts are still all held in with that sack.
There was not one drop of
blood, not one smear of goo.
Nothing on the floor.
We all seemed to pull it together
and do a pretty good Job.
To see the undead come
to life and then boogie,
it's the coolest thing.
Judges, why don't you take a closer look?
That feels like a tendon.
Eww. Eww.
For whatever reason,
they spend 10 million years on my zombie.
And I was, like, "Oh, my God,
oh, my God," like, insanity.
There's a, kind of a
creepiness to the sculpture.
It feels really leathery,
which I think is fantastic.
I'm not sure what this spike sticking out,
I don't know if that's supposed to be...
I think it's supposed to be a tooth.
- Tooth or a...
- Couple of teeth in here, too.
This is Tom, yeah?
I've given up trying to
read their expressions
or their lips when they
take the closer look.
Tire tread.
I do notice that Ve notices
my tire tread mark and
I'm feelin' pretty good.
This way.
I'm a little nervous
about the two people being sent home.
If the judges really just
look at the face piece,
I'll be okay.
This is an appliance here, too.
But it's the arms that I'm worried about.
There's a distinct line
between prosthetic and hand
and that's really bothering me.
There's some organs there,
there's a sternum.
Oh, dear, she's stuck.
There's so much blood,
it's really hard to see exactly
what that sculpt looks like.
Okay.
The judges would like to
speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
So, Tom, if you'd please step forward.
Glenn, let's start with you.
Although I do love the asymmetry
and I think that you really
tried to get in there
with the limited time
that you had to sculpt,
I have some big problems
with the weight of the skin
and physically how the skin decays
and the patterns of the wrinkles.
If you would have gotten in
there and done some, like,
tight veining or modeling,
that might have helped, also,
with the sculpt.
Totally understand what you're saying,
but I feel that my zombie
is a little beyond vein work
because he's pretty leather.
I love the idea of the tire tracks
and all that whole scenario.
Thank you.
But the overall concept was kind of boring.
I do have to agree with Glenn
that some of the texturing
in the sculpture was a little
bit distracting for me.
I felt the brow was maybe
a little bit heavy
and the wrinkles across the
forehead looked a little carved.
Thank you very much. You can step back.
Tate. If you would please step forward.
How you doin', girl?
Hi, guys.
There's some things that you know are
in diametrical opposition
to things that I've said.
Don't put things over their mouth
so that they can't articulate
and they couldn't perform,
but you decided to go ahead and do that.
Glenn seems to be the hardest
of the judges to impress.
He looks me in the eye and, you know,
"You chose to do a static mouth.
"I know you didn't forget."
And I was like,
"Crap, I'm going home."
There's some things that you know are
in diametrical opposition
to things that I've said.
Don't put things over their mouths
so that they can't articulate
and they couldn't perform
and clearly you knew you were doing that
when you designed this make-up
but you decided to go ahead and do that.
I respect that decision and it paid off.
Thank you.
It's the success of a zombie makeup
and I'm really happy with it.
Thank you very much.
Well, I gotta say she was most
effective when she walked out.
I love the whole broken
back routine and the walk.
You did a great job.
Thank you very much.
What are those slashing on the...
what I basically saw, a grab
from behind and tear open.
Opening. Okay. Very cool.
I wanted to emphasize the fingernail trails
as they ripped her flesh open.
Sorry, I think about these things.
Well, you should think about those things.
That's part of our job.
I thought it's great.
I really appreciate that.
Thank you, Deb.
Let's talk to Sam.
Sam, tell me about your back story.
I wanted her to look a lot different from
the other female zombies that
were gonna be out here today.
A lot of them were gonna
be on the skeletal side,
and so I thought bigger
is better in this case,
she'll stand out a little bit more.
I think that's very, very successful.
Since you were going with
kind of a fat makeup,
it would have been nice
to maybe build the neck
out a little bit more
so that it didn't just look like
she had kind of chubby cheeks.
Did she have appliances on her arms?
She does. Yeah.
Is that what I'm seeing is
the end of the appliance?
Yeah.
Not so good, huh?
But, all in all,
I think you did a very effective makeup.
Thank you.
Gage, please step forward.
The shrapnel ticking out...
That's good.
If you're talking about a guy
who was in a plane crash
had this horrible explosion and
there's shrapnel in his face,
the hat would probably be either
burned off or fused to his head.
Absolutely.
I think the left hand is highly successful
in showing anatomy underneath there.
My big concern is the color.
You used a lot of warm colors.
Was that a creative decision
or did the makeup kind
of go in that direction?
Originally, I was trying to do
a lot more blues and
purples towards the wound.
As I did that, though,
he started to lose a lot of
the depth and a lot of that,
so I stopped doing that and
it went in this direction.
But the pinkish overall
tone is a problem for me.
Other than that, I think it's really cool.
Thank you.
I love that look, I think
it's very powerful.
It's like creating a
strong, bold direction.
Thank you, guys.
Gage, thank you very much.
Megan, you are next, please.
Can you tell us the story of ts character?
A lot of people tend to get
plastic surgery living in L.A.
And I figured that they would
go and cut her face off
and everything that they fixed on her.
This idea of exposing
the silicone underneath
is a great one.
On the face, sculpturally,
it seems like you got there
but it's just so heavy on the blood gel.
The whole face being peeled off,
it's a really cute idea.
I think you went a little
heavy-handed with the blood.
Megan, I want to give you
a 10 for the concept.
I think it's the best concept tonight.
I think everybody agrees
with that, that this,
conceptually speaking,
that was a great idea.
Great sculpture drives a lot
of the power of the makeup
and sometimes you have to make sure
that you don't cover it too much.
Anthony, please step forward.
I think you kind of failed a little bit
on the sculpture on her face.
It doesn't really have
a lot of detail in it.
It looks a little lopsided
and not really well thought out to me.
I'm kind of bummed out.
My biggest thing is, actually,
is that everything sort of
becomes one blob in the top.
But it's one of the concepts
I thought were interesting
so I've got to give you that.
Thank you.
I don't know where the clothing ends
and where the chest appliance
begins and where the bra is
because the color of her wardrobe
and the color of some of the painting.
It's hard for me to really
see where one starts
and the other one ends.
I can definitely see what you're saying.
Conor, if you would please step forward.
I would shoot that tomorrow
on any zombie movie.
I think it's amazing.
Appreciate it.
You got every detail
absolutely perfect,
right down to her arms, her fingernails.
You even aged her hair to the right color.
It's-it's a stunning makeup.
Thank you.
The only thing I was not impressed with
was your concept.
I felt it was not something very original.
Glenn, why don't you tell
us about the top looks.
This week, our top two looks are...
Conor, for excelling in both
sculpting and painting.
Thank you.
And Tate...
For really strong concept,
creative, bold decisions.
So who's the winner?
This week's winner is...
Tate.
Oh . Whoo!
Come on, now.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you so much.
McKenzie. High five.
I've been busting my ass
off to get them to notice
that I'm here for a reason, so I'm psyched.
Whoo, okay.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
You have earned the right
to advise the judges
on which two contestants you
feel should be eliminated.
The rest of you can head
back to the makeup room
until the judges have
reached their decision.
Thank you.
Well, congratulations, Tate.
Who do you think did the worst job
this week on this challenge and why?
This isn't easy.
I would have to nominate, possibly, Megan.
I have yet to see something that
kind of creatively defines her.
I would prefer not to... to do a second.
Thanks, Tate.
- Thank you, Tate.
- Thank you very much, guys.
Good Job, Tate.
- Thank you. I appreciate it.
All right, judges.
Let's talk about Anthony.
What are your thoughts?
That was a bit of a mess.
I think he had a great idea in his head
but I just don't think he
ever really got it there.
It's just at this point,
he's out of his depth
with what's left here as far
as the competition goes.
Let's move on to Megan.
Conceptually,
it was more interesting than
some of the other makeups.
The idea was great.
I just don't think that the execution
quite fulfilled the idea.
That makeup could have
been done in 45 minutes
out of construction makeup out of the kit.
And what do you think about Tom?
Tom, that is one traditional,
plain zombie with not too much to...
Create something unique and special.
Bottom line, it really could
have been a pullover mask.
I think that maybe tom's
makeup was stronger.
- Yeah.
- But that Megan's concept was stronger.
It's a tough one.
So, judges, have you reached your decision?
- Yeah.
- We have.
Glenn, why don't you tell
us about the bottom looks?
Anthony,
you had significant sculptural mistakes
and critical flaws in your color.
Tom, tonight's challenge had
creativity and originality
in the overall concept
and I think that's where
you fell down this week.
Megan, I-I see what you're trying to do,
but for me, the blood's obscuring it.
Glenn, who is the first
person going home tonight?
The first person going home tonight is...
Anthony.
If you would please head
back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Again, judges, thank you so much.
It's been a pleasure.
Bye, guys. Thank you.
I'm going home.
You did good, man.
One more of you is going home tonight.
So, Glenn, who else has been eliminated?
The second person going home tonight is...
So, Glenn, who else is
going to be eliminated?
The second person going home tonight is...
Tom.
Tom, I'm sorry, but you
have been eliminated.
That's cool.
Guys, once again, thank you.
And I'll be seeing you again, I'm sure.
- Good luck, Tom.
- Good luck.
- I'm going home, guys.
- What?
- Yes, sir.
- Get the... out of here.
What they were looking for
wasn't what I gave them.
So...
Wow.
There has been some amazing
moments on this show,
and a lot of moments that
I'm super proud of...
images that I never want to forget.
Being a part of this show,
being able to showcase my
makeup to the whole world,
I had fun.
And that's all life is about.
Sync by YYeTs
Corrected by ThreeSixes
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net