Welcome to the season finale of "Face
Off".
12 talented special effects makeup artists
came to Los Angeles to compete
to join the world's elite.
Your time starts now.
You can't play it safe.
They made it really clear.
Time after time,
they showcased their tremendous
skill and creativity.
- It's genius.
- I'm blown away.
It's a stunning makeup.
And it didn't take long
for the pressure to take its toll.
You want to do details? Do details.
I don't want to lose to
the guy who's trying to get laid.
Every time I hear her laugh,
I want to punch someone in the face.
But challenge after challenge...
It will be down to the second.
Their numbers dwindle.
The person going home tonight is...
Jessica... Sergio...
Frank... Marcel...
Jo... Anthony...
Tom... Megan.
Now four have risen above the rest.
Your final challenge is to
reinvent two characters
from a classic fairy tale.
This is a ridiculous amount of work to do.
It's nearly impossible.
They'll have to dig
deeper than ever before.
I'm ready to win this $100,000.
I basically just lost the competition.
I'm freaking out.
I am not sure we're getting this done.
But to win it all,
they'll have to blow away our judges
one last time.
Ve Neill, legendary makeup artist,
whose work includes "Edward Scissorhands",
"Beetlejuice", and the "Pirates
of the Caribbean" films;
Glenn Hetrick, cutting-edge makeup
effects artist on "Heroes",
for "Independence Day", "Godzilla",
and director of "Underworld:
Rise of the Lycans".
Who will be the next great
name in movie magic
and earn $100,000 dollars
and a year's worth of makeup from alcone?
One of you is our champion.
Find out who claims victory
tonight on "Face Off".
Sync by YYeTs.net
Corrected by jabbberwock
www.addic7ed.com
It's still setting, like,
"Wow, we're the final four."
And this final challenge
is going to be amazing.
They've thrown everything at us.
Growing up was really
interesting, to say the least.
My stepfather was a mechanic
and my family lived in a trailer
that was in the middle of a junkyard.
So being a winner could really
help me and my family out.
I'm determined to make that happen.
This next challenge will define each of us
individually, artistically.
My girlfriend, she's everything to me.
And we both really want kids,
so if I win this competition,
we'll buy a crib.
We'll see what happens.
I've been in the middle the entire time.
Always on the safe, you know?
It's like, "I didn't really
come here to be safe."
Yeah.
I've made it this far.
I've got this chance to win the prize.
I know the judges have high
expectations of me now
and they're hoping to see me
show them something amazing.
The judges kp harping on me about concept.
I know that the one thing
I have to prove to the judges
is that I can think out of the box.
They want to see Tate-level...
- wackiness?
- Yeah.
I'm going to do everything
I can to win this hundred grand.
This isn't, "Oh, I'm just
trying this out
to see what I can make
in this competition."
I'm here to win.
We're going in to be introduced
to our final challenge.
It's really nerve-wracking.
It kind of feels like you want to vomit
and you're happy about it.
So it's weird.
Hey, guys.
- Hi.
- McKenzie.
Well, you should be feeling
pretty good with yourselves
because you are the final four.
The only thing that is
standing in between you
and $100,000 is your final
spotlight challenge.
Your final challenge is to reinvent
two characters from a classic fairy tale.
The judges have very high expectations,
so do not hold back.
I'm thinking, okay, this is great.
I have to show my creativity
and my ability to conceptualize
if I'm going to impress the judges.
These fairy tales are
"Little red riding hood",
"The frog prince", "Hansel and Gretel",
"Sleeping beauty", and
"The little mermaid".
As usual, it's not quite that simple
because there's a twist.
You will also be choosing
a theme to go along with your fairy tale.
Your themes are post-apocalyptic,
haunted, industrial,
psychedelic, and outer space.
And finally, you will be working
with our production designer
to create a complete background
where you will pose your characters,
essentially creating a living work of art.
Cool.
And three days from now
your tableaus will be on display
during an exclusive cocktail party
at the "Face Off" reveal stage.
You'll be judged on creativity, technique,
and the final presentation
of your characters and background scenes.
This is a ridiculous amount of work
to do in the time that we've been given.
People have no idea how long it takes
to get stuff done in the effects world.
This is "Mission: Impossible".
It is time to pick your fairy
tales and your themes.
Sam, as the winner of last
week's spotlight challenge,
you will get to choose first.
Ooh. All right.
This one.
So it looks like you picked
"The little mermaid".
And I think I'm going to
have to go with psychedelic.
I picked psychedelic because I feel
that psychedelic colors and
aquatic creatures go together.
All right, guys, I will be
choosing you in random order.
- Tate.
- Yes!
Thank you, McKenzie.
The last thing I want is
outer space "Sleeping Beauty".
So I'm really excited.
"Little red riding hood".
And post-apocalyptic.
I'm already putting together a vision
for post-apocalyptic
"Little red riding hood".
Getting the opportunity to
pick that for the finals
is a dream come true.
- Yay!
- Gage.
I had my sights set on "hansel and gretel".
But unfortunately Tate
took post-apocalyptic,
which was what I really wanted.
You have industrial "Hansel and Gretel".
- Yeah.
- All right.
Who's next?
My first choice was
"Little red riding hood",
but Tate got it.
And he got the post-apocalyptic theme,
which I also wanted.
- I'll go "Frog Prince".
- Oh, okay.
But I knew a little bit
about "the Frog Prince" fairy tale.
I knew there was a lot of potential there.
I'm going to go with haunted.
Remember, this is for $100,000.
Clock starts now.
I know how much I have to do.
I'm not even thinking
of whether or not I can
actually get it done.
All I know is that I have to.
It's the final challenge.
I want to prove that I can, as an artist,
bring something interesting and intricate.
The first step to creating a prosthetic
is coming up with a design.
I'm not going to start
trying to sculpt today.
I want to really get my characters down,
knowing that they're looking
at the whole picture.
So what are you thinking of, Gage?
I have a scene in my head
that I really, really love.
I want to convey something
evil and something innocent,
because these kids are kidnapped by a witch
and they're being fed to be eaten.
They're not supposed to
be happy about that.
I think I'm doing the scene
in "The little mermaid"
where her fin is splitting
apart into human legs.
I'm going to have her
pinky toe with long
spires coming off of it,
and then her legs will
be together as a fin.
- That's great.
- Yeah.
But I'm trying to figure out the witch.
I see this band of renegade warrioresses
called the crimson cloaks,
and basically a world overrun
with werewolves everywhere.
These women band together
and they have to fight the big bad wolf.
So I'm makina werewolf.
I'm doing simple character
stuff on the female,
mostly wardrobe and scars
and maybe making her arm the gun.
The next in creating a prosthetic
is sculpting Clay on the
cast of the model's face.
There is this passage
where the frog describes
how he was turned into a frog by this witch
and he used to be a prince.
So at that point it struck me
that could be my scene right there,
where the witch is actually
transforming the prince into a frog.
And that can be painful and horrific
and that fits my haunted theme.
- Hi, Sam.
- Hello, how are you?
I'm good. Pretty colors.
Thank you. Well, I have the
psychedelic little mermaid.
So things are going to be really splashy.
What I'm hoping for for the background
is a stylized coral reef...
everything brightly colored.
Think of the psychedelic swirls.
What kind of props?
She's reclining on something
that's either a clam,
if you can find a clam shell, or a rock.
I've got a crazy world for you.
I want to set up a battle scene
where my red riding hood is
facing off with the werewolf.
I'd like to see an industrial cityscape,
but the land is icy and rigid.
Lots of blues. I'd like it to be nighttime.
For the backdrop, what I
thought would be cool
would be this candy shop.
I wanted to use a lot of bright
colors for some of the stuff
because it would contrast perfectly
with the fact that it's all faded
and torn down and dilapidated.
So even though they're bright
colors, they can be faded.
I'm picturing the scene in which the prince
has the encounter with this witch.
It is probably outside the castle.
So maybe woodsy foreground,
castle in the background.
Vines would be great.
I want the whole mood to be
as frightening as possible.
All right, that's time.
Time to go, y'all.
I'm freaking out because we have three days
to design, fabricate, and
execute this makeup.
That's not a lot of time.
Not enough at all.
There's a lot of stuff
going through my head.
Then, of course, I'm also thinking,
"this is exactly the type of competition
that Tate could kick my ass in."
I always bite off more than I can chew,
but I will get it done.
I will make a werewolf in three days.
- Hey, guys.
- Uh-oh.
Please come gather around.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, my God.
Here comes McKenzie.
Everybody knows that when we start
to hear those heels clicking,
that means she's going to
throw some kind of twist in
and we brace ourselves.
Here comes McKenzie.
Everybody knows she's going to
throw some kind of twist in
and we brace ourselves.
Yesterday you were given an
extremely difficult challenge.
It really is a lot for
one person to handle,
so I've brought help for you.
Guys, would you please come in?
- Wow!
- Oh, my God.
That's insanity!
It's overwhelming, the fact that,
suddenly, everybody's back again.
What's up, guys?
Oh.
Awesome.
So some of the biggest
names in makeup effects
are not only great artists,
but they also know how to lead a team.
So each of you will choose two
of your former competitors
to help you with your final challenge.
There are people that I like.
There are people that I don't like.
I know right away who I want to pick.
I will draw your names to
determine the selection order.
You'll each pick one person,
and then we'll go back
around and do it again.
Let's get to this.
- First name... Tate.
- Tom.
What's up, man?
Welcome back.
- Gage.
- Marcel, obviously.
I am really excited to help Gage.
I was like, "let's do this."
- Sam.
- Jo.
- Hello!
- Come on down, roomie.
- Conor.
- Frank.
Megan's my buddy, but this
is the final competition.
Regardless of all the
chaos he likes to cause,
Frank's an experienced technician.
Okay, you're second choice. Tate?
Anthony.
I'm happy with my team
because we're all indie artists,
and he have a huge task in front of us
that I don't think a lot of shop people
would even consider possible.
- Gage.
- I want Jessica.
- Yay!
- Sam.
Um, I'm going to go for Megan.
I was concerned about
picking both jo and Megan,
but I really believe that the both of them
are professional enough that they can
take their differences and put them aside.
I wasn't jumping for joy
when Megan got picked
because I knew that I would
have to pick up the slack.
And, Sergio, go ahead to Conor.
How's it going?
I have my concerns about Sergio
just because of his overall
lack of experience.
But I think he also wants
a little redemption.
Now, your former castmates
are here to help you.
How you choose to use them
is up to you, so good luck.
I wanted you because you paint faces a lot.
Yeah.
I know for a fact you can
do the eyes on her cheeks
with the tears coming
down really, really well.
I'm so happy to have
another shot to be back.
At least I can show people I
have so much more potential
that nobody got to see.
So basically it's the
little red riding hoods
versus the big bad wolves.
First thing I want to do
is delegate out the
sculpting responsibilities.
I'm going to get on the head.
I know tom has these great
chests that he makes.
And Anthony I've got on sculpting the legs.
I would love to have her molded
and probably the legs
molded by the end of today.
I picked jo because she did very well
in the body-painting challenge
and I knew that my particular design
was going to take a lot of painting.
Megan kind of bounced
between whatever it was
I was directing her at.
The witch I'm not addressing yet,
but it's just going to be a
face appliance and fingernails.
And we're going to make a scepter.
So want don't we start
with casting your arm?
Sergio, start sculpting a right frog foot.
Okay, how's this looking for you, dude?
Good.
I'm looking around the room.
I see some of the work that Gage is doing
with his project that's orinal.
I haven't seen anything like it before.
Sam's characters, I'm not
sure what I'm seeing.
I don't want her to look
like she's got a beard.
Okay.
Tate's trying to do this
full body werewolf suit,
so I think he's a bit stressed out.
There's supposed to be some sort
of big cocktail party associated with this.
So there's no telling what else is coming.
- Heya.
- Hey, what's happening?
Patrick walks in, and the
thing that I'm hoping
is that I haven't done something
that seems typical to him,
because Patrick invented a lot
of really cool werewolves.
We're doing arm extensions, legs.
We've got a chest.
We're doing spring action jaw.
Right. And you have a tail.
Werewolves usually don't have any.
It's kind of nice to see it.
It's very different. Very impressive.
Really likes the design, the sculpt,
he likes everything he's seeing.
So I'm feeling really good about it.
He's going to have a frog left hand,
but with a human finger,
and his right leg from the
knee down will be frog.
The witch is going to have a
scepter with leds in it and stuff.
- Wow.
- That's your prop.
I haven't done any props up until now.
- This is a new Conor.
- Just add to it. I know!
Patrick is the big creature designer.
If anyone needs to be impressed
when it comes to creatures,
it's him.
My two characters are the witch and gretel.
All the classic witches
have this witchy nose.
And I want her jawbones to be
dislocated and hanging down.
McKenzie oh, so that's
her jawbone up there.
And gretel is sitting like this
and her mouth is going to be
stuffed full with candies.
I really want to present
something that I haven't done.
Something that's fresh and new,
and bring it to the plate this last and.
The jellyfish is going to have a hood
that goes over the top and back.
And coming down from that, instead
of hair she has her tentacles,
which will then cover her chest.
Time wise, how do you feel?
Now that I have help, so much better.
He knows that it's a lot to get done
and it's something that's
really quite different.
It's certainly not your typical
special effects getup.
- Good luck, Sam.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you.
So what did you think of
Tate's to start with?
Every time he's pushing the,
the boundary, especially on the
amount of work as well. My
big concern is that even with
the help of Tom and Anthony, he
may not have enough time.
He cannot afford to have
any set backs.
So what do you think about
what Conor's come up with?
He knows we keep bringing
back to the table,
we need him to go about beyond boundaries
and show us something more creative.
He knows this is the time to do it
and he's going full blown,
and I like to see that.
What do you think about Gage's work?
Gage is happy. There is so much excitement.
He's got the ultimate team
you could ever dream of.
I love seeing that.
But more than that, I'm extremely impressed
how vibrant and imaginative
Gage's vision is.
He could take the whole
thing if he pulls this off.
Sam's seems the least dark of all of them.
I love the color scheme and
her idea to use tentacles
but I'm worried that if
she runs them in silicone
they could be really heavy.
You know, it's great.
This is going to be four
very different tableaus,
and a very different vibe
between the four of them.
That's going to be exciting.
Good luck, guys.
- Thank you so much.
- Thanks, guys.
- Thanks.
- Bye.
When the sculpture is finished,
it's time to make the mold
by putting a cement-like substance
on top of the sculpture.
Once it hardens, you clean out the Clay
and fill it with foam or silicone,
which eventually becomes a prosthetic.
Since the clock was ticking down,
we got to get this mold out.
So we're going to open up one of
the molds and run it in foam.
It's one of those things
where you're either behind or you risk it.
- The back's coming off.
- Okay.
No.
- We got a major split.
- What was that?
I hear that crack and
immediately my heart stops.
I am.
What?
We just lost it.
When we opened one of the leg molds
it broke into four pieces.
Go get some plaster bandages
and a bucket of water.
We'll get it wrapped on our way out.
You can't get mad at yourself.
You know if you pop a mold too early,
it's probably going to crack.
But sometimes it doesn't,
and that's where the reward
of risk entices you.
There's no way we're going to get
the bandages to set in three minutes.
We'll fix it for tomorrow.
It's lucky that we sculpted ambiguous legs.
They will work on either side,
so we're just going to run two of the one.
So just stack it under there
and make sure that we get it right.
You want them all in foam, right?
All right, guys, that's time.
Let's hit the road!
All of the sudden there's
more people here again.
I love having you guys here.
I think it's what we all needed,
you know, me and Sam, Tate and Conor.
While I'm happy to see everyone,
they're kind of in party mode
and I'm in the finals.
So it's hard for me to escape to anywhere
to really evaluate what I'm dealing with.
Actually, it's kind of stressful
having everybody here again.
Honestly, it got loud again.
Having everybody back is
definitely a mixed bag.
There are people who I'm
happy to see again.
And then there are people
who got eliminated
and I was happy to see them go.
The minute that the competition
and winning and money
become your main focus,
you lose sight of your actually makeups.
You've kind of already lost.
I didn't come here just for the hell of it.
I came here to win.
Walking into the lab,
there are lots of little
things we're behind on.
We need to finish sculpting the tentacles
and run them out of silicone,
and the mermaid fin has to be finished.
I'll divide that between jo and Megan.
So we should cut these and...
yeah, we could cut them
and make two sets of intestines with them.
Or not intestines. Tentacles.
I'm really surprised at how
well the team is working.
That definitely looks like...
so what are you going to do about this?
We're going to sculpt this.
We're going to sculpt two lines of that.
Or maybe we can do more lines
and it will help push them out.
- Cool.
- Go for it.
This is the finals.
There's never enough time.
There's always pressure,
there's always too many things to do.
But I do really well under pressure.
Alright, so we've got you in arm land...
- foot, yeah.
- Correct?
- Yeah.
- Paw land.
Today we have to start
assembling the werewolf suit
and putting the hair on it
and I've still gotta make
the gatling gun for little red riding hood.
That's awesome.
That looks good.
I'm gonna use this cotton
latex stuff for the vine,
I want to wrap it around there.
Once we get that, we'll hit it
with some browns and stuff.
Frank's working on the scepter.
He did exactly what I saw in my head.
He even came up with a couple of
cool ideas that I didn't think of,
like putting cellophane in the
globe to give this even glow.
My hat's off to him.
The witch, I'm gonna
start painting the face.
Right away, starting off the day,
I feel really good about where we are.
You're so witchy!
I'm gonna start pre-painting my foam pieces
and they can focus their efforts elsewhere.
Which boob do you want out, Gage?
- Huh?
- Which breast do you want exposed?
It would be, well, she's gonna be,
it's gonna be on her right side.
Marcel and I start sculpting out
the chest and the belly
of the witch, you know,
Jessica's gonna start
working on the gretel,
so I feel really good because we're already
starting off with a really
great spot to be in.
- Go crazy.
- Go crazy?
I'm gonna go get started on that leg.
Uh.
I grab the frog head and I turn it.
It's useless.
The whole back of it's collapsed,
there's this air pocket about an inch thick
between the foam rubber and the skin.
For sake, really?
- Is it on the front, too?
- Yeah.
I'm thinking I can't use this foam.
What do I do? What do I do?
Conor's over there freaking out.
He's in trouble.
It's collapsed everywhere.
The entire back is collapsed.
I've just lost the competition.
Might as well give up now.
Coming up...
So much is going on, we
were so crunched for time,
it could make or break your career.
She's very disturbing.
What's the concept about, though?
Just an intricate and
well-executed concept.
You achieved what it was
that you set out to do.
The winner of "Face Off" is...
Upon first examination,
my frog head looks great
and I turn it and I start to think
this is like some kind of bad dream
because the whole back of
my frog head collapsed.
I've just lost the competition.
I'm really lost at this point.
And I go back to sculpting the
witch and I'm thinking, okay,
"what do I do? What do I do?"
I just have to make this work.
So I assess it and decide to
glue the pieces back down
just hoping this will work out.
Can you flip the switch from there?
Let's go out and start
sticking the metal pieces on.
What that time say? Five minutes?
Five minutes and 27 seconds.
That's time, everybody. We are done.
So today is application day.
It's a race against time
and it's a race against
challenging yourself and
what you're capable of.
I'm gonna try.
I'm gonna try my damnedest to take
this competition with my makeup.
Once the prosthetic is set up,
it can be removed from the mold,
applied to the model's face and painted.
- Hi, how are you?
- How you doin'?
It's good to see you.
They bring our models in and
I sit Deb down and I say,
"look, this is the witch
we're gonna make you."
We glued the chest piece and
the stomach piece down.
We started applying her face.
We're really able to put in
all these little details
and it was just awesome.
This is a balloon that inflates the throat.
So it's gonna be your task to...
Make it do that.
Normally, when it comes to
any kind of articulation
in a prosthetic, ideally,
the makeup artist handles it
himself so the actor can act.
But in this case, I can't stand
behind him blowing air
into a throat bladder.
Although I run the risk
of it looking like crap by exposing a tube,
it'll be worth it if I can
make this throat do what it's supposed to.
Blow into that tube.
Oh, my God.
We're not just doing a static piece,
we're doing a frame from a movie.
These two are gonna be at war.
This is going to be a battle between them.
There's blood, there's cuts,
there's actually going to
be a spear penetration
through the wolf,
bullet holes from the gatling gun.
Oh, wow, man, that came out awesome.
With the time given,
I am very worried about something
falling through the cracks,
because it's a whole lot of
running back and forth and
quickly switching tasks
and I'm feeling a little bit off my game.
All right, guys, that's time.
Time is up.
So much is going on, we were
so crunched for time, like,
there's so many pieces that
still need to come together
and we only now have an hour.
Two minutes.
All I ever said when I got here
was I wanted to build a werewolf,
and today I built a werewolf.
I'm ready to show them what I'm about.
Okay, guys, time is running out.
Let's get the characters placed
in front of their backdrops.
This is it.
Right foot back a bit.
This is make or break time for me.
I feel my reputation is on the line.
A little more, like,
down, yep, there you go.
This is the finals.
There is a lot at stake here
and it's really kind of scary.
Everything's good with your gatling gun?
Yeah?
Just go ahead and pop yourself in.
Looking around the room,
I know that mine is not nearly as engaging
as some of theer pieces.
It's not the over the top thing
that I really hoped to
be putting out there.
We understand that there's
a lot on the line.
The possibility of $100,000.
That's a big deal.
All right, guys, that's it.
- Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
When the party guests
come in, I'm thinking,
the pressure's really on here.
What do you have going here?
"Hansel and gretel."
Guests at the party are
huge in our industry.
It's a little overwhelming,
because it could make or break
your career from this point on.
My version of "Hansel and Gretel",
the only thing I did different was
that the witch gets the kids.
Doesn't have a happy ending.
This final challenge,
I'm able to create my vision,
my characters my way
with the people I want
and I'm super happy with
the way it's turned out.
Gage's witch makeup is just nuts,
there's just metal Springs and
shards of steel everywhere.
He has a great concept.
That's the kind of thing that
the judges are looking for.
He brought it.
In this scenario,
little red riding hood is the aggressor.
The werewolves are the victims.
I'm completely satisfied.
Yes, there are technical issues.
You can't lay 30 pounds
of hair in two days,
it's just not possible.
But it is an accomplishment
that no criticism can make me feel bad for.
I love it.
I'm looking at something
that I'm extremely proud of.
I think Tate's whole character dynamic,
it's so intense and so well conceived.
In "The little mermaid",
there's the witch that she goes
to have herself transformed,
and this is my... my best
stab at psychedelic.
I know that I just made the best thing
that I've made this whole time,
and I'm really satisfied with it.
It's the piece that I'm the most proud of.
Sam chose a real tough one.
But I love that she
challenged herself, you know.
Very imaginative, isn't it?
- It's really nice.
- Thank you.
I wanted to give the illusion
that she's something that
grew out of the ground.
This isn't human tissue.
Looks like tree bark.
And when rob operated that
bladder, just like, wow.
That's awesome.
So I feel good.
I'm proud of what I've accomplished.
Conor's is really well-executed,
but it's not my favorite of his, honestly.
I feel like his creativity
is still somehow typical,
but I can't take away from
how beautifully it's done.
Gage's is just the most disturbing
thing I've seen in years.
I'm looking at all the fine
details and I'm thinking,
boy, he hasn't missed a mark here.
I think what Sam did is really neat.
There's a lot of vibrant colors.
I actually like the story
that Tate's tells.
You get a chance to look around,
and it says a lot to me.
I really like Conor's.
It's a beautiful design in
the amount of time he had.
I can't believe how great he did.
If I had to pick one,
I think I'd probably go
with "hansel and gretel,"
because of the imagination.
- Hi.
- Who'd you pick?
- I was dying to do two of them...
- I know.
It's so overwhelming.
I'm not gonna ask you who,
but do you have your favorites
that are simmering in your head?
- Not yet.
- Not yet. Really?
This party seems to be wrapping up.
Why don't we go talk to these guys?
- Great.
- Yeah, let's.
The party dwindles down,
then McKenzie brings in the judges
and that is very nerve-wracking as well.
- Hi, Gage.
- Hi, guys.
- How are you?
- Good.
You gotta be ready to explain yourself
and explain your decisions.
You have industrial "Hansel and Gretel",
Yes, ma'am.
So, Glenn, why don't we start with you?
I'm sweating bullets.
I'm freaking out.
- Hi, Gage.
- Hi, guys, how are you?
- Good. How are you?
- I'm good, thank you.
So you have industrial "Hansel and Gretel",
Yes, ma'am.
How do you feel you did with this?
I feel really good about it.
It was a clear vision in my head
and I feel I conveyed it pretty well.
It's very, very frightening.
Frightening is not an easy
concept outside of the movie
cut and edited, you see it as a piece.
Who's idea were the eyes
on the outside of the lids?
Mine. I put lenses in her, too,
just in case they asked to open her eyes.
Oh, could you open your eyes?
And they're like she's been blinded.
- It's freaky, too.
- Wow.
Can wewe see the back?
You may want to step back.
Back it up.
She's very disturbing.
What's the concept about thshrapnel?
She was human at one time.
So then more of the witch
started to come out
and she started doing
all kinds of things to
herself with pieces of metal,
and I wanted her to be...
really be fused with that industrial feel.
Little bit of piercing going on as well.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Got ya.
Conceptually, the strongest
thing you've done.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
- Nice work.
- Good job.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
Thank you.
- Hey, Conor.
- Hello.
- How are you doin'?
- Good, thank you.
So you had the haunted frog prince.
How do you feel you did with this?
I know that a big issue
with me was concept,
and so I really pushed this
as far as I felt I could.
How does the haunted part come into this?
I tried to take the transformation
from prince to frog,
tried to make it look painful in
the design and the paint scheme,
and you can see it's not
happening to him easily.
The left side of his face
has a lot of bruise
coloring and so on in it.
Tell us about the bladder.
How does it work?
I took the foam run and I cut out all this
and built latex in a tube
right into the mold,
hid the tube up underneath the lip.
So he operates the bladder himself.
- Yeah.
- By blowing into the tube.
I love that that's integrated,
I love that that's intrinsic to the makeup.
Look at the top of the head.
That's a great paint job, too.
This entire color scheme is very unique,
it intrigues me.
- Nice job.
- Great.
- Well done.
- Well, thank you.
- Conor. Thank you.
- Good luck, man.
- Hi, Sam.
- Hi, guys.
- How are you doin'?
- All right.
So you have the psychedelic little mermaid
of hans Christian andersen.
That's right.
How do you feel you did with this?
I started off by wanting to have something
that was obviously bright,
almost cartoony, bubbly.
I wanted most the texture
to be subtle texture.
The background is extremely powerful.
Very vibrant colors and you
got the characters muted
and so I wish the opposite
would have happened,
'cause if they were in front of
a much more mellow background,
they probably would come out stronger.
Exactly.
What was behind the thinking
leaving the arms, feet and the
middle of the face flesh tones?
It was part of the transition.
Her limbs would go first.
The face is pink.
I wanted to have it one more element
of the skin tone in there somewhere.
Just to not have, "oh, well,
here's some arms and some
feet that are skin tone."
I think I would have liked
to see the makeup continue onto the face.
It would have pulled it together.
Yeah, because the arm now
starts to feel quite alien,
because the arms are
that pink like the face
and you wonder what's a
natural color in there.
I do really like the shapes
that you've created.
- Yeah, I do, too.
- A good concept.
Thank you, Sam, good luck.
- Hey, Tate.
- Hey, what's goin' on, McKenzie?
- How are you?
- Good.
So you have a post-apocalyptic
little red riding hood.
Yes, I love it.
Tell me about the idea
behind the lights in the eyes?
I'm, you know, obviously a big
graphic novel comic book fan,
and from the beginning that
this story popped into my head,
I saw japanese anime and I wanted to
traditionalize it with that kind of style.
I know there's a cheese factor,
but I really wanted to go
into the red glowing eyes,
and also, the red is my
overall theme of this so...
well, it actually makes sense
when you describe this.
I think she's an incredible character.
She really fits well in this world,
and the proportions, the way she's dressed,
she's very successful for me.
You created something very cool there.
You made the right choices, you know.
Thank you very much.
I also like the fact
that you actually put bullet holes in him,
because she is carrying that gatling gun,
so that was kind of a nice
little touch as well.
I'm really happy with what you've done.
You did a really good job.
Thank you very much.
- Thank you, Tate.
- All right, Tate.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- I appreciate it.
Well, judges,
what do you say we go chat
about who the winner is?
- All right.
- Let's do that.
Okay.
So it's time to figure out
who our champion will be.
When I walked out here I went,
- "Oh."
- Yeah.
It's gonna be really hard tonight.
I mean, they all are, like, neck-and-neck.
I think Sam,
the fact that she is even here
tonight says a lot for her.
It's testament to her raw skill.
And I think she realizes that
she did not quite bring
it all to us tonight.
What do you think about
Conor's work tonight?
As usual, Conor has succeeded
at a technical level,
very well thought out,
and I think he did finally
expand his design.
I almost wish that he would have
gone a little crazier
throughout the whole show.
I wish he would have taken
that note a little earlier.
I was blown away with the witch concept,
that non-traditional approach
of coming up with this sort of elemental...
that was very effective.
And the bladder was absolutely amazing.
Yeah, that worked great.
I mean, that was very clever
having it be self-contained.
What I also liked, it felt
like really something
that was in transition.
There was a lot of energy
on the way the skin was pulled on the face.
Bottom line is, he really
went all the way with this.
That brings us to Tate.
What are your thoughts on him?
I think he did a great job.
I mean, he actually did a full suit.
I loved the storyline, I loved
that spin on red riding hood.
I thought it was awesome.
I loved the color choices,
I love the fact that the werewolf
is white instead of brown.
The decision to just make the
red riding hood character
a really strong character
with very little makeup,
it's a great story, it's a great idea.
And then he poured it
all into the werewolf.
I think it worked out really well for him.
All right, what about Gage?
I think Gage knocked it
out of the park tonight.
I think he totally blew me away.
- I didn't expect it, I mean...
- None of us.
He has made this challenge
very difficult for us to judge.
I think that it is, by far, his best work.
Oh, yes, definitely....
and I was excited to see
what he was gonna do.
And he blew me away as well,
I think that it was absolutely amazing
how far he went for this challenge.
- He brought it.
- He did.
You know how much things
were in the pieces that
told the story of what was
going on, was happening.
Like the candy in the mouth.
Like the hands pushing in
the stomach of the witch.
All those things were telling
you a story without, I think,
he didn't have to explain to us.
They all did an amazing job tonight, I...
this is a really,
this is a tough one for us.
Appropriately, the hardest so far.
So, have you reached a decision?
- We have.
- Yes, we have.
All right, let's bring them
back out and crown our winner.
Welcome back to
the "Face Off" reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you will win $100,000,
and a year's worth of makeup
supplies provided by alcone.
Glenn, tell us about the looks overall.
Tate had a really robust concept
and it was just a really
ambitious, huge makeup.
A lot of application and clearly a lot of
passion to bring that concept to life.
Conor, a stellar performance,
technically very, very beautiful makeup.
The application was tight,
the painting was tight,
the sculpture was tight.
Thank you.
Sam, huge concept and some really
interesting color choices.
And Gage, huge leap forward for you.
Just an intricate and
well-executed concept.
I really feel like you achieved
what you set out to do.
Thank you.
Well, we still have four of you
and only one can win.
Glenn.
The first person to be
eliminated tonight is...
Sam.
Sam, you've done so much
progress from the beginning.
Look where you are tonight.
We're very, very proud of you.
Thanks.
Sam, if you would please,
step next to the others.
I'm really proud of how much
I've progressed on the show,
but I wish I could have
represented the ladies
with a stronger piece.
All that included, I'm pretty
proud of being where I am.
All right, leaves us with the three of you.
One of you is our champion.
So, Glenn, who is the winner of "face off?"
The winner of "Face Off" is...
One of you is our champion.
Once Sam was eliminated, it got very real.
Tate couldn't stop swaying,
so now I'm nervous.
This is it.
So, Glenn, who is the winner of "fe off"?
Before we make that announcement,
I just want to say something to you guys.
You all succeeded this evening.
You've really made this hard on us
because we loved all three makeups.
The winner of "Face Off" is...
Conor.
It feels fantastic.
I can't be any happier than I am right now.
Oh, my God.
I am extremely happy for Conor...
for him, for Gage, for
Sam, proud of myself.
I... I feel like I've gained
the respect of the judges.
It's been an amazing experience.
I feel really good about my placement,
and I feel really good about
what's to come from it,
because it's just the beginning
of something greater,
so I don't know what will
happen, but I'm excited for it.
I think it's awesome.
Oh.
This experience has meant a lot of things.
It's meant validation, it's meant exposure,
and also, personally, it's
forced me to look within myself
and develop creativity.
I'm proud of what I've accomplished.
Sync by YYeTs.net
Corrected by jabbberwock
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net