McKenzie: Previously on "Face Off"...
12 talented special effects makeup artists
came to Los Angeles to compete
to join the world's elite.
I wanted to get you an ice
cream cake or something.
I think she's just trying to
win him over with her "charm."
You will work in teams of two
and create an alien species.
Holy crap, we're gonna do aliens.
This is a perfect example
of piss-poor collaboration.
You did a beautiful job. Congratulations.
And the winner is... Conor.
The person going home tonight is...
- Frank.
- I'm out, bitches, I'm out!
Now, only nine remain.
And tonight on "Face Off"...
I see the psycho house up on the hill,
mother bates up in the window.
Your challenge this week
is to create your very own movie villain.
It's a great overall design. Well done.
It's genius.
This design is a vessel of your ineptitude.
To make it to the top,
they'll have to impress
our award-winning panel of judges...
Ve Neill, legendary makeup artist
who's work includes "Edward Scissorhands",
"Beetlejuice", and the "Pirates
of the Caribbean" films;
Glenn Hetrick, cutting-edge makeup
effects artist on "Heroes",
"Legion", and "Buffy the Vampire Slayer";
and Patrick Tatopoulos,
visionary creature designer
for "Independence Day", "Godzilla",
and director of "Underworld:
Rise of the Lycans".
Who will be the next great
name in movie magic
and earn $100,000
and a year's worth of makeup from Alcone?
Get ready for "Face Off".
Kinda un-fun right now.
It's not very fun at all. It sucks.
Frank's elimination, in one fell swoop,
divided the whole group, like,
straight down the middle.
Either you're with Tommy and Jo,
or you're with Conor and Megan,
are, like, "Guys, are you for real?
How old are you?"
Frank went home and not Megan?
It's just insane that she's still here.
Yeah.
It's about to get really nasty.
With Conor and Megan, the way
that that's working out,
lot of people are starting to get upset
and really seeing it for what it is.
We saw with the body painting,
Conor does have weaknesses.
When he's out of his element, what happens?
He dropped all the way to the...
All the way to the bottom
and then freaked out.
He was a nervous wreck that entire time.
I just hope Megan becomes Conor's weakness.
We'll see how it plays out.
Could Megan be used as
a tool against Conor?
Quite possibly, because I think he's gonna
get sucked into the drama
and forget about the art.
We find out that we're going
to universal studios on the back lot.
And it's pretty strange because
we don't know what's cooked up,
and then we see the Bate's motel sign.
We're all, like, pretty excited
because it's only one of the
most iconic film images ever.
As we walked around the corner,
I see the psycho house up on the hill,
mother bates up in the window,
rocking back and forth.
This is definitely my element.
Welcome to the famous bates motel and house
from the Alfred Hitchcock
classic, "Psycho."
The reason we're here is
because your spotlight challenge this week
is for each of you to create
your very own movie villain.
And Norman bates, as we all know,
is one of the original movie villains.
And since then, we've seen
the likes of Freddy Kruger,
pinhead, Jason Voorhees, and many others.
With me today is our guest judge
who, over the past 30 years,
has produced more than 25 films,
including "Friday the
13th", "Deep Star Six",
"Freddy vs. Jason", "The New Kids",
and "The Last House on the Left".
He's the man who brought Jason
to life on the big screen.
Producer and director, Sean Cunningham.
Oh, my God. It's Sean Cunningham,
who did all these awesome
movies I grew up with.
So, Sean, why do you think
Jason resonated so much with audiences?
Jason is, I think, the
quintessential boogieman.
There's something profoundly scary
about a death threat that
can't be negotiated with.
Also, I think, the hockey
mask doesn't hurt at all.
So, then, in your opinion,
what does it take
to make a great movie villain?
I think a great movie villain
has got to be rooted in...
in some kind of unspoken fear,
the kind of thing that, as a kid,
you felt there might be
something beneath the bed,
something that could
attack you at any moment.
It has to have a strong presence,
and it doesn't hurt to have
an unforgettable weapon.
Normal serial killer
villains aren't something
that's right up my alley, so
it's gonna take me some time
to figure out what I'm doing.
I don't know, maybe I can use Megan.
That would be my villain at this point.
These days, it takes an
original marketing campaign
and a great movie poster to get
your audiences into the theater.
So your job is not only to
create the villain and
his or her back story,
but you will also be working
with a production designer
to create a movie poster,
complete with title and tagline.
Oh, that is cool.
On elimination day, you will
reveal your villain on stage,
in front of your custom movie poster image,
just to help set the scene.
The judges will be looking
not only at your technique,
but also your overall concept,
and movie poster design.
All right, when you get back,
you can pick your models
in the order that was selected randomly.
Get out of here and start working.
Good luck.
We get back to the lab,
and there's a certain
level of tension there
because Sean Cunningham
is the judge of this,
he's the guy who created Jason.
So today, we only have 4 hours,
and what we want to do is
just sketch our ideas and start sculpting.
This challenge will force
everyone in the room
to put their money where their mouth is.
There's no hiding from this competition.
You have to sculpt, you have to
mold, you have to be creative.
People's weaknesses are
gonna really be highlighted
on this challenge.
Gage and Marcel hanging out together
is kind of a cool thing because I think
their creative energy feeds off each other.
I hope it doesn't bite 'em in the butt
and make their pieces look too similar,
like their coming from the same project.
We did the same thing. No, we're not.
They're brothers. And they kill people.
We're the only ones that talk anymore.
I know, I think it's because
everyone's just deep in thought,
and really trying to bust out
their ideas, and get them going.
I feel so pressured by this challenge
because I can't sit back and be, like,
"I'm gonna run another
foam latex appliance,"
or, "Oh, I'm gonna sculpt
something really easy."
I've gotta go big or go home.
I'm feeling a little uneasy
going into this challenge
because I just didn't have something there,
and all I could start
thinking about are these
Halloween characters I created years ago,
and after the whole situation with Frank,
I want to choose for safe.
Do you mind if I, uh...
No, Conor, I'm using all of 'em. Yeah.
Shut up, Meg.
Oh, that's very pretty on you.
- It goes with my eyes.
- Yeah.
Megan's laugh is terrifying,
and it makes me violent.
Every time I hear her laugh, I
want to punch someone in the face.
As a girl, I was terrified
of porcelain dolls,
so I'm making a broken doll face
because it was that specific
face that scared me.
This character, she's a nun,
and she comes out of surgery deformed,
and she takes everyone's confessions,
and goes out into the world
and kills them by the way
that they're sinning.
I am creating a deformed burn person,
but I don't want it to look super realistic
and disturbing, I want it to be fun, too.
My goal today is to get
all of my sculpting done
so the following day, I
can mold it and cast it.
To bring my character to life,
I'm sculpting a gigantic head appliance.
He has these makeshift arm crutches
that support the weight of the head.
No, no, he's a genetic anomaly,
and he has a completely
weak and incapable body,
but he controls people with his mind,
so he can make people murder themselves.
Tate's character is all mental power,
and he sculpts this huge
head, and he tells me
he's gonna run it in silicone,
and I was a little concerned for him
because silicone prosthetics
can be very heavy.
I'm sculpting the facial
prosthetics for my character.
He refused to grow up, and
he has this Teddy bear
that's probably been tied to
his face most of his life,
so I am going to use a silicone skin
for his flesh area, and
then the Teddy bear,
the mask part will be fabricated
between fur and maybe some soft polyfoam.
I haven't even looked at it 'cause
you're sculpting on the other
side, and I can't see it.
You should come look.
Come look at it, Tom. Yeah.
I'm sculpting a very intricate piece.
I'm running it out of silicone,
something I've never done,
and I'm having to pull
this thing together and
make her look scary.
Ooh, I love those teeth.
And the cleft lip's cool.
It's 'cause she went through a windshield.
Jo's nun looked like she took Julie Andrews
and put a lighter to her face,
and just put some corn in the mouth.
- What are you gonna make it out of, silicone?
- Silicone.
As soon as I hear her say
she's gonna use silicone...
Okay. I mean, it's your project.
Let's see what you can do.
Everyone all of a sudden
is jumping on the silicone bandwagon
because the judges liked
my silicone prosthetics.
But silicone is not always the way to go,
especially if you're not
experienced with it.
It can be really difficult
to blend and glue down,
and sometimes paint.
I think Jo's in trouble.
I am extremely worried that this
is not gonna turn out well.
With this challenge, we
are gonna have to make
original movie posters, so you
have to design a tag line,
you have to design a title,
you have to design the
aesthetics of the poster,
what happens within it,
and then your makeup
is the forefront of the challenge.
Oh, I'm gonna make it...
We'll be meeting with the
production designer today
to help us with our movie poster.
- How are you doing?
- Tate.
I'm Majken, the production designer.
- Nice to meet you....
- Nice to meet you.
My concept with this character,
he's definitely been locked away
from people for a long time.
I'm calling him "him", h-i-m,
which will be the name of the film as well.
My tag line is "Your mind, dot, dot, dot
his playground."
My whole piece takes place
in the late 70s, early 80s.
- Okay.
- And it's a slasher film.
And it takes place in a
roller-skating rink.
My movie is supposed to
be funny and kitschy.
That's part of the vibe.
I just hope the judges get it.
The move is called...
- "Final Skate."
"The class of '78 is going to pieces."
I want to have my model placed
here on the right hand side.
And I was thinking of
having a lighthouse here.
The title's gonna be "Cautionary Point."
My tag line is "Heed the warning."
My villain is a lighthouse operator,
so I want my killer to be half-burned,
and then the other half,
a water-logged corpse.
We only have four hours today,
so I'm sculpting everything out in Clay,
so I can start molding the skull
in the amount of time allotted.
The name of the movie is "London Twilight,"
and the idea is that it's a
roving gang of psychopaths,
and the villain is a psychotic
surgeon who's deformed.
- Tag line?
- I'm working on it.
I'm gonna keep it clean,
I'm gonna keep it simple.
I'm not gonna go crazy.
Because I'm rehashing this
character I made in '97.
I'm thinking "The Doctor is Out",
and then dot, dot, dot, "of his mind.
- You wanna do that?
- That's the first one right now,
and I know it might come
off a little cheesy,
so I gotta really play with that idea.
I would like a backdrop of a church.
Maybe, like, blood dripping
from either the top
or, like, from the door.
- Name?
- "Confession."
- Tag line?
- "Confession won't always save you."
I'm going outside of the box with my idea,
and I'm excited about running the silicone,
but on the other hand, you know, it's scary
because I don't really know how to do it,
so I'm gonna have to learn
that, too, you know,
in 13 hours of getting this
entire thing together,
if there could be a portrait here
of a blondish family, because
this girl has black hair.
For the title of the movie, I've
decided to go with "Baby Doll",
and the tag line is
"Daddy's little secret
has come back to play."
Sam's one of those people that
could easily be a dark horse.
She hasn't shown a lot of weakness.
She's got skills.
She's a really good illustrator,
she's really good at sculpting.
Sam's coasting through the
middle under the radar,
and I think that's a good place to be.
My idea is a demon of vengeance,
and through voodoo, he's summoned,
so the title for the
concept is "Voodoo Dawn."
It's supposed to take place in the bayou.
I'd like some kind of a swampy backdrop.
Okay, do you have a tag line for me?
"Death is just the beginning."
Okay.
I am trying to get more
reference down of wrinkles,
and so I start scrunching my face
and trying to see my brow furrow.
And I'm, like, "Oh, who has
a really pissed off face?"
- Hey, Conor?
- Yeah.
Could you do this for me?
You want to see crow's feet?
All right, very good. Thanks.
I see all the happy little crow's feet,
and I'm, like, "Oh, perfect. Thank you."
Why did you come to me for that?
Uh, you were the closest.
And I have the most wrinkles.
I picture a kid's bedroom, but dark.
And I would love to use kid's play blocks,
you know, with letters.
I want it to say "Teddy told me to".
And then, my tag line is
"It's all fun and games
until someone dies."
I think Tom does kind of
Halloween quality work.
That's not the kind of
stuff I would expect to
see in a feature film.
My concept is an evil photographer,
and his victims are the people
that he takes photos of.
- Do you have a name?
- "Chester's Photography".
"A picture says a thousand
words, his victims say none."
Okay.
I don't know that I would
want to go see "Chester's Photography"
because when she explained the concept,
it sounded a little thrown together.
As I'm sculpting, I'm just not feeling it.
Anthony, it seems like he's just
really taking a safe route.
I think this is the time to take chances
and make something mind blowing.
I don't feel good about
creating this character anymore
because as an artist, I'm
not trying anything new.
What's your story? Can I ask?
You wanna know what it is?
It's a big, big, epic story
of none of your business.
What am I gonna do now?
I'm in trouble.
I don't have time to start all over again.
- Thank you, Marcel.
- Marcel: You're welcome.
Oh, my God, what are we gonna do?
We only have eight hours.
It's the second day of
our spotlight challenge,
and there's still a lot to do.
Just being able to bring it in
the amount of time allotted
gets really hard because
we're on such a schedule.
And then Glenn walks in with McKenzie.
Hello, Megan.
Oh, hey.
- Scared you, huh?
- Yes. Hi.
Well, that's appropriate for the category.
Good God. I'm gonna have a heart attack.
What are your plans for this?
This is gonna be a foam piece,
and then the teeth are gonna
be made out of acrylic.
When he articulates,
what's going to happen?
Are the teeth going to move with the foam?
I wasn't planning on him articulating.
I don't think Megan's works
because it doesn't move.
I get her guy's about photos,
but it's more a mask than a prosthetic.
Are we gonna see under the mask...
- No.
- ...During the reveal?
This mask is fused to his face.
It doesn't come off.
He's also gonna have a giant yo-yo.
He's beaten people with it
- or strangled them, or whatever.
- Okay.
Every horror villain needs his machete,
so I picked a yo-yo
because it's a kids' toy,
and it's kind of creepy.
I really love early 70s,
early 80s slasher flicks.
I remember watching those,
and it just scared me,
the idea of a deformed
person chopping up people.
Foam or silicone?
- I'm gonna do silicone.
- Cool.
It's gonna be a one-piece face appliance.
I'm gonna try and do silicone on it.
I'm planning on doing a silicone mold.
I'm doing everything in silicone.
- You're gonna run in silicone?
- Seems to be working for me.
It's got three-piece silicone.
So I'm gonna go more flesh,
so I'm doing it in silicone.
I really want more articulation.
All right, well, we'll leave you to it.
- Thank you.
- See you guys.
What do you think of some of the work?
A little worried about
some of the color choices.
- Really?
- On the whole, yeah. Marcel, Anthony.
When you're working with
realistic-looking skin,
it's more difficult.
In the end, it'll sell better
as a realistic makeup
if you can pull it off,
but there's less latitude there.
And it's more monstery, if you will,
when you go with heavier colors.
How do you feel about everybody
seems to be doing silicone?
Well, I think that they're
learning as they go
that it reads better.
It's not always the right choice.
This is gonna be a true test
of their painting skills.
- That's gonna be interesting.
- It is.
- Bye, guys.
- Bye.
See you tomorrow. Good luck.
Messing up the Teddy hair?
Yeah, I'm gonna trim it all down,
- and make it look like it's been used.
- Awesome, man.
Is there a text book way
to make a Teddy bear?
Maybe. Do I know that? No.
To me, it's not how you
get to grandma's house.
It's just the fact that you get there.
Today we need to get everything into molds,
and start casting the prosthetics.
To make a mold, you have to cover
your sculpt in wet cement.
When your mold has set, you're
gonna take your silicone
and pour that into your mold.
Oh, God. Please be good please be good.
Running the silicone is
pretty nerve-wracking.
I don't know if it's gonna
set completely or not,
so I'm nervous to see what
it's gonna come out like.
Did you vaseline your stone?
- Uh-oh.
- Oh, this scares me.
Me and Gage forget to release our molds.
Releasing the mold is where
you put in something
that puts up a barrier between the plaster
and whatever you're putting in there
so it doesn't stick to the
plaster or seal itself shut.
Adding mold release is easy enough.
Let's see, what have we got here?
You can use cooking spray,
anything oil-based.
Soap, shaving cream, baby powder works.
It allows you to easily
peel your appliance away.
If not, it forms a bond.
That can be bad because
silicone is really tough.
You guys just pop these things open?
Or did he have to use that thing?
I literally had to put then
on my feet and pull it.
If it flies, it's gonna
break my fingers off.
One, two...
Beautiful piece.
God, you scared me.
It came out great, and it's beautiful.
That's something that my mother
would be proud of me in the end.
I'm proud of it, definitely.
Ooh, it's exactly how I wanted it, too.
♪ I'm excited ♪
Anthony: That's a good release there, Jo.
That came right out.
Yeah.
Son of a bitch.
Hey, Conor, could you
come here for a second?
- I forgot to release it.
- Oh.
What?
- It's coming.
- Okay.
Okay, got mine out. Thank you, buddy.
We got it out, I was, like, "Whew."
- Conor.
- Conor: Yo.
Can you help me with mine?
Oh, for ***.
Okay, if mine is this hard to
open, Gage's gonna be bad, too.
Yeah, just hold it right there.
No.
Hold it steady.
Everyone's coming over
and trying to help me.
Oh, dude, that's not...
Gage's will not open for anything.
It's, like, sealed shut.
You're gonna have to chip it out. Sorry.
I'm looking at my mold,
and I'm totally worried
about my prosthetic.
I'm screwed.
I basically have lost everything.
Coming up...
The eyes don't fit.
This is gonna be a heck of a horror film.
I really like this makeup.
This design is a vessel of your ineptitude.
Tonight, one of you will be eliminated.
AAA
no.
I am looking at my mold,
and I am freaking out.
You're gonna have to chip it out.
Now I'm really worried for him.
If you guys need any help,
I don't want to shove my hands in there.
No, no, you're good.
Gage forgot to release his mold.
It's stuck in there.
You're either gonna ruin your
mold or your prosthetic,
and you probably won't get a
chance to get a second go at it.
The face lifecast, we have copies of those.
The sculpt, on the other
hand, was a one-time deal.
So he needs to be able to preserve
the sculpt part at all costs,
especially because there's
already silicone inside of it.
It just comes down to having
to break the lifecast.
It's going to cost him a lot of
time, chipping this lifecast out.
Let me see? How is it?
- Here.
- Oh, here we go.
It tore. Meg, you're tearing it.
Really?
She starts ripping it off,
and then she leaves.
Yeah. Just... yeah.
Awesome. Thank you.
That's just another kink
in the whole process.
Already being under a time crunch,
already having to pull it out and
paint it and everything else.
No, I think it's coming.
Now I have to sit here
and pull everything out
piece by piece, literally.
Here we go.
It's almost like peeling a
stubborn hard-boiled egg.
It's, like, you get a piece off,
and there's little pieces that cracked,
and you have to go through individually
and get all those little, tiny pieces off,
so he spent a good time doing that.
I'm, like, peeling it out piece by piece.
And it sucks.
Today's the day of the application,
and we have five hours to
complete this project.
- How you doin'?
- What's going on?
Your face definitely helped a lot.
Does that feel about
right on your chin area?
- Yeah.
- Just go ahead and...
Take your hand and just
hold it there for me. Cool.
Megan ripped my prosthetic, but
because it's a nice, clean tear
it's gonna fit right back together.
And then whatever crease is there,
I'm just gonna use
silicone to go over that.
So I think it's gonna work out really well.
I'm placing the appliance on her face,
and I'm realizing, like, my
edges aren't that great.
An edge is literally where the
prosthetic meets the skin.
If that doesn't blend down, you can see it.
It automatically looks fake.
Really great.
My edges are not staying down.
They are lifting up again
and again and again,
and I am having to keep adding more glue.
The chest piece, instead of backing it up
with a lighter weight foam,
I just filled the whole
thing with silicone,
and it ended up kind of weighing a ton.
You wear safety pins?
I have not connected my head
piece to my chest piece.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I have not connected the horns,
and I've still got plenty
of painting to do.
My work's cut out for me.
Think "Clockwork Orange".
Think sort of like Dr. Jekyll, Mr. Hyde.
I'm starting to get scared,
looking around the room
during application day,
'cause I'm starting to see these characters
actually flush out and come together.
I basically just recreated
stuff that's been done
a million times over.
I think this is it, I'm gonna lose,
and I have no one to blame but myself.
We're packing up our kits
to go over to the stage
for last looks, and we
still have so much to do.
We've got an hour to
finish up our characters,
and I could be in trouble.
The success or failure completely hinges on
the application end of it.
I get so jittery.
My edges are starting to look bad.
I have to constantly
keep adding more stuff.
It's a complete bummer.
The eyes don't fit.
I am worried.
I sculpted out her eyelids because
my character doesn't blink.
My problem is the eyelids have stretched
well beyond the size of
my eyes that I created,
and there's no more time
to make bigger eyes.
Hey, guys, there's only 15 minutes left.
I'm freaking out inside
so much that I'm, like...
"Okay, gotta get it together.
Get it together."
But it's so intense and so stressful,
and I really tried on this.
One minute. Okay, stand up, jump up.
Welcome to the "Face Off" reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you will be eliminated.
Say hello to your judges.
Owner of optic nerve makeup effects studio,
- Glenn Hetrick.
- Hello.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
Welcome back, everybody.
Creature designer and
director Patrick Tatopoulos.
Hi, guys.
And our guest judge this week,
the man who ought Jason Voorhees to life,
director a producer Sean Cunningham.
- Hey, guys.
- All: Hi, Sean.
This week, your spotlight
challenge was to create an
original movie villain,
along with a movie poster,
title, and tag line.
So, let's see what you've come up with.
When my poster comes up, my guy comes out
walking on these arm crutches,
and it's the creepiest
thing I've ever seen.
With the risk that I took, I
couldn't have been happier.
Cunningham has, like, a
huge smile from the get go.
I'm looking at him,
and I look at all the
other guys, I'm, like...
I knew I'd kind of just
thrown this one away,
and I just felt sick.
I'm happy with the end result.
I really incorporated all the elements
into my character that I wanted to.
When Kimie looks around
with those creepy eyes,
I can see people who are watching this
get physically uncomfortable around her.
I feel like mine was the creepiest.
He does his little wave.
I mean, it was so me. I love this villain.
I feel like it's exactly
what I had in my mind.
It was cool seeing up
there, all put together.
As soon as I saw my poster come up,
I was just, like, "Oh, my God. Oh, my God."
I don't like to look at
the judges reactions
because not only is it
Ve, Glenn, and Patrick,
it's also Sean Cunningham.
It's hard to hear people you
admire so much tear you down.
It really, really cuts deep.
As my character comes up, I realize...
What if the judges don't get it?
All right, judges, why don't
you take a closer look?
Indeed.
Can you see right here?
Can you see my hand?
Without turning your... No.
Is this built into the lip prosthetic?
Don't go past it, don't go past it,
don't go past it, don't go past it.
You, you, you.
There was no way in hell
mine was gonna be best.
I wasn't shooting for best.
I was shooting for middle ground.
Yeah, yeah.
Let me see your mask on.
- Did she make the mask, too?
- Glenn: Indeed.
Are you able to move your mouth,
open your mouth and close?
Can you turn your head this way?
I'm feeling nervous because
I didn't know really where I stood.
Oh, my God.
Everyone's was so different.
Can you turn your head, please?
Okay.
Well, the judges have
scored your creations.
Conor...
Sam...
Jo...
- You are safe this week.
- Thank you, God.
If you would please head
back to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Come on, beautiful.
Oh, my God. I'm so happy I'm back here.
The rest of you were the best
and the worst of this week.
The judges would like to speak
with each of you to learn
more about your work.
First up, Gage.
Gage, can you tell us a little
bit about your character.
Yeah, absolutely.
He used to be a lighthouse worker
and maybe fell asleep behind
the light, and it burns him.
So, after that, other people there
are starting to get killed off one by one.
I chose silicone for the translucency,
especially on the burn, so...
I like it. The paint job I like.
I think it's kind of like
an old '50s horror movie,
and that's kind of really
cool that you went for that.
I think you did a great job.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Ve.
Some of those characters we're
seeing tonight inspire more pity.
They look like twisted being
that will not frighten me,
but this one felt very powerful.
- That was a big deal for me.
- Thank you.
I thought the lighthouse,
and the remote place,
and this great weapon, and
I think it's really scary.
This is gonna be a heck of a horror film.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
All right, Gage, thank you.
All right, Anthony.
What's this guy's deal?
Why should I be so afraid of him?
Dr. Edward psychobabble
is the leader of the gang London twilight,
and the idea is that
they were a roving gang
similar to "A Clockwork Orange",
where they terrorized London.
And I'm more into, like, mental horrors
than a brute standing in a
doorway, hacking people up.
Not... not to say anything
about "Friday the 13th."
What it seemed as if you were doing
was a movie that I've just seen to death,
and I was thinking why
today am I gonna go out and see this movie?
I'm not real happy with this
makeup, to tell you the truth.
- Okay.
- The paint job's crappy, his mouth is off.
I think you kinda, like,
flunked out on this one.
You've squandered an opportunity here
to come up with something truly original.
This design, unfortunately,
has become a vessel of your ineptitude.
I'm very disappointed.
Anthony, thank you.
I felt like crying right there
'cause I knew it wasn't who I was.
I could do so much more.
Megan.
It's a very simple makeup.
You had one feature.
We concentrate on the teeth,
and I wish you'd gave them more depth
because it's your central piece.
I agree with Patrick that the
smile didn't work for me at all.
He can't articulate, he
can't do any of the things
that you would need him to do dramatically.
I'm not sure you've quite
thought through how it
would actually be used.
We never design anything
to be a single shot,
even if it's supposed to be a single shot.
Unfortunately, I think
you've missed the mark here.
All right, Megan, thank you very much.
All right, Tate.
I think design-wise, this
is very impressive to me.
The proportion of the eyes has
something very mystical
and disturbing about it.
It feels like a mummified creature.
There is something very
much alive about this face
and that, to me, is quite amazing.
Thank you very much.
I think I would have liked
to have seen just possibly a little bit
more highlighting going on on the
actual paint job on the head,
and I think you lose a lot of the detail.
Other than that, all in all, the
totality of it is wonderful.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
- I really appreciate that.
- Congratulations.
I wish you would have made the eyes blend.
The static eyes are one of the
things that throw me off.
I absolutely find it, overall,
visually riveting. I love this makeup.
Thank you very much.
That means a lot. Thank you.
All right, Tate. Thank you.
Marcel.
How successful do you feel
you've been with this makeup?
Painting silicone is tricky.
I wanted to keep it translucent.
I feel like, for the time
I had, I'm happy with it.
I'm not.
I'm just not getting the character
and how the character lives
in that environment.
I love late '70s, early '80s slasher films.
His graduation class decides
to break into the roller rink.
She busts in, or he busts in, with an ax,
and dispatches them in
horrible, horrible ways.
I see a crazy person on
roller-skates chopping people up.
You know, I didn't have a
sense of being scared.
I could be grossed out.
You know, your coloring
is a little bit off.
I think, possibly, you might have been
better off doing this out of foam.
I mean, it doesn't really
match up around her mouth.
So I don't think you really
completed the makeup job.
It doesn't look like a makeup
to me, it just looks like
a rubber mask you've stuck
on and tried to paint.
I wish you fill out more, the actual...
the weapon, for example.
We're on the skating rink, you
could have used something
more related to the skating world.
It doesn't feel iconic.
Marcel, thank you very much.
All right, Tom.
Well, I gotta tell you,
when you walked out,
or I should say, when he
walked out, I thought,
this guy has got some deep rooted
problems with a Teddy bear.
I took a note from Sean when we
met him at the psycho house,
he said one of the things
that scares people the most
is stuff they were afraid
of in their childhood.
You just did a really good job.
I also like the way you took
the time to finish the hands.
Thank you.
I love the button eye.
It's so creepy. I'm a fan.
I'll go see this movie. Well done.
It's genius, and I don't
need to tell much more.
I think you've created a character there,
and it's very, very strong.
The way you blended the fur
into your prosthetic is flawless.
Other than that, I think all I have to say
is that if you win, I hope
that you spend some of
the money on therapy.
All right, Tom. Thank you very much.
You can step back.
- Good job, man.
- Nice work.
Glenn, tell us about the top looks.
This week's top looks came from Tate.
Very strong. Great profiles.
Also from Gage. A really cool,
cohesive concept, your character.
And from Tom, the really exciting
and unique take on the villain.
This week's winner is...
Tom.
Tom, congratulations.
You have earned the right
to consult with the judges
on who you feel should be eliminated.
The rest of you can head
back to the makeup room
until the judges have made their decision.
Thank you, guys.
Good work.
Who do you think should go home this week?
My honest opinion is I think
Megan should go home.
I believe that she's the weakest
artist left your group.
She has slipped through
the radar several times.
I just feel like today sold it.
It was not functional, like you guys
all pointed out, as far as the mouth.
Tom, thank you.
- You can head back to the makeup room.
- Alright.
All right, judges.
Let's start with Megan.
What are your thoughts?
That makeup, we've seen
done well a lot of times.
- Right.
- And this wasn't one of them.
To stick that big old plastic mouth
in there was not really adequate.
She really hasn't performed
and done anything really exceptional.
You're right. It's an awful decision.
- I wish she would have gone another way.
- Bad, bad.
- And the teeth were even badly done.
- Bad.
What did you all think
about what Tom had to say?
I'm feeling that most of that
is animosity generated by
last week's situation.
I think we have to take
that into consideration.
What do you think about Marcel?
Marcel seems to be always quite satisfied
- with what comes out.
- Exactly.
And I'd like him to be a
little bit more self critical.
It makes me feel like someone that may not
feel he needs to progress.
I really just didn't get
the whole thing today.
I mean, I think that he
threw the burn makeup in
as something to do, as opposed
to creating an iconic character
that would carry through franchise films.
I've seen far too many people like that.
They actually think what
they are doing is good.
It makes it impossible for
them to learn and to grow.
I like that Marcel took his chances,
I just didn't much like the concept.
And what are your thoughts about Anthony?
Anthony has proven to be
a pretty decent artist,
but today he failed.
It was just very plain and very boring.
He had that poster with the fog,
but there wasn't anything
scary or anything...
Special about it at all, I didn't think.
We don't want someone in our industry
who's gonna constantly
be ducking and covering
every time there's a big
challenge that comes our way.
It's not a very good strategy, I agree.
Judges, have you reached a decision?
We have.
So who is going home tonight?
Glenn, who is going home tonight?
Marcel...
Really unhappy with the
quality of the sculpture
and the paint job and the overall concept.
Megan, the decision to
make a inarticulated mouth
was a poor one.
And Anthony, you
obviously played it safe.
There's no room in our industry
for people shooting for mediocrity.
The person going home tonight is...
Marcel.
Glad I got this opportunity,
and I want to thank you guys.
Please head back to the makeup
room, and pack up your kit.
- I'm out, guys.
- Jo: No, you're not.
- No, you're not.
- Yeah, I am.
Are you kidding?
- I don't know.
- Jo: What?
- McCloud.
- Nice meeting you, dude.
- Come here, Jo.
- No.
I tried my best.
I tried my hardest on each challenge.
I met great people.
You don't deserve to leave, Marcel.
We will see you after this.
I started out when I was a little kid,
no formal training, and
I've got pretty far,
and this is what I'm always gonna do.
Sync by YYeTs.net
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net