Previously on "Face Off"...
12 talented special effects makeup artists
came to Los Angeles to compete
to join the world's elite.
Your challenge is to create
your very own movie villain.
Anthony is just really
taking the safe route.
-Did you Vaseline your stone?
- Uh-oh.
I'm screwed. I basically lost everything.
This week's winner is... Tom.
Who is going home tonight?
Marcel.
Now only eight remain.
And tonight, on "Face Off"...
You're gonna need to turn
the bride into the groom,
and the groom into the bride.
This can't be happening.
And we have set the stage,
and invited their friends
and family to witness this all.
What the heck were you thinking?
I was very impressed with this.
To make it to the top,
they'll have to impress
our award-winning panel of judges...
Ve Neill, legendary makeup artist,
whose work includes "Edward Scissorhands",
"Beetlejuice", and the "Pirates
of the Caribbean" films;
Glenn Hetrick, cutting-edge makeup
effects artist on "Heroes",
"Legion", and "Buffy The Vampire Slayer";
and Patrick Tatopoulus,
visionary creature designer
for "Independence Day", "Godzilla",
and director of "Underworld:
Rise of the Lycans".
Who will be the next great
name in movie magic
and earn $100,000 dollars
and a year's worth of makeup from Alcone?
Get ready for "Face Off".
Face Off 1x05 - Switched And Hitched
Original air date February 23, 2011
Sync by YYeTs.net, corrected by addic7ed.com
www.addic7ed.com
Last night's elimination bummed me out bad.
Marcel was, like...
Well, yeah, you guys were,
like, best friends.
Yeah.
I think the competition's
gonna change a lot now
now that Marcel's gone.
We're not here to, like, find boyfriends.
This isn't Melrose Place.
He's completely lost his
focus as to why he's here.
This freaking guy wants to see
me gone in the worst way.
And it sucks, 'cause, you know,
he came in here all Zen.
He let that girl get in his head, man.
That's why superheroes
don't have girlfriends.
We're all in a strict competition.
I don't want to lose to the
guy who's trying to get laid.
- Good morning, guys.
- Hi.
This is a Foundation Challenge.
The winner of the Foundation Challenge
gains some sort of perk or advantage
going in to the Spotlight Challenge.
This challenge is based on
a very specialized skill...
hand-laying facial hair.
Now, I know how to do beards.
I know how to do hair work.
I've been doing it for years.
This is my second chance, I'm reborn.
I'm the phoenix rising.
Here with me, we have our guest
judge for this challenge.
He's one of the best hair-laying
specialists in the business.
He won an Oscar for the
movie "Beetlejuice",
was the department head on "Lost",
and has worked on dozens
of Hollywood blockbusters.
Makeup artist Steve Laporte.
- Good morning.
- Thanks, Steve, for being here.
So what are you going to
be looking for today?
I'm looking for proper blending of hair,
application, the right
amount of glue being used.
Something that can be good on camera.
I hate hair. I've got big caveman hands.
You know, my nickname is Yeti Finger,
so having a judge like Steve Laporte?
Yeah, it's a little bit more
scrutiny than I want to deal with.
So let's bring out your models.
Our models come out,
and they're all in almost
time period outfits.
I see, like, a biker guy, a pirate,
a renaissance guy, a Rastafarian.
Not only do you have to apply
a precise facial hair design,
but you're going to have to
match a certain era or style.
You'll have two hours to design
and apply your facial hair.
Before we get started, you
will need to pick a model.
First up...
Sam.
- Whee.
- I went towards the western
simply because I had this image in my head
of that big ol' bushy mustache.
- Tom.
- I'm super excited.
I love hair work, I feel I'm
really good at hair work.
I'm ready to win this one.
All right, Megan took the pirate.
Conor. Nice.
Jo.
Anthony.
Gage.
And Gage took the biker.
I'm not that versed with ethnic hair,
and it's hard for me.
All right, artists, your time starts now.
Go ahead and post up. I'll be right back.
There's just a variety of
different hairs at this point.
We have human hair, yak
hair, synthetic hair.
I need to go with something
coarse 'cause the Spaniards
have coarser hair,
and I'm gonna have to
turn this thing into a
curly, crazy mustache.
I have a little secret
trick that I like to use.
You take the spirit gum
and put it on cardboard,
it actually evaporates
a lot of the alcohol,
and it makes it more gummy and sticky.
I'm feeling it.
I'm feeling like I actually got this.
Did somebody say we had a hackle?
There is a hackle.
What a hackle is, it's very dangerous.
It's when you have two colors of hair,
you just throw them in, and it
kind of blends them together,
pulls the two colors together.
I look at his cheesy future man costume,
and I was, like, "Okay,
I'm gonna turn this guy
into a 1950s future man
that's an evil villain."
Hand-laying facial hair
is pretty hard, actually.
You have to place it properly,
you have to make sure that you block it out
properly in the first place.
If not, you're gonna end up
with hair all over the place.
I need to impress the judges.
But, jeez, my pirate looked
like, you know, a samurai
more than a pirate.
I'm not 100% settled on how
I'm gonna tailor this,
but I'm thinking kind of maybe
a cleaner Lars Ulrich,
or something like that.
All right, everybody.
Here's your 30 minute warning.
I grabbed about three different
types of hair colors,
and I'm blending it together.
Each batch that I pull
up, I'm trying to get
a little bit of each one into it.
At the last minute, I decided,
long beard, I need a long hair.
And I just hurry up, threw it on his head,
put his hat on. Done.
Pirate. Yar.
Everybody, your time is up.
We all finish our beards.
I start looking around the room.
Gage has this huge biker thing going on.
Megan's, I don't know, it was a total mess.
The more I look at everybody,
I see fake beards.
And I look at mine, and I'm,
like, that's totally real.
Anthony, how are you doing?
- Hi, how are you doing?
- Nice to meet you.
So, what do you think, Steve?
Oh, well, turn this way
a little bit for me.
I'd like to have seen a little more length,
considering the guy who's
got his hair this long
probably would've really let
himself go in the beard area, too.
I don't think that he was impressed.
He was expecting this full,
nappy Rastafarian beard.
The mustache is a little big and thick,
but certainly kept within
the realms of a style.
So it's great. Really nice.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
You could've probably used
half this amount of hair,
and gotten the same look,
and used the shaping
and the body of the beard to fill it out.
Fill it out? Yeah.
My first thought is that
I would have liked to have seen a lot more.
- Sure.
- You could've given him some beard stubble.
You could have added a lot more character.
Because he has a young face,
you didn't go over the top.
He has shorter hair, so you kept
it nice and neat and tight.
Very nice. Good job.
All right.
It's great that you blended
the hair like that,
- 'cause I like to see that.
- Thank you.
Matches the costume.
Yes, that was my inspiration.
I also notice you put hair in the eyebrows.
- Yes.
- Which is a nice touch,
'cause a lot of people
don't think about that.
I was forced to mess with
hair, and by the end of it,
I was, like, "Wow, this actually
looks really good.
I would put this on camera."
Let's take a look at the pirate, Steve.
What do you think?
Turn for me a little bit.
Is this a synthetic you
were using, or is it...
- I believe it's a synthetic.
- Synthetic?
I'd like to see a little
more broken up in here.
Steve whips out his comb, I'm, like,
"Oh, sir, no, no, no.
Put that down. Please, don't."
Last thing you want in a middle of a take
is a big hunk of hair falling and sticking.
Steve does a little tug on her beard,
and a whole bunch just starts coming out.
She didn't secure it properly.
Look up for me here.
It's very nice. Good job.
I don't see a lot of glue.
It would certainly be admissible I think.
- Thank you.
- I'm feeling pretty confident, you know.
My beard looks pretty realistic.
If I saw this guy on the street,
I wouldn't second guess it.
Steve, what did you think
of the work today?
I saw some really good work,
and I saw some work that wasn't so good.
So, then who were some
of your favorites today?
Um, Tom, with your Amish.
You had dressing to the beard,
there's curl that had shape to it.
- It looked good.
- Thank you.
Tate, you did the futuristic guy.
I think you did a great job.
You did good hair blending,
you accentuated his eyebrows,
which is a big part of that look.
Thank you very much.
So, who is the winner of the challenge?
The winner is...
- Tate.
- Thank you.
I appreciate it. Thank you.
Good job.
- Thank you.
- I never would have guessed it.
I'm blown away, completely.
Thank you, Steve, so much for being here.
- My pleasure.
- Great having you here today.
Good luck, everybody.
Thank you very much.
Let's talk about this
week's Spotlight Challenge.
You're going to be working with
models that you have never
worked with before.
But in order for me to
introduce you to them,
we need to head outside.
Why don't you come with me?
McKenzie tells us "Your models
are here, come outside."
And we're all looking at each other,
like, what the hell is going on?
McKenzie tells us our models
are here, come outside.
So we go outside, and a limo pulls up.
You know, we're all thinking
all these crazy things.
Like what horror star,
director's gonna jump out.
And then these couples start filing out.
Your Spotlight Challenge this week
is to make up these real
life engaged couples for their wedding day.
But there is a twist to this challenge.
You're gonna need to turn
the bride into the groom,
and the groom into the bride.
This is a gender swap challenge,
and your makeups will be revealed
in front of their friends and family.
You'll be working in pairs of two,
but you will get to pick your teams.
So why don't you go ahead and
decide who you want to work with.
Sam, girl.
This is the first time we get to pick
our own partners, which is cool.
Me and Jo went right for each other.
We're gonna win this.
I have a lot of respect for
her skills in beauty makeup.
I know immediately that, if anyone
was gonna pull this off, it was Megan.
I know that she's skilled
as a beauty makeup artist.
So, Tate, as the winner of
the Foundation Challenge,
you will get to choose which
couple you would like
your team to work with.
Everyone else's couples will
be chosen randomly for them.
Why don't you discuss with
Anthony which couple you'd like to choose?
Turning a woman into a man is not so hard
because you're adding features,
cheek bones, chins, things like that.
When you're turning a man into a woman,
you're looking for ways
to take things away.
So when I see this pretty Asian man,
I'm, like, done, I want him.
My and Anthony both agree,
number three is for us.
Number three, that is Peter and Kathleen.
The rest of you have each
been randomly assigned
to one of the remaining couples.
Why don't you all take a moment
to get to know your couples,
because your time starts now.
Hey, how's it going? I'm Gage.
- Hi.
- I'm Conor.
Willie has a very masculine chin,
and kind of a heavy brow.
Our first question is would
you shave your hands?
Sure.
Tom and I got quite the couple.
I'm really worried about
turning Dean into a female.
If we put prosthetics on him,
he's gonna look like some sort
of plastic surgery victim.
Would you be willing to
shave your eyebrows?
Not shave, but just a little pluck.
- Maybe we pull a couple out.
- Yeah, I do anyways.
Oh, okay.
We just want to get to know
your guys' shapes and sizes.
Annie's face was very round.
And to transform a very
round, very feminine face,
into a masculine face meant
that we had to add a lot.
It's time to say your good-byes
for now and go get started.
The first step to creating a prosthetic
is coming up with the design.
Okay, what kind of angle
can we take on this?
I mean, is everybody really
gonna just do a cross dresser?
Do you want to go with a period thing?
What if we did an Elvis wedding?
What if we did a Vegas...
we turned her into Elvis...
- Silly.
- Yeah.
- I like that.
- Sideburns.
How do we make his nose smaller?
We have to give her platform
shoes or something.
We came up with this '70s
theme that's a little goofy.
We might get castrated
for it, I don't know.
We needed something with a
ruffled shirt to hide our
actual bride's breasts.
The challenge here will be how simple
can you make it look, but
as realistic as possible?
I think that's gonna be
a huge challenge here.
We're going to attempt a
double old age makeup,
which some people will say is insane.
Which it is, within the
time span that we're given.
- So what's your theme?
- Theme?
Why, do you have a theme?
We're doing a Vegas wedding.
I figured it'd be an easy enough way
to make something out of nothing.
Genius. I just did a belly,
too, on another film.
All right, I'll whip a
belly right on to this.
About three weeks ago,
I actually did a short film
where I had to make a pregnant
belly out of silicone,
so I'm sculpting everything,
molding everything.
I was already in that same vein
of how to make one real quick.
We're making a belly.
Tate's doing, like, an Elvis Vegas wedding.
I want to stick with formal.
Let's keep it classy.
Okay.
You want to work with people's features.
When it comes to the man,
what do you want to subtract from his face?
You don't always have to use prosthetics.
This is where shading and
highlights come into play,
when you're using beauty
makeup and foundations.
My only concern with him
is the size of his chin.
He's got a very prominent chin.
The next step to creating a prosthetic
is sculpting clay
on a cast of the model's face.
You can't place tape, they made it
really clear, on the last challenge.
Yeah.
Old age makeups are one of
the hardest things to do.
We knew that if we were gonna pull
it off, we needed to do a lot.
We're sort of relying on the fact that
androgyny sets in in old age.
It's gonna be a full face, a bald cap,
a back of the neck appliance,
and then two hand appliances for her.
And the same for him, so Sam and
I got some pretty big balls.
I'm sculpting boobs.
I'm gonna sculpt them out of silicone,
but I'm gonna encapsulate
it so I can smooth it down into the chest,
because we are going with '70s feel,
so she's gonna have a '70s
hippie kind of dress,
so I want it to blend in really nice.
Giving 'em a nice rack.
I don't think either Gage
or Sam have actually
done an old age makeup before,
and now they want to pull off two
in two days. Are you guys nuts?
We don't know if they're
gonna like it or not.
We could be eliminated for this decision.
We went small right off the bat,
which was contrary to what everybody
else in the competition did.
Tate and Anthony decided to do
this full facial appliance.
I'm looking at Gage and Sam,
and they've decided to
do two old age makeups,
and then there's Tom and
Jo, sculpting boobs.
Boobs, do you need 'em?
- Yeah.
Today, my goal is to get
this sculpture pushed out.
I'm hoping that tomorrow
I can get a mold done,
and then run the silicone the same day.
Get this done.
Gage and I are creating two prosthetics,
one for each of the engaged couple.
I like making my own bald caps.
That's what these red heads
are for, is making bald caps.
I make a bald cap because it's a female.
I'm gonna have to run her hair
out the back of the bald cap,
and down her wardrobe in the back.
It's a time consuming process,
that's the downside of making a bald cap.
Hey, guys.
Day two of the challenge, I
start molding the pieces,
start fabricating things,
and Ve Neill walks in.
Hey, Anthony, Tate. Who's working on what?
Ve Neill is the perfect person
to critique the gender swap.
She did win an Oscar for "Mrs. Doubtfire".
For the male, we're gonna rely on makeup,
because adding more onto his
face, he's already huge.
- Even him out?
- Yeah, even him out.
Also a chest piece, obviously.
Obviously.
We decided to age them and
make them an elderly couple.
That's an interesting twist.
- You really picked a tough one there.
- We did.
Now, are you gonna leave these one piece,
are are you cutting 'em up,
or what are you doing?
Well, it's a one piece,
also it's a neck appliance,
hand appliances.
What are you gonna make 'em out of?
I think we're gonna go with foam
because adhering silicone,
especially around the mouth area,
can get a little tedious.
- Thank you very much. Keep up the good work.
- Thank you ladies.
- Bye, guys.
- Bye.
What are some of your
worries with some of them?
Some of the things you've seen?
Probably my biggest worry is the fact
if they can paint it to make
it look like a human being,
because that's usually where
everybody fails so miserably.
You know, if they don't get
that intrinsic coloring right,
they could have a lot of problems.
How do you feel about the old age,
because I know old age is so difficult.
You know, they probably
bit off the most to chew.
Gage and Sam should be spending more time
putting that into their
facial pieces as opposed
to working on hands,
because unless you really
do a close-up of hands, you never see 'em.
What's some of the biggest things
you'll be looking for
tomorrow on the challenge?
I always say, you can take a bad appliance,
and if you put a good paint job on it,
you can get away with murder.
Well, it's gonna be exciting to see.
- Hey, bye, everybody.
- Bye, everybody.
- Bye.
- Good luck.
Could you start prepping some silicone?
Step by step, Conor has told Megan
exactly what they're gonna be doing,
which is more what he's gonna be doing
because Conor is doing all of it.
When the sculpture is finished,
it's time to make a mold.
You do that by putting
a cement-like substance
on top of the sculpture
so once it hardens,
you clean out the clay, and fill it
with foam, or silicone,
which eventually becomes the prosthetics.
Silicone requires a lot of maintenance,
especially around the mouth,
where there's, you know, a lot of movement.
So we decided to go with foam.
They broke the first two
rules of old age makeup.
They did it one piece,
and they did it in foam.
If you're putting your ass on the
line with an old age makeup,
it better be perfect in
front of those judges.
As soon as you point a
light at something foam,
it bounces right off, and then
you can see that it's fake.
Silicone allows the light to react softer.
Silicone is the closest
thing on the planet that
looks like human skin.
It has the same flexibility.
Nothing else does.
That's why it's the weapon of choice.
I don't think many people are
using foam on this one but us.
This girl's gonna look
like Charlie Manson when
we're done with her.
That's awesome.
It's gonna look great.
You okay? You need help with that?
I might have a lock.
What do you mean?
When you can't open it.
I can't pull it out.
There it goes. It's not a lock.
It's not a lock, see?
You guys, getting all worried...
Oh, ********.
Look at this, man.
- Tate?
- Yo.
The positive just snapped.
Look at this, man.
Your positive is the stone version
of your actor's head, and
that's what you sculpt on.
In that way, what you sculpt
fits perfectly onto your talent.
Right on the neck.
- Which one was...
- No, the neck one.
So now, we haven't even
cast a prosthetic yet.
We have no duplicates
of this stone positive.
It's not gonna register the same. At all.
At this point, I start
to get really worried.
Everything started breaking.
I was, like, holy ****,
this can't be happening.
You know, the judges, they don't
want to hear your excuses.
They want to see something great.
- Coming up...
- I don't know
that we're gonna get done in time.
You know, it's down to the wire.
Conor's giving Megan credit
I know she doesn't deserve.
Jo, do you have something to say?
You're acting disgusted.
Who did what precisely?
- Tate!
- Yo!
The positive just snapped.
Look at this, man.
Our positive snaps.
There's only one lifecast
of each of our models.
So I immediately start problem-solving
and trying to get us back in the game.
Even though we have a good mold,
we can't make our prosthetic
without the lifecast,
which is now broken.
So I took a vaccuform,
which is a plastic version
of our actor's face that we already made,
and realized that I could run a prosthetic
with that in its place as the lifecast.
- What is that?
- Sand.
This is what we call ghetto-rigging a mold.
By filling it with sand, we got the weight
that the lifecast would have given us
so we can make our
prosthetics out of the mold.
That's another thing I pride myself in.
I get it done.
- You know?
- I know.
Megan's cleaning a lot.
She's Conor's little maid to say the least.
Conor molded everything,
he sculpted everything.
It will help her in this challenge,
and she'll probably stay one more week
and I'm probably going to be
that much more upset about it.
Oh, my God.
That's an amazing pair of boobs.
Oh, look at those.
Anthony's finally whole.
All right, guys, pack it up.
Let's go!
We did good, honeybee!
Nice work.
It's application day,
and we are going to be
down to the wire on ours.
Once the prosthetics has set up,
it can be removed from the mold,
applied to the models face and painted.
We have five hours for application
and we have one hour of Last Looks
before they go onstage.
I really did try to incorporate
some of the notes I was given
from the Foundation Challenge.
A big part of it is shaping
to make it look natural.
And as you lay it, you have
to work backwards, kind of.
Because if you put the top
of a mustache on first,
you'll never get the bottom
underneath that hair.
Doing okay?
- Right here?
- Yeah.
Doing the beauty makeup today,
this is where I'm going to thrive.
This needs to be extravagant,
almost like a drag queen,
but not too glamorous.
Is he starting to look hot?
If I blur my eyes a little bit,
I'm starting to get a little, like, "Ooh!"
- What's your name?
- What's up, girl?
All right, guys, that's 15 minutes.
15 minutes.
Have you seen yourself yet?
Honestly, dude, you could
pass for a chick, easy.
As the clock's ticking down
to the last couple seconds,
I'm finishing it up before
we go to the studios to do our Last Looks.
It's hard to impress these judges,
so I'm really getting nervous.
We're backstage, and we have
one hour to do our Last Looks.
We're about to go out on stage
and I'm not feeling great about it.
We lost a lot of time with the air pockets,
so we're hoping that the judges understand.
Five minutes, everybody!
All right, guys, that's it. Tools down.
I know the judges are going
to have their critiques
and we may be on the chopping block.
If we're going out, we're
going out with a bang.
We walk onto the stage
and it is like the Four Seasons...
Trees, lights, and a live
audience in the studio.
Welcome to the "Face Off" Reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you will be eliminated.
So this week, your spotlight challenge
was to make up real life engaged couples
for their big wedding day,
but you had to do a gender swap...
Turn the bride into the groom
and the groom into the bride.
And we have set the stage
and have invited their friends
and family to witness this all.
I realize how much harder
this challenge is now.
This is not just about
us versus the judges.
It's us versus the judges and the
couples' friends and family.
Let's say hello to our judges.
Owner of "Optic Nerve" Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening, guys.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
Hi, everybody.
And creature designer and director
Patrick Tatopoulus.
Good seeing you guys.
Hi, Patrick.
Let's get started.
First up is Conor and Megan's
couple, Willie and Cecily.
It looks like Grace Jones
and Lionel Ritchie.
It was perfect.
And the chin, even though Conor put it on,
I blended it in with makeup.
He looked gorgeous!
The chin didn't really make the woman.
To me, it still looked like I was watching
Priscilla, Queen of the Desert.
You could still see the guy in there.
What are you laughing it? You look great!
Sam and Gage's couple, Greg and Annie.
Seeing my couple come down the aisle,
I was so happy with our makeups.
I know they could have been better.
I know that, but for what
turned out and what they were,
I'm really happy with it.
Old age makeups are tough
without trying to do a gender
swap at the same time.
I can see edges all the
way around both of them.
Their makeups don't look done.
Next is Tom and Jo's
couple, Dean and Mirai.
When our models come out,
you know, it's kind of jokey.
You know, ha-ha, they're
in a powder blue tuxedo
and this Viking man-wife.
It's fun.
I love this challenge.
This is so great.
I'm sorry.
And lastly we have Tate
and Anthony's couple,
Peter and Kathleen.
Tate and I, we are so confident now.
We have this. The room loved it...
Even the other contestants.
They start walking down the aisle,
and all the sudden Peter
starts having contractions.
It was genius.
She struts up to the judge's table,
takes her sunglasses down, looks at them.
It was awesome.
Who wants to judge?
To the friends and the family
of the engaged couples,
I'm sure on their wedding
day, at least, I hope so,
they will look much more recognizable.
So with that, thank you all
so much for being here.
Well it was great to have a
little levity for a change,
but now it's back to the competition.
"How am I doing?"
"How are the judges going to rate this?"
Judges, why don't you
go take a closer look?
Could you lean down for us?
I'm looking at my competitors' work
and I think Sam and Gage
are in deep trouble.
Is it the foam, or is it
just glued down incorrectly?
I know the judges are going
to be extremely critical,
and I'm sweating bullets.
I'm freaking out.
Could you lean down for us?
I'm terrified that they're
going to immediately hone in
on the spots where the applied prosthetics
have very visible folds
and wrinkles in them.
Is it the foam or is it just
glued down incorrectly?
Is it skinned? Maybe it got skinned.
It feels this a little...
It looks like it.
Mind all the little details.
The chin.
The brow cover is a pretty good idea.
Wish she would have refined
the brows a little bit more
since she covered it.
Could have made it really feminine.
I have so much insecurity
based on previous competitions.
I'm not assuming anything.
Nose. Cheeks, too?
It's a lot of color for a flesh makeup.
They're, like, touching the eyebrows,
trying to figure out
what exactly I've done.
There aren't any prosthetics on him.
It's all just makeup.
- Is that your nose?
- Mm-hmm.
I think she's got a forehead on, too.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
What happened here?
Cut himself shaving.
This is the kind of stuff I like.
As far as the people that
I think are in trouble,
it's not because of their execution,
it's because I feel that mine
and Anthony's are superior.
The judges have scored your couples,
and this week they would
like to speak with each
and every one of you
to learn more about your work.
Gage and Sam, please step forward.
From far away, when they first came out,
I liked the overall idea of
the design and everything.
There's copious amounts of
color on both of their faces
and I'm not seeing a lot
of diversity in the colors
that you picked to try to
bring the skin to life.
You guys really bit off more
than you could chew here.
I think that we both really wanted to try
to do something very different.
And a lot of this is fairly new to me.
And I think that in some cases,
it really does show.
I think this aspect of mixing the gender,
that works maybe a little bit easier
when you do old age makeup.
And I think that's maybe
very clever that way.
You pushed, you challenged yourself.
This is something to admire.
That's my take.
Thank you.
I think that you took a very bold step
in trying to do that age makeup.
As many times as I've done them
they're very difficult for me to do.
My hat's off to you for a good try, guys.
Thank you very much.
If you would please step back.
Thank you.
Now let's talk to Conor and Megan.
The first question I want to
ask you about these makeups,
who did what, precisely,
with detail, please.
Together, we took snaps from the
vaccuforms of their lifecasts.
And we molded it all together,
got it from the gelatin.
Conor is giving Megan credit
that I know she doesn't deserve.
There are things that he's saying she did
that she didn't do.
Once the appliances were on,
you handled all of the makeup from there?
Yes, I did.
I also tinted the nose and chin for her.
Excellent job.
I'm really happy with
both of these makeups.
Thank you.
Really well done. The coloring is solid...
Jo, do you have something
to say over there?
You're acting a little bit disgusted.
Oh, not disgusted.
It's just that when it came to duties,
it did seem like Conor was taking over
the majority of what was going on.
So, Megan, what exactly did
you do on these makeups?
On the bride I did the beauty makeup.
You didn't do any of the
sculpting of the prosthetics?
I did. I did the chin.
You sculpted the chin on the bride?
- Yes.
- Okay. Nice job. Very well done.
- Thank you.
- I love the bride.
I think she's gorgeous.
Can I just say that Megan was...
I chose her as a partner
because of her skills
as a beauty makeup artist?
She helped me every step of the way...
Conor, out of curiosity,
why did you feel the need
to defend Megan's position?
Um, because I really don't like
some of the back-biting that's
been going on in this competition.
And I don't understand
why our time up here had to be interrupted.
Understood.
Conor, Megan, you can step back.
- Thank you.
I'm furious with Jo.
She was my teammate two challenges ago.
I really gave her a lot of
credit in that challenge,
honestly, I think, moreso than I needed to.
Tom and Jo, please come forward.
Okay, I got to ask, who
made the Keebler elf?
I'm responsible for Keebler elf.
Really? What the heck were you thinking?
He's kind of a trailer park '70s guy.
He kind of looks like he would be in
the Pirates of the Caribbean ride.
He does! He looks like one of
those bad animatronic critters.
That's not a good thing, Tom.
Tom, I like that you're trying to play with
some funky little trailer trash thing...
'70s, it's all cool.
My biggest thing is that face
looks very feminine still.
I would have worked on the nose.
Make it maybe a little bit harsher.
Anything, just still
keeping that '70s look,
but making it more male.
I don't know what the
heck went wrong there,
but it went all the way wrong.
All right, and what did
you do to the bride?
We didn't want to add prosthetics on him.
So he has no prosthetics on.
No prosthetics.
- Just a lot of really gray makeup.
- Um...
- Is that it?
- I guess so. Yeah.
Yeah.
I'm disappointed, guys.
Jo, Tom, could you please take a step back?
Thank you.
Tate and Anthony, would you
please step forward.
I got to tell you, your idea was great.
It was definitely the crescendo
of my laugh attacks.
- So, um...
- Thank you.
Who did what with the makeup?
I sculpted the Adam's apple appliance,
the chin, cheekbones, nose, forehead.
I did the beauty makeup.
He was already very
androgynous, so we felt...
- Yeah, he's very pretty.
- Absolutely.
He's gorgeous.
I like the fact that he has fingernails.
That's nice.
I think it was a real paying of attention
to transform a female into a male
beyond the typical beard
and things you expect.
Thank you.
I was very impressed with it.
I appreciate it. Thank you.
Thank you. If you'd please step back.
Nice work, homey.
So, judges, have you come to a decision?
- Yep.
- We have.
I want to remind all of you
that the winner of the
Spotlight Challenge will
have the opportunity
to consult with the judges
on who they think should be eliminated.
Glenn, why don't you tell us
who the top team is tonight?
Tate and Anthony, you took a
huge risk and it paid off.
Conrad and Megan,
the execution of your
beauty makeup was flawless.
Our top team tonight is...
Conrad and Megan.
Good job.
So, then, who's the winner?
We feel that the most
successful transformation
was on Willie.
It's a beautiful beauty makeup,
and, Megan, you were most responsible
for the makeup on Willie, is that correct?
Yes, that's correct.
Then you are our winner.
Congratulations.
You deserve it.
I covered my face. I almost fell over.
I was like, "Oh, my God."
Thank... thank... thank you.
Thank you! Thank you a lot.
What?
I thought I was going to
vomit all over the stage.
That is the most disgusting
thing I've heard since I've been here.
Congratulations, Megan.
You have earned the right
to consult with the judges
on who you feel should be eliminated.
The rest of you can head
back to the makeup room
and wait until the judges
have reached their decision.
Thank you.
That was insanely different
than I had imagined.
At least we know who's going home.
They ripped my makeup apart
worse than they ripped yours.
If they're judging this
competition in particular,
than I will be packing my bags.
Megan, who do you think did the
worst job on this challenge?
Um, the person I feel did the worst is Tom.
The eyebrows, the coloring, the beard...
Out of all the lineups, it
definitely stood out as the worst.
Megan, thank you very much.
Thank you.
So, judges, it's pretty apparent
that you thought Tom and Joe
were the weakest team tonight.
What are your thoughts on Tom?
I think that Tom's makeup is the
stand out in terms of quality.
The hair work, the eyebrows...
I don't know why the nose
wasn't more masculine
if you're going to sculpt a nose.
There was no attempt to
try to make that face
less feminine and more masculine.
I don't know. The whole thing threw me off.
I couldn't get past the beard.
With Jo you have, basically,
a foundation makeup.
At least Tom attempted prosthetics.
Jo did a very basic beauty makeup
with no dynamics or color of any kind.
It was completely flat.
And allowing your makeup
to go completely gray
because of poor layer choices...
even without prosthetics she
could have used stipple coats
to create a new flesh tone
that looked alive and real.
Even if that wouldn't have succeeded,
at least showing fundamental skills...
Today they both did something
that was really not acceptable, I think.
Megan was saying that, you know,
Tom should go home.
I think if we gave Tom that
chance 100 times over,
Tom would try to send Megan home
and Megan would try to send Tom home.
So, judges, have you reached
your decision then?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
All right, let's bring them out, then.
So, judges, who's going home tonight?
Tom, your makeup tonight was an
abysmal failure on all levels...
The eyebrows, the beard, the coloring.
Jo, you also had an unmitigated disaster
because it was unambitious
and it was a simple color makeup
without prosthetics underneath,
and we failed even on that level.
The person going home is...
Jo.
Thank you.
Please head back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Okay.
Oh, Jo.
Walking away at this
point, I've done a lot,
and it does put that flame
in me to keep going.
I might be right out of school,
but at least I know how to **** make a mold.
There you go. Get it out.
Megan, you know what you've done here.
If you think that you can do better, do it.
Don't hold back or pull
on someone's coattails
to get you to the win.
- Peace out, girl.
- Bye, Jo.
Everything that I have
has gone into my work
and I think it shows.
I definitely think that I've proved
that I work hard enough, I
have a place in this industry.
Sync by YYeTs.net, corrected by addic7ed.com
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net