Previously on "Face Off"
12 talented special effects makeup artists
came to Los Angeles to compete
to join the world's elite.
Your Spotlight Challenge is...
Zombies.
- Yes.
And the stakes are higher than ever,
because two people will be eliminated.
I need a wardrobe change.
I just crapped my pants.
This week's winner is...
Tate.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
Glenn, who is going home tonight?
Anthony.
The second person going home tonight is...
Tom.
And tonight on "Face Off"...
You will be disguising yourselves.
And your disguises will be put
to the test in the real world.
A special guest is going to be sent in,
and you are going to have to fool them.
Oh, oh!
It's such an overwhelming challenge.
I'm sweatin' it.
Oh, my God.
Phenomenal, very realistic.
I am thoroughly disappointed.
The judges aren't happy.
It's an insult to everybody else
that's worked so hard in this competition.
To make it to the top,
they'll have to impress our
award-winning panel of judges.
Ve Neill, legendary makeup
artist, who's work includes
"Edward Scissorhands",
"Beetlejuice",
and "The Pirates Of The Caribbean" films.
Glenn Hetrick,
cutting edge makeup effects
artist on "Heroes",
"Legion",
and "Buffy The Vampire Slayer".
And Patrick Tatopoulos,
visionary creature designer
for "Independence Day",
Who will be the next great
name in movie magic
and earn $100,000 and a year's
worth of makeup from Alcone?
Get ready for "Face Off".
Sync by YYeTs
Corrected by ThreeSixes
www.addic7ed.com
We are down to two people in this loft
and it's getting a little empty.
down to five people all together.
That's pretty crazy.
So we're all gonna condense
and see how it is to all live together.
What's up, y'all?
- Hey, roomie.
We all just kind of look at
each other and it's like, wow.
The reality of the situation
is weighing now, you know.
It's insanity.
Cray-cray bananas.
Well, now there's only five
people left in the loft.
I worry because it's just...
it's too unpredictable.
We're all going home soon.
It's just a matter of who goes first.
We walk in and McKenzie's waiting for us
and she has these black envelopes.
It's like, oh, God.
What is this now?
Hey, guys.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Welcome back to the lab.
Makeup artists can be masters of disguise
and your next Spotlight Challenge
is gonna take this to a whole other level.
However, you will not be disguising
your models this time.
You will be disguising yourselves.
For the next two days,
you will have to create and apply a look
that will completely alter your appearance.
Think of this as your very
own "Mission Impossible."
Instantly, I start thinking
about character disguise.
I'm like, oh, this could
be cool, this could be cool,
but what the hell's in this envelope.
After you create and apply your makeups,
you're gonna have to play the
part of a wig shop employee.
I'm thinking, should I change my ethnicity,
I'm thinking, should I change my age.
I'm really worried about how
do we change our appearance?
One at a time, a special
guest is going to be
sent in to see you,
and you are gonna have to fool them.
Now, inside these envelopes
is a picture of your target.
I go and I open it and
there's blond, there's blue.
Oh, oh!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, it's my mom,
and I start freaking out.
It's my mom.
As you can see,
we have brought in
one of your loved ones
who has no idea what this
challenge is really about.
Why don't you show us who you have?
This is Brian. This is my husband.
This is Matt and he's my boyfriend.
This is my mom.
Her name is Donna.
This is my girlfriend, Holly.
This is my sister, Colleen.
They actually think that
they're buying you materials
for your next challenge,
and what they don't know
is that they're gonna have
to buy them from you.
You will be required to interact
directly with your target
and the judges will view
footage from you mission.
So they will be looking not
only at your makeup technique
but also at how much you interact
and whether or not you fool your target.
The only thing left is to start that clock.
Your time starts now.
We have our lifecasts,
which are stone replicas of our own faces,
and on top of those,
we'll sculpt new features out of clay.
I'm gonna have to round out my face a lot.
It's such an overwhelming challenge
because we haven't seen our
loved ones in so long,
yet I have to convince my
boyfriend that I'm a
totally different person.
So I don't know why, but
there's something inside me
that wants to bust out and turn myself into
an overweight black woman.
It's like, it's gotta be done.
My sister has some
knowledge of prosthetics,
enough that I would expect her
to see through a disguise
if there's a lot of latex on my face.
So I went into this half
seen portion of my face,
I'll make a smaller mold
and I immediately cast my teeth
and poured dental acrylic into the mold.
I was definitely gonna utilize those.
I am doing a pregnant, bitchy woman,
because my mom, she hates bitches,
but if I'm pregnant, she's not
gonna know how to conduct herself.
Now, see, I think that's
the biggest part of this
is knowing who you're dealing
with and fooling them.
Yeah, I'm totally gonna be disgusting.
I'm gonna, like, snort and
snot and ask for her number.
The advantage of being with
my girlfriend of six years
is that I know the things
that drive her crazy.
And she really has a problem
with fat, pasty goth kids.
So I'm gonna sculpt a double chin,
obviously, a brow piece
to cover up my brow.
My goal is to have the sculpture
done by the end of the day.
This is gonna be so awesome.
I hope my mom doesn't make me laugh
'cause she knows my laugh.
We all know your laugh.
Can't even tell you how
excited I am to see Brian,
I'm just gonna want to run up and kiss him.
This is the hardest challenge
that I can conceivably think of.
Every single last one of
us is just fretting over
how do we pull this off?
Unless I decide to make myself male.
I finally came down to the
realization that changing gender
had the most impact and it
seemed to make the most sense
with my particular facial structure.
I'm going to increase the size
of my brow just slightly.
And, of course, the Adam's Apple.
Big old fat gelatin belly,
a little paunched happy
trail and a belly ring.
Ugh. Come on.
I'm definitely gonna go with gelatin
'cause gelatin's usually
really easy to work with.
It is a risk due to its weight
and I'm gonna be in it all day,
but it will look beautiful
if I can pull it off.
I'm really nervous about
fooling my boyfriend
because he knows me,
which is why I'm going all out.
I'm changing my skin tone,
I'm covering my tattoos,
I'm taking all my piercings out,
I'm doing full prosthetics,
I'm doing the wig, 'cause
I want it to be real.
I want it to be believable
and I'm just gonna go there.
I'm worried about Gage's makeup
because I truly believe that less is more.
Transforming a lanky, tall white boy
into a heavy-set black woman
isn't gonna be easy.
I'm sweatin' it.
Like it's... I'm really a
bundle of nerves now.
The challenge that we received yesterday
was to create a costume disguise
so that when somebody who is
very close to us shows up,
they are unable to recognize us.
It's good.
It's going to be really
hard to fool somebody
who has been staring at
you for three years.
When the sculpture is finished,
it's time to make a mold.
You do this by putting a
cement like substance
on top of a sculpture.
So once it hardens,
you clean out the clay,
and fill it with foam or silicone,
which eventually becomes a prosthetic.
So I'm doing prosthetic ears.
I just molded them to
cover up my piercings.
Yesterday, I made teeth.
I just kind of had to improvise,
put a little bit of copper wire in there
to make it look like a gold cap.
Teeth are a really great way
to create a quick change
to someone's appearance.
I decided to grab a mannequin,
start sculpting this fat belly.
I'm gonna cast the belly in
gelatin, so... I can't wait.
It's gonna have a little bounce.
I'm tryin' to get my voice down.
Huh.
Oh, my God.
I started toying with my voice and stuff.
And then Glenn walks out with McKenzie.
Hey, Megan.
- Hi.
How are you doing?
- Good.
So is this your inspiration
for your altering?
Yes.
I mean, ever since day one,
I love her structure in her face.
Yeah, she has a great look.
She's absolutely gorgeous.
It's funny because Megan,
for her inspiration,
she chose Diana, which
was Conor's last model,
and model before,
and she's sculpting her
exact face on top of hers.
It's an odd approach.
So the entire makeup is just this piece.
That's the only prosthetic.
I really think subtlety is the key here
'cause I think if my face
is covered in rubber,
she's gonna notice.
Tell me about the materials
for both pieces.
What I think I'm gonna do with the stomach
because I don't want to
deal with too much weight,
I'm gonna do a decently thick gelatin skin
and then I'm gonna push
foam into the back of it.
What material do you plan on using?
Probably gelatin.
I'm using gelatin because it
takes just minutes to do,
but gelatin is a funny substance.
It can mimic flesh in a beautiful way.
But it also is heat reactive
and it can actually melt
right off of the actor.
I look forward to it.
- Yeah, good luck.
Thanks, guys.
Thank you.
How do you feel about, individually,
what they're doing?
How they're gonna alter themselves?
With Conor, it's the most minimal.
I really am interested
in seeing where he goes with that idea.
It seems like it would be easier,
but it's more difficult.
It stands in stark contrast
to what gage is doing.
I kind of think that those two
polar opposites probably have,
in my mind, the best chances of succeeding.
What do you think about Tate's?
I'm a little worried about
the weight of the gelatin.
When you have that much weight,
just getting it on is a challenge.
Going on to Megan, then.
I'm looking at the size of it
and just thinking gelatin
is gonna be really heavy.
If she goes with just straight silicone,
I think it could come to life for her,
but it's gonna be all about the color.
And then last, Sam.
I think that the head
sculpture's a bit blocky.
Sort of half and half, where
some of it's masculine,
some of it's feminine.
It may come out just looking like
this sort of weird, androgynous makeup.
Bye, guys.
Bye.
- Good luck.
Do you have the teeth in?
All right, guys, that's it.
Get out of here.
I'm working on the fly.
I am not making decisions
until they have to be made,
and I am a bit freaked
about this whole deal.
It's all fine and good up until
my boyfriend comes into play.
Walks in the door.
I am tensing up at the thought of it.
Tate, let's go shave.
Tate needs to shave his face,
I need to shave mine.
Neither one of us want to do it.
But we have to for the makeup.
We're suffering for our art.
I'll be 12-years-old when I get back.
It's not gonna be pretty.
All right.
- Oh.
I haven't... dude.
I know.
I'm right there with you, dude.
It's okay.
She'll still love you.
You know guys that walk on their toes
and they kind of fall forward all the time?
They just kind of...
everybody seems a bit anxious at the house.
Practicing our walking,
practicing our talking.
Just going over our mannerisms.
I've got a gut, there's some love handles.
So I just kind of revert back to slouching
and walking with kind of
my feet pointed out and...
well, plus, you're older
so your bowlegging it.
Yes, I'm an old man so...
did you notice Meg's reference today?
Yeah. The model?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's weird.
I know.
It's only weird because
is she turning herself into that model?
It's possible.
I wouldn't put anything
past her at this point.
Today is application day.
Once the prosthetic has set up,
it can be removed from the mold,
applied to the model's face and painted.
And we get assistants for about two hours.
When our helpers come in,
we immediately get down to applying.
They're there to assist us in
putting on our prosthetics
and covering up the back areas
where we wouldn't be able to get to.
I think the one bad thing
about thin gelatin...
Little tiny air bubbles.
It's a hard challenge
and I don't know if it's gonna work.
I'm doing things with types of materials
that I haven't really used before
so I'm coming at this like,
"I'll tell you when I get there."
It already looks disgusting.
I can't wait to get into costume.
On a black person you use
a lot of reds and a lot of browns.
You need to layer it, you need to build it.
And aside from applying the face,
I still have to do my
arms from the elbows down
and my legs from the knee down.
I'm so paranoid that my sister's
gonna see through the disguise.
My main focus today is
getting the prosthetic glued
down and getting it blended,
and doing just good hair work
that's gonna be convincing,
yet changing it up enough so that it's
not gonna be recognizable as me.
Lookin' good, Conor.
Your ass is so big.
Oh, my God, how dare you.
This just looks awful. I mean...
no, it really does.
This is not gonna pass for anything.
I'm realizing as we're putting it on,
things are not working out.
I'm like, "There's no way
that I'm gonna fool my mother
with all these freakin' buckling edges."
I could definitely see
what Megan was so concerned about.
She did have this problem
with folds being created
in the piece whenever she moved,
but I actually thought she
did a really good job.
Had she walked past me on the street,
I wouldn't have even looked twice.
First I peel off the neck,
then I peel off the cheeks.
Maybe I can save the
jawbone and the nose.
And then I look at the profile,
and I said, "Oh, no.
This all has to go."
I just know that this appliance on my face
is not gonna work.
I see Megan and she's
struggling with her piece.
Really, really, really struggling.
And she eventually starts ripping it off.
I'm not feeling this makeup at all.
It's not working.
And if it's not working,
I'm not gonna continue
going down that path.
What?
My biggest fear was time,
and she didn't have good edges
and she wasn't convinced by the prosthetic.
She's thinking at this point it's a fail.
She knows that she's in trouble.
We were given two hours with an assistant,
but that time is up.
I would not have been able
to get this on without you.
I want to hug you but...
nice meeting you, yeah.
- You, too.
- Bye, Gage.
- Bye.
Bye-bye.
My plan b is to do
an awesome foundation
beauty makeup on myself.
I am going to change my
skin tone three shades,
I have my wig down, I
got the green contacts.
I want to make this thing come together.
Damn.
My biggest concern is that
this makeup's gonna last all day.
This isn't like doing an application,
walking it in front of the
judges, and that's it.
Everybody seems a bit anxious.
When it comes down to trying
to fool somebody in person,
the smallest of details can make it real,
or it can make it a disaster.
There's a lot of anticipation now because
the hard part with the makeup's over,
now we gotta perform,
and we have to fool our loved ones.
So you guys excited?
I'm actually terrified.
Why?
I'm gonna try and be as
offensive as possible.
We should practice our voices.
So if you have to handle the wig and cap.
Here you go.
We have an amazing model
that we've worked with before named Deb.
She's there posing as the other co-worker.
Deb's gonna be signaling
us and calling upon us
to do certain tasks in the store.
Here, honey.
That's it. That was it.
That's it.
Here, girl.
No. I don't know.
"He-ah."
I'll figure it out out there.
My sister goes into this
thinking that she's helping
me out with a challenge
where she needs to pick up a couple wigs.
So she knows that the cameras are on her.
- Hello, there.
- Hi.
Welcome to Wilshire Wigs.
Is there anything in particular
you're looking for today?
- I'd kind of like to look around a bit.
- Okay.
Sort of maybe grab something
that catches my eye.
All right.
I'm a little paranoid, of course,
'cause I have no idea if she's gonna
notice anything wrong.
I like that one.
Could you bring us a wig cap?
Oh, yes.
There's a number of parameters
we need to follow going into this.
I have to hand her a wig cap.
Here. You need wig cap.
Okay.
And, yes, I have to speak to her.
No. That's okay.
It won't be my color.
And ultimately, I have to ring up the sale.
- It's going to be $160.
- Okay.
- And here you go.
- Great. Thank you.
You're welcome.
How about a hug for your brother?
Oh, my God.
That was awesome.
Did you have any idea?
No.
Well, mission accomplished, then.
Let's get out of here.
By the time it was time for me to go out,
I'm like, okay, "Let's just do it.
Let's just do it."
The long ones tend to be around the top
and the short ones are
dotted all over the place.
Okay.
- Take a gander,
and then bring 'em and we'll try 'em on.
Cool.
No matter what you do makeup-wise,
there's just an uncanny feeling
that they're gonna know.
I mean, what's that gonna
look like if he's like,
"Oh, my God. Gage!"
So I decide to make Monique,
my character, more withdrawn,
a little bit more soft spoken,
because it's so polar opposite of who I am.
So you want...
yes. -
Go with this one?
Yeah.
- I think so.
And then, of course, one of my
main challenges is to ring him up.
Perfect.
$180.
Out of $200.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Thanks.
He still didn't know.
He didn't know at all.
He goes, "Oh, okay, thanks,
and turned to walk out".
Hon, it's me.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
I'm a black woman, hon.
- Hey. My God.
I did get him,
because he still didn't recognize me
even after I revealed myself,
so that's pretty good.
I think that's pretty good.
Oh, my God.
Did you know it was me?
I had no idea. I had no idea.
I was all, "Here you go."
I had no idea.
Oh, my God.
The funny thing about holly is
she's also a special effects artist.
Not only do I have to fool this person
that has seen me for six years daily,
I have to fool her with the same
thing that she does that I do.
I don't know that I even have a shot.
Welcome to Wilshire Wigs,
I'm Deborah.
- Oh, hi.
I have my back to the door,
and I hear Holly come in,
and I go full Gavin.
Dark brown, black.
I start mouth breathing
and I start waddling around the room,
and then I turn and I make eye contact.
She looked directly into my eye,
and then she looked away.
And I was like, "Yes!
My strategy worked."
I think I want something
probably a little darker.
Deb.
Yes, Gavin.
It's a blue wig.
Okay, well, this is a blue
wig from Gavin there.
Yeah, that's a little crazy.
Could you get us a wig cap
to try one of these on?
Deb, what color?
I want to go with a dark wig cap.
- Okay.
And Holly is just doing
everything she can to not look at me.
This is just pretty like you.
I even smelled her hair
and she didn't move, she was frozen.
Gavin, would you mind
ringing her up for me?
Oh.
Okay.
- Come on, now, you remember how to do it.
Deb.
You've got it. You're fine.
Okay.
Sorry.
- That's no problem at all.
Thank you. - Have a good night.
Thank you very much.
Uh, Miss Martinez.
Yes?
How you doin'?
Oh, my God.
Did you know it was me at any point?
- What did you...
- I was trying to not pay attention.
Let's get out of here.
Fooling my mom is gonna be
harder than maybe anybody else's
'cause, you know, she's
known me since day one.
I thinking that it looks
like Megan with a spray tan.
How can you fool your own
mom without a prosthetic?
Hello, there.
- Hi.
Welcome to Wilshire Wigs.
I'm Deborah, nice to meet you.
I'm Donna.
Oh, my God.
I hear my mom's voice.
I don't know what to do.
I just don't think this is gonna work.
-
- Coming up...
He's just across the cash register,
I'm going to be found out.
There's still so much of you
coming through that makeup.
All that's incredible, so fantastic work.
I think you were pretty darn
successful, and congratulations.
Fooling my mom is gonna be
harder than maybe anybody else's,
'cause, you know, she's
known me since day one.
Hello there.
- Hi.
Megan had problems with her prosthetics
so she didn't use any.
But moms have this weird voodoo
that they know their kids, you know?
So I have no idea how she thinks
she's gonna make it work.
At first, I start hiding
my face a little bit,
I'm just like going around
like this, like, "mm-hmm."
But we're supposed to
interact with our loved ones,
we're supposed to help them out,
so I start playing off of the
other people in the shop.
I start to test out my voice on them.
You okay here?
And I'm like, okay, okay, I can do this.
How you doin' over here?
You good? Great.
This one's nice natural.
This one right here.
It's a bit lighter.
Then comes the moment of truth.
Nancy, would you mind ringing
her up with these two?
Did you find everything
you were looking for?
Uh, yeah.
Uh. Oh, van-damnit.
I'm going through this like,
"Please don't recognize me,
'cause if you do, then that
just might show the judges
you're not that good
with beauty makeup."
You did need a prosthetic.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Mom, it's me.
It's Megan. It's Megan.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, you look so cute pregnant.
No. No, no, no, no.
Oh, did you know it was me?
No!
My husband and I have been
together for three years.
He studies people's faces and
postures and walking patterns.
He's really observant.
It seems impossible.
Hello.
- Hello.
How are you today?
I'm good, how are you doing?
I hear his voice, and I
look like myself still.
I... there's no way that he
cannot know that it's me.
So I'm trying to just show my profile
because it looks least like me.
Oh, wow.
Would you like to try this one on?
Give it a shot. See what it looks like.
Mark, could you get a wig cap for us?
Put this on.
Okay.
Every time Deb gives me an instruction...
Mark, could you... oh, perfect.
You read my mind.
Could you bring that one over here?
Go and give him a wig cap.
Go and pick out this wig.
Suggest that you like it.
It's kind of hard to resist, yeah.
Take a look at that.
I'm terrified all over again
that I'm gonna be found out.
Mark, could you ring him
up for these two, please,
and I'll start putting these back.
And then the very end,
this was the part that was
the most nerve-wracking
to me because, I mean,
he's just across the cash register.
The lighting is not
normal effects lighting.
Every part about it is
just like, "Oh, of course,
this is the time I'm
going to be found out."
Thank you very much.
Thank you, sugar.
Have a good one.
Brian.
- Oh!
Oh, wow.
I can't believe you did this.
How are you?
- Ohh.
Wow.
Yeah.
Going back to the loft,
we all got to, you know,
just meet and mingle.
It was cool, I mean, challenges aside,
that is hands down the
most levity we've had
since we started this.
Woo-hoo!
Hey, it's nice to meet you finally.
We were shut off from our
loved ones for so long,
to have them come into
this world and have...
just be able to be like,
"Oh, now you see what
I've been dealing with
and you're part of this
one section in our life
that will never happen again."
We're gonna do a really big
toast to everyone who's here,
who made it this far and who
trekked across the country
to be here tonight.
Thank you. You're amazing.
Cheers.
It's time to go.
Once our loved ones had left for the night,
I think we were all infused
with a new sense of motivation,
and a new sense to keep going.
Welcome to the "Face Off"
reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you will be eliminated.
Say hello to your judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve
Makeup Effects Studio,
Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening, guys.
Three-time Oscar winning makeup artist,
Ve Neill.
Welcome back, everybody.
And creature designer and director,
Patrick Tatopoulos.
Hello, everyone.
Hi, Patrick.
This week, your Spotlight Challenge
was to disguise yourself
and fool those closest to you
by posing as a wig store employee.
Let's check out some of your videos
and see how you did.
My video comes on and it's just so
awkward to watch.
You're gigantic.
I knew that he had no clue who I was,
but what the judges are
gonna see of my makeup,
I have no idea.
It's very nerve-wracking.
Hon, it's me.
- Oh, my God.
As soon as my video starts playing,
I'm pretty excited about it.
Let me try both...
Of these, I guess.
I loved my makeup and I liked my acting.
Oh, van-damnit.
Oh.
I did get the vibe that her mom knew,
'cause it'd be really
hard not to have known.
Mom, it's me, it's Megan.
- Oh.
Oh, did you know it was me?
No!
Oh.
- No. My God.
I definitely don't like this color
- I like this one.
You know, I feel great that
I pulled off the challenge.
It's going to be $160.
But now it's like,
how are the judges gonna rate this?
How about a hug for your brother?
Oh, my God.
Actually, you do kinda
look a little like that.
Put this on.
Okay.
It's pretty cool to see
more of my husband's reaction.
I felt nervous all over
again, sort of like,
"Oh, is he gonna recognize me?"
I have the hardest time
reading the judges' faces,
so watching them,
I can't really tell what they're thinking.
Brian.
- Oh!
Oh, wow.
I take it back, I don't
want to see mine now.
I completely changed everything about me,
I changed my jaw line, my nose, my walk,
my breathing,
so I don't know that I will be in the top,
but I don't feel like I'm going home.
All right, well, the judges would
like to speak with each of you.
Sam, you're up first.
I really hope I get a win this time.
I've been in the middle
the entire competition.
I think that this ended up...
Terrible.
All right, well, the judges would
like to speak with each of you.
Sam, you're up first.
When I came in and I sort of
looked at your sculpture,
I thought that we were
in some trouble as to where it was going.
We've talked about not having
a completely solid idea
before you take the next step
and start turning it into makeup.
And here, I think that this ended up...
Terrible.
Terribly successful.
I... I'm blown away by the fact that
it came from where you were
in clay to that. And...
but I wanted so badly to do the multi-piece
because I know you were
stressing it before,
so I decided to leave the edges unsculpted
so that I could at least adjust
and pull in various places.
That was an absolutely brilliant
decision to leave this open
so that you could move it around
on your face and manipulate it
during the application,
especially when you're
wrestling a gelatin piece,
putting it on yourself.
I was blown away by the color that
you achieved in your gelatin,
especially for someone who doesn't do it.
Well done.
Thank you.
And you know what?
You did a couple of things there
that are very impressive to me.
It looks like a masculine face.
It doesn't look like a woman
wearing a masculine makeup.
All that is incredible, very realistic.
It's a male figure that I'm looking at
and I buy it.
So fantastic work, Sam.
Thank you.
I'm really proud of you, Sam.
This is amazing.
You have progressed leaps and bounds.
He looks kind of like one
of these kind of weaslly,
sickie type guys with dirty hair and...
I wouldn't have thought twice
to look at him again,
that it was like some weird makeup job.
You did a great job.
Thank you so much.
Good job, girl.
That's awesome.
Tate. You're up next.
All right.
In a case like this,
I felt the idea would have been
to be a bit more discreet,
and make something more casual.
But no, you went beyond that
and you just created a character again.
I'm a big fan of that side
of your work, man, so...
thank you so much. - I'm on board.
How successful do you feel you were
with the technical
execution of this makeup?
You know, I'd have to say about a six.
I liked the character.
I could have, obviously,
done better with more time.
I like it.
I think that it was pretty successful.
The performance and the wig,
I think, were the two things
that had the greatest
chance of giving you away
because it was over the top and the...
the mutant level mouth breathing
that you were doing was,
although hilarious,
I think it was almost endangering you
of giving yourself away
because it was so over the top,
but it has nothing to do with your makeup.
I think that it was very successful.
Thank you very much.
You know what?
I didn't even want to look at you.
So, I mean,
I think you were pretty darn successful
and congratulations.
He was nasty.
Wow. Thank you very much.
Gage. You are next.
Okay.
Upon initially visiting you in the studio,
my feelings towards your makeup were
grave amount of trepidation
because of what you were trying to do.
It's just so much stuff.
But after seeing it on,
I think that you did a really good job.
I think that it was very bold to try to
incorporate this many different aspects.
I was a little scared of the
voices that you were making
when we were at the studio,
as I think everyone was.
Yeah.
I'm glad you decided to
pull that back a bit.
Yeah. Absolutely.
This was a really brave move on your part
to do the gender swap and ethnicity.
Just because I find it so interesting
that you did Monique,
how come you didn't put
any beauty makeup on her?
I tried to and it just started
looking really cartoony.
I find some aspect of the
appliance on the face
a little patchy color-wise,
but you really sold the character.
She's very much believable.
Thank you. Thank you so much, you guys.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
Conor. You are next.
Please step forward.
Hey, Conor, another really
beautiful makeup job.
Thank you.
Unfortunately, he looks just like you.
I mean, it looks like a
terrorist version of you.
I can't disagree. I mean, I didn't know
exactly how it was all gonna look.
He's your ugly cousin, dude.
Yeah. No, I don't disagree.
I... I see myself in there as well.
It was just a little too on the safe side.
I wish you pushed a little bit more
the aspect of the sculpt.
And you could have twisted
yourself a little more
and still be quite realistic,
so it's just right there.
Unfortunately, I agree
that there's still so much of
you coming through that makeup
and this week was all about
disguising yourself.
Conor, thank you very much.
Megan, you are up next.
I had full intent of using prosthetics
and when that didn't come out,
I went with plan b.
Hopefully, the judges take
that into consideration,
but who knows?
Megan, you are up next.
Megan, I am thoroughly
disappointed in this makeup.
You probably had some technical problems
with the time that you had.
I get all of that.
That said,
when the competition is to
create a makeup effect,
and you've been here in
front of us several times,
and we keep saying we
want to see what it is
that you have to offer us,
presenting us with what
you were trying to do
would, in my opinion, have
been a better approach
than doing a beauty makeup.
So that's all I have to say about this.
Last week you just barely skated by,
you were on the fence and I think you have
totally fallen off the fence this time.
And to think that you're gonna,
like, hide your face and
get away with that,
I mean, you had your back to
the camera most of the time.
You were hiding behind wigs and
your hair and whatever you could.
I mean, I don't think you
fooled your mother at all, quite frankly.
She's just smart enough
not to say anything.
You know, all the people
that have been dismissed
from this competition,
and then you do this?
Megan, it's hard for me
to add anything else.
I mean, there's no point
telling you more than what
you just heard already.
I... I have to say, I'm
extremely exhausted.
And I'm tired.
I'm tired.
All right, Megan.
Judges, have you reached a decision?
Yeah.
- All right.
I'd like to remind you all
that the winner of
the Spotlight Challenge
will have the chance to advise the judges
on who they feel should be eliminated.
Glenn, why don't you tell
us about the top looks?
This week's top two looks are...
Sam.
You were the most
unrecognizable of the group.
And Gage,
for really going for it and
swinging for the fences.
A massive amount of work.
And you also succeeded in burying
yourself in your character.
Very tough decision.
A lot of good makeups this week.
So, then, who is the winner?
Our winner this week is...
Sam.
Yay.
Congratulations.
Finally.
I'm thrilled.
I mean, I'm so glad to have
this chance to finally say,
"Okay, this is something that
I'm really, truly proud of."
Sam, you have earned the
right to advise the judges
on who you feel should
be eliminated tonight.
Actually...
That's not gonna be necessary this evening.
There's a singular clarity
to our decision process this evening.
The person going home tonight is...
Megan.
Megan, being tired and being
worn out is not an excuse.
It takes a tenacity to
succeed at what we do.
I hate to send the women home.
That's heartbreaking.
There's so few of us that can stick to it,
it bums me out to have to send you home,
especially with such a huge failure.
Megan, if you would please head back to
the makeup room and pack up your kit.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
You are our final four.
Next week, one of you will
be crowned the winner.
Congratulations.
- Congratulations, everybody.
Good work.
- Thank you.
I'm ready for that final challenge.
I'm ready to win this $100,000.
I'm ready to show why I'm here.
Sam, congratulations.
Great job. - Thank you, lady.
I don't want to go home right now.
I have a lot to do, still,
and I still want to spend
more time with Conor.
I'll miss you most of all.
You were a great partner.
Thank you.
I know I totally screwed up.
I don't feel like a failure, though,
because I've been
through so much
and nothing's gonna stop me
from being in this industry
and giving my all.
Sync by YYeTs
Corrected by ThreeSixes
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net