RuPaul: Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
We're not just having
one premiere.
We're having two premieres,
and you lucky seven
are the first group of queens.
♪ I--I--I'm a bitch,
I--I'm a bitch ♪
♪ I'm a bitch ♪
[cheers and applause]
Literally
I would steal that line.
It was some next-level shit.
Widow Von'Du,
you're a winner, baby.
[applause]
This week, no one's going home.
♪ Made it ♪
Live another day, girl.
Oh, my God.
We're back in the workroom
after our "elimination,"
and everybody's gagged.
So what do you guys think
happens from here?
Girl, I have no fucking idea.
-Anything can happen.
-Yeah.
I think
what's gonna happen is
this is gonna happen again,
but not with us.
[alarm]
RuPaul: Ooh, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
What's happening?
-What?
-Again?
What's going on?
I just sat down.
Hey, ladies.
Good job this week.
So are you ready to meet
the other queens?
No!
Leave a message on the mirror,
and they'll get back to you
as soon as they can.
-Oh!
-No way.
-All right.
I hope these bitches
are ready to eat the leftovers,
because that's usually what
you do when you're number two.
[laughs]
-Give 'em a little kiss.
-Mwah!
-Yeah!
-Yes, honey.
They don't know
what's coming to them.
-Whoo!
-Whoever these girls are,
I hope they brought
their A game,
because we are serving it.
All: We done already
done had ourses!
Good luck, bitch.
RuPaul: The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
and a cash prize of $100.000.
With extra-special guest judges
Thandie Newton and Robyn.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
RuPaul: Welcome
to the second premiere
of RuPaul's Drag Race 2020.
All tuck and no play
makes Rock M. a crazy bitch.
[laughs] Whoo!
Whoo!
Woop, woop, woop, woop!
I'm Rock M. Sakura,
and am I really Japanese?
Who knows? Is it
cultural appropriation?
We'll find out. Stay tuned.
Where should I go next?
Should I just sit on the stairs?
A lot of my influences come from
anime, manga, and video games.
Rock M. is very indicative
of Rock'Em, Sock'Em Robots,
because I got big arms
like these.
How sturdy are these tables?
I am a high-energy
comedy anime queen
that can dance, sing.
She's just a big explosion
of legs and arms
and some other body parts
that you might not even want
or care to see.
Huh!
It's so exciting to be here.
This is my chance to show
the world that I'm a superstar.
What's over here?
"We done already
done had ourses?"
What does it mean?
Were there people
that are already here?
Oh, no!
There's already stuff here.
Aah! Aah!
Are you ready to live a little,
sin a lot?
I'm Dahlia Sin,
and I'm here to take your man.
Eew. [laughs]
I'm from the Haus of Aja,
who you might know
from Season 9 and All Stars.
The Haus of Aja
is definitely known for drama.
All we do
is talk shit about--
[laughs]
talk shit about everyone.
-Hi-ee!
-Hi, honey.
-Welcome, new sister.
-You look gorgeous, bitch.
Oh, mwah.
You look like a chandelier,
but like a sexy,
denim chandelier.
Oh, oh, oh.
Come on, denim, look good.
I'm Rock M. Sakura.
Oh--oh--oh, okay, bitch.
I'm from San Francisco.
-Oh, okay, nice.
-What about you?
Well, I'm from New York,
but I currently live in L.A.
-Okay.
-And we gonna win.
Ooh, ooh.
Don't count out
San Francisco yet.
I actually live
for San Francisco.
The San Francisco queens
are cunt comedy queens.
L.A. is more of a look.
Okay, when I get there,
the first thing they notice
is the smell.
[both laugh]
I definitely consider myself
a look queen.
My style is very Vanjie.
It's fierce, it's better
than all these other bitches
that are gonna be on the show.
[laughs]
Hope you saved room for dessert,
because I brought Pie.
[laughs]
I'm Sherry Pie, and I am
the queen of camp. Ooh.
You're a funny little lady.
Oh, yeah, oh, ooh.
Sherry is a big, loud,
Broadway dame.
When you enter
a Sherry Pie show,
I expect nothing less than
laughs, hoots, and hollers.
Yes, bitch!
-Hi, Mama!
-Hi.
I'm so excited.
I want that crown
on top of my wig.
I'm, like, gagged, gooped,
beguiled,
bewitched, bothered,
and bewildered.
That's a musical theater
reference
for all you kids
out there. Hello.
-I'm Rock M.
-Hi.
Rock M. Sakura.
I'm from San Francisco.
I haven't really seen
the drag there.
What's it like?
My brand is very,
like, dumb humor.
Slay.
If you think about it
driving to the gig,
and be like, "This song is dumb.
I wanna do it like this
and dress like a hot dog."
[moans]
Oh, I want a hot dog
real bad.
Okay, I'm gonna stare at myself.
[whistle blows]
Oh, oh, oh.
Hey, y'all,
let's play some basketball.
Yes!
I'm Jan, I'm 26,
and I'm from New York City.
I hope everybody
caught the reference.
If you heard Fergie
singing the national anthem
at the NBA All Star game,
you know that she ended that
saying, "Let's play
some basketball."
Basketball?
I am wearing my varsity
cheerleader outfit.
My look just really encapsulates
everything that I am
as a drag queen.
It's fun, it's flirty,
but it's fierce.
-Hi!
I gagged to see Jan come in.
She's a New York City sister.
She has an amazing voice,
she's an amazing actress.
Hi, I'm Jan.
Nice to meet you.
Jan, nice to--oh, Jan.
Jan [bleep], right?check
Oh, it's just Jan.
-Just Jan.
-Yeah.
Just Jan!
[all laugh]
Bitch, come on. New York in
the motherfucking house, bitch.
Yeah, New York City!
Coming up
in the New York City scene,
I really, really wanted to get
to the top very, very quickly.
I'm really ambitious,
I'm very driven,
and I don't apologize for that.
And I'm just ready
to go Team Jan.
What's that mean?
There's messageseses.
Oh, Jesus, people are--
oh, my--wait.check
There's already queens here,
girl.
Some of these stations
are filled.
I'm shocked. I'm confused.
-Oh!
-Oh, oh, oh.
Hey, bitches.
She's here!
She is a woman.
Hey, bitches,
it's Jaida Essence Hall,
the essence of beauty,
and I'm here to slay
the competition.
When Jaida walks in a room,
she's very classy, very bougie,
she smells like money.
Turquoise, ooh.
I look fabulous,
I'm wearing something
that's off-the-shoulder
so you can catch
all of these shoulders
and all of that good zhuzh
up here.
Her shoulders.
That's all I can talk about
are her gold,
glistening shoulders.
They should sell her shoulders
at Barney's.
Hello!
-You look hot.
-Thank you.
I'm living for
the beat bitch in person.
I have to say this color
looks beautiful on you,
by the way.
-Thank you. Thank you.
-You look amazing.
She's like, "You're welcome."
Although I support
any other styles of drag
and I like the art of it,
for me, drag is exuding,
like, feminine energy.
I don't consider myself
really too much of a drag queen,
but more
of a female impersonator.
Jan: What's your drag like?
I sew professionally.
I have, like, a fashion line.
-So did you make this?
-Yes, I made it.
Like 99% of the things
that I brought I made.
What do you feel like
is mainly your style of drag?
I'm a singer, really.
That's my main thing that I do.
-Oh, sing something right now.
-Yeah.
[bluesy]
♪ Hey-ey-ey-ey-ey ♪
-Oh!
-My turn.
[off-key] ♪ Hey... ♪
[all laugh]
How about you sing,
and then she lip syncs it?
Five, six, seven--
♪ Hey-ey-ey-ey-ey ♪
Yay!
Season 12
is about to be in-Zhane.
We got a spooky queen.
I am Aiden Zhane,
and I am here to slaughter
the competition.
Okay, she's the odd one.
I think the other queens
are immediately gonna be like,
"Oh, this is the weird bitch."
People would probably describe
my drag as kind of mysterious.
I don't think there's really
another drag queen out there
that you can compare me to.
You can try, but good luck.
-Hi!
-I'm Sherry.
-Aiden.
You can sit next to me.
I love crazy.
Tell us what your scene's like.
Well, isn't that the question?
[all laugh]
Do you have the answer?
Atlanta, it's not very diverse,
I guess.
You know, I wish there was
more room for just crazy.
Is that what you do?
Yeah, I'm definitely
a little bit psychotic, so...
-Wow.
-Sickening.
So if I'm coming to see you
in a show, what do I expect?
I'm definitely an actress,
first of all.
Like, I love to emote,
I love to give expression.
When you say you're an actress,
do you have drama training?
No, I don't have any, like,
actual background training
in acting.
Rock: Where do you perform?
See, the closest city
for me to perform is Atlanta,
and it's like an hour away.
How many times a week
do you perform, then?
None a week, currently.
Well, then how
do you do drag there?
[all laugh]
My drag background, I would say,
is a lot different
from a lot of queens.
I don't have
the same performance background,
because I don't have
drag family.
I don't really have
that many drag friends.
But don't let that fool you.
We need to talk about
this mysterious message
on the mirror.
It says, "We done already
done had ourses."
Are we having another Shangela
or Vanjie moment?
I think
it's a Season 6 moment,
where half of the dolls
are already here.
Jan: We should Nancy Drew it.
I wanna try
to clock this spoof.
Damn, some of this stuff
looks real cute.
Some of it
also looks real tacky.
[all laugh]
Can we just take a bunch
right now,
since they're not here?
I think we should hide
everything.
[alarm]
Oh!
RuPaul: She done already
done had herses.
Yo, ma'am!
My queens.
[cheering]
Remember,
it's not about who comes first,
it's about who comes hardest.
So put some Fosse in your posse
and razzle-dazzle me.
Five, six, seven, eight--
Oh, wait a minute.
There's only six of you...
for now.
[all laugh]
Ooh, bitch!
[evil laugh]
What's a "Fosse?"
Hello, hello, hello.
-Oh!
-Oh, my God!
-RuPaul!
Welcome to the second premiere
of RuPaul's Drag Race 2020.
[cheers and applause]
Now, you may have noticed
that you're not the first queens
to arrive.
-Yeah.
-I see.
Now, this week, you six
get your very own premiere
so we can scrutinize every inch
of your charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent.
#DragRace.
So to kick things off, we wanna
see what you're packing.
So for today's mini-challenge,
you need to model
a Spring and Fall look
worthy of a star-studded
Fashion Week runway show.
[cheering]
Yeah!
Jaida: I'm so excited that there
are two runway looks on day one.
I'm excited to see who the hell
is gonna be out here.
I wanna meet some celebrities
and just show these judges
exactly what I'm made of.
Are y'all ready
to change the world?
[cheering]
I'll see you on the runway.
Let's go.
It's faster this way! Oh!
[cat yowls]
Michelle,
it's Andre Leon Talley.act 2
Don't look.
I owe him 20 bucks.
[whispers] Oh, no.
So we have our very first
mini-challenge today,
and it's anything but mini.
We have to do a Spring
and a Fall look.
I don't wanna have,
like, a fashion disaster.
Fingers crossed.
Serving Spring eleganza:
Rock M. Sakura.graphic
Ross: Anime-zing.
I know that RuPaul's there,
but I can't tell
who any of the other people are
because I am in focus mode.
Rock M.'s spring look is
inspired by Commes des Garcons,
and I can feel
my full haraduku fantasy.
I drew this design myself
because I want them to see
my full range of talents.
I want them to look at
the picture and then look at me
and go, "She is a drawing
come to life."
RuPaul: Come on, Afro Puff.
Ross:
If you can't wear yourself,
how the hell you gonna
wear somebody else?
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Dahlia Sin.
Michelle:
Now that's Andre Neon Talley.
RuPaul: Oh, okay.
Ross: Sin is in.
I got my drag name
based off of the Black Dahlia
and the seven deadly sins.
I'm feeling very sexy
with my big, orange pumpkin wig
and my fat ass pose
My body is everything
when I'm doing my runway.
Michelle:
Her lip gloss is poppin'.
And by her lip gloss,
I mean her ass.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Sherry Pie.
Michelle:
Look, it's Sherry Tasselhoff.
She's huge in Germany.
[all laugh]
I wanna come in
as the camp queen
who also can do fashion.
So Sherry Pie is giving you
some old Hollywood,
some old New York City.
I am dripping in florals
for Spring groundbreaking.
RuPaul: Ooh, yeah, honey,
you better slice me
some of that Pie.
Ross: That Pie's got cake.
[all laugh]
Jan. No last name, just Jan.
Michelle: Marie Jan-toinette.
Jan: When I do my shows
in New York City,
normally I'm in a leotard.
But I'm excited to show people
that I have
a different side of me.
You're gonna be getting
some looks from me this season.
My spring look
is Dolce & Gabbana-inspired,
and it could also be interpreted
as "high on a hill
was a lonely goatherd,
leidey-odeleidy-odelei-hee-hoo."
RuPaul: Choke her?
I just met her.
[all laugh]
Jaida Essence Hall.
Ross: Peekaboo.
RuPaul: She's gonna put
somebody's eyes out
with those things.
I love just being
really ladylike, very dainty,
but it's still got cute details,
and it looks expensive as hell.
You see
a little bit of peekaboo,
and you get that
little bit of that sexy,
because that's what Jaida
is all about.
Ross: Ooh. Oh, oh.
Punch my titties.
[all laugh]
Aiden Zhane.
Ross: Category is Garden Ho.
-Oop. And a-oop.
-A-oop!
[all laugh]
Aiden: My Spring look
is very April showers
bring May flowers.
Aiden might be creepy,
but she is also
colorful and fun.
She loves to be cute,
but she's always got
a little bit of freak in her.
Michelle: The rain in Spain
falls mainly on Aiden Zhane.
RuPaul: A tree grows in Sylmar.
Well, you know, this season
is all about global warming
and bugle beads.
Now, serving fashion for Fall,
Rock M. Sakura.graphic
Rock: Koi toy.
For my fall look,
I'm feeling very fish.
I'm wearing
a classic mermaid skirt
that's made completely of felt.
I said I felt. [laughs]
I actually don't have
a lot of connection
to my Vietnamese
or Filipino background.
The culture that I have adopted
is cartoons, anime.
TV has raised and shaped me
into the person I am today.
RuPaul: Don't shoot till you see
the white of her eyes.
[all laugh]
Dahlia Sin.
Ross: Inspired by Michelle
before electrolysis.
[all laugh]
Dahlia: My fall look is the more
high-fashion version of Dahlia.
I give off very bitch face
when I'm in drag,
and people will not talk to me.
[laughs]
I just can't help it.
That's just my face.
I'm not really a bitch,
but I can be a bitch.
[laughs]
Michelle:
What becomes a legend most?
RuPaul: Alimony.
[laughs]
RuPaul: All right,
another helping of Sherry Pie.
Straight out the lovin' oven.
Or was it a Dutch oven?
[all laugh]
Sherry Pie's Fall runway
is a little bit of Zorro,
is a little bit of
Victor/Victoria,
and also I feel
a little James Bond.
Girl, I'm giving you
all the references,
because that's what drag queens
are supposed to do:
give you the fantasy.
RuPaul:
Does anybody still wear...
-A hat?
Ross: Jan.
RuPaul: Guacamole.
Ross: This fall, from Crocs.
[all laugh]
Jan is the girl next door,
but she's so much more
than just that.
A lot of the things that I like
are very sleek,
they're really polished,
they're sexy.
Ariana Grande, Lady Gaga,
Kim Petras,
all those looks
wrapped up in one.
RuPaul:
See you later, alligator.
Ross: After while, crocodile.
[all laugh]
Jaida Essence Hall.
I used to room
in Jaida Essence Hall.
-Oh, at college.
-Yeah, in college, yeah. Mm-hmm.
Come on, Tom Whored.
[all laugh]
Jaida: Growing up,
I always loved fashion,
I always loved art,
and I never thought that I
would have the chance to do it.
And when I found drag,
I'm like, oh, my God,
I can do everything
that I've always wanted to do
all the time.
And it's like home for me.
Ross: She's such a beret
of sunshine.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Aiden Zhane.
She seems very cozy.
[all laugh]
Michelle: Somewhere there's
a bunch of tea kettles
that have no clothes on
right now.
[all laugh]
Aiden Zhane loves ugly things,
but fashionable things.
I am definitely a thrifty,
crafty kind of queen.
I'm not really a seamstress,
but I love
to piece things together
and, you know, find one item
and kind of map it out
from there.
The return
of Shields and Yarnell,
minus Shields.
And Yarnell.
[all laugh]
Bitch!act 3
Darling.
-Ooh.
I can't wait to see
what you guys look like
out of drag.
We have been in drag
all morning,
and it is time to reveal
the beast underneath.
Oh!
I really don't wanna see
anybody out of drag.
[laughs]
We're taking our clothes off,
I'm looking to the left,
I'm looking to my right.
[humming burlesque music]
Meh.
[laughs]
My favorite part
about taking off the tights
is feeling that steam from,
like, the third or fourth layer
come out like
some sort of Hot Pocket.
-Girl, wow.
-[laughs]
That is so gross.
Girl, I about to get
a nerf burn.
[sniffing] I can--I can smell
the trade in the room.
Ugh.
Dahlia is trade central.
Aah!
My dumb ass didn't have,
like, any, like, underwear,
so I'm like, well, I guess
I'm getting naked. [laughs]
Like, my whole ass just right
on the first episode, bitch.
[laughs]
Dahlia looks hot
in and out of drag.
The bitch turns looks.
Ooh, you bitches
are looking mass for femmes.
Say hello to my double chin.
There she is again.
Do any of you have day jobs?
What's your day job?
Just a prep cook,
nothing exciting.
-What kind of restaurant?
-IHOP.
So you're good with knives.
That's good to know.
Aiden looks kind of
like backwoods-ish.
She looks like
she's gonna go huntin'.
You know, go trappin'.
I don't know what people do
in the woods.
♪ She's a boy now ♪
Rock M. has
the biggest transformation
out of all the girls.
I was not expecting
these little muscles,
little tight booty.
I just want to poke her butt.
Aren't y'all happy
we all getting along right now?
-I am.
-Are we?
Everybody here has brought it,
and I don't like any one of you.
[all laugh]
Hey, squirrel friends.
-Hi.
-Hey.
Who are you dudes?
[all laugh]
That's that RuPaul girl.
Ladies, now that you've shown us
your passion for fashion,
we need to see how well
you can captivate an audience.
So warm up your jazz hands,
because for your first
maxi-challenge,
you'll be performing
in an original musical number
called You Don't Know Me.
[cheers and applause]
Now, each of you
needs to write and perform
an entertaining verse
that tells us who you are.
-Word.
-And together,
you need to come up
with the choreography.
-Oh. Okay.
-Oh, no!
Now, this is your chance
to break out from the pack,
so don't fuck it up.
Yes, yes.
[applause]
I'm so excited.
It's a Fosse number,
it is in my wheelhouse.
I'm like, yes!
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[cheers and applause]
Our first challenge
is a Fosse-esque musical number.
I'm super-excited,
because I love Fosse
and I'm like, girl,
we're about to kill it.subtitle
[sigh] She--he--she?
He--she--she--
Girl, Fosse is
the main character of Chicago?
Is it? I don't know.
I'm bad with this.
Don't judge me.
Ooh.
Going into this challenge,
I feel pretty confident.
Musical theater is my life.
It's right up my alley,
and I can't wait
to bowl a fucking strike.
I'm excited because
it's the first challenge
that we get to do and we get
to showcase our strength.
I have a show back home
where I do a different
musical every single week,
and I drag it up.
So I'm really excited, actually.
The people who look the most
confident in this challenge
are sitting right next to me.
[tongue pop]
So I'm thinking
how can I set myself apart
in a very interesting
and fun way?
Honestly, I've never
written lyrics before,
so I kind of want
to hide behind a character.
I'm thinking of maybe
doing, like, an accent,
like Fosse 1920s.
I'm thinking about Chicago
and Fosse
and all I can think about
is like a voice,
like... [gangster accent]
oh, we gotta make someone
who's nice and cutthroat, see?
Have you seen Chicago before?
Oh, no. Yeah, I have.
The show?
No, the city.
Yeah, I've seen the show.
[all laugh]
We desperately need to start
on the choreography then.
-Yeah.
-Girls!
-Yes, ma'am?
Ladies.
Aah!
Stop!
Who here has done,
like, choreography
and stuff like that?
-I have.
-Okay.
Who here has done, like, musical
theater choreography, though?
When I was in middle school.
Does that count, bitch?
What were you, apple tree
number three on the side?
Just like... [humming]
[all laugh]
Does everyone know who Fosse was
and what Fosse is all about?
I mean, I wouldn't say
I know what he's all about.
I'm a little nervous,
because I'm asking these girls
if they know anything
about Fosse,
and they're just looking at me
like I got six heads.
The only concern I have
is bringing the Fosse to life.
He's all about details
and being super clean.
Okay, choreographer.
I'm not--
I'm not doing any of that.
Well, Sherry, you seem like
you have the most knowledge.
So you're the choreographer.
[laughs]
But I'm certainly no dancer.
Does anybody feel good
about kind of spearheading
the choreography?
I teach a dance class,
but I learn
other people's choreography
and then teach that.
But I know about formations
and I know about dancing.
I mean, I would say Rock.
I would actually say Rock.
I'll spearhead it
if you help edit me.
Okay.
Yeah, you could be
the dramaturge.
And then does anybody know
the style, like, Fosse?
Well, some of the iconic moments
come from the silhouettes
of the dancers.
Totally.
Like very clean, artistic poses.
It's all about
those formations, right?
Like what is it--
a Fosse amoeba or whatever,
when they, like--when you move,
like, across the stage,
like, all together,
but you're all, like,
doing different stuff?
Yeah.
It was so controlled
and amazing.
I mean, I think it's like cute
to make sure that that's there,
but at the end of the day,
like, we are doing
our own rendition of it.
We don't wanna, like,
purposely make anybody look bad,
you know what I mean?
I guess we need to decide, like,
do we really wanna
stick to the Fosse style
and make sure that
that is the thing
that we put at the forefront?
The last thing we wanna do is
come out like Broadway babies.
We wanna make sure, like,
everybody's comfortable.
What?
Of course it needs
to be a Fosse number.
Oh, my God.
This is a Fosse challenge.
Have I taken crazy pills?
Have I lost my mind?
No, you've lost your damn mind.
Oh, God.
[chatter]act 4
-I'm real excited.
-Oh, my God.
The time has come for us
to learn some choreography
for our main stage
Fosse-inspired number.
This is huge.
This is major, actually.
We have to choreograph
this number ourselves,
and this is day one.
We just met each other
three seconds ago.
Okay, I think
for the Fosse style,
we should start off,
like, silhouetted first.
Cute.
So very dynamic shapes
and levels.
I'm thinking high to low:
high levels, medium levels,
and then the two in the front
are gonna be low and high.
I want to make these bitches
look fierce.
I want whoever
the other girls are
to know that our group
is going to kick their asses.
Every time we do a new pose,
I think we should
change the levels.
So if you're low, go high.
So I feel like
that's gonna be a lot.
But it's only, like,
two or three.
Okay. Okay. Good.
Because
that just confused me.
I am very concerned, because I
know that learning choreography
is not my strongest suit.
So we don't have to really
produce a Broadway production,
because we don't have
that much time,
and sometimes
that can take years.
All right, hit your high poses.
Hit your medium poses.
Aiden, that looks too kung fu.
Go for Fosse.
Because you're like a crazy
Fosse character, so be like...
I am a horror queen,
not a Fosse queen.
Can we do
one of those Fosse blobs,
where we all huddle like this
and she has us
to work off of, like a shelf.
I don't get it.
I repeat. I'm not a dancer.
I'm thinking, like, we need
to incorporate this move,
and I'm wondering if we do this
to start out the first verse,
so it's... ♪ bah-bah-dun-dun ♪
♪ Dun-dun-dun-dun-dun ♪
Pose.
Okay, so that
is significantly easier
for everybody who is "high,"
not for somebody
who is down here.
That's what I was trying to say,
because I'm like, I don't want
nobody, like, struggling.
Let's try one more time and see.
Yeah, let's just
figure it out.
Because we need to get off
the beginning, yeah.
This is taking too long.
♪ We're running out of time ♪
Jaida feels like
we are wasting time
trying to do little details.
But at the same token,
we can't be basic bitches
doing a box step.
It has to be good.
Here, I have an idea.
So pose, melt, pose, pivot,
turn, walk to a spot,
and hit it.
-I like that.
-Okay, then let's do that.
Baby, we done wasted
a lot of time.
Stressful.
Yeah.
I'm getting a little frustrated
because it's really hard
to learn the choreography
when it's always changing.
Bitch, let's do this
and get it moving.
I have--
I have a really crazy idea.
Because
this is just the beginning.
-We gotta get this done.
-Okay.
I think we should just do
a good, old-fashioned
click, click, unh, unh.
And it's mean,
you're mad, you're angry.
Keep it simple and detailed.
That's what Fosse's all about.
Not about doing, like,
ooh, ah, ee, pblblbl.
That's what I've been saying.
I definitely feel like maybe
my opinions are not valued.
Oh!
-Let's--let's--
-From the beginning,
I said we should have did
something simple. Didn't listen.
Then now we stuck here.
The simplicity is now,
like, out of the window.
Like, it doesn't really matter
if it's simple
if people did not catch
where they should be
when they should be.
Do you not feel like
you know the transitions?
-Not really, no.
-Me, neither.
Dude, like, it's really
just walking and blocking.
If you're used to doing that,
then it's walking and blocking.
But if you're not used
to walking and blocking,
baby, it's gonna been--
But it would have been that
either way.
Either we would have had
all the time
and it would have been
walking and blocking--
But the thing that I'm saying
is if we walk and blocked
when we had time
to walk and block,
then people would have had time
to learn where we were walking
and blocking to.
But you're not really
contributing that much
to what we were trying to do.
From the beginning,
I said we do not need
to produce a Broadway show.
I said we need to make sure
it's nice and simple.
You saw that I had offered
advice several times.
I even said, like, hey,
is anybody listening to me?
You said simplify it,
but what does that mean?
I said simplify,
and I offered advice.
Girl, shut the fuck up.
Everybody stop arguing.
We're just going in circles.
It's making me
so fucking nervous,
I am like on the verge of tears
at this point.
Are we doing a last run or--
No, we're done.
We don't have time.
Well, all right.
All the time
has been spent arguing.
What are we going to do now?
We're all
just gonna stand around
and be like...
♪ You don't know me ♪
♪ Dah-dah-dah-dah ♪
♪ I don't have any choreo,
yeah ♪
So--
Oh, my goodness,
we're gonna fail this so hard.
I feel bad because I feel like
I'm responsible for this.
[whispers] Sorry, guys.
I was put in charge,
and I basically
sent everyone off a cliff.
Listen, we're all actors here.
Even if you don't claim
to be an actor,
you are an actor.
You're a drag queen.
So sell it,
even if you don't know
what you're doing.
It's time to buckle up
and get ready.
I do not know what's gonna
happen on the main stage
after this rehearsal.
Are you gonna complain about it
or are you gonna rise to
the occasion and figure it out?
Ooh, bitch.
Whoo!act 5
First time
there's boys in the
workroom.check
Our very first maxi-challenge
is to perform
in a Fosse-esque number
called You Don't Know Me.
And today, we have to perform it
in front of the judges.
It's all in the bag.
I don't know if the girls
are gonna be able to bounce back
from that rehearsal that we had,
but I believe in myself to be
able to deliver a performance.
I'm gonna be fine.
Last night I was really nervous,
but the thing about it is
is that I'm a professional,
and, bitch, I'm gonna
make it work and turn it out.
Is anybody nervous?
We didn't end too cute
on our rehearsal.
Staying up all night in my room,
every commercial that came on,
putting my headphones in.
I'm nervous for all of y'all
except me.
[all laugh]
Listen, as long as Jaida
doesn't scream at me anymore,
we'll be fine.
And I'm here for that, bitch.
-Aah!
-Okay.
[bleep] her highness.
[all laugh]Sis.check
I feel like I need
to let the whole room know
why I've been shutting down
a little bit.
I learned a lot about myself
during rehearsal.
I have a whole bunch
of triggers,
but I, like, kind of feel
kind of odd in leadership roles.
Yeah.
I never wanna be
put into a position
where I lead someone
to feeling bad.
A big thing
when I was growing up
was my mother
was addicted to meth.
And she was, like,
completely addicted to drugs.
She took me aside
a couple times,
and she would say, "I'm addicted
to drugs because of you."
"Because..." [sobs]
"Because of you, because
of you kids, I'm doing drugs."
And I didn't realize it
until yesterday
that I have these triggers.
When I feel responsible
for other people,
it kind of puts me in a...
it puts me in a dark place.
That always stuck with me,
because when you love someone
so much
and they tell you
that you're the reason
for their unhappiness,
it'll mess with you a bit.
Honestly,
you are not responsible
for anybody else's,
like, baggage.
Like, in life,
you are only responsible
for your own actions.
Like, what anybody else does
is not on you.
Remember to make sure you take
care of yourself first, always.
And, Rock,
you have us now, bitch.
This is new beginnings
for all of us.
If anything, yesterday I was
more offended by your farts.
Those are what you should
have apologized for,
but you did not, bitch.
There's more coming.
These girls are starting
to understand me
a little bit better
than I can understand myself,
and they really care for me,
even though we haven't
known each other for very long.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Get shorts that are a little bit
longer next time, okay?
And walk like this?
Oh, my God!
[screaming and laughter]
Girl!
She brought
her cookie-cutters, baby.
Oh, my God.
I'm so excited,
because my first number
that I did
in New York City in drag
was based around Chicago.
Oh, word.
And so I'm like
this is so serendipitous.
Like, all right, bitch, you're
in the right spot, let's do it!
[laughs]
See, you have, like,
so much character to you.
-You're so bubbly, and just--
-Thank you.
I like to think
that I'm just a cheerleader
on too many caffeine pills,
like the bitch
from Saved By the Bell
who's so excited.
Like, that's me.
I'm a little concerned right now
for Aiden
because Aiden was so in her head
in rehearsal about the dancing.
-Aiden.
-Yeah?
How art thou feeling?
I know you were, yesterday,
feeling like a little--
I was literally on the verge
of tears yesterday
at the end of rehearsal.
I hope that wasn't my fault.
It wasn't that it was
anybody's fault, exactly.
I know how you were feeling,
and I would never want you
to feel like that, so--
You have to shake all that off
and just leave everything
on the stage and just kill it.
We gonna go out there,
and we gonna be giving them
some Fosse realness.
Jaida: We had better.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
RuPaul: And what?
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage,
it's our second big opening.
I could smell it
from here. Yeah.
The hilarious Ross Mathews.
Now, are you
a song-and-dance man?
No, but I am a little light
in the loafers.
[all laugh]
Jazz hands.
Thandie Newton.
Darling, you made it.
I did.
My bucket list is complete...
once I get the chicken
out of it.
[all laugh]
The amazing Robyn
is here. Hello.
Hi. [speaking Swedish]
Wait. Squeeze me?
What does that mean?
Ru, it's just
"don't fuck it up."
[all laugh]
Good advice. I'll take it.
This week, for our
second season premiere,
we challenged our new queens
to introduce themselves
with an original song and dance,
You Don't Know Me.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
RuPaul: Curtains up,
light the lights.act 6
It's the world premiere
of You Don't Know Me.
♪ You think you know me,
but you don't know me ♪
♪ Everything that you heard
is wrong ♪
♪ You don't know me ♪
♪ Aiden Zhane,
oh, that's me ♪
♪ A little bit insane,
hmm, maybe ♪
♪ Crawling from the shadows
and into Technicolor ♪
♪ If you don't know me now,
you sure will later ♪
♪ Cute and sick ♪
♪ And that's
just the half of it ♪
♪ I've got
multiple personalities ♪
♪ Just imagine it ♪
Ooh...
Aah! Hi, boys.
I don't know you,
but you definitely know me.
I grew up
in a big city full of sin,
where everyone knows my name:
[whispers] Dahlia.
♪ I've won titles,
sold out venues ♪
♪ Took their money
and their guys ♪
♪ And now I'm here to claim
my rightful prize: the crown ♪
♪ You think you know me,
but you don't know me ♪
♪ Everything that you've heard
is wrong ♪
♪ You think you know me,
but you don't know me ♪
♪ I got my secrets in my bra ♪
♪ You don't know me ♪
♪ Yeah, it's Jaida,
the essence of beauty ♪
♪ The gowns, the face,
and tons of booty ♪
♪ But don't you be fooled
by the perfect facade ♪
♪ She always rises
despite the odds ♪
♪ She's funny, she's witty ♪
♪ She's got talent
beyond recognition ♪
♪ And that's how mother dear
will slay the competition ♪
♪ Marsha, Marsha, Marsha,
move over, sis, it's Jan ♪
♪ The girl next door
with so much more ♪
♪ There's no choice
but to stand ♪
♪ Work so hard to get here,
but I still want more ♪
♪ Push farther into mainstream
than any queen before ♪
♪ My stunning look,
this sickening hook ♪
♪ I can do everything ♪
♪ And did I mention you'll be
gagging when I start sing? ♪
♪ You think you know me,
but you don't know me ♪
♪ Everything that you've heard
is wrong ♪
♪ You think you know me,
but you don't know me ♪
♪ I got my secrets in my bra ♪
♪ They're in my bra ♪
♪ You don't know me ♪
♪ The name's
Rock M. Sakura, see? ♪
♪ Back in San Francisco, I'm
famous for a couple of things ♪
♪ Dipping down low, splitting
like there's no tomorrow ♪
♪ And so much white liner,
it masks my inability ♪
♪ To establish a deep,
personal connection ♪
♪ But most of all,
my dazzling 23-skidoo 'do ♪
♪ A high kick to a fart ♪
♪ That can send a grown man
back home to his mama ♪
♪ In a nice, little cab ♪
♪ Sweeter than Sherry ♪
♪ Hotter than a Pie, ouch ♪
♪ This campy queen
will serve it ♪
♪ Till you bust your gut
and cry ♪
♪ And I'm high-calorie ♪
♪ I'm full of fat ♪
♪ No, I'm not gluten-free,
eew ♪
♪ So open up, get ready
for a mother-tucking show ♪
♪ I'm fully baked and I'm ready
to feed you till you blow, oh ♪
♪ You think you know me,
but you don't know me ♪
♪ Everything that you've heard
is wrong ♪
♪ You think you know me,
but you don't know me ♪
♪ I got my secrets in my bra ♪
♪ They're in my bra ♪
♪ You don't know me ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Aah ♪
[cheers and applause]
Michelle: Amazing. Amazing.
RuPaul: Category is Tulle.
First up, Aiden Zhane.
Oh, my goodness,
I can see her tulle from here.
Michelle: I pity the tulle.
Aiden: I am serving you
a lime-green princess,
but as usual I'm still
very wicked in the face.
I feel like a badass.
Ross: Whose lime is it anyway?
Thandie: Kermit
is rolling in his grave.
[Ross laughs]
RuPaul: Dahlia Sin. Now,
her tulle is red and engorged.
[all laugh]
There's an ointment for that.
Dahlia: My look is very inspired
by the eighties.
It's very glam,
it's big, it's rocker.
That bitch
that walks on the runway,
its just like, damn,
I'm gonna go to
what I know best: sex.
Ross: Those boots are kinky.
Robyn: They are so kinky.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Jaida Essence Hall.
Michelle: Would you
pull that crap with Annette?
[all laugh]
Jaida: I'm ready
to show the judges
exactly how elegant I can be.
I feel like a big, yellow,
floaty cupcake
coming down the runway.
Light, airy, and I have
these sickening shoulders
to accentuate the whole look
and tie it together.
Ross: Butter?
I hardly know her.
Michelle: Very good, Ross.
Yell-err.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Jan. Simply Jan.
Ross:
Well, she wore her tulle-belt.
Thandie: She did doubles.
It's a double entendre.
Michelle: No,
it's a double en-tulle-dre.
Jan: I am bringing the T-O-O-L
to the T-U-L-L-E,
and I'm giving you
a fashion-forward silhouette.
I want to do things
that other people
aren't going to think of doing.
It's a win.
Ross: Oh.
Well, that throws
a wrench in my plan.
[laughs]
Ross: This is embarrassing,
but I can see her manhole.
Michelle: Oh, no!
RuPaul: Rock M. Sakura.
Oh, tulle's out for summer.
Michelle:
She's acting quite a-loofah.
Rock: They told me
to do a tulle runway,
I'm gonna do a tulle runway.
I'm wearing
800 to 900 yards of tulle.
I have dynamic silhouettes
and big ideas.
Michelle:
Welcome to the netting zoo.
Robyn: She's a fluffer.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Sherry Pie.
Michelle: Oh, no!
RuPaul: Somebody left Sherry Pie
in the rain.
Michelle: Aw.
Sherry: I'm just crying
my big bum down the runway.
I just feel like
a little cumulo-nimbus cutie.
It's campy, it's clever,
it's just kind of whimsical
in the best way.
Ross: Does she remind
anyone else of Stormy Daniels?
[all laugh]
This is what global warming
looks like.
Yeah.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Welcome, ladies.act 7
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques,
starting with Aiden Zhane.
Hi.
In the fashion show,
you were a sunflower.
It was very, very cute.
You managed to keep things
campy and fashion,
which is a difficult line
to balance.
And then your other look
was very Thanksgiving-y.
Yes.
The centerpiece of a table,
perhaps.
You had a very meaty tuck.
It could use some work.
-Do you know that already?
-Yes.
Listen, a little duct tape
will fix all those things.
[all laugh]
That dress is making my body
talk part one, two, and three.
[all laugh]
There's a kind of
Grey Gardens vibe.
I'm a little frightened,
but fascinated.
Right out the box
I was really impressed
with what I saw
in that performance.
It was very Sally Bowles.
It was a great, great lip sync.
Your lyrics say that
you have multiple personalities.
Well, honey, I cannot wait
to see who walks
around that corner next week.
Thank you.
Up next, Dahlia Sin.
In your fashion show,
you gave us the fabulous
neon green with the red hair.
That was a really great pairing.
I loved your
Sissy That Sasquatch fur number.
I thought that was so fun.
This red is so gorgeous on you.
I just wanna make sure that
you are painting loud enough.
Okay.
Remember,
nothing's subtle in drag.
Okay.
You've gotta pop
like you're Soju
in the first week.
[laughs]
Eew.
In your performance tonight,
you felt a little nervous to me.
I could feel a little bit
of holy shit.
-Mm-hmm.
-Did you grow up in Vegas?
Because in your lyrics, you said
"a big city with lots of sin."
Brooklyn.
[all laugh]
You've won titles?
What are those titles?
Mostly just, you know, being
on the train, being a whore.
Those are more my titles.
-Uh-huh.
-That's it.
So what I'm saying is I
didn't get to know much of you,
and I'd like to get to know you
a little bit more.
-I got you.
-Okay.
Up next, Jaida Essence Hall.
Any relationship to Arsenio?
Not yet.
[all laugh]
Yes, it's Jaida,
the essence of beauty,
the gowns, the face,
and all that booty.
Those lyrics were spot-on.
Like, I learned
so much about you.
What I felt when I watched you
lip sync was your playfulness.
You have that way of moving
that feels very, very natural.
It made me really happy.
It made me smile.
Thank you.
In the fashion show,
I specifically loved
the Fall look.
I thought that
was super-duper chic.
But at the end of the day,
the confidence
would have sold any garment.
-Thank you.
-Mmm.
What a delight.
Just beautiful.
You remind me of
a Bollywood princess, and...
Ooh.
And Josephine Baker
all combined.
-Thank you.
-I love the tone of that yellow,
and I love that you chose
the pink nails with it,
because it looks like
you'd wear it
to the gayest Easter ever.
[all laugh]
Thank you.
Up next, simply Jan.
Just Jan.
This tulle look
was really smart,
because you knew
that everybody was gonna come
in these frou-frou
Vera Wang numbers,
and it was smart
to do something different.
It was smart
to pull out the tool.
You have a lot of skills
in your tulle-belt.
[all laugh]
You've got frigging
traffic cone earrings.
-I mean, come on.
-Ooh. [laughs]
You're a feast.
I just really, really wanna
pay attention to the details.
This is my favorite show.
I listen to the critiques,
and I wanna apply them to myself
every time I step on the runway.
And it needs to be different
every single time.
And you did all of that
the first time we saw you.
Yeah.
When you were out
doing the lip sync number,
I felt Demi Moore
in the height of her heyday,
this ambition.
Even in your lyrics, you say,
"push further into mainstream
than any queen before."
Hmm. I have a little issue
with that.
[all laugh]
You have a lot
on your to-do list.
I do.
-One thing at a time.
-Yes.
-Show us who you are.
-But don't try to do too much.
-Yes, thank you.
Up next, Rock M. Sakura.
Hi, hi.
Let's talk about
your fashion runway looks.
The first one, you came out with
the anime-loving Spring look.
I drew the illustration
that was on the side.
-Oh, you drew them?
-Yes.
It's anime on acid.
It's amazing.
Your performance
was very interesting,
because you did
kind of 1920s, see,
and then you went into scat
and... fart humor, yeah?
Yeah.
-Because is that--
-Yeah, that's part of me.
At least, like, 10 times
in the workroom, I've farted.
These poor ladies had
to keep reapplying their makeup.
It kept melting off.
You said,
"A high kick to a fart
that can send a grown man
back home to his mama."
That's right.
That's always the sign for me
of someone who has something
important to say.
It's true, yeah.
[all laugh]
This look tonight,
you sort of remind me
of any guy who goes on a date
with Michelle Visage:
you are getting swallowed.
[all laugh]
Can't even argue that.
It's a lot.
I would love to just edit
everything down just a skosh.
I love this outfit.
I love how huge
and ostentatious it is,
and the same with your makeup.
It's performance art, it's not
trying to just be beautiful.
So you go for it.
All right, up next, cut me
a piece of that Sherry Pie.
I love a queen
that can make me laugh,
and your lyrics
made me laugh right away.
POV, OMG, and LOL.
[all laugh]
If Meryl Streep could be
a drag queen, it would be you.
It would.
There's something there.
In the fashion show,
the first look was lovely.
You know, it wasn't dynamic,
but it was beautiful.
Then she turned around and
came out as Zorro the Gay Blade.
[all laugh]
I loved everything about it.
It told us a little bit more
of who you are.
Your dress is amazing, because
it does something when you move
that is really pleasant
to look at. Yeah.
[all laugh]
Thank you.
Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
Now, while you untuck backstage,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right, now just between
us squirrel friends,
what do you think?
Aiden Zhane.
I think Aiden knows
that she is different,
and that that's a cool thing.
The lip sync was great,
but it was also
how she was telling the story.
It was almost
listening to, like,
a children's book
being read or something.
She defines originality.
Ross: Aiden is a natural.
Watch out for her.
She is so memorable.
She's got something,
and it's important for her
to fine-tune whatever it is
that is.
Mm-hmm.
Dahlia Sin.
This is a beautiful girl
who knows how to walk a runway
and who knows how to put
a look together as well.
Dahlia is beautiful,
Dahlia is sexy,
but Dahlia tries to be sexy.
Because I'm not 100% sure
Dahlia knows who she is yet.
Mm-hmm.
I feel like
she's limiting herself
to just thinking
about the aesthetics.
-Mm-hmm.
-And I think that sometimes,
when you're kind of hemmed in
by what your aesthetic value is,
you know, looking gorgeous,
it makes you a little stiff.
RuPaul: Jaida Essence Hall.
Jaida Essence Hall
Pinkett Smith.
[laughs] Zeta Jones.
Zeta Jones.
She is just
so much fun to watch.
She makes me feel like
I want to also get up and dance,
which is very special.
I was a little concerned,
because Jaida has so much poise
that she wouldn't
be able to let go
and kind of get dirty
and have fun.
But that lip sync
showed me she was down.
Jan.
Ooh, Jan wants to win.
I think Jan wants my seat.
-Yes, she does.
-I think you're right.
Jan pulled out all the stops
to say, I can do this,
I can do this, I can do--
It was like her résumé,
which I can't blame her for.
I actually kind of loved
that she did all that.
She was a wonderful performer,
and hitting
that great high note.
The positive energy
was so apparent, strong,
and then also a lot.
A lot at the same time.
-[laughs]
-Yeah.
She's got so many things
going around in her head
that maybe she's not
being present enough
to focus on
what's happening right now.
Rock M. Sakura.
I loved Rock M.'s spring look,
especially when I found out
that she drew it herself.
That, to me, took it
to this whole other level
of, okay, this girl's
got something to say.
Her performance was good.
Um... Fart humor
makes everybody laugh.
I just don't know
if it was the first thing
she should come out with.
Tonight on the runway,
I actually liked that
tulle dress that she had on.
It's a very smartly
constructed outfit,
because she did have a waist.
Michelle, I have to disagree
with you. I just--
Her whole body was shaped out.
What you talking about, Ross?
This is the challenge
where you're supposed
to show us who you are.
I couldn't even see her,
let alone Sherry Pie
standing behind her.
[laughs]
Sherry Pie.
I live for this kind of queen.
I mean, this is
the kind of queen
where you're using the urinal
and you look up,
and there's a flyer
for her face up on the wall,
and you go, "Oh, hey,
what are you doing tomorrow?
She's performing." I mean--
Wait, who are you
talking to at the urinal?
Who am I not talking to
at the urinal?
That's the easier question.
Her performance
was so fantastic.
Every little nuance that
she could throw in, she did.
Uh-huh.
She's so excited
by what she does.
There's a delightedness
in her eyes, and a sparkle.
I'm really excited
to see what comes next.
All right, silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
RuPaul: Welcome back, ladies.act
I've made some decisions.
Jan, you're a sharp tool,
and, girl, you can belt.
-You're safe.
-Thank you.
Aiden Zhane.
You have multiple personalities,
and tonight,
all of them are safe.
Rock M. Sakura.
Your heart's in the right place,
but you could have left
your fart in San Francisco.
You're safe.
Thank you so much. [sobs]
Dahlia Sin.
Beauty is only skin deep.
We want you to go deeper.
You...
are safe.
You may join the other girls.
Thank you.
I'm confused.
How did we end up in the bottom?
Jaida Essence Hall,
Sherry Pie.
I'm not sorry, my dears.
Because you are
the top two queens of the week.
[laughter and applause]
Come on, yellow.
Oh, my God.
Nobody is going home this week.
[cheering]
Yes!
I'm like, yes!
I'm so excited.
But--and it's a big but--
[all laugh]
There will be one winner.
Two queens stand before me.
Prior to tonight,
you were asked to prepare
a lip sync performance
of Call Your
Squirrel Friend--
I mean, Girlfriend, by Robyn.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and win a cash prize of $5.000.
-Mm.
-Ooh!
-Oh, my God.
-Make it rain.
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing] for your life!
Sherry, girl, you cute,
but, bitch,
I'm gonna get this money.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
[music plays]
♪ Call your girlfriend ♪
♪ It's time you had the talk ♪
♪ Give your reasons ♪
♪ Say it's not her fault ♪
♪ But you just met
somebody new ♪
♪ Tell her
not to get obsessed ♪
♪ Second-guessing everything
you've said and done ♪
♪ And then
when she gets upset ♪
♪ Tell her how you never meant
to hurt no one ♪
♪ And you tell her the only way
her heart will mend ♪
♪ Is when she learns
to love again ♪
♪ And it won't make sense
right now ♪
♪ But you're still her friend ♪
♪ And then
you let her down easy ♪
Oh. Oh.
♪ Call your girlfriend ♪
[cheers and applause]
♪ It's time you had the talk ♪
♪ Give your reasons ♪
♪ Say it's not her fault ♪
♪ But you just met
somebody new ♪
Whoo-hoo!
♪ And now
it's gonna be me and you ♪
♪ Call ♪
♪ Call your girlfriend ♪
♪ It's time you had the talk ♪
♪ Give your reasons ♪
♪ Say it's not her fault ♪
♪ But you just met
somebody new ♪
[cheers and applause]
Yes! Yes!
Oh, my goodness,
that was fantastic.
I'm sure Robyn
is very proud right now.
I'm so glad. Thank you.
RuPaul: Well done.
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Jaida Essence Hall...
you're a winner, baby.
Oh, my gosh!
[cheers and applause]
Yes!
Shantay you slay.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
RuPaul: Con-drag-ulations.
You've won a cash tip of $5.000.
[tongue pop]
I feel, like,
$5.000 heavier right now.
I'm, like, so excited.
Oh, thank you.
Sherry Pie, you're safe
to slay another day.
[deep voice] Yeah!
Con-drag-ulations, ladies.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
And speaking of somebody else...
I think the time has come
for you to meet...
your competition.
Oh!
Here they are,
the other group of girls.
It's like a clash
of the titans, bitch.
Same, same, same, same,
camp, camp, same.
Next.
[yawns]
I am 100% getting a vibe
that the girls
in the other group
think that
they're better than us,
and that's really cute.
But cute next to gorgeous,
gorgeous is gonna,
you know, devour cute.
-Meh.
Uh-oh.
Did these bitches just "meh" me?
I don't know
who these queens are,
but I'm ready to show them
what I'm made of.
There's too many bitches
in the workroom.
We gonna send them home
like dominoes:
one after the other.
RuPaul: Next time,
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
So far, you've all been safe
from elimination.
That's about to change.
You'll be improv-ing a show we
like to call the World's Worst.
We are...
All: The Fruity-Patooties.
You're broccoli,
but you're in the fruity group?
I'm a fierce Brocc-ella.
I loved what you did
on the runway.
I would love if you could merge
your beautiful art that you do
with your face.
[all gasp]
We were carrying you.
These girls, some of them
are a little bit fake.
Us bitches are about to
start going home one by one.
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪
♪ Am-Am-Am-Am-American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪