RuPaul: Previously
on RuPaul's Drag
Race...disclaimer first
You need to overact
in Gay's Anatomy.
-Aah!
-[laughs]
[deep voice]
Get this baby outta me!
I'm about to shove my baby egg
in your--sorry.
Heidi N Closet.
I almost feel like I'm looking
at two different outfits.
Nicky Doll.
I just wanted you to do more
with this super funny drag baby.
Heidi, shantay you stay.
Nicky Doll, sashay away.mirror?
Oh, my God, girl.
Jeez Louise.
Oh, Nicky.
Watch out, because I don't plan
on lip syncing no more.
[all laugh]
Don't put me in the bottom
no more!
I had been doing so well
up until this point,
and then bang, oh!
It was like taking me
from 100 to a 10 real fast.
But I think I showed everyone
just what I'm made of,
and I'm ready to send
all them home if I need to.
Brita, how did you feel
about being towards the bottom?
I was shook, honestly.
I don't know why
I was in the bottom.
And I don't know why,
honestly,
why my scene partner
wasn't in the bottom with me.
Again?
We're doing this again?
Why does she get a free escape
when all of our stuff
was together?
All we can do
is try to bring what the judges
are asking from us specifically.
Just because Brita views herself
as a strong competitor
and is upset that
she is in the bottom this week,
she feels like somehow
that's my fault.
Look, we all were great
in this challenge.
There is no mother-freaking
excuses anymore.
So you better
be on your Ps and Qs, bitch.
This is not
RuPaul's Excuse Race, bitch.
Let's go.
Let's get out of drag.
How you feeling, boo-boo?
It's just been a buildup
from the moment we got here.
Oh, I understand.
Yeah, I understand.
I don't wanna have to continue
going through this competition
in those moments feeling good
about myself,
just to have other people,
like, tearing me down.
These bitches have been
coming for me from day one.
Honestly, I'm not here for it,
so quiet Aiden isn't gonna
be quiet for much longer.
At the end of the day,
it is what it is.
All we can do is fucking slay.
There's 10 girls left
in this competition.
It's time to step up my game,
because I am not satisfied
with just being safe now.
If you're accepting
any less than the top,
then you might as well
get packing.
Whoo!
RuPaul: The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
and a cash prize of $100.000.
With extra-special
guest judges
the stars of Mean Girls,
Daniel Franzese
and Jonathan Bennett.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪shoes???
Another day to see the light.
We're on Drag Race!
How fun!
It's a new day in the werkroom.
I haven't won a challenge yet.
Just Jan has been just safe.
So I'm ready to slay
whatever's coming my way.
Hello, hello, hello!
[cheering]
All right, suit.
Yeah, the Emerald City
has arrived.
Now, ladies, for this week's
maxi-challenge...
We're playing the Snatch Game.
[cheering]
Pick a celebrity
that you can impersonate,
then make me
and the world laugh.
RuPaul Charles
done shuck up the building.
It's the motherfucking
Snatch Game.
I'm excited!
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win!
[applause]
Yes!
Let's get snatched.
I wanna know
who everyone's doing.
The Snatch Game
shows the drag queens
at their celeb
impersonation best...
or not so best.
Brita, what are you
thinking of doing?
Jennifer Holliday.
Jaida, what about you?
I'm doing Cardi B.
-Aow!
-Oh, shut up.
Yes, so, okurr?
I'm doing...
Widow, who are you doing?
You can't tell by the hair?
-It looks like Tinta Turntur.
-Thank you.
Someone's cultured
in this bitch.
I'm thinking of doing
Ike and Tina.
Widow's doing Tina Turner,
but then halfway through
she wants to do Ike Turner.
But I don't know
if that's a good idea.
Like, eww.
It seems like
a very sticky situation.
Luckily, I did good
in the last improv,
so hopefully I can continue
my improv career.
Yeah, I was in the top group
that week,
but as my sisters in that group
liked to say,
they "carried me through," so...
Yeah, they did say that,
didn't they?
Aiden?
I am doing Patricia Quinn.
Who's that?
She played Magenta in
The Rocky Horror Picture Show.
Oh.
She's like an old,
kooky woman now, so--
Are you playing the old her
or the new her?
The more current old her, yeah.
She's somebody
that I've met personally
and I've had lunch with.
Oh, okay, cute.
I hang out with my mom.
It doesn't mean she's funny.
Good luck, bitch,
because she doesn't have
any scene partners in this one.
Our maxi-challenge today
is the Snatch Game.
I'm super excited
and a little terrified.
America is judging you
during Snatch Game.
Hey, stars!
-Hey!
We've got company.
-Ooh!
-Uh-oh!
Bam, bitch! Yeah!
[cheers and applause]
Aah! Vanjie is here!
I am so excited to see her.
Vanjie!
-Vanjie!
She has the iconic Miss Vanjie.
-Miss Vanjie.
-Vanjie.
I'm not a regular there.
I'm cool.
Thank you, Miss Vanjie.
I thanked myself.
She's one of the most popular
people from this competition.
Vanjie and I are here
to school you
on the dos and don'ts
of winning Snatch Game.
Y'all know I'm here
for the don'ts.
[all laugh]
My Snatch Game was...
[whistles, laughs]
What's up, Dr. Phil?
Oh, shit, I'm sorry.
I mean, Ru.
So I'm here to let
the chickenheads know
what not to do for Snatch Game.
That's what we're doing today.
Come on, Vanjie.
I want you to meet Heidi.
-Hi!
-Hi, Heidi.
-How are you doing?
-Good, and you?
I'm doing blessed
and highly favored.
That's right, mm.
[laughs]
See, now, that's funny.
Are you in character right now?
That was Heidi, but, no,
I got Leslie Jones on the back,
and she's about
to come out here, so, yeah.
Oh! Now, Heidi,
you're very charismatic.
How are you gonna infuse that
into Leslie Jones?
Leslie Jones, her comedy
is very loud, in your face,
and very thirsty with her skits.
So I can really
tap into that real well,
so I'm going there.
Why did you choose someone
who's got a Southern accent
who's very close
to your personality?
You know, all you bitches
come in here,
and you think
you're Meryl Streep.
[laughs]
Why not stay
a little bit close to home?
That way, you don't
have to work so hard.
I feel like you could
definitely give me
one of the Housewives
of Atlanta.
-Phaedra.
-Oh, Phaedra.
She sounds like her,
doesn't she?
Yes, you give me
a lot of Phaedra.
You know, that's what
I'm getting, the vibe.
Atlanta Housewives, Phaedra.
That's somebody who I feel that
she could execute naturally.
Ooh, that's big. "Execute."
Child, I almost choked
saying that one.
Just start tapping into whatever
you naturally can do,
you know what I'm saying?
Because you already
naturally funny.
Bitch, you got acrylics, too?
These are my real nails.
What are you talk--acrylics?
[both laugh]
-Aah! Let me see them.
-She needs to feel it right now.
Them is sophisticated.
Yeah, don't do these ones.
Don't talk me
into feeling things.
You see how
you just responded there?
You see that volley
that you just did?
That's what Snatch Game is.
But if you have to think
too hard
of did Leslie Jones do that,
that will make you stumble.
I don't know who Miss Phaedra
is personally, and...
I think I'm gonna stick
with Miss Leslie Jones.
That's it, all right.
Aah! She definitely
snatched you bald on that one.
All right, make me laugh.
-Awesome sauce.
-All right.
Come on, Vanjie.
[laughs]
Vanjie, I wanna introduce you
to Simply Jan.
I see a little Tony.
Yeah, she's won a Tony.
You're getting warm.
Lindsay Lohan.
Oh, I know.
Bernadette Peters.
[imitates Bernadette Peters]
That's correct, Ru.
[laughs]
Musical theater is something
that I grew up with,
so I love her.
I know in your audition reel
you did Kris Jenner.
That was my music video.
I did Call Me Mother
for my tape as Kris Jenner,
walking around
my uncle's house, doing it.
That was pretty phenomenal.
I actually started doing drag
as Kris Jenner.
I was not even going by Jan.
I was just going by my boy name
"as Kris Jenner."
-Really?
-Yeah.
So you're doing Kris Jenner
today, then.
-Basically the fucking story.
-No, no.
I feel more comfortable being
able to riff as Bernadette.
I know her voice is
kind of like a babydoll voice.
[normal] Mm-hmm.
[Bernadette] Hi, how are you?
Are you having a good day today?
I'll tell you this because
I'm gonna tell you the don'ts.
Don't be switching your voice
halfway through.
I started with a voice,
and I was like that--
you know,
by the second question,
I said, "That has to go."
So don't be switching
your voice.
-That would be a don't.
-Do not.
Well, we will see you out there.
-Yes, see you out there.
-Come on, Vanjie.
Do it. Go on now.
Vanjie, meet El DeBarge.
No, I mean Not El DeBarge.
This is Crystal Methyd.
-Hi, Vanjie.
-Hi.
So I see a blonde wig, I see
a pink, furry something there.
I was gonna be the pop superstar
android Poppy.
Who?
So she is a robot
or not a robot?
She's a real person
playing a robot.
She's got a robot persona.
Well, that sounds like
a laugh riot.
If I were you, I would do
motherfucking El DeBarge.
Fuck. Hello!
Well, I mean, you need a brick
to fall on your head?
Ru doesn't seem to know
who Poppy is.
I really just don't wanna
make a fool of myself
during this challenge.
I'm a little nervous.
I never do characters,
and I thought it'd be something
easy to do.
But I'm a little worried that
it's not gonna help me stand out
and really show myself.
Yeah. Well, whatever you do,
make sure you stuff your
character full of behavior.
And preferably something
that can volley with me.
You know, I throw you a ball,
you go, oh, yeah,
motherfucker.
And, uh, bop.
I just--I'm putting
all this pressure on myself
because I know I didn't do good
in the improv challenge,
and this is so similar.
You know, I, like...
It's, like, really,
um, frustrating
that I've been
in the bottom, and...
Uh. And...
I just really wanna bring it
this challenge.
Okay, but I can tell you're
very sensitive right now.
-Yeah.
-Do you want a hug?
-Yeah?
-Okay.
Now, don't cry on my suit, okay?
[all laugh]
I really wanna do good
in the Snatch Game.
I know I have what it takes,
and I know what's inside of me,
but I just have so much
self-doubt in me right now,
and I...
I don't know
how to get over it.
Whew.
What got you here
in the first place
is what you already have.
You have to remember
who the fuck you are.
You're freaky, you're fun.
You are
El motherfucking DeBarge.
[all laugh]
You just gotta pop.
Is there anything else
I need to tell you?
Um... "You're the winner
of this week's challenge."
[all laugh]
See, now, that's how you volley.
-Do that, okay?
-Okay.
Seeing Crystal, I could totally
relate to how she's feeling.
I just hope that
she could shake this off
and, girl, press reset.
We'll see you out there.
Jackie Cox.
Salaam, RuPaul.
You are cute!
-Oh!
-Uh-huh.
You know, I'm known
for going into the werkroom
and walking out with a piece.
-[laughs]
-I ain't no sugar mama,
but I could give you a Lunchable
or something, you know.
Go ahead, don't be jealous.
Don't be mad.
The peanut gallery.
Now what you wanted to ask me?
Yes, I'm single.
Well, you know,
I am a taken man back home,
but we're, you know,
always down to make friends.
Next! Who out there--
who's single?
All right,
I see a little wig here.
Are you doing Ruth Buzzi?
Well, let's take another look.
-She's a housewife?
-She's a housewife.
-Oh, Lisa Rinna.
-There she is.
She's always trying
to sell herself,
and if it's not her, then
it's her husband Harry Hamlin,
who she will name-drop
at the drop of a hat.
Well, I mean,
on paper it sounds great.
What were your other choices?
Dame Julie Andrews.
Oh, I love her!
-I love her, too.
-Yeah.
But I mean, this wig,
I would probably do a little bit
more of a reddish.
I love Julia Roberts.
One of my favorite movies
is Pretty Woman, so...
Well, darling, I cannot wait
to see your Julia Roberts.
[laughs]
Make me laugh as Julia Roberts.
And what about Julie Andrews?
Thank you. I love Julia.
Oh, okay, bye.
I don't know. Well...
Well, Gigi Goode.
Good morning, Miss Paul.
Do you have any guesses, Vanjie?
She bald-headed.
There is this very famous robot
who she's been on
a number of talk shows,
she's famous for being
the first robot U.S. citizen.
This is a real person?
-Wait. No, it's a robot.
-She's a literal robot.
But how do you
make a robot funny?
The references
that I'm going to make
are more along the lines
of mechanics and science
and stuff like that, which
sounds so incredibly boring.
Yeah, it does.
However,
I have never seen someone
with a drier sense of humor
than a robot.
Yeah. May not work
with Snatch Game.
-You understand my concern.
-Absolutely.
Because a robot
doesn't really volley.
It's a lot
of rapid-fire stuff,
and I'm thinking that's
gonna be very difficult.
I understand your concern,
but I do not have
the same concern.
Okay, all right.
Well, you have
a lot to think about.
I do.
But mainly, make me laugh.
I'm going to.
The biggest personality
won the Snatch Game: Silky.
She was TS Madison.
She was doing the most.
And trust me, these bitches
gonna be big and loud.
Yeah.
All right,
we will see you out there.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
-Bye. Come on, Vanjie.
-See you later.
I feel like Gigi is taking
probably the biggest risk
so far in this challenge,
because Ru wasn't really
understanding the character.
So good luck to her.
All right, ladies, gather round.
Gather round, ladies.
So, Vanjie, do you have
any final words of encouragement
for my girls?
Mm-hmm,
just one simple thing.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up, bitch.
[laughter and applause]
Turn it out, bitches.
If not, catch me outside,
how 'bout dat?
Oof, the prime example
of what not to do.
Bye!
Welcome to Snatch Game!
Let's meet our contestants.
He was Damian in Mean Girls,
the legendary father
of the house of Glen Coco,
Daniel Franzese.
It's all for you, Ru Coco.
You go, Ru Coco.
Our next guest played the role
of Aaron Samuels
in Mean Girls.
Welcome, Jonathan Bennett.
Jonathan,
did anyone ever tell you
that you look sexy
with your hair pushed back?
That's not the only thing
that's pushed back, Ru.
Ooh!
[all laugh]
All right, contestants,
let's meet our stars.
First up,
from Saturday Night Live,
the hilarious Leslie Jones.
I'm back, Ru!
I just got the girls done.
Blacker the berry,
sweeter the juice.
I thought it was
"darker the berry."
What berries are black?
Blackberries.
[all laugh]
From the Real Housewives
of Beverly Hills, Lisa Rinna.
Hello, Ru. I just flew in.
I was busy selling my new line:
adult diaper swimsuits.
Hello!
-I needed one of those!
-Oh, they are perfect.
You're on the beach,
and you can have a piddle
and a puddle, honey.
Owning it!
[all laugh]
Up next, Grammy award-winning
rapper Cardi B is here.
Hey, y'all. Hey.
Ooh, and I see you're
featuring the girls there.
Ooh, always.
Now, what was
the first purchase you made
when you started
making all that money?
I got these
motherfucking teeth fixed.
[all laugh]
Which set?
The bottom ones.
Up next, we've got
a Broadway legend.
Bernadette Peters is here.
Now, of all your roles,
which one is your favorite?
My favorite is the one
that I won this bad boy for:
Annie Get Your Gun.
You were fantastic in that.
Thank you.
I starred
in off-Broadway production
of Annie Get Your Cum.
There's no business
like show business,
so let's send in the clowns!
Wait. They're already here.
Yeah.
[all laugh]
Up next, simply the best,
Tinta Turnter is in the house.
-Hey, Tina.
-How you doing, Ru?
Oh, you look fantastic.
What does love
have to do with it, Tina?
When you find out what's love
got to do with it...
-Uh-huh.
-I'll let you know.
[laughs]
This is salty Tina.
Now let's move on down here
to Maria the robot.
Hi, Maria.
What's up, bitch?
Ooh!
[all laugh]
So Maria, getting to the studio
today, do you drive yourself?
I'm so sorry. I'm unable
to receive that information.
I wonder if you can receive
a big black cock.
Oh, yes. Let me tell you,
I've got quite
the USB port for it.
[all laugh]
Up next, she played Magenta
in The Rocky Horror
Picture Show.
Loved that movie.
Patricia Quinn is here!
Are you ready to do
the Time Warp again?
I have no idea what
you're talking about, Ru.
Really?
Whatever happened to you?
Did you make other films?
I don't remember a damn thing.
You don't remember anything.
If you had done
as many drugs as I did
while filming
The Rocky Horror Picture Show,
you wouldn't remember
shit either.
Sis.
All right, up next,
the original Effie from
Dreamgirls, Jennifer Holliday.
Hi, Jennifer Holliday!
It's a beautiful day, because
it's a Jennifer Holliday.
-[laughs]
-I'm curious.
Are you still able
to hit all those notes?
Yes, I have a very--
a signature sound.
Okay.
Up next, she's a YouTube
sensation: Poppy.
What's new, Poppy?
Oh, just working on new music.
I'm really into death metal
right now.
Hmm?
Were you always
into death metal?
No, I started with pop music,
but they make me listen
to death metal now.
Who makes you listen
to death metal?
They, my cult.
Your cult? Oh, my goodness.
Hmm?
Moving on down,
she's won four Academy Awards.
Katharine Hepburn is here.
-Now, Miss Hepburn.
-Mm, yes?
I've always wanted to ask you,
if you could be any kind
of a tree--
Yes?
What tree would you be?
This question has popped up
so many times.
[all laugh]
Yes.
Yes, I think I would be...
mm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm-
mm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm--
an oak.
[all laugh]
All right, who's ready
to play Snatch Game?
The time has come
for you to snatch
for your life, people.
Welcome back to Snatch Game.
Daniel and Jonathan,
here's how the game works.
I ask a question
and you give an answer
that you think will match
our celebrity contestants.
Okay, here we go.
First question is for Daniel.
Mean Girls' Regina George
is so mean,
when you type her name
into your phone,
it autocorrects to blank.
Ducking fitch.
Stop trying to make fitch
happen.
It's not gonna happen.
[all laugh]
All right, let's go
to our celebrities.
-Lisa Rinna.
-Ah, hello, Ru.
I was talking about
Cardi B earlier,
and I remembered
I am wearing a cardi-gan.
This is my Lisa Rinna duster.
So, you know, I love an outfit
that is coming and going.
And speaking of people that
I hate to autocorrect to,
the other Lisa,
my arch-nemesis--
I can't stand her--
it is Lisa Vanderpump.
She has pulled me
into so many of her schemes,
and I'm out,
I'm out, I'm out.
Not a match.
Oh, is it time
to take your vitamins?
Oh, yeah, uh-huh.
Do you ever take
Harry's vitamin D?
I take Harry Hamlin's
big vitamin D.
He went right up
in my Melrose Place.
You know what I'm saying?
Absolutely.
Have you met Harry Hamlin?
My husband, Harry Hamlin.
Yeah, from
Clash of the Titans.
My husband, Harry Hamlin.
Let's move on down
to Maria the robot.
Maria, we are looking
for "ducking fitch."
What say you?
Shit.
Oh, God, fucking hands.
So lifelike. Just like us.
Gigi's physical comedy
is hilarious.
Watching her
try to pick up her cards:
comedy gold.
I said "vageena."
Yeah, I think she meant
"vagina."
I meant what I said.
[all laugh]
Actually, I went to high school
with a girl named Vageena.
She was a little saucy.
I'm just loving watching
her pick up-- [laughs]
Maria, stop.
You trying to control me?
[all laugh]
How very dare you.
Let's go on down to Poppy.
What did you write?
I thought Regina George
was a meanie.
All right, we're looking
for "ducking fitch," Poppy.
I've never heard of that.
Great title for a song.
I'd love to hear you sing it
right now.
They don't let me release
my music without permission.
Well, I think we're giving you
permission right now, Poppy.
-They.
-[laughs]
-Gotcha.
Ru is giving her bones.
He's, like,
trying to clue her in.
Bitch, I would have been, like,
♪ I'm motherfucking Poppy ♪
or something.
Let's go on
to Jennifer Holliday.
Mean Girls Regina George
is so mean,
when you type her name
into your phone,
it autocorrects to what?
And I'm telling you,
Jennifer Hudson.
Are you friends
with Jennifer Hudson?
Who?
Jennifer Hudson.
-Who?
-Jennifer Hudson.
[laughs]
No.
I guess that answers that.
I hope Brita has a little
more for Jennifer Holliday
than just the... [braying].
Let's move on down to the great
Miss Katharine Hepburn.
Well, Ru, I think
the answer is obvious.
What does that say?
Ducking fitch.
[all laugh]
That is a match.
[applause]
Okay. Next question
for Jonathan Bennett.
Michelle Visage is a cool mom.
When her daughters' friends
come over,
she doesn't serve ice cream,
she serves blank.
Freshly brewed teabags.
-Not the tea.
-No, teabags.
The teabags.
She's serving
freshly brewed teabags.
Tea. bop. Yep, there you go.
What say you,
Patricia Quinn?
Well, you know,
I still have no clue
what the hell's
going on here, but--
Okay.
I put "a blunt."
Because if I had
one of these right now,
I might remember
where the hell I'm at.
Aiden isn't referencing anything
from Rocky Horror,
and none of this is landing.
I don't think anyone
is laughing.
I hear crickets.
Let's go on over to Leslie.
Oh, your hair is different,
Leslie.
Yes, I had to let
the civil rights hair out, Ru.
-Oh.
-Real tight in there.
I'm not gonna lie, young man.
This ain't a match.
But last time I was here,
I saw Widow's ugly-ass shoe,
and I told her not to wear
this ugly-ass shoe no more.
This is hideous.
Just throw it in the trash.
It's one inch away
from being a flat.
Well, not a match.
I'm trying
to be your match, baby.
All right,
let's move on down to Cardi B.
Now, Michelle Visage
is a cool mom.
When her daughters' friends
come over,
she doesn't serve ice cream,
she serves what?
Ass.
[all laugh]
Okurrr?
I always wave this ass.
-[laughs]
-Oh, okay.
Took me from stripper poles
to selling multiplatinum albums.
That's true, very true.
What say you, Bernadette?
She serves them green, green,
nothing but green.
Parsley, peppers, cabbages,
arugula, all of that.
-Not a match. Sorry about that.
-Not a match.
Into the Woods
does not match Mean Girls.
Into the woods, around the dell,
behind the bar at Mickey's,
I know it well.
[all laugh]
Yes.
It looks like Ike Turner
has joined us.
Hi, Ike.
Tina was here earlier.
Now Ike is here.
It's Ike and Tina,
Ike and Tina.
What say you, Ike?
She serves them a good old cake.
-Cake.
-You wanna eat the cake?
[all laugh]
You wanna eat the cake?
Oh, she's gonna eat it.
I mean, damn,
this is good cake.
Not a match.
All right, let's move on down
to Jennifer Holliday.
Michelle Visage doesn't serve
ice cream, she serves...
I said "loose jaw."
-[laughs]
-Loose jaw.
-Yaaaaah.
-Huh. Loose jaw.
Well, it takes one
to know one, huh?
All right.
Oh, God.
Jennifer Holliday
is really
just a loud version of Brita.
Okay, now, Jonathan,
this is a question
that is perfect for you.
Oh, good.
Ross Mathews does not
understand the rules
of his gay softball team.
Instead of hitting the ball,
he blanks it.
I think Ross Mathews
would swallow it.
-Swallow the ball.
All right, celebrities.
What say you, Lisa?
Oh, my. First of all, Jonathan,
you are very handsome.
Not as handsome
as my husband Harry Hamlin.
Harry Hamlin, I love you, baby.
Yeah, from L.A. Law.
Harry Hamlin.
-Have you met my husband?
-Say it one more time.
Harry Hamlin.
Don't talk about my husband!
I love Harry Hamlin.
Yes. [laughs]
What say you, Lisa?
I gotta say "owns it."
Own it, baby!
Own it! Own it!
Jackie is cracking me up.
Own it, baby!
My husband is Terry Hamilton
or something.
[laughs]
Let's move on down
to Maria the robot.
Do you know Siri and Alexa?
One second. Searching.
Okay, here's what I've found.
She's my sister, bitch.
[all laugh]
I said he "pegs the ball."
Pegs the ball.
I just learned what pegging is.
Apparently everybody knows
what pegging is except for me.
In my day,
it was called fucking.
[all laugh]
Sorry, Maria, not a match.
Are you losing it, Maria?
Oh! I smell smoke.
There's smoke
coming out of her backside.
Get a fire extinguisher.
Oh! Reboot. Marie, reboot.
[all laugh]
I've seen Brandi Glanville
do that a couple times.
-You know what I mean, Ru?
-Yeah. [laughs]
How about you mind
your own fucking business?
Oh! Oh!
[all laugh]
All right, let's move on down
to Patricia Quinn,
Rocky Horror Picture Show.
You guys filmed it--
what year was that?
Today I thought I was
on the way to the hairdresser,
and look, I'm here, and I don't
even know where I am now.
Oh, okay.
What say you? Ross Mathews,
what does he do with that ball?
Well, much like Ross Mathews,
I do not understand
the rules of the damn game.
So I put he tucks it.
He tucks the ball.
Not quite.
All right, let's move on down
to the great Katharine Hepburn.
We're looking for
"swallowing balls."
I wrote...swallow?
[all laugh]
It's a match!
I love being in the movies.
[all laugh]
Poppy, how are you feeling?
Um, I'm feeling good,
and I'm ready
to write a new song.
Oh, good, can't wait to hear it.
Now, what did Ross Mathews
do with that ball?
Well, they've never let me play
any kind of sports before,
so I just drew a picture
of a flower
because I love nature.
Well, how about that. Wow.
At this point, I don't know if
Crystal's gonna tell any jokes.
Because at this point,
there are no jokes.
It's--it's a moment.
It's something.
Well, that's our show.
That means the winner
of Snatch Game is...
Registered voters.
Because they've earned
the right to bitch
and do something about it.vote
sign
Until next time, we'll see you
on the Snatch Game.
Say good night, Vanjie.
Bye!
Today is another
elimination day,
and one of these queens
is getting the boot.
Today's runway theme
is Frozen Eleganza,
inspired by the Broadway
musical, and I'm so excited.
My look for this is so cool.
Snatch Game, it was not
what I expected at all.
Snatch Game
was a whole different animal
than I thought it was gonna be.
But I feel like I did enough
to stay another week.
When it was lights, camera,
action, I was just...
[all laugh]
Like, I was just struck.
Once you take the lines
away from us
and we have to start improv-ing,
ooh, girl.
Inside, I was like, aah!
We all know it's coming.
This is the one challenge
you have the most time
to prepare for.
I was nervous because Ru didn't
really know who Poppy was.
I didn't know who Poppy was,
either.
I always just get really nervous
that I'm not gonna do well.
-Poor El DeBarge.
-[laughs]
I'm a fan of Poppy,
and everything that Crystal
was doing
was something that Poppy
would have said or done.
I feel so bad for Crystal,
because as accurate
as the portrayal of Poppy was,
it just wasn't funny.
Aiden, how are you feeling?
You're being quiet over there.
Talk to us.
I mean, I know my performance
wasn't definitely in the top
this week, by any means.
I'm just gonna focus on today
and see what happens.
I am feeling nervous,
but I am hoping
that there were some
weaker contestants, maybe.
And at the end of this,
I will make it through.
But Aiden, come on,
was it her forgetting?
You gotta be straight with us.
In my head, yeah,
there was that moment, like,
I don't know where she lives.
So the easiest thing
for me to do
was, like, the bitch
doesn't, like, remember shit,
so just try to,
like, go to that.
My look for this runway is
very cartoony, campy, and fun.
So I'm just hoping
that at the very least
I am safe this challenge.
Did anybody, like,
pick their character
because of, like, a personal
connection to the character?
I picked, you know, Tina Turner
for the sole purpose
that I've been through
a lot of relationships
that were very abusive.
Like, mentally, physically,
emotionally.
Like, I was--
I was homeless for a year.
I slept in
an abandoned building downtown.
Like, I drank
from sunup to sundown
just to get through the day.
The person underneath
all the glitz and glam
has a lot to deal with.
That's why I gravitate to Tina.
I know how that is.
After my mom died,
my uncle kicked me out
because I was gay.
I dropped out of high school,
started couch-surfing,
floor-surfing,
boy-surfing.
I dated
a lot of horrible people.
I had to stop, you know,
letting douchebags
treat me like shit.
I think you
just sharing this story
is gonna be empowering
for people to know
that, like, you can rise up.
It's not just Tina Turner,
it's also Widow Von'Du
who, like, got out
of that cycle of abuse.
Drag has given me everything
I've ever wanted in life.
I was able to pull myself out
of having absolutely nothing,
being homeless, being verbally
abused and mentally abused.
Drag lifted me
out of all of that.
Like now, with my husband
of two years, you know,
I've got a fabulous marriage
and I have a great cat.
Come on, cat!
You've gotta go through some
shit to see some shit.
[tongue pop]
I had to learn that
I could be strong on my own,
and to appreciate myself
before someone else
could appreciate me.
She has not just survived,
honey, she has thrived.
And arrived, mama!
Good for you, baby.
That's hard.
Of all the characters
we could have chose,
I'm like, you chose a robot.
[all laugh]
I knew it was gonna be risky
because, you know, she's bald.
Like, she's a bald character,
which is definitely
more of a masculine thing,
and I kind of rely so heavily
on looking feminine,
and I think that that's
kind of how I feel my best.
And I mean, I've kind of always
teetered between male/female
throughout my whole life.
I think I really always carry
some sense of female in me,
even when I'm in,
you know, non-drag.
Your non-drag.
Growing up, I've always been
interested in feminine things.
I wanted to wear dresses
to school.
I've kind of always thought
there was no point
to putting a label on anything
in regards to gender.
I don't even think
I've ever said this out loud,
but I think I'm fluid.
Sometimes I identify
as more male,
and sometimes I identify
as more feminine.
I think I'm both
and I'm neither.
I realized
at a very young age, luckily,
that I don't care
what other people think.
-Yeah.
-It's just only made me stronger
and have more faith in who I am.
I'm so thankful to have a mother
that shaped me into
the person that I am today.
When I was 12,
my mother brought me
to my uncle, who is gay.
She took me to his house
in Chicago,
which was full
of orange shag rugs
and egg chairs
hanging from the ceiling
and a giant Game of Life
wheel on the wall.
And it was just like--
it was just like paradise
for somebody like me
in that current mindset.
My uncle was the first person
to talk to me about gay culture,
and LGBTQIA-plus community.
My uncle is the first person
who told me who RuPaul was.
He was a big reason why I am
so comfortable with who I am.
Ooh, bitch, they can see
my colors today.
They'll be like, Heidi,
your makeup has improved.
You are the winner
of this week's-- [laughs]
In my dreams.
Let it go!
[all laugh]
The level of disrespect.
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
And what?
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage.
Do you wanna build a snowman?
Why the hell not?
My face is already frozen.
[all laugh]
Style superstar Carson Kressley.
Do people ever say
you look like someone famous?
Oh, you know what,
I get Cate Blanchett a lot.
From which angle?
[all laugh]
I can see it!
Actor and comedian
Daniel Franzese.
Now, who would you play
in the Snatch Game?
Ru, I think
I would have to do Barney.
[imitating Barney]
Hey, Ru! Sashay, shantay.
Sorry, it's a copyrighted
character.
Oh.
Actor and TV host Jonathan
Bennett, how's your cakes?
Never had any complaints, Ru.
[laughs] Are they moist?
Oh, they aren't dry,
let's just say that.
[all laugh]
This week
we challenged our queens
to snatch our attention
with their best
celebrity impersonations.
And tonight on the runway,
inspired
by the Broadway musical,
category is Frozen Eleganza.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
Inspired
by the Broadway musical,
category is Frozen Eleganza.
First up, Heidi.
Michelle: Why the long hat?
[all laugh]
Carson: Are those
Dr. Zhiva-gogo boots?
Heidi: She is walking
down that runway,
head held up so high,
because, you know, she's the
high empress to the Yeti folk.
She's on her way down
to the ski resort,
and she's hoping
to find her a husband
so he can help carry
her big muff around.
[laughs]
Michelle: She's giving us
the cold shoulder, you guys.
RuPaul: Yes, let it ho,
let it ho, let it ho.
[Michelle laughs]
RuPaul: Jackie Cox.
Carson: Let me reflect
on this for just a minute.
Daniel: Snowflake it
till you make it.
Jackie: The inspiration
for my Frozen Eleganza
is Elsa's crown.
The petals are to the metal.
I'm being very brave
in wearing bright blonde hair
for the first and maybe
only time on this runway.
Not really my color,
but I think I'm making it work.
Jonathan:
Naughty, but ice.
[RuPaul laughs]
Daniel:
It's a shiny hiney.
Carson: All right,
let's see somebody Elsa.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Jaida Essence Hall.
Ice, ice, baby.
Daniel: Ooh, Jackee Frost.
[all laugh]
Jaida: In this look,
I am Frozen to the core.
I am up all of north,
and what's left of Antarctica--
Antarctica's at the bottom,
ain't it?
I am giving you whatever
is left of the polar ice caps.
I just feel a fantasy
of, like, ice goddess,
frozen, naked,
and beautiful, okay?
Jonathan:
Storm in a snowstorm.
RuPaul:
Well, you know what they say:
beware of black ice.
[all laugh]
Simply Jan.
Carson: How's your head?
[all laugh]
Jan: For this runway, Elsa,
she's gonna go off
and become a White Walker
from Game of Thrones.
I am dripping
in silicone icicles.
I can do conceptual looks.
I'm not afraid
to go to those places.
Jonathan: I've heard
of having cold feet,
but this is ridiculous.
Michelle: Hypothermi-ya!
[all laugh]
RuPaul: The Widow Von'Du.
[blows whistle]
Oh, she's got a "lip sync
for your life" preserver.
[all laugh]
Widow: For the first time,
I am wearing a period piece
on the runway.
Titanic survivor realness,
bitch.
The judges are getting
what I'm serving,
because they looking at me,
I'm feeling frozen,
and they wanna save a bitch.
[laughs]
Daniel:
Clearly, she likes cruising.
Carson:
Totally tubular.
Michelle: Do the bustle!
[all laugh]
[blows whistle]
RuPaul: Gigi Goode.
She got 31 flavors,
but a bitch ain't one.
Carson: Is that soft-serve?
Because I like it hard.
Gigi: Tonight I'm just that
fun-loving ice cream woman
who is coming down the street.
My ice cream brings
all the boys to the yard,
and I feel so goddamn cute.
My nose is pink because
it's chilly in here.
I wanna show the judges that
not only can I be fashionable,
I can be campy and I can
also think outside the box.
Michelle:
It's clear she's got Good Humor.
RuPaul: Yes, definitely.
Carson: Or she's a Dairy Queen.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Aiden Zhane.
If you stay Yeti,
you ain't got to get Yeti.
Carson:
Hey, my eyes are up here.
[all laugh]
Aiden: I'm giving you
an Abominable Snowman
from the old Christmas
Claymation cartoons.
I'm feeling goofy,
I'm feeling campy,
and I am serving this little
Frozen treat to the judges.
RuPaul: Well, she got
Yeti Davis eyes.
Michelle:
You better Yeti that walk.
RuPaul: I don't think
y'all ready for this Yeti.
Carson: It's unfor-yet-able.
That didn't work.
-No.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Brita.
Michelle: How many plushies
had to die for that wrap?
Carson: One in the mink...
[all laugh]
Brita: This hot bitch
is ice cold.
The entire gown is iridescent,
and I am serving you every
single color of the rainbow.
I am like a gender reveal party
in the snow.
You don't know if it's blue
or pink or orange.
Goddamn, I look gorgeous.
RuPaul:
Oh, look at all that ice.
Michelle: Coldie Hawn.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Crystal Methyd.
Michelle: There's no business
like snow business.
Crystal: I am really excited to
show this look to the judges.
I'm wearing the most elegant
pair of pajamas
that have ever been made.
My runway look is inspired
by Mr. Freeze
from Batman & Robin.
I've added glitter
all over my lashes,
and I look like I've just
been blown in the face
by a blizzard.
Michelle: Glacier?
I hardly know her.
Carson:
I own 51% of Antarctica.
[all laugh]
Welcome, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
When I call your name,
please step forward.
Heidi.
Jaida Essence Hall.
Jan.
The Widow Von'Du.
Ladies, you are all safe.
You may leave the stage.
Ladies, you all
represent the tops
and the bottoms of the week.
It's time
for the judges' critiques,
starting with Jackie Cox.
This look on the runway
is great.
The skirt, very pretty,
beautiful fabric,
looks like liquid silver.
Very effective, very beautiful.
I absolutely loved
your Lisa Rinna.
-You know what I'm saying?
-I thought it was hysterical.
You went for every joke
that you could,
and I thought you really shined.
As a comedian, you want somebody
that can play back with you,
and you were hitting every
volley that someone threw you.
Though not every laugh landed,
you went for every single
opportunity you had.
Good conviction and good
commitment to a character.
Thank you.
You work with the entire group
really well.
You really did your homework,
you knew a lot about her.
Wearing her cardigan from QVC
was very smart.
You used props
and you used costuming
and you used makeup
and you used hair
to tell us that story,
and it worked.
Thank you, Carson.
Up next, Gigi Goode.
Good morning.
This runway look,
the silhouette is really great,
the fit is perfect.
I like the little pink nose.
It's the details with you
that I look for.
Good job tonight.
Your performance was fantastic,
and I thought it was one of the
silent but deadly performances
of the night.
You knew enough
about the actual robot
to be able to do
some spoofy things,
and you were picking up jokes
and taking them.
I thought you did a great job.
Well, you made her naughty,
which I love.
I didn't expect you
to be, like, you know,
calling Ru a bitch,
which made me laugh very hard.
You landed all the jokes, and
I thought that was brilliant.
I loved how you were
completely committed.
When the camera's not on you,
you were still in it
and still over here--
The funniest part was
you fumbling with your cards.
Huge hit for me.
I was worried about you
after the walkthrough,
but, oh, my goodness,
it was so funny.
It was unexpected.
Home run.
Thank you so much.
Up next, Aiden Zhane.
Hello.
As far as your runway look,
I love cartoon stuff,
and I thought it was adorable.
I think it was a cute idea,
but I do think
it's really rather simple.
Let's talk about Snatch Game
Patricia Quinn.
You kept hitting dead ends,
and that doesn't work
in Snatch Game.
I felt like Ru was throwing you
all these things,
and you were swatting them
to the floor.
When you say, "I don't know,"
it's a full-stop dead end for
whoever's performing with you.
And we just
want more out of you.
What made you choose
Patricia Quinn?
She's somebody that I have met,
so I kind of have
a firsthand knowledge of her.
So you met her, then you know
she has a British accent.
-Yes. [chuckles]
-Okay, just checking.
Did you have any preparation
done on her?
Not, like, specifics,
as far as, like, the year
the movie was filmed.
But it was more so just trying
to take her characteristics
and turn them into
a bigger character, I guess,
is what I had tried to do.
Didn't work.
-I'm aware.
-Okay, good.
Rocky Horror is very dear
to a lot of us in here.
I feel like a smarter choice
would have been to do her
as Magenta.
Maybe it might have been easier.
I gave it my best shot,
but unfortunately
I completely missed the mark.
Up next, Brita.
This runway look, I love.
I think it's opalensce--
Opalescence.
[all laugh]
She earned everything.
-Yes, you do.
But to me,
it does say Frozen Eleganza.
So that was a big success.
You chose the great singer
Jennifer Holliday.
Mm-hmm.
You looked great, but it was
just one note that went nowhere.
And I'm telling you,
I'm not buying it.
[all laugh]
I love you and I love her,
but it just--
that wasn't working for me.
You kind of worked yourself
into a corner, unfortunately.
I know, a cornapple
that I don't wanna be in.
-Yeah.
-[laughs]
The past two weeks,
I've been in the bottom,
so I've kind of been in my head.
People hold me at a high
standard in New York City,
and I'm their queen,
essentially.
And I'm just so--
I was upset with myself
because I wasn't doing
such a great job here.
And I just froze.
I froze on the set.
I, like, didn't know what to do.
Is there anything
in the werkroom
I could have said to you
that would have helped?
I was listening
to everything that you said
to every girl in the room.
You said everything
in order for us to succeed,
but did a bitch listen?
I don't know.
I try to let you kids
know in advance
what to expect
when you're expecting.
[all laugh]
Thank you, Brita. All right,
up next, Crystal Methyd.
This look, is that Ice-Escada?
You are so stupid.
-It's Esca--It's an old lady
brand.
-It's a fashion joke.
Anyway, I love
that it's tailored,
I love the material,
that there's a lot of Lurex
to kind of give us that sparkle.
I frigging love this outfit.
It's so chic.
Thank you.
Watching your performance
of Poppy in Snatch Game,
I didn't know
what I was watching.
And then I went home
and googled Poppy,
and I watched her videos,
and I still didn't know
what I was watching.
[all laugh]
I have two teenage daughters,
so I have been obsessed
with Poppy for a long time.
I just think because so many
people don't know who Poppy is,
you then have
to make Poppy crazier...
-Yeah.
-Bigger, funnier.
Some of the jokes I wasn't
understanding, you know,
and I wasn't getting
enough funny.
You were thinking
a little bit too much.
Actually, my concern
for the robot with Gigi
is actually
what happened to you.
Sorry I wasn't able
to throw it back at you.
Had you done El DeBarge,
like I asked you--
I know!
[all laugh]
-All right, thank you, Crystal.
-Thank you.
Up next, Sherry Pie.
Tonight on the runway,
this is really fantastic.
It's still quintessentially you,
but you look different,
which is wonderful.
I loved your performance
in the Snatch Game.
Ducking fitch.
-You are so funny.
-Thank you.
Even she would have enjoyed
that performance.
The visual was kind of similar
to the mother in Gay's Anatomy,
but it was still Katharine,
and it was just wonderful.
Yeah, the only place
I can fault you there
was that the makeup
maybe was a little--
it still looked
a little Waylon and Madame-y.
For the people at home,
Waylon and Madame--
Right, right.
She was the Poppy of the 1970s.
Yeah. That's right.
And you're welcome.
[all laugh]
Well, thank you, ladies,
I think we've heard enough.
While you untuck backstage,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
Okay, now just between
us mean girls,
what do you think?
Jackie Cox.
Jackie was so funny,
and I am a sucker
for a prop comic,
and she had not one, not two,
but four or five prop gags.
And a pratfall and a prop gag,
you got me.
I would have gone
with the lips even bigger,
but she was great
because she went for it,
and I love that about her.
Gigi Goode.
I liked the juxtaposition
of seeing her as somebody cold
and mechanical as the robot,
and then seeing her,
like, warm and friendly
as the little ice cream girl.
I thought she was great and
it was a great night for her.
She was really, really funny.
What's up, bitch?
Gigi Goode has proven again
that she is smart,
she's on top of things,
and she is confident.
She has what it takes
to back it up.
All right, let's move on down
to Aiden Zhane.
I've been kind of obsessed with
Aiden since the show started.
There's something really great
and pure about Aiden
that I love.
But the Snatch Game was
definitely not her thing.
She was in character, though.
She didn't break character,
so I'll give her credit for
that.
She was consistent.
She just didn't understand
the improv and the humor
that is Snatch Game.
Yes. Brita, please.
Brita, I think
in the Snatch Game
was kind of reminiscent
of her vibe in Gay's Anatomy,
where it was a bit one-note.
And you almost lose her
a little bit.
She doesn't pop
in these kind of group numbers.
Sometimes when
you're parodying someone
that doesn't have very much
of a public persona,
you've just gotta give them,
like, a plus-one.
Like she's this,
plus she's angry,
or she's this,
plus she's, like, slutty.
Just give us one more plus.
It doesn't even have to be true.
Yes. Crystal Methyd.
She wasn't telling us enough
about this character.
Like, tell us who it is.
Oh, just working on new music.
Let us all become Poppy fans.
She didn't give us enough
to really sell it.
It just wasn't that funny.
You know, do whoever you want,
but make it funny.
The bottom line
is where are the jokes?
Where are the jokes?
Sherry Pie.
This ducking fitch.
[all laugh]
She gave us great theater.
I thought she was so funny,
so good.
She's chosen even
an old-school kind of icon,
which was a smart choice.
Jonathan, who would you do
on the Snatch Game?
Oh, Ru, I'd do
Valerie Cherish
on RuPaul's Drag--drag--
RuPaul's Drag Races, you know?
So... No, no, you're wrong,
it's Drag Race.
So we're doing
RuPaul's Drag Race.
-So you know--
-You knew that.
Mark! No, you can't use that.
You can't use that, Jane. Jane!
[all laugh]
Silence!
I've made my decision.
I've made my deci--
I've made my--
I've made my decision!
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Gigi Goode,
ice cream, you scream,
we all scream for you, queen.
Con-drag-ulations. You're the
winner of this week's challenge.
[applause]
Yes!
Fuck.
You've won a cash prize
of $5.000.
Oh, my God.
I won Snatch Game.
That's huge.
Thank you so much.
Gigi, you may join
the other girls.
[applause]
Jackie Cox, you're safe.
Thank you guys.
Sherry Pie, you're safe.
Thank you.
Aiden Zhane, your Snatch Game
was a bit of a rocky horror.
Brita, your Snatch Game
was no dream, girl.
Crystal Methyd,
your Poppy just didn't pop.
Crystal Methyd...
You're safe.
Thanks.
You may join the other girls.
Aiden, Brita,
I'm sorry, my dears,
but you are up for elimination.
I am up against
a powerhouse performer.
I need to slay this
if I am going to stay here.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing] for your life!
I will fight to survive.
I'm not going anywhere, sis.
Like, I'm gonna serve it to you.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
[music plays]
♪ The snow glows white
on the mountain tonight ♪
♪ Not a footprint to be seen ♪
♪ A kingdom of isolation ♪
♪ And it looks like
I'm the queen ♪
♪ The wind is howling ♪
♪ Like this swirling storm
inside ♪
♪ Couldn't keep it in,
heaven knows I tried ♪
♪ It's time to see
what I can do ♪
♪ To test the limits
and break through ♪
♪ No right, no wrong,
no rules for me ♪
♪ I'm free ♪
♪ Let it go, let it go ♪
♪ I am one
with the wind and sky... ♪
Now we have snow
that is coming onto
the goddamn stage!
♪ You'll never see me cry ♪
♪ My power flurries through
the air into the ground ♪
♪ My soul is spiraling
in frozen fractals all around ♪
I'm doing everything I can
to win this lip sync.
I'm giving you a Broadway show.
Bitch, I even brought
a magic trick
♪ Let it go, let it go ♪
♪ And I'll rise
like the break of dawn ♪
♪ Here I stand
in the light of day ♪
♪ Let the storm rage on ♪
♪ The cold
never bothered me anyway ♪
[cheers and applause]
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Brita, shantay you stay.
Thank you.
You may join the other girls.
Good job. You slayed
the competition.
-Love you.
-Thanks, babe.
Aiden, you are a queen
with a special power.
Never let it go.
Now sashay away.
I just wanna say
that I am truly sorry
that I have not been able
to break free
of the voices and the things
going on in my head.
Thank you so much
for the opportunity.
Thank you.
[applause]
And also I will not
leave this competition
being the quiet bitch.
So on that note...
Aaah!
[laughter and applause]
-Yes!
It sucks.
It sucks to be going home.
But I am going
to hold my head high,
I am going to be proud
of what I was able to present
to the world.
Being in any kind of sisterhood
with other drag queens
can get messy.
But, bitch,
I am on
RuPaul's fucking Drag Race,
and this is only the beginning.
Con-drag-ulations, ladies.
And remember,
don't eat yellow snow.
[all laugh]
And if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an "amen" up in here?
-Amen!
All right,
now let the music play.
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪vote
♪ Just like you, too ♪
Aiden: Boo!
RuPaul: Next time
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
You get to star in Madonna:
the Unauthorized Rusical.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
♪ Boy toy, baby ♪
We do not have a lot of singers
in this group.
[off-key]
♪ Ah-ah, ah-ah, ah-ah, oh ♪
Your performance was amazing.
You are right
exactly as you are.
I'm so thankful that
you're part of our country.
I hope that somebody
tears y'all down
just as much as y'all
tore us down, I'm sorry.
-Ooh.
-I'm really over today.
We couldn't just be
Best Friend Race
for the whole season, could we?
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪
♪ Am-Am-Am-Am-American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪