RuPaul: Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
You'll be improv-ing a show
we like to call
the World's Worst.
♪ Row, row, row your boat ♪
All: Three girls with one brain.
I'm a fierce brocc-ally.
Nicky Doll.
I felt you disappeared
a little bit.
Dahlia Sin.
The broccoli
was just lost in the sauce.
Sherry Pie.
You are the winner
of this week's challenge.
Nicky Doll, enchanté, you stay.
Dahlia Sin, sashay away.
Whew!
Ooh, child.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
First elimination
has just happened.
Dahlia is no longer with us.
RIP, honey.
"I love you all, Dahlia."
Love you, too, Dahlia.
I think that this was a pretty
fucking strong wake-up call.
Every single episode,
one of us is gone.
Dahlia going home,
like, one of the most
beautiful girls amongst us,
it feels like
anyone can go home.
Now the competition has begun.
I love you, Broccoli.
[all laugh]
After the lip sync,
I have a fire under my ass.
And if I have what it takes
to send Dahlia home,
I have what it takes to send all
the other girls back home, too.
So be ready
for the French bitch,
because she's coming for you.
[speaking French]subtitle
It feels so,
like, mixed emotions
that, like, Dahlia just left
and Sherry just won
at the same time, so, yeah.
-Congratulations!
-Yeah!
-Yes!
-Thank you.
I am feeling a bit vindicated.
Like, bitch, I told you so.
You didn't lead us at all.
At times, I felt like
we were carrying you.
I thought I did a good job.
I am happy that I chose
two powerhouses of queens
for my team,
and we fucking did it.
I still think that Aiden
is a weak competitor,
but she's definitely
a smart bitch.
I mean, she picked me.
I thought I did a good job.
I mean, it would have been nice
to get critiqued on something
that I like to think
that I'm very, very good at.
It was nice to be safe,
but, like,
I wanna be at the top, honey.
Because of Brita's reputation
in New York,
she came in here
expecting that her name
would carry her
through the competition
and that she would slay.
But unfortunately, Brita,
it doesn't work that way.
It's like Nicky said.
I mean, different situations,
of course,
but it's a wake-up call for me.
I feel like
the past two challenges
have been things that
I should be excelling in.
I sing, I dance, I do improv.
I wanna be in the top.
I want $5.000, too.
Jan seems to be really pissed.
Bitch, I just lip synced
for my life
and I'm listening to you
saying, like,
"I really wanna be on the top."
Well, listen,
that was the first one down.
There's gonna be many more.
That's right, 12 girls...
All: With one brain.
[all laugh]
And if we ever
work in a group again
and I tell you we fucking
did good and to calm down,
listen to me, bitch!
For me, I thought
I did light makeup for that.
I'm not gonna lie.
Your makeup is distracting.
You thought you did light makeup
for the challenge?
-Yeah!
-Girl!
What the hell?
That's light makeup for you?
I don't even do that face
on New Year's Eve.
What light makeup
are you talking about?
I'm glad you're still here,
Nicky.
But watch out. You're next.
[all laugh]
This is a very strong
group of girls,
so it's time to start
stepping up my game.
Oh!
This is still a competition.
Even though we're playing nice,
we gotta play to win.
I gotta play to win.
Whew!
Whoo!
RuPaul: The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
and a cash prize of $100.000.
With extra-special guest judge
Leslie Jones.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
Another day, another dollar.
A little skip-skippy-dippy-dip.
I wasn't at the top
in this last challenge.
Going forward,
I need to show the judges
the true Brita that everyone
in New York City knows, loves,
and the reason why
I'm perfectly capable
of winning this entire
goddamn thing.
How'd y'all sleep?
Y'all sleep good?
-Yeah.
-So well.
I slept like a baby.
I had an amazing dream
last night.
-What was it?
-What was it about?
I won RuPaul's Drag Race
Season 12.
And then you woke up.
[all laugh]
[alarm]
RuPaul: Ooh, girl!
[cheering]
She done already
done had herses.
My queens, does a baller
make you holler?
Well, take a swing, Miss Thing,
and then drop it like it's hot,
or you're gonna have to bounce.
-[gasps]
-Swish-swish, bish.
[cheers and applause]
Hello, hello, hello!
[cheering]
Yes!
Ladies, America's
next drag superstar
needs to think globally
and act locally.
For today's mini-challenge,
you'll be raising awareness
of the world's declining
bee population.
-Aw.
By shaking your stingers
to a buzzy little mash-up
we calling The Beehive Jive.
[cheering]
♪ Oh, Pit Crew ♪
-Oh!
I've never seen you
wear more clothes.
Now, using
these bee-utiful fixins,
plus hair products from Hask
and pads from Planet Pepper,
you've got 20 minutes
to get into quick bee drag.
#DragRace.
Get to it, busy bees!
It's complete, utter chaos.
Bees communicate through dance,
and the only thing that we're
communicating right now is aah!
Bitch, I look butch.
RuPaul: Ladies, time's up.
Beehive, get in formation.
Now, bees are a crucial part
of our ecosystem,
pollinating fruits, vegetables,
and the grains we eat.
So basically, without bees,
we are fucked.
And without dees--
[all laugh]
Let's keep the bees alive
doing The Beehive Jive.
Hit it!
[Flight of the Bumblebee plays]
Where's my EpiPen?
[record scratch,
Freaky Money plays]
Widow Von'Du!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Come on, party bee.
[cheering]
Jackie Cox.
-Hey!
-Come on, girl!
Yes, Jackie!
It don't mean a thing
if it ain't got that sting.
Sherry Pie.
[Record scratch,
Flight of the Bumblebee plays]
[record scratch,
Freaky Money plays]
Rock M. Sakura.
She needs to run a honeycomb
through that wig.
[cheering]
Why are you killing the bees?
[all laugh]
Heidi!
I will never say
"Heidi N Closet" ever again.
I'm just putting that out there.
My bee likes to make
a statement.
If you take a close look
at her drawers,
it says, "Bee-lieve."
[laughs]
Don't get your knickers
in a honeybunch.
What did I call me?
Brita. [laughs]
Yeah!
Whoo!
Nicky Doll.
Get it, Miss Sting.
Oh!
[cheering]
Jaida Essence Hall.
Come on, girl.
[laughs]
Whoo!
Ooh, she is giving me Bee-yonce.
Aiden Zhane.
Ooh, and this bitch
is giving me Bee Arthur.
Aiden is definitely
the Edith Piaf of the beehive.
Bitch look sad.
Simply Jan.
[cheering]
Oh, honey.
Yes, honey!
Crystal Methyd.
Ooh, careful
with that stinger.
Just the tip.
[cheering]
Gigi Goode.
-Yes!
-[laughs]
Hey!
Yes!
[cheering]
Shake that stinger, mama!
Ladies, the winner
of today's mini-challenge is...
Gigi Goode.
Yes!
[applause]
Yes, I won
the mini-challenge! [laughs]
I think this means
that I'm the Queen Bee
of the season, doesn't it?
Con-drag-ulations.
You've won
$2.500 cash money, henny.
Okay! All right!
And in your name,
Hask will be making
a $2.500 donation
to the HoneyBeeConservancy.org,
where you'll find simple things
you can do to save the bees.
Aw. Yay!
[applause]
And most importantly,
we'll be posting your bee videos
on Instagram
at RuPaul's Drag Race
to haunt you
for the rest of your lives.
[all laugh]
Now, ladies, did you know
Drag Race and sports
have a lot in common?
They both involve competition,
colorful outfits,
and balls.
Okay.
So for this week's
maxi-challenge,
we are throwing
a fashion ball, darling.
[cheering]
Why y'all gagging so?
She bring it to you every ball.
Always gagging on the balls.
Now, you need to slam-dunk
three homerun looks.
The first look is Lady Baller,
serving sexy Title IX realness.
Second look,
Basketball Wife Realness,
a posh look that screams,
"He owns everything, henny."
And for your third lurk,
you need to design and create
a look that serves
Balls to the Wall Eleganza.
[murmuring]
Now, to create
your eleganza look,
you can play
with all these balls,
plus materials
from the F&S Fabrics wall.
I have been waiting
for a design challenge,
so I'm really excited
to show what I can deliver.
Hey, listen, I gotta bounce,
but, uh, gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[cheers and applause]
[sighs]
I am a little nervous.
You know, this is the first
design challenge we have,
and I've only sewn
one garment before this.
So just pray for me.break
Gimme the balls!
This week's challenge
is the Ball Ball.
We have three categories.
Our first two looks
can be pulled from our wardrobe
that we brought with us,
but the Balls to the Wall
Eleganza
must be constructed while
we are here from scratch.
[crash]
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry.
-Brita!
Come on, Season 12,
let's get sewing!
Hey, miss.
What are you doing?
I wanted to have
a little bit of Latin flair.
Mm.
Carmen Miranda's
a big inspiration of mine
because I like wearing
lots of necklaces and bracelets.
I wanted to show the judges
my Mexican side,
so I thought it would be fun
to glue a bunch of balls
to my head.
And I wanna look like
I'm a piñata.
Doing everything myself
is something
that I'm really proud of
when it comes to my drag.
I'm excited to show everyone
what I can do.
I'm also really excited
to see some people fail.
Oh, wow.
These were the very first things
I saw,
and I made sure that nobody else
was gonna get these,
because I have a plan.
I have a plan, too.
You got cheese balls?
-Girl.
-Just to snack on?
I'm gonna step on the runway
and be like...
My ball comes
from the voguing scene
in Harlem, New York,
in the eighties,
and it's basically categories
that you have to
portray yourself in.
And you have to sell
the garment, darling.
Miss Nicky.
So what are you doing?
I'm really gonna do,
like, this fringe dress.
But covered with those fringes,
so it's just gonna--
I'm gonna have, like,
a very tight structure.
Oh, it's just gonna move.
And it's gonna move on the legs.
I feel like they have been
praising me for the fashion,
but arriving with fashion
is good,
but you wanna show them
that you're really
part of the process,
and this is my attempt
to show them that I can do that.
Great.
Finally, no English needed
for that one, honey.
No, bitch.
Finally, something
that I can fucking slay.
I don't have to work
with bitches I don't know.
I'm just relying on myself.
This is creative,
this is fashion-forward,
this is what I like to do.
It's good
to be a good seamstress,
but it's better
to be a good designer.
I like what Nicky's doing
right now.
My biggest threat in this
challenge is Nicky Doll.
She definitely has
a concept together,
so I do kind of feel
a little bit of pressure on me
to kind of step up my game.
I think I'm gonna go,
like, really mod sixties
and just, like, add these balls
every which way.
-Whichever way you can, yeah.
-Yeah, girl.
Oh, bitch.
Since, though,
I am a seamstress,
I really pride myself on being
able to construct a garment.
I wanna make this
look like something
that was very impeccably
put together.
I wanna win this challenge,
you know?
You said you used to play
soccer, right, Jan?
I did. I grew up
playing soccer my entire life.
Does this hurt you, seeing
this soccer ball destroyed?
No, because it's just like
the patriarchy.
Oh, yes.
Tear it down, rebuild it.
I started playing sports
when I grew up.
Soccer was my number one thing,
and I played that for 13 years.
Growing up in a Catholic school,
it's not really great to be gay.
And because I played sports,
I think that people kind of
gave me a little bit of a pass,
because they thought,
oh, well, he's really athletic,
so he can't be that gay.
Like, sure.
But I like to call myself
the Troy Bolton of drag,
because, yes, I do love sports,
but I also love
some musical theater.
I love to belt it out.
Getting your patterns out, girl?
Yes'm.
Remember,
the neck is at the top.
[laughs]
Right now, I am freaking out.
Everyone is, like,
cutting fabric,
they have, like,
concepts laid out,
and I'm--I don't--
I have no idea what I'm doing.
Jackie, I got it.
I think you're done, Brita.
I think this is it.
I might get eliminated, though,
because I have no shape.
Round is a shape, actually.
[laughs and coughs]
My asthma.
Is that cheating if I just
wear this as a hoop skirt?
Pineapple Princess.
I could be a pineapple.
I have enough green.
-There you go.
-That's pretty freaking cute.
Now I have a concept,
but, like, how the fuck
am I gonna construct this?
Like, I don't know
what I'm doing.
Gigi, you sew, right?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm gonna need some help.
I'm freaking out a little
bit.break
This week's challenge
is the Ball Ball.
We're gonna have
some basketball, some football,
some hanging balls,
some highballs, some lowballs.
-Jan's got a plan.
-Blue balls.
I'm just ready
to play with the balls.
Let's go. [laughs]
In order to make the look
that I've envisioned,
I'm gonna go with this method
that we use for cosplay.
You create a cast of your body
using tights and some duct tape.
Crrrrk!
Who wrapping gifts over there?
Rock M., what are you doing?
The roll's too loud!
I can't hear you!
When you wrap all this duct tape
around your body,
it'll hold
the shape of your body
and then it'll become
the base of my outfit.
Ah, she's free!
My goal is to put as many balls
as possible on this dress,
and to really impress the judges
with just how big
my outfit is gonna be.
I need more duct tape.
Someone that I'm concerned
for is Rock M.
I'm very confused
on what's going on.
It looks like a science fair
project gone wrong.
We're all still hustling,
we're all still trying to think
how can we make this better?
How can we top ourselves?
How do we turn this
from an outfit to an eleganza?
So, friends, what do we think
the judges are actually
looking for in this challenge?
It has to read ball,
but scream high fashion.
-Exactly.
-Just walk down the runway,
and you scream "high fashion"
at the top of your lungs.
High fashion!
This is high fashion!
Balenciaga!
Screaming high fashion
right now.
Wow. [laughs]
The concept for my
Balls to the Wall Eleganza look
is a beautiful white gown.
There's more white balls
somewhere.
Normally, I'm not the type
to be running around
playing with white balls.
But for this look,
I'm gonna have to get my hands
on as many white balls as I can.
♪ She's gonna need
a bunch of popcorn balls ♪
♪ To make it through ♪
♪ She's gonna take
some wiffle balls ♪
♪ To make it through ♪
Jaida's got this white gown
going on.
I don't think
it's a cute bottom of it.
It kind of disconnects
a little bit.
She was gonna be a lovely gown,
but, darling, major issues
I'm running into at this moment.
My original idea
is to make this beautiful gown.
But I just realized that
there are not enough white balls
to do exactly what it is
that I want to do.
So right now my heart
is palpitating shit.
I don't know what the hell
is going on.
A bitch is going through
a little bit of panicking.
Bitch, this might
have to be a leotard.
I'm sewing my base garment,
and then I realize, oh, my God,
I just spent so much time
making this stupid base.
Like, oh, my God,
I'm running out of time
to put these balls on it.
And, oh, my God,
am I gonna have time
to make this dress
come to fruition?
The stress is setting in.
I have to cover
this whole thing in balls,
and I've already spent hours
just making a white dress.
Oh, I hope it's enough.
Other girls have
half-finished garments,
so I feel kind of fucked
right now.
I'm really enjoying
this black-and-white theme.
My look is turning into sort of
a pinup kind of moment.
I'm honestly loving
what I'm creating.
The only thing about mine
is I'm just, as of now,
hoping it's not too simple,
maybe.
[clucks tongue]
I am racking my brain,
trying to find ways
to zhuzh up this outfit.
[hums]
But I am feeling like
if I add anything else,
it's going to lose shape,
it's going to lose meaning.
And one thing I don't wanna do
is walk down that runway
looking like a mess.
Like I said, I know
it's, like, more simple.
Mm-hmm.
But that's, like,
generally my drag.
I'm most worried for Aiden.
It's a two-colored corset
with a couple of droopy balls.
[nervous chuckle]
It's not necessarily about--
-Having to have the most on.
-Having it be the most, yeah.
It's if you have
a strong concept.
This is, like, referee.
It fits perfectly
with the sports theme.
I didn't even
think of that, yeah.
Bitch, you didn't know
that you were creating
a pinstriped
white and black costume
that resembles a referee?
It's a ball challenge.
Girl, what?
I'm trying to think
if I have a whistle
that could go with that.
That would be hilarious.
Jan has pointed out that
it sort of reads as referee,
and it's this sort of
lightbulb moment
that's just adding another layer
of confidence on my outfit.
I think I might
be pretty much done.
Aiden is done working on it,
and isn't really
going the extra mile
to see if there's anything else
that he can add to the
look.break
Woop, woop, woop, woop.
It's time to get ready
for the ball.
Yesterday
I just wasn't really sure
if this dress
was going to come together
the way that I wanted it to,
but last night I was able
to work on my dress,
so this morning
I've just decided
to hike up my panties
and make it fucking work.
[laughs] Oh, my gosh.
Get your inches!
Nicky, we gotta put our wigs on.
Okay, let's see
who has the best human hair.
One, two, three.
Oh, yeah.
You just slapped me
with your hair, bitch!
Well, that's what happens
when you have
this much volume, Nicky.
Too much volume. Real.
The problem that Nicky is having
in this competition
is that she's not
letting the judges
see the goofy side
that we all see.
I feel like Ellen DeGeneres.
[all laugh]
And that's not gonna bode
very well for her.
How you feeling, Miss Heidi?
I'm feeling good.
My vision
kind of came together.
It's really cool.
It's very clean.
I love the lines.
I didn't want it to just be
a bunch of balls everywhere.
[laughs]
I wanted--I wanted--
Good thing she's on the other
side of the room right now.
I wanted them to be, like--
Miss Thing.
I wanted them to be
meticulously placed.
Uh-huh, I see.
The shade starts this week.
Rock M.'s garment could use
a little bit of editing.
It's a little too...
It is balls to the wall,
and that it is,
very balls to the, mm, wall.
[tongue pop]
With the challenge,
I feel like
I really, like, turned it.
Anybody else, like,
really happy with what they did?
Aiden, how well do you feel?
Because I know you had,
like, a lot of time left
between what you did.
Yeah, I was the first one done
out of everybody.
So last night, while I'm, like,
struggling to finish this dress,
Aiden is over here
in the corner taking a nap.
She took the least
amount of time on her look,
and she was on the couch
sleeping.
Aiden isn't working hard enough.
I'm actually really happy,
like, with what I made.
I think it's, like, totally me.
Don't you think you
could have added more to it
with, like, the extra time?
-Because, like--
-No.
I think if I had
added anything else,
it would have pulled away from
the vision that I have for it.
-Okay.
-And like I said,
I do tend to have sometimes
a "less is more"
kind of aesthetic.
My face is something
that I use to kind of pull--
like, bring my looks together,
if that makes sense.
But don't you feel like
this is gonna be an issue
in front of the judges,
when it's a fashion ball
and not a face category?
Well, I'm not
just going down there
with my face painted and naked.
Nicky: No, no, no, for sure.
This is an eleganza challenge,
and to me, that means
do as much as you can
and be as creative as possible.
There's a lot of shit
you can do to spice it up.
Well, somebody's
going home today.
Shit done got real, honey.
Come on, Sakura.
I live for this mug.
This is so nice.
Ooh, thank you.
I first started doing
Sakura face
because the first time
I ever started in drag,
someone told me, oh,
it must be really easy for you
because you're Asian.
And, like, you don't
have to try very hard.
-Yeah.
-Oh, my God.
They're like, you don't have to
try very hard at all, do you?
And I was like,
I'll show you who's not trying.
And so I just started
putting more and more
and more makeup on.
The fact that people think
that Asian queens
don't have to try too hard
because they already
look like women
or they're highly feminized
really got to me.
So I started to look like
I was at least
trying hard with my makeup.
But now that I paint so bold,
all I ever hear is, wow,
you're giving me Trixie makeup.
Wow, you're giving me
Kim Chi makeup.
But the thing is I've been
drawing anime-ish styles,
I had that
How to Draw Manga book
ever since I was a little kid.
And a lot of people do this
style and have done it before.
Sakura, you took it
to a whole other level.
I'm a lady now.
Just like you girls.
[giggles]
[all laugh]
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
And what?
[laughs]
Yes!
[all laugh]
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage.
Now, do you play any sports?
No, my doctor doesn't want me
doing any activities
that involve balls
flying at my face.
Well, there goes
your social life.
Ooh!
And the hilarious Ross Mathews.
Did you ever play ball?
Well, I don't wanna brag,
but in college,
I was on
the varsity brunch team.
Oh.
Yes. I still play sometimes.
[all laugh]
I'm a natural.
And the one and only
Leslie Jones.
Girl, you betta werk!
Leslie, are you recording this?
Yeah, girl,
this is how I do it at home.
I live-tweet live.
[all laugh]
And you is bomb.
You like a banana birthday cake.
And you look amazing.
Thank you.
I'm channeling Diana Ross
tonight.
Call her Miss Jones.
[all laugh]
This week,
we challenged our queens
to bring three looks
to the Ball Ball.
I'm so excited.
And tonight,
they're ready to roll.
[all laugh]
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
Aah! You just did that
in front of me!
Oh, my God,
I'm losing my mind.break
Oh, my God, you guys,
it's starting!
Category is Lady Ballers,
serving Title IX realness.
First up, Jackie Cox.
Leslie: You are
crossing the line, girl.
[all laugh]
Jackie: I am serving you
Amanda Bynes,
She's the Man, Canadian
lacrosse player realness.
Don't know exactly
how lacrosse is played,
but I'm gonna win it.
RuPaul: Is it wrong for me
to say she's a lacrosse dresser?
Ross: I thought it was hockey.
Yeah. Yeah.
Nicky Doll.
Leslie: Ooh, tackle me, bitch.
Michelle: The Dorothy Zbornak
sports collection.
[all laugh]
Nicky: My lady baller
is serving you quarterback
from the Lady Gaga planet,
fully dripping in rhinestones,
with like
a very holographic makeup.
I'm serving you the future
of drag, and I'm here for it.
Michelle: Now, that's
a tight end, y'all.
[laughs]
All: De-fense! De-fense!
Leslie: Oh, yes, baby!
Michelle: That's so butch.
Thank you!
RuPaul: Aiden Zhane.
Oh, my God, she's in
A League Of Her Own.
Michelle: It's the sequel.
RuPaul: That would be
a load of her own.
-Aah!
-Ooh!
Aiden: I am really channeling
this vintage
female baseball player
in a total Aiden Zhane way.
I am just living
my best baseball fantasy.
Ross: I heard she lets you
get to third base.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: There's no crying
in Drag Race.
Michelle: No!
RuPaul: Rock M. Sakura.
Michelle: She's nesting.
[all laugh]
Michelle: She came in
like a wrecking ball.
[all laugh]
Leslie: Oh, my God,
it's a tetherball.
Rock: Bam!
Imagine Ariana Grande,
but instead of a ponytail,
she had a tetherball braid.
I'm gonna rope them in
with this look.
I'm having so much fun.
Leslie: Ooh! Mama said
knock you out.
Yeah, I've had balls
knock me out.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: LeBron Essence Hall.
Michelle: Looks like a pump,
feels like a sneaker.
[all laugh]
Jaida: My lady baller's look
is a WNBA player.
I wanna pay homage
to all of these super-crazy
talented girls
who work really hard
on the court,
and they don't get the shine
that they deserve.
RuPaul: White men can't jump,
but black queens sure can strut.
Leslie: Yes!
This is a slam-dunk, though.
Nope. I spoke too soon.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Brita.
Michelle: Now, is she a pitcher
or a catcher?
Leslie:
Oh, she does both, baby.
-Oh!
-Ooh, ooh.
Brita: I'm serving you
baseball the house down.
My shoulders
look like baseballs
with the stitching in it.
Forget sliding into bases.
You can slide
into my DMs, honey.
Ross: Before you're with her,
you better
seventh inning stretch.
RuPaul: Crystal Methyd.
Leslie: Ooh, she's about
to bowl me over.
Ross: Honey,
stay in your lane.
[all laugh]
Crystal: Before coming
to this competition,
I worked in the basement
of a bowling alley,
and I know
a lot of old bowlers.
I've got cute little glasses
that I made sure to take off
and give Michelle a wink,
so she can see my new makeup.
Leslie: Oh, my God, I wanna be
on her bowling team so bad.
RuPaul:
Striking. Just striking.
[all laugh]
Jan. Simply Jan.
Michelle: Soccer?
I don't even know her!
Ross: Beckham?
I don't even know him!
[all laugh]
Jan: I'm so excited
to bring the soccer Jan-tasy
to this runway.
This look is chic,
not to mention I'm dribbling
a soccer ball down this runway.
Who else?
Ross: She's at my goooal weight.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Well, you know,
any hole is a goal.
[all laugh]
Heidi.
Michelle:
Whore! I mean, fore.
[all laugh]
Ross: She is giving me
a Tiger Woodie.
Leslie: She's definitely
a ho-in-one.
[all laugh]
Heidi: She thinks she's about
to make her PGA debut,
but she's really
just gonna go for putt-putt.
But she loves
the sport of golf, honey,
and she's ready to swing
all over these holes.
Leslie: Whew.
Don't lose your balls, now.
Ross: Ooh!
Leslie:
Oh. She did lose her ball.
RuPaul: Sherry Pie.
Well, I see she brought out
the old ball and chain.
[all laugh]
Sherry: My lady baller look
is inspired
by Roald Dahl's Matilda.
I am crunching
down that runway.
I am swinging that hammer,
and, oh, I have to
touch up my lipstick.
Well, thank God
it's also a purse!
Michelle: She's a little
shot-putting at first.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Widow Von'Du.
Leslie: Giddy up.
Ride that pony!
Michelle:
Oh, yes, she betta glue.
[all laugh]
Widow: I am giving you
save a horse,
ride a cowboy,
polo player realness.
I feel like I'm about to accept
an award for winning the match.
RuPaul: They shoot whoreseses,
don't they?
[all laugh]
Leslie:
She done already had horses.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Gigi Goode.
Croquet, you stay.
Ross: Cro-kurrr?
[all laugh]
Who the fuck is Heather?
Gigi: I am wearing a look
inspired by one of my very
favorite movies, Heathers.
I'm trying to give my just
rich teenage bitch fantasy,
and, honey, I'm just giving
my resting bitch face.
RuPaul:
What's your damage, Gigi?
[all laugh]
Fuck me gently
with a chainsaw.
[all laugh]
Oh, my God,
I just saw a runway!
[all laugh]break
RuPaul: Welcome back
to the Ball Ball.
Category is Basketball Wife:
He Owns Everything.
Jackie Cox.
Ross: She's a bellbottom.
Jackie: This lady
is married to some ball player
that she doesn't bother
learning the name of.
Touch this net.
Touch all of this net.
My net worth
is 51% of this company.
Ross: Know what she's
gonna catch with that net?
-Hmm?
-A cold.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Nicky Doll.
Leslie:
This bird is cooked.
Michelle: Cock-a-doodle-doo.
Nicky: I'm going for the
Azzedine Alaia-inspired look.
I have this oversized
ostrich coat.
I am serving you badass bitch
heading to Paris fashion week.
Leslie: Pluck it, girl,
just pluck it.
[Michelle laughs]
RuPaul: Aiden Zhane.
Leslie: She thinks
she has it in the bag.
RuPaul: Well, she's got
the receipts to prove it.
[all laugh]
Aiden:
I am just really trying
to channel
my inner Peggy Bundy.
I am trying to give the judges
a basketball wife
who thinks she's glamorous,
but really, the bitch
is just delusional.
Michelle: Basketball wives
of Edison, New Jersey.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Rock M. Sakura.
Did somebody say
Golden Globes?
Leslie: Yes.
Rock: I'm trying
to show the judges
that Rock M. can do sexy.
So this woman, she can get
anybody on the team,
and she wants her husband
to know that.
Leslie: I wish Lil' Kim would.
RuPaul: Now, I ain't saying
she a gold-digger.
[all laugh]
Jaida Essence Ball.
Michelle: Look, it's
Mahogany's sister Burgundy.
[all laugh]
Jaida: I think a basketball wife
is just about a feel
that you give.
Like when you see a woman and
she just looks pulled together,
that's a basketball wife.
I mean, look, my man
do not play basketball,
and I'm a basketball wife
in my mind.
Michelle: Y'all, how do you get
a wine stain out of this fur?
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Brita.
Leslie:
I thought I thaw a putthycat.
Brita: This is a take on
Kim Kardashian's Mugler dress
that she wore at the Met Gala.
I mean, I look expensive, too.
NBA money, honey.
RuPaul: She owes everything.
[all laugh]
She owes! [laughs]
RuPaul: Crystal Methyd.
Michelle: Paris Hilton
looks...different.
RuPaul: Actually,
it's Paris Ramada.
[all laugh]
Michelle: Oh, there you go.
Crystal: With my makeup
being so light,
I definitely feel like
an actual woman.
I wanted to have
the longest hair.
I am making sure to fling it
as much as I can
because my husband
bought it for me.
That's so hot.
-It's totally hot.
-It's so hot.
RuPaul: Simply Jan.
Leslie:
Uh-uh, girl, she the bomb.
Ross: She got an over
the shoulder boulder holder.
Jan: I have my completely
rhinestone track suit
and my Louboutins,
not to mention
my custom handmade Janel bag.
I look flawless.
RuPaul: She's dripping
in Janel Monáe.
[all laugh]
Heidi!
Michelle: Straight from
Ramseur Country Club.
[all laugh]
Leslie: Ooh, this is
the shiestiest church service
I've been to.
[all laugh]
Heidi: My basketball wife's
realness is Shalonda.
She does not
wanna be looked at,
don't touch her, don't breathe
in her direction.
She just trying to check out
the other basketball husbands.
Ross: Don't you dare
sign that prenup.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Up next, Sherry Pie.
Leslie: Ooh, yes.
Michelle:
Y'all know it's serious
when she got hair
coming out of a hat.
[Ross gasps]
Leslie: Yes!
Sherry: My basketball wife
is a rich bitch.
Her husband gave her
a money gun.
That's how much money they got.
Leslie:
Yes, make it rain, boo!
[all laugh]
Michelle: If you liked it, then
you should have put a hat on it.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Widow she betta Du.
Ross: Something tells me she's
got something up her sleeve.
[all laugh]
Widow: Oh, bitch,
I'm buying everything.
Charge it to the card,
put it in the car,
carry it up the stairs.
That is what I'm serving you
right now.
RuPaul: The Widow wore white.
[all laugh]
Gigi Goode.
Michelle: I anaconda do.
[all laugh]
Gigi: I'm recently divorced,
however, I have acquired
most of his assets.
I'm busy on Rodeo Drive
trying to spend
all the money he's earning.
Leslie:
Get that motherfucking snake
off of that
motherfucking runway!
[all laugh]
Category is
Balls to the Wall Eleganza.
First up, Jackie Cox.
Ross: Make it rain, coat.
[all laugh]
Jackie: She is serving you
this gorgeous, elegant,
1960s,
future-also-disco woman.
She is a Blade Runner fantasy
of Breakfast at Tiffany's
meets Saturday Night Fever.
RuPaul: Now, most people
don't know this,
but she's actually
Jacqueline Bouvier Cox.
Leslie: Booty-ay.
RuPaul: Nicky Doll.
Ross: Ex-koosh-me.
Nicky:
My concept is Copacabana.
I'm having a cocktail
in the sunset in Brazil.
And I'm going all fringe dress,
but I'm bringing
a little French twist to it
by adding extra hips,
so very Marie Antoinette like.
RuPaul: Michelle, is there
an anal bead option?
[all laugh]
Michelle:
You're soaking in it.
RuPaul: Aiden Zhane.
[whistle blows]
Ross: Lady Footlocker.
Leslie:
Oh, show me a size 12, girl.
Aiden: I am serving you
a little bit of Bettie Page,
but I'm also giving you
the nod to a referee.
I am loving this
black-and-white color scheme.
I've got my whistle, so
don't you dare commit a foul.
RuPaul:
What's in this season?
Black, hairy balls.
[all laugh]
Ross: Every season.
RuPaul: Rock M. Sakura.
Leslie: What is
that thing called
that you jump in
with all the balls in it?
Michelle: A ball pit.
[all laugh]
Rock: They said
"dripping with balls,"
so I dragged balls
all over this outfit.
I have every color
you could possibly imagine.
It doesn't exactly make
too much sense,
but it looks visually appealing.
Michelle: This is what
it looks like when the cat wins.
Leslie: I think I shouldn't
have took that LSD, you guys.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Jaida Essence Hall.
Leslie:
Calgon, take me away!
RuPaul: She's the bath bomb.
Jaida: Bitch,
I'm really excited,
because my look
turned out amazing.
It's giving me
this rich bitch fantasy,
dipped in a beautiful,
sudsy, foamy bubble bath.
And I just feel the fantasy
sweeping over me.
Michelle: Look, y'all.
She's got a bubble butt.
[all laugh]
Ross: I haven't seen
that many white balls
since my fraternity days.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Brita.
Brita: I'm walking
down the runway
with this fierce
pineapple dress.
I'm giving you
my pineapple crown.
A beautiful, tight pencil skirt
with pineapple segments
at the bottom
and pineapple tidbits
on my shoes.
I got my pineapple powder puff
that I'm wiping
the oil on my nose with,
because she is just oozing
of pineapple juice, honey.
Ross: Corn?
Is it corn?
Is it a pineapple?
-It's a pineapple.
-Oh.
Is that a pineapple?
Yeah, it's supposed to be
a pineapple.
Crystal Methyd.
Ross: Ay-yi-I love it.
Leslie: Chiquita banana.
[all laugh]
Crystal:
I went with a silhouette
inspired by Carmen Miranda.
She's one of my favorite
style inspirations.
She's always wearing
the most amount of accessories,
and I really appreciate that
in a woman.
Michelle: You know,
the last time
I had that many balls
on my head...
Oh, Jesus.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Simply Jan.
This looks like the DNA
of the Blue Man Group.
[all laugh]
Michelle:
She's turning violet, Violet!
Jan: My Balls to the Wall
Eleganza is high concept,
it's cool, it's different,
and it's fashion.
Ross: Anyone else
have blue balls?
Michelle: You guys
know about blue balls,
but what about blue boobs?
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Heidi.
Michelle: ♪ Ho-ho-ho,
green drag queen ♪
[all laugh]
Heidi: She's giving you
very space alien,
and all my balls
are so meticulously placed.
I got a ball cap, so you know.
She's even got a little
cue ball on the runway, mm.
I'm giving you all balls
everywhere.
Ross:
♪ Mr. Queen, Mr. Queen ♪
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Sherry Pie.
Michelle: Al-gee,
your hair smells terrific.
[all laugh]
Leslie: She can now
celebrate Arbor Day.
[RuPaul laughs]
Sherry: I'm just
walking through the forest.
giving you greens, greens,
and nothing but greens.
I am just feeling
my magical fantasy.
Ross: Now this is forest green.
[all laugh]
Leslie: Run, Forrest, run!
RuPaul: Widow Von'Du.
This is what the fashionable
are wearing in Machu Picchu.
Michelle: Yes.
Widow:
My Balls to the Wall Eleganza
kind of looks like
Wakanda Forever
and Christmas
with Cindy Lou Who.
And a bitch gots a ponytail.
Ross; Yellow?
It's your shoes.
[all laugh]
Leslie: No!
You can't do that to me, no!
RuPaul: Gigi Goode.
Silly rabbit.
Trix are for kids.
Ross: Now with drag berries.
[all laugh]
Gigi: I am so proud
of what I came up with.
It has a cute little
box-pleated skirt,
puffy little pirate sleeves,
and, yes, bitch,
there's a zipper.
No one else in this challenge
has made a look
as elaborate as mine.
Leslie: I got
a pocket full of quarters.
I want some of them gumballs.
RuPaul: Young and full of gum.
[all laugh]
Young and full of gum!break
RuPaul: Welcome, ladies.
Based on
your 36 Ball Ball looks,
I've made some decisions.
Jackie Cox.
Crystal Methyd.
Jan.
Heidi.
Sherry Pie.
The Widow Von'Du.
Ladies, you're safe.
You may...bounce.
[all laugh]
You represent the tops
and the bottoms of the week.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques,
starting with Nicky Doll.
This is a fashion challenge.
I expected a lot from you,
and you delivered.
In your first look,
the Lady Ballers,
you heard of fantasy football?
You were my football fantasy.
-Ooh!
-Basketball Wives realness,
girl, you worked that.
On your Balls to the Wall
realness,
I think this is fun.
It's a corset with a panty,
but you threw
a lot of stuff on it
that brought us into,
like, a fantasy.
The color palette is perfect.
-Thank you.
-There's a lot of whimsy in it.
My favorite part is what
you've done with the hips,
because it gave you a shape.
We know that you have
a nice aesthetic,
but I'm gonna challenge you
to keep pushing
that personality up.
Get out here and be a fool.
[sighs] I understand completely
what you mean.
I think it is hard to really
understand my personality,
and it's up to me
to deliver it to you.
What's the wackiest
you've ever been in your life?
I'm always wacky.
That's the most
frustrating part.
Make an ugly face right now.
Yeah!
[all laugh]
-Thank you, Nicky.
-Merci.
Up next, Aiden Zhane.
Lady Baller was adorable.
It was perfectly
in the right era,
which I really appreciated
and loved.
You hit a home run
in the first inning.
-You guys follow me?
-Very good.
What is that?
Is that baseball?
Oh, my gosh!
And then your team
had a drought.
Basketball Wives realness,
it looked just like
minor leagues.
And again, with this last look,
the execution isn't as polished
as it needs to be.
This is not
going to be enough, Aiden,
because this is a corset
with cotton balls on it.
My drag sometimes
does tend to maybe have
a little bit of a less is more,
maybe, thing about it.
I'm not always the girl
who puts everything on.
Yeah, it doesn't have to always
be more, more, more.
It just has to have
a consciousness behind it
that says, "I am here,
and I have something to say."
You've got it, kiddo.
Now spread those wings
and what?
♪ Fly ♪
Up next, Rock M. Sakura.
Hi, hi.
In all three of your looks,
your hair and makeup, girl.
That tetherball,
when you came out
and swung that thing
around your neck,
I was like, oh, that's dope.
The problem was
there was nothing exciting
going on below the ball.
For your Basketball Wife
realness look,
I thought you looked
really beautiful.
There was just an issue
with the padding.
It was a little disjointed.
Mm, mm, mm.
Now, this look, it takes a lot
of balls to wear that look.
[all laugh]
We were just saying, Aiden,
that sometimes
more, more, more is not right,
and I'm gonna use you
as an example.
I feel like maybe
every single thing
that you could have
gotten your hands on
is on your body right now.
And then the chest
is very far open,
and it almost looks like
you have sores on your chest.
Sometimes you do need to edit.
Imagine, if you could,
a world where you
cut the dress off at the knees.
That would have been chic.
That hair and makeup, dope.
Just, you gotta bring
the outfits now to match that.
Up next, Jaida Essence Hall.
Girl, I've played basketball
since the sixth grade.
You cannot play.
[all laugh]
You cannot play, girl.
But you know what?
I would still pick you on
my team, 'cause you looked fly.
I was like, oh, my God.
The second look,
the first thing I thought about
was Porsha
from Atlanta Housewives.
Yes.
You were living
the rich fantasy,
and tonight,
this is really fun.
This is the glamorous woman
taking a bath.
She so rich,
she bathes in diamonds.
Yeah, I mean,
the proportions are fantastic,
and it's really beautiful.
Thank you so much.
I think I would change
the same thing
about all three
of your looks tonight:
not a damn thing.
Thank you.
Up next, the great Brita.
We're gonna start
with your Lady Ballers.
You chose baseball.
I thought it was really fun, the
puffy kind of baseball sleeves.
The baseball socks, they were
kind of a little loose,
so they were kind of baggy.
The Basketball Wives,
it didn't have
that kind of "I'm married
to a baller" vibe to it.
It was just kind of
clubby pedestrian.
This look, I'm still confused.
Like, is it corn,
is it a pineapple,
is it a cornapple?
It's a pineapple.
What you talking 'bout, Willis?
Because that is not a pineapple.
It's a pineapple.
No, I say, no!
[all laugh]
My family lives in Hawaii.
My mom calls my sisters
"pineapple princesses,"
so I wanted to be one, too.
I just love your energy.
I think
that is so beautiful
that your family calls you
little pineapples and cute.
But listen, if you're telling
a story, we should get it.
We shouldn't wonder,
"Is it a corn?"
If you have a vision
and we don't know
what the hell's going on,
you did not execute your vision.
Up next, Gigi Goode.
Your first look
was a Heathers moment,
with the croquet, and
it was gorgeous and fabulous.
I mean, there's nothing sexier
than a woman in a blazer,
I think.
Maybe because
they look most like a man.
[all laugh]
The Basketball Wives,
the snake print with the collar
up and the black hair,
I'm partial to black hair.
Can I just say that I wanna eat
your hair right now?
It looks delicious.
And it's all mine.
That was funny.
Tell another one.
[all laugh]
This look, it's perfection.
Thank you so much.
It's exciting, and it's chic.
It's like you've been studying
this for a very long time,
which I actually think
you probably have been.
My mom is a seamstress.
She's taught me
everything that I know.
She's made, like, most
of the looks that I brought,
and she does not give herself
enough credit.
And she means the world to me.
Honestly, the biggest reason
that I'm here
is to make my mom proud.
And your mom is proud. Trust.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
While you untuck backstage,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right, now,
just between us ball queens,
what do you think?
Nicky Doll.
Nicky is a fashion queen,
and she served us fashion
in every single look.
What's missing for me
is the personality.
I don't know anything about her,
apart from the fact
that she's French.
I'm rooting for her, because
I think she does have it.
I love the aesthetic.
What I need for her to do
is work from the inside out.
You know, she's got
the outside working.
That's good, girl.
Aiden Zhane.
Where Nicky Doll
is lacking in kooky,
Aiden Zhane has plenty of kooky
to go around.
Her first look was amazing,
but no, no, no,
you are not putting on
a pair of panties and a corset
and trying to pass that off
as a look to me.
Aiden's such an original,
but I worry
that she's overwhelmed.
What she's gonna have to do
is get her head out of her ass
and put on some blinders
and go for it.
It's about channeling
that energy to fuel you
rather than to fear you.
Exactly. Thank you.
Rock M. Sakura.
You know, when Rock M.
first came around the corner
with her Lady Ballers outfit,
I saw her face and I was like,
ooh, she looks gorgeous.
And then my eyes panned down.
[laughs]
She's the only queen who really
gave us a show with the balls,
you know what I mean?
And if she did that in the club,
people would go crazy for it.
Yeah, they would.
It was a fun concept,
but it wasn't enough
to make the outfit great.
And then her final look tonight
was probably my least favorite
on that runway.
The outfit was just not good.
It looks like cats
just lost they mind.
Yeah.
[all laugh]
Jaida Essence Hall.
I loved Jaida tonight.
She was just gorgeous.
The Balls to the Wall
extravaganza was my favorite.
She just looked so glamorous,
and I just thought
she was a star tonight.
Three points for Jaida.
Is that a basketball term?
That's a basketball term,
thank you!
-It is, three-pointer.
-Three pointer, that's a thing?
Yeah, it's a thing.
Thank you!
All right, up next, Brita.
I love her energy,
it's infectious.
I just think that tonight
was a little bit of a miss
for Miss Brita.
What was she pulling out
of her mouth at the beginning?
I don't know what it was.
Chewing gum?
I can't get past this.
If you're auditioning
for a musical
and they say
come with three numbers,
you don't do
the same number twice.
-Right, right, right.
-Right.
And she wore essentially
two yellow dresses.
She's better than that.
Yeah, yeah.
And then I had to look up
a pineapple,
because I was like, that is not
what a pineapple look like.
The only thing worse
than not knowing you ate corn
is not even knowing
you're eating corn.
[all laugh]
It's hard to digest,
and so were her looks.
[all laugh]
Damn! Damn!
All right, let's move on now
to Gigi Goode.
Not only was each look
better than the last,
but with each look that she
showed us, there was a story.
That's what fashion should do.
She's so perfect, she almost
looks like a mannequin.
Like if I walked into a store
and saw this mannequin,
I'd be like,
where is the salesperson?
I want this outfit now!
She's a sample size.
But take away the body,
and you still have fabulous,
gorgeous clothes
with texture and storyline
and a consciousness behind it.
Just fabulous.
Gigi Goode
was a triple threat tonight.
All right. Silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.break
RuPaul: Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Nicky Doll,
you look magnifique.
Now show us your freak.
You're safe.
You may join the other girls.
Jaida Essence Hall.
Girl, you really cleaned up
this week.
Thank you.
You are safe.
Thank you so much.
Gigi. Tonight you weren't
just good, you were great.
Con-drag-ulations.
You're the winner
of this week's challenge.
[applause]
Thank you so much.
And you've won
a cash prize of $5.000.
-Yes!
-Nice!
I feel so incredible.
I feel like I secured my place
in this competition,
and I let every last one
of these bitches know
who to look out for.
Aiden Zhane, you're in a league
of your own,
but tonight on the runway
you made a bad call.
Rock M., I like
that you take risks,
but tonight it was
a bit of a swing and a miss.
Brita, you're a sweet
pineapple princess,
but tonight you didn't crush it.
Aiden Zhane.
You're safe.
You may join the other girls.
Bitch.
Oh, my God.
Bitch, too bad.
I'm safe. End of story.
Rock M. and Brita,
I'm sorry, my dears,
but you're up
for elimination.
Please, please, please,
please, please.
I take a deep breath, and I say
if you wanna be here, you fight.
[mouthing words]
Look at her. Oh, my God,
this is gonna be good.
My arrogant ass thought that
I wasn't going to lip sync.
But I am a performer,
and I'm gonna perform
the house down.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing] for your life!
Dramatic lighting.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
♪ Na, na, na, come on ♪
Oh, my God, you guys.
Whoo!
♪ Na, na, na, come on ♪
Yes, go on, girl!
♪ Na, na, na, come on,
come on, come on ♪
-Tear it off!
-That's right, girl!
Take it off! Go ahead!
♪ Feels so good being bad ♪
♪ There's no way
I'm turning back ♪
-♪ And all the pain ♪
-Oh, no.
♪ Is for pleasure ♪
♪ 'Cause nothing can measure ♪
Oh, my God.
There you go.
♪ 'Cause I may be bad ♪
♪ But I'm
perfectly good at it ♪
♪ Sex in the air,
I don't care ♪
♪ I love the smell of it ♪
♪ Sticks and stones
may break my bones ♪
♪ But chains and whips
excite me ♪
♪ 'Cause I may be bad, but
I'm perfectly good at it... ♪
I am lip syncing
for my motherfucking life.
I am desperately trying
to fight to be here.
♪ May break my bones, but
chains and whips excite me ♪
♪ Na, na, na,
come on, come on ♪
♪ I like it, like it,
come on, come on, come on ♪
♪ I like it, like it ♪
♪ Oh, it's exactly... ♪
I'm just in, like,
war zone right now.
Rock M.
is doing all these tricks,
and I am not going anywhere.
♪ And meet me in my boudoir ♪
♪ Make my body say ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ I like it, like it ♪
♪ 'Cause I may be bad, but
I'm perfectly good at it ♪
♪ Sex in the air,
I don't care ♪
♪ I love the smell of it ♪
♪ Sticks and stones
may break my bones ♪
♪ But chains and whips
excite me ♪
♪ S, S, S and M, M, M ♪
[cheers and applause]
Girl, way to leave it
on the stage, girl!
You left it on the stage,
literally.
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Ooh, here we go, here we go.
Brita, shantay you stay.
You may join the other girls.
Thank you.
-I love you.
-I love you, too.
Thank you.
My dear Rock M.
Keep sockin' it to 'em.
Now sashay away.
-We love you, Rock!
Never give up on your dreams,
and tell yourself
that you love yourself.
[cheers and applause]
Love you guys.
[Rock M. cries]
I wanna stay here so bad,
and to leave now
is very disappointing.
I'm feeling completely crushed.
I may not have gone very far,
but I have so many things
to be grateful for.
Con-drag-ulations, ladies.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an "amen" up in here?
-Amen.
All right,
now let the music play.
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue
♪graphic
♪ I am American, American
♪ Just like you, too ♪
RuPaul: Next time,
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
You need to over-act
in Gay's Anatomy.
-Aah!
-[laughs]
[deep voice]
Ge this baby out of me!
There's an anal--
Oh, child.
That look is fierce.
I might steal it.
[all laugh]
You missed the jokes.
I really did think that
you were probably in the bottom.
Ooh!
Whoo!
[sighs]
These fucking bitches.
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪
♪ Am-Am-Am-Am-American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪