[static]
Looking for a new
political party?
Are you tired
of politics as usual?
I'm Donald Trump,
and I do not approve
this message.
Join the RuPaul's
Drag Race party!
♪ I am American... ♪
Life, liberty,
and the pursuit of opulence!
Let's meet your candidates.
Here we go, sis.
Ha-ha!
Y'all thirsty?
[laughs]
Ahh.
My name is Brita and I am
the queen of New York City.
I'm the first bitch here.
Aah!
Everyone who knows drag
in New York City
knows who Brita is.
I was really hoping
the other girls would be here
so that
they could see the winner.
I have seven shows a week
in New York City.
I literally do it all:
commercials, TV,
singing, dancing.
I took over New York City,
and now it's time
to take over the world.
Oh, girl, I look good.
Most people think I'm like,
a big ol' black lady,
but I'm a Polynesian princess.
My dad is from
the kingdom of Tonga.
Out of drag,
I'm definitely Maui,
and then at night,
I turn into Moana.
I guess we'll just wait
for those other ho's
to come out. Yes, mama.
I'm so excited.
I can't wait to see these other
girls that I'm gonna beat.
Well, that was a long flight.
[speaking French]subtitles
I am originally
from Paris, France,
and recently relocated
to New York City.
My looks are very inspired
by European runways
from the nineties,
and my performances are dancey
without all the shenanigans
and the splits and all that.
So I'm bringing glamour...
without breaking my hip.
Hello!
-Nicky Doll.
-Mwah-mwah.
Nicky Doll, oh, yes!
You're from New York City!
-Yes!
-Look at you, mama!
You like my little
Jean Paul Gaultier realness?
Yes, come on,
New York City queen.
Wait, aren't you
from somewhere else, too?
I'm originally
from Paris, France,
but I moved to New York
a year and a half ago.
Oh, I see.
Nicky Doll is the fashion queen,
and she's gonna bring beauty,
grace, and a cute little lace.
But she ain't comin' for me
in the performance area.
I'm happy to see that there's
another New York queen here.
I know, right?
I'm gonna win, though.
Yeah, well,
I'll tell you goodbye
when it's the right time.
Relax your throat, bitches,
'cause you're gagging.
[laughs]
It's Widow Von'Du.
30 years old,
but you couldn't tell.
I mean, she looks good, though.
[laughs]
Werk, bitch.
Slay mother goose, mother god.
For those of you
that don't know me,
I am the nastiest bitch
from Kansas City.
And for those of you
that do know me...
you're fucking welcome.
[laughs]
Hi! How are you?
-Good. How are you?
-You look gorgeous!
Oh, my God.
Yes, bitch, you are beat!
Come on, big girl.
They call me The Thiccums
herself, honey.
Get you a taste.
Look at this.
Get into all of this.
All of it.
And that's all,
with like four As, eight Os
and three Ls.
"Aaaaoooooooolll!"
Yes, bitch.
[laughs]
How do you feel being sandwiched
in between us two
big girls right now?
I feel safe.
I've got my security guards.
You know, just in case
another ho is super jealous.
The big girls
about to bring it
to these little skinny ho's.
They better be prepared.
Jackie: Roll call!
I know that bitch.
I'm Jackie.
Salaam! The Persian Princess
of drag has arrived.
Aah!
I'm Jackie Cox,
and I'm 34 years young.
I am a Middle Eastern nerd,
and I am the Persian
Annette Funicello of drag.
-Oh, hello!
-Oh, my God, Jackie!
-Aah!
I'm so excited to see Jackie Cox
in the workroom.
That's my sister from NYC.
-Oh, my God!
-We made it!
I know someone,
I know someone.
-Right?
-Jackie Cox is the queen
of the cabaret scene
in New York City.
-What are your names?
-I'm Widow.
Widow, I'm so sorry.
[all laugh]
I do a little comedy,
I do a little singing.
I love performing off Broadway.
Ta-da!
I love to drop into a character.
Wait.
What does your dress say?
Oh, it says my name in Farsi.
So it says Jacqueline in Farsi.
-Oh, Jacqueline.
-Oh, I love it.
But watch out,
because Jacqueline
is also the name
of my evil twin.
Jackie is not really
so much of a look queen.
I know that she's gonna
bring her smarts to the show,
But I don't know
if she's gonna give us
the glamour that you need
for RuPaul's Drag Race.
Three New York City queens
so far
Three? Oh, 'cause
you're from France.
-Yeah.
-I'm like, France!
New York City!
In the house, honey!
America, it's time
to stop hiding in the closet.
[high-pitched trill]
What the fuck
is this bitch doing?
[high-pitched trill]
All right, tongue power.
Okay, is someone trying
to come for my culture?
You know, it sounds a little bit
like a Persian trill.
I see you're not the only
cunning-linguist
in this group here.
[all laugh]
I am Heidi N Closet.
I am 24 years of fabulousness,
and I am from Ramseur,
North Carolina,
where the chickens
outnumber the people.
Heidi is serving
her pimp-tress outfit.
I know I look good in
my...subtitle
Aah!
My drag is very SPF 100.
Sassy, professional, fierce,
and she keeps it 100.
What kind of drag do you do?
Well, she is more of
just a performance queen.
She's always ready
to dance and twirl
and kick and everything.
The most important part to me
in drag is to be entertaining.
Because
if you're not entertaining,
it's like watching the wall dry.
Is that how you say it?
Producer: Mm-hmm.
-Oh, my gosh, we're here.
-Yeah!
Crazy.
[high-pitched trill]
That's my mating call.
Clearly, I'm single.
[all laugh]
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Ahoy.
My name is Gigi Goode,
and I'm not just good,
I'm incredible.
When I am entering a room
in drag,
I really am trying to have
that Cinderella story moment
where everyone is just
kind of like, who's that bitch?
Argh, mateys!
I love it, honey!
The Pirates of the Caribbean
was in town. Oh, my God.
Is one of her legs a peg leg?
I need to know right
now.subtitle
Fashion
means everything to me.
I see my drag
going to the cover of Vogue.
Period.
Hey, everybody!
What's up?
Hi, I'm Gigi!
I've heard about you.
I've seen you on Instagram.
You're like, fierce.
So nice to meet you.
Okay, so Gigi Goode
is also bringing fashion.
I know her from Instagram.
She's definitely
going to be tough competition,
and I can't wait
to put her down.
I am living
for this outfit of yours.
Thank you.
My mother made it.
Birth mother
or your drag mother?
-Both.
-Your mom is your drag mom?
Technically, yeah.
She's a theatrical
costume designer, so most--
Oh, yes.
Are you a good seamstress?
-I'm sure, 'cause--
-I am.
My mom taught me
how to sew, so--
Awesome.
How old are you?
I'm 21 years old.
-21.
-Oh.
Fresh off the boat.
[laughs] Oh.
I think
the first impression of me
is going to be "Oh, God,
here's another fashion queen,
no personality, no talent,
no humor."
I'm going to prove each
and every one of them wrong.
-We're here.
-We're here, Isn't it wild?
H-E-A-R, hear.
I was hoping to be
the skinny one. Nope.
Maybe All Stars.
[all laugh]
-Uh-oh.
Who's ready to party and play?
Checkers anyone?
Michelle Visage's nightmare
just arrived.
I'm Crystal Methyd,
and I'm a little devil
that likes to raise hell
in the Bible Belt.
I spit.
You can typically catch Crystal
rocking bright colors,
tropical print and cheetah.
I think the most impressive
thing I bring to the table
is my sick moves.
I'm known as the dancing diva.
No.subtitle
[laughs]
I think my most impressive
drag talent
would be my makeup skills.
I want to make sure that
these other girls know
that you're never gonna know
what to expect
from Crystal Methyd.
Oh, my God!
[laughs]
It's not just the season
of New York now.
It's now the season of Missouri.
-Missouri's in the house!
-Yes!
Crystal, good to meet you.
Crystal? Just Crystal?
Crystal Methyd.
Oh.
Crystal comes jumping
into that workroom
looking like something
jumped out of the box.
All of a sudden, I'm hungry
for, you know, a croissant-wich.
So you're like a look queen,
comedy queen, clown queen?
I'm a look queen,
I'm a comedy queen,
I'm a talented queen.
[all laugh]
You can definitely tell
that these other bitches
are feeling some type of way
about Miss Crystal.
But y'all better be ready.
The bitch is fierce.
Ooh, bring on the next girl.
-No.
-Let's go, where are you?
[alarm]
Ooh, girl!
She done already
done had herses.
What in the hell is going on?
Ru-Mail is playing and...
there's only me
and six other bitches here.
Wait, is this it?
What the hell is going on?
Can somebody tell me where
the rest of the bitches at?
Hey, racers.
-Hi!
Are you drop-dead gorgeous?
Do you slay well with others?
Because whether you're a part
of a lucky seven,
a baker's dozen
or a mènage á trois...
-Ooh.
-I'm looking for that bitch.
[tongue pop]
Yes, girl!
Hello, hello, hello!
[cheering]
Welcome to RuPaul's
Drag Race 2020.
[cheering]
Now, this is a year
of life-changing choices,
and now, more than ever,
we need your charisma,
uniqueness, nerve and talent
to help save the world.
So I am proud to announce
your candidacy
to become America's
Next Drag Superstar.
#DragRace.
Now, I have to warn you.
It's a crowded field
of candidates this season.
So to get to know
each of you better,
we're not just having
one premiere.
We're having two premieres.
And you lucky seven
are the first group of queens
to make your case to the nation.
-Yes.
First in, best in.
For your very first
mini challenge,
it's Fashion Week
at RuPaul's Drag Race,
presented by Bubly
Sparkling Water.
Come on, bubbles.
I want to see all the fun
and flavors of fashion
as you slay the runway
in both a Spring
and a Fall look.
-Oh.
-All right.
I'm like so excited
for this mini challenge.
I want to be walking the runway
in Fashion Week.
Like, how fucking fun is it?
I take fashion very seriously,
so I need to fucking
nail this challenge.
Now, I know for a fact
that major players
in the fashion world
watch Drag Race for inspiration,
so let them have it.
Oh, God.
I'm hella nervous right now,
because with there
only being seven of us here,
the microscope
is on each and every one of us,
and any little slip-up
could send us
right out that door.
Racers, your campaign
for the crown starts now.
RuPaul: The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics
and a cash prize
of $100.000.
With extra-special guest judge
Nicki Minaj.
RuPaul: Presenting
the Spring Collection.after
teaser
You never get to see
the Summer Collection.
No, that's resort.
Summer is resort.
I prefer cruise.
-You do.
-I heard.
For our very first
mini challenge,
it's Fashion Week,
and we have to walk in
both Spring and Fall categories.
I am like, so excited.
Oh, wait,
the show is starting.graphic
Serving fashion
for spring, Brita.
Brita: This is so exciting.
Ru is there, Michelle
is there, Carson is there.
I see Raven.
Oh, I love Raven so much.
Grab a tulle
and start banging.
I look like a waterfall fairy,
with all this tulle
swishing around like water.
I let it go and it releases
and then you see
just strand of tulle
just following behind me
like a trickling stream.
Make it known,
Brita is here!
Oh, I guess she's not
gonna take the train.
She's gonna walk.
RuPaul: Nicky Doll.
Carson:
She's very wisteri-ous.
Nicky: For the spring look,
I'm serving you nymph
going to Olympus,
and I am on Zeus's list, bitch.
Michelle: She's lilac-tating.
Nicky: When it comes
to drag aesthetic,
France is highly inspired
by runways and high fashion.
This is what I do.
I'm a look queen.
Carson:
I can see her "oui-oui."
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Widow Von'Du.
Make some room, bitches.
Make some room!
I'm poppin' the shit
out of this runway,verify
wearing all the brightest
of neoprene.
That's my look.
A ratchet-ass queen
with some high-class fashion.
It's hot.
Let me take my jacket off.
Boom! Matching bra.
What's that? Nero-prene.
What's it called?
-Neoprene.
I'm on it right now.
It stops the internal bleeding.
Widow: Most big girls, they're
afraid to be who they are.
They see all the skinny girls
wearing absolutely nothing,
and they're like, Oh, my God,
I can't do that.
Fuck that.
Carson: If you liked it,
you should've put a hood on it.
RuPaul: Jackie Cox!
Michelle: Emilio Hoochie.
Jackie: My spring runway
is Jackie-a-go-go.
I always bring
a little bit of retro-glam
into whatever I'm doing.
I love Barbara Eden,
so the nods to Barbara Eden
in the hair,
the little spit curls
on my cheeks,
Not only do they hide
my sideburns,
but they're freaking cute.
'Cause a lady
do always have a purse.
-A lady do carry a purse.
-Always.
RuPaul: Heidi N Closet.
Mm-hmm.
RuPaul: Welcome to Timbuktu.
Carson: I love
the way this drapes.
I mean, it is drapes.
Literally.
Heidi: I am super excited
to show these judges
who Heidi N Closet is.
She's giving genie in a bottle,
psychedelic
Springtime realness.
It represents me being
just over the top,
glamorous, splashy,
sparkly head to toe.
And all of a sudden...
You could see
her civil rights hair.
Oh, Lord!
But I keep going.
I keep going,
and that's important.
Michelle: Hats off to her.
RuPaul: Gigi Goode.
Carson: I love
a spring prance-suit.
Gigi: This spring look
screams Gigi Goode.
It's Easter Sunday
at the trailer park.
I just joined
a lesbian motorcycle gang
and, bitch, I am ready to ride.
Carson:
Watch out for her peeps.
Gigi: This is what
I excel in.
I am a fashionable bitch.
Ooh, pastel-equent.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Crystal Methyd.
Don't try this at home.
Michelle:
Skip-to-my-Ru.
Crystal: This is a pretty
girly look for Crystal Methyd.
It's colorful, it's creative,
it's intentionally
over-accessorized.
I feel most comfortable
when I am being a weirdo.
Carson: She has got to stop
putting Viagra
in her fabric softener.
[all laugh]
Now serving fashions
for Fall, Brita.
Just when you thought it was
safe to go back in the
water.graphic
Brita: I am serving you
oil-spill realness.
You've got oil spilling
into this gorgeous, dark blue.
I am cinched, I cannot breathe,
but it doesn't matter
because I am here
to slay the game.
RuPaul: No glove, no love.
Carson:
I'll take one glove love.
RuPaul: I think there's been
a fisting accident,
Nicky Doll.
Ooh-la-la.
Gaultier.
Nicky: For the fall look,
I'm hitting that runway
like Paris Fashion Week.
I'm serving you
Jean Paul Gaultier,
Karl Lagerfeld, Chanel.
I'm putting all my fucking
culture in one outfit.verify
RuPaul: Now, Nicky's French.
Carson:
What is Nicky French for?
Nicky is French for nooky.
[all laugh]
Carson: Au revoir!
Widow Von'Du.
The Widow Von'Don't.
Get into it, bitches.
Get into all of it.
My hair is big, my hips are big.
Oh, guess what?
Ooh!
Pants!
Oh, darling, it's mother
of the house la beige.
-Huh.
-[laughs]
This outfit is bad
as a motherfucker.
It's tans, tans, tans
across the board!
Jackie Cox.
-Thoroughly modern Jackie.
-Mm-hmm.
Jackie: My sense of fashion
is a little bit more old school
than some of the other girls.
Mom got a divorce,
and she's never been happier.
Jackie: I love that ability
to kind of create this
whole fantasy of silly people,
and then live in that world.
RuPaul: She's serving
early Ruth Gordon.
Michelle:
But with Bader-Ginsburg.
Heidi N Closet.
Oh.
-Her hips don't lie.
-Nope.
Heidi:
Soon as I turn the corner,
I can hear just that:
[gasps]
Oh, that was breathtaking.
They was living for me!
Them's child-bearing hips.
I enjoy the small-town
simple life.
But Heidi needs the big city
so she can blow up
and have some fun.
Oh, sweet Jesus.
Well, that explains
the hip replacements.
[all laugh]
Gigi Goode.
Michelle: Where's Gigi Bad?
Hmm, that's what
I want to know.
Gigi: I'm just serving
your average,
every day, BDSM horse-jockey.
Also made by my mom.
So, bitch, this outfit
is fitting me like a glove.
Carson:
Is this a yea or a neigh?
They shoot whores,
don't they?
[all laugh]
Carson: Tally-ho!
RuPaul: Crystal Methyd.
Carson: Freddy or not,
here she comes.
Michelle: One, two,
fashion's coming for you.
Crystal: It is a full gown
inspired by Freddy Krueger.
I make a lot
of my own drag myself.
I love thrifting to create
weird and unique looks,
and I'm hoping
I get some goodies.
RuPaul: If you stay Freddy,
you ain't got to get Freddy.
[applause]
♪ Daddy see, look at me ♪
Michelle:
♪ Scary drag queen, whaa ♪
-Whaa!
♪ Sexy, sexy drag queen ♪
Carson: Michelle,
is that your leg again?
Michelle: Sorry.
It's my third leg.
We did it, ladies.
Mini challenge over and done.
Oh!
We done did
our first runways.
We did our first challenge.
Can one of you sirs unzip me
so I can peel out of this
like a can of biscuits?
Yeah, I'll help you, mama.
Now it's time to rub it off,
untuck it,
and show some things.
-Oh!
-Ooh, werk.
Nicky, Nicky...
looks French.
She's selling baguettes at night
and selling different baguettes
during the day, honey.
[laughs]
Heidi is definitely
a love child
with Mayhem and lemurian.
Fuck. Lemurian.
It's like an animal
that has big-ass eyes.subtitle
A lemur?subtitle
Heidi definitely
looks like a lemur.
Oh, this is always
the best part of drag.
-Getting out of it?
-Crystal, that is a wig.
I love that hair, girl.
My dad had a mullet that was
like, down to his crack, so...
-Wait, really?
-I'm trying to get there.
Who would have thought
that behind this clown makeup
was such a cute twink?
What does your tattoo say?
I got it at a concert,
and it says "One Direction"
No, I don't trust you.
You have a tattoo that says
"One Direction" in Arabic?
Yes.
-Do you speak Arabic?
-No.
But I didn't want
everyone to know
that I had
a One Direction tattoo.
[all laugh]
I guess y'all
are wearing clothes.
I should just
put on something
because I feel like a ho
right here.
-You don't have to.
-No, that's fine.
No one's gonna make you
put clothes on.
Jackie,
damn, Jackie is hot.
I definitely can see
where all the hummus go.
'Cause come on, bubble butt!
Hummus, the hummus.subtitle
-She's Persian.
-Oh, hummus!
Hummus. Oh, my God!
-I'm sorry. [laughs]
-Girl.
Hey, squirrel friends.
[cheering]
Where'd all the ladykins go?
They're gone, packed away.
Ladies, now that we've had
a sneak peak of your fashion,
it's time to dig
a little bit deeper.
Now, for your first
maxi challenge,
you'll be performing
the bad-ass rap single
I'm That Bitch.
[cheering]
Now, each of you needs
to write her own verse,
and as a group,
you need to work together
on the choreography.
Uh-oh.
[all laugh]
Now, this is your big chance
to introduce yourselves
to the world
and break out from the pack.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman--
Wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
I can't believe I almost forgot
to tell you this part.
-Uh-oh.
-Okay.
Not only will you be
performing your rap
on the main stage,
you'll be performing it
in front of our extra-special
guest judge.
Young Money!
Shut up!
Miss Nicki Minaj.
[cheering]
That's right,
Think pink, bitches.
Holy moly.
Nicky Minaj is going to be
judging my rap skills,
and I have never rapped
in my life,
so I am terrified.
Gentlemen, start your engines
and may the best woman win.
All right, we got this.
-Whoop, whoop!
-I'm that bitch.
I am that bitch.
I am so excited
for this challenge.
It's a motherfucking
rap challenge!
I've never even
sang karaoke before.
I love to rap and write music.
This is my shit, like--
But are you good at it?
There's a difference
between people writing stuff
and being good at it.
Are you good at writing?
Are you good at doing music?
I went to school
for musical theater, like--
Going to school and doing it
are two separate things.
Oh, baby, I've been in
Broadway national tours.
Don't come for me.
I'm gonna sound like
Weird Al Yankovic.
I don't know if people
would consider Jackie Cox
really having a lot of flavor,
but I do love
writing parody lyrics.
Does anyone know
a good rhyme for naughty?
-Body.
-Ody, ody, ody.
Body. Body.
That's not a bad one.
Shoddy.
Shady lady, Peter Brady.
-[chuckles]
-You don't love that?
Well, start packing.
[all laugh]
All right, guys.
Well, so far I think
I'm that bitch, so...
Okay. Then we got to
figure out how we're dancing.
Are we ready
to put together a number?
Well, bring your ass
over here and let's see.
[speaking French]
-What?
-That's French.
I'm gonna take the
Meredith Vieira spot over here.
Okay, raise your hands
if you feel comfortable
choreographing at all.
I've had some experience
choreographing
like for other girls
back at home.
Widow?
I choreograph my talent numbers
when I do my pageants.
I have six backup dancers
sometimes,
and, I mean, but we dance.
-Right.
-I think that the people
that are used
to choreograph shows weekly,
should probably
take the lead.
Heidi and Widow should do it.
Before we do that,
who actually dances?
Okay, well, let me tell you,
I can't even touch my toes.
Oh.
I mean, in the girl group
that I am in,
I am the slowest learner.
I am so concerned right now.
It's hard working with bitches
who don't dance.
Can we at least
just not over-complicate it?
Like, let's keep it like
Spice Girls level of dancing.
Heidi and I are nominated
to be the leads
of this choreography.
I've watched this show enough.
If you are the captain
of this ship,
you are going down.
-Oh!
Where the magic happens.
Oh, my God.
It is now time for us
to start doing choreography
for I'm That Bitch.
Nicki Minaj is going to be
like 15 feet away from us.
And we're gonna
knock it out of the park.
I think we should have
our choreographers--
I'm looking at you two--
you open it since
we're gonna rely on you
for this first choreography.
All right, chocolate sister.
Let's choreograph this shit.
All right.verify
So I was thinking
that what we should do
is three come in from here,
three come in from here,
and you march down
as if you're--
we're the Bad Bitch Army.
♪ I--I--I'm a bitch ♪
♪ I--I'm a bitch,
I--I--I'm a bitch ♪
Of all of these girls,
I'm probably
the least coordinated.
Can people crump?
Can everybody crump?
Nope.
I don't know dance moves,
I don't know terminology.
I can't even count.
Five, six, seven, eight.
I'm just gonna look
so dumb doing that.
I'm gonna be honest right now.
But goddamn it, I'm gonna
fucking pull it together,verify
and I'm not gonna
let myself go home.
Hit it.
One, two, three, four.
-Okay.
-So three is a circle.
One, two, three, four.
Widow, she keeps on
pulling out the same moves.
She just keeps on
doing this little thing.
Just kept on keeping.
That's okay, but like
what else do you got?
Yeah, "don't you wish"
is when you should
start marching out.
I think that we should
switch it up just for variety.
Do something like, simple.
First we got
to get out here first
before we start switching it up.
I think if we had like
staggered movements
at certain times.
'Cause the focus is
supposed to be on the soloist.
Unless you want
the four of us
to just strut
on that first four.
They're already strutting,
I mean--
That's the way it is,
don't--don't--don't you wish?
-I like that.
-You could be that bitch.
Miss Jackie and Miss Brita.
You two ho's, shut up
and let me do my job.
Or we can just drop,
take a knee,
watch Brita go,
work, hype her, yeah.
No. That's--no.
I think if there were
like moments of like, pose.
Okay, switch, pose.
But we've seen routines
of bitches just posing.
[sighs]
I hope you can hear all that air
I just exclaimed from my body.
We can do like--
you know the type of--
like J-Lo choreography
where it's like
Human Centipede thing?
Yeah, I love that.
Not the human centipede!
I'm feeling some auras
from Widow.
Like I can feel the steam
coming off her wig.
Widow's frustrated,
and I don't blame her.
We can't get through
a single move.
People keep chiming in
on what they want to do.
That's when
you start behind me.
[all talking]
There are just too many
motherfucking chefs
in this goddamn kitchen.
I think we should go ahead,
because there's six verses,
and we're stuck
on the first one now.
Augh!
The time is ticking
and we all trying to put
our own little zest of lemon
in the choreography,
and it's not going anywhere.
I think someone
should take the lead.
-Yeah.
-We talk too much.
It's got to be
one of you two.
Yeah, yeah.
Do you want
to take the lead or--
Honestly, I don't know.
I've been trying
to give lead advice,
but no one wants to listen,
so I'm like, girl.
We want it, we want it.
If you feel uncomfortable
doing it,
then take the lead, honey,
please.
'Cause you're already coming up
with stuff that's good,
and I think
we just need to like do it.
Okay. So we need to find
the easy choreography
that we're gonna re-use
for each person's--
You know what?
I'm just gonna sit here
and be quiet. Fuck it.
Y'all want to do it?
Go ahead.
Show me what you got.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
Go ahead.
I think to open it up,
we could just do the posing
for like the first part,
and then choreograph later on.
Miss Widow, when I started
taking control a little bit,
I could feel like all daggers
pointing at me.
I think we should start
on stage.
I think that would be best.
So it starts
with me and Venom.
-She called me Venom.
-Venom, oh, my God.
-Why'd I call you Venom?
-Venom?
I think we should go a little
bit like cliche rap song.
When they start clapping,
we can just like twerk.
I can't twerk.
You can twerk, Brita.
Come on.
Brita has a hard time catching
up with the choreography,
and she seems to be
shaking in her boots.
In New York, she has
such a big reputation.
So I'm surprised to see her kind
of buckling under the pressure.
But you ain't that bitch.
It's unanimous, uh, uh,
I'm that bitch.
Wait. One minute. Sorry.
Okay, we have some work to do.
Homework.
We're gonna need to practice.
I mean, we still have parts
to like figure out, though.
At the end of the day,
I'm nervous as hell.
We barely have anything.
Like I can't go home.
I have to represent
for New York City.
[pretending to cry]
Oh, my God!subtitle
That's right.
Come on! First runway.
It is time for us to get ready
for the first judging,
and the motherfucking stakes
are high.
Last night's rehearsal
was shit,
and I am nervous as all hell.
I'm glad we got to work
a little bit more last night.
I stayed up all night long,
practicing, so...
I did not sleep a wink.
I didn't get to rehearse like
everyone else did last night,
so I'm a little worried.
Why? What's up?
I actually had
a really bad allergic reaction,
and I had to be taken
to the emergency room.
Last night?
After an hour of sleep,
I'm running on adrenaline,
so, I mean, we'll see.
We're relying on you
to turn some stunts and tricks
in this number, so...
I'm a little nervous
because back at home,
I'm known as a dancer.
And if I go home
on a dance challenge,
that's gonna be like the crack
of the century for me.
-Jackie.
-Yeah?
So I know that you have
a Persian background.
Yeah, we're like
international queens,
I was born in Canada,
but I'm half Persian.
I'm terrified
of Persian people seeing this
and like,
what's that gonna be like,
because it's not okay.
Like being gay is still
punishable by death in Iran.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Oh, my God.
I've never met
another Persian drag queen.
I know very few Persian members
of the queer community
because it's such a dishonor
to your family,
and that's where I struggle.
Because I really started
to embrace my Persian heritage,
but also knowing
that there's a pretty oppressive
government in Iran
that would rather see me dead.
My experience living in Morocco.
I moved there when I was 12,
which is like--
When you're queer, like 12
starts to get to be the age
where you start to realize
that you're different.
And being in a country,
like, say,
where you could go to jail
for being who you are.
Is it illegal in Morocco, too?
If you kiss someone in public,
people can call the cops
and you end up in jail.
Wow.
So I didn't come out
until I came back
to my country
because I didn't feel safe
at all.
We complain,
but there's places where
it is way harder for us
to just even exist.
But we got
to keep fighting for it,
because this election
is coming up,
and I don't want this country
to go the way of some others.
Nope, nope, amen.
I want any kid
who feels like
they're culturally not allowed
to be who they are
to realize that
you can be gay and a drag queen
and anything you want to be.
Are you guys feeling ready
for the choreography?
Yesterday during rehearsals
I was feeling very overwhelmed.
Oh, my God, me, too.
Widow, I can tell
you were getting
a little frustrated yesterday
in rehearsal.
You still mad at us?
No.
Did you let it go?
I know I'm gonna stand out
in my part,
but I'm worried
that Jackie and Brita
are gonna throw me under the bus
because I was nominated
as the dancing choreographer.
And I don't want to go down
with this ship.
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe
let your whole body talk ♪
RuPaul: And what?
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
She's got that super bass,
Michelle Visage.
Darling, did you use
the wrong door?
Did I?
I mean, I came in
where the queen
was supposed to come in through.
I think you're supposed
to be over here.
Please don't tell me
I did something wrong.
I don't want to get
in trouble by Ru.
[RuPaul laughs]
Oh, she's coming.
Okay. You're doing great.
[Michelle laughs]
I'm going as fast as I can, Ru.
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe
let your whole body talk ♪
RuPaul: And what?
Welcome to the main stage
of Nicki Minaj's Drag Race.
[all laugh]
Aah!
I'm so glad you're here.
Young Money in the house.
Brrrrr!
[laughs]
Her anaconda do,
Michelle Visage.
You should know
what my anaconda do.
Style superstar
Carson Kressley.
You ready?
I'm ready to pound the alarm!
Even though I've never
pounded anything in my life.
[all laugh]
I haven't. Not yet.
This week, in honor of our
extra-special guest judge,
we challenged
our first seven queens
to introduce themselves
with an original rap.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win!
Hey, world, it's the premiere
of I'm That Bitch.
♪ I--I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ That's the way it is ♪
♪ Don't--don't--
don't you wish ♪
♪ You could be that rich? ♪
♪ But you ain't that bitch ♪
♪ It's unanimous ♪
♪ I--I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ That's the way it is ♪
♪ Don't--don't--
don't you wish ♪
♪ You could be that rich? ♪
♪ But you ain't that bitch ♪
♪ It's unanimous ♪
♪ I--I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ Looking at these ho's,
you can tell I'm the one ♪
♪ 'Cause they be givin' up
and I'm not even done ♪
♪ I came here to win and
I ain't leavin' till I won ♪
♪ And while
I'm snatching crown ♪
♪ Imma have a lot of fun ♪
♪ It's Brita, bitch,
Imma say it again ♪
♪ If you don't remember,
better grab a pen ♪
♪ B-R-I-T-A, that's the end ♪
♪ I'm a fiercer bitch
than you've ever been ♪
♪ I'm that bitch don't
you know, you'll never be ♪
♪ Missouri girl ready
for the world to love me ♪
♪ I'm here to take the crown ♪
♪ Make my mama proud ♪
♪ Some say I'm weird,
but they're just lame ♪
♪ Go fix your mug,
we're not the same ♪
♪ My looks are flawless,
and, yeah, I'm so dusted ♪
♪ I'll have you all screaming
Crystal Methyd ♪
♪ Good morning, campers ♪
♪ Good morning, Miss Goode ♪
♪ Hope you saved room
for thirds ♪
♪ G-G-G-G-Gigi Goode ♪
♪ I'm a good girl ♪
♪ And I'm gonna bring
the fashion to this bad world ♪
♪ If you think
that I'm conceited ♪
♪ That's on you, girl ♪
♪ Mama, I don't want
to fight nobody ♪
♪ I'm just here to win
and leave a bitch on read ♪
♪ In case you forgot,
let me remind you that ♪
♪ I--I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ It's the way it is ♪
♪ Don't--don't--
don't you wish ♪
♪ You could be that rich? ♪
♪ But you ain't that bitch,
it's unanimous ♪
♪ I--I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ That's the way it is ♪
♪ Don't--don't--
don't you wish ♪
♪ You could be that rich? ♪
♪ But you ain't that bitch,
it's unanimous ♪
♪ I--I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ Heidi to the Closet
is her name ♪
♪ Being soft and supple
is her game ♪
♪ She's a young fierce diva
coming from the East Coast ♪
♪ And she's 'bout to slay
every one of her souls ♪
♪ She'll never back down
and she'll face her fears ♪
♪ You could even say
she's wise beyond her years ♪
♪ She's a small-town queen
with no time to waste ♪
♪ Her first bout up
and it's won first place ♪
♪ Hey, I'm Jackie Miss Cox
if you're naughty ♪
♪ Just like my girls Laverne,
Deb, and Courtney ♪
♪ Giving schatzi style,
take it to the floor ♪
♪ I'm not just the
Persian princess next door ♪
♪ Fab, funny, feminine,
and absolutely fierce ♪
♪ So salaam, nasty boys,
that's how I say cheers ♪
♪ From the streets of Hell's
Kitchen right to the runway ♪
♪ This beat is so bitchin'
you better say shantay ♪
♪ In case you forgot ♪
♪ Let me remind you that ♪
♪ I--I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ That's the way it is ♪
♪ Don't--don't--
don't you wish ♪
♪ You could be that rich? ♪
♪ But you ain't that bitch,
it's unanimous ♪
♪ I--I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ That's the way it is ♪
♪ Don't--don't--
don't you wish ♪
♪ You could be that rich? ♪
♪ But you ain't that bitch,
it's unanimous ♪
♪ I--I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ And I say, girl,
I is in town ♪
♪ The new look, one that
brings the house down ♪
♪ Watch me prance
my way to the ground ♪
♪ Are you ready?
Uh-uh, are you ready? ♪
♪ There's power in fashion,
it's what I bring to you ♪
♪ And I guarantee
you ain't no movie, boo ♪
♪ Somebody to New York
to au revoir ♪
♪ Fasten your seatbelt,
enjoy the ride ♪
♪ In it tonight
serving Aphrodite ♪
♪ KC MO
is where you can find me ♪
♪ I wouldn't try me
low key or high key ♪
♪ No, Widow Von'Du,
yes, bitch, I might be ♪
♪ The baddest bitch alive,
ain't no surprise ♪
♪ Girls get mad when
they look at these thighs ♪
♪ As they rub together
like they harmonize ♪
♪ And I'm still serving looks
when I'm eatin' these fries ♪
♪ In case you forgot ♪
♪ Let me remind you that ♪
♪ I--I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ That's the way it is ♪
♪ Don't--don't--
don't you wish ♪
♪ You could be that rich? ♪
♪ But you ain't that bitch,
it's unanimous ♪
♪ I--I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ I--I'm that bitch ♪
♪ That's the way it is ♪
♪ Don't--don't--
don't you wish ♪
♪ You could be that rich? ♪
♪ But you ain't that bitch,
it's unanimous ♪
♪ I--I--I'm that bitch ♪
[cheers and applause]
♪ Love you,
you're a superstar ♪
Category is Sparkle.
First up, Brita.
How's your head...wrap?
[all laugh]
Brita: I am serving sparkle
everywhere.
There are so many mirrors
on this jumpsuit,
I am a damn disco ball.
Nicki: Yes, ma'am.
RuPaul: Brita, please.
[all laugh]
Crystal Methyd.
Carson: What the hell?
Crystal: Walking down
this runway for the first time,
I am feeling hot.
This outfit represents my drag
because I love dressing up
like a beautiful monster.
Nicki: Yummy.
RuPaul:
I guess it's today, Satan.
[all laugh]
Gigi Goode.
Carson: Worst case
of helmet hair I've ever seen.
Michelle: She's jaded.
Gigi: Gigi does not
use rhinestones,
so tonight on the runway
I'm using glitter.
Just head to toe, clean lines.
I feel stunning.
Nicki: Yes, chicness.
Love it.
Michelle:
The bike still running?
Heidi N Closet.
Michelle:
Heidi sings the blues.
Heidi: I am living
my rich woman fantasy,
and I'm going slow.
And I want them to count every
last one of these riboles.
I want them to know she paid
a nice dollar for this gown.
RuPaul:
Come on, pussycat wig!
Michelle: Yes!
Carson: I got to pick up some
ramen noodles. That reminds me.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Jackie Cox.
You've got to climb
Mount Everest
to reach
The Valley of the Dolls.
Jackie: I'm walking out like
I'm emerging from her boudoir.
And she takes her doll
and that doll will make her
sparkle, Jackie, sparkle!
You got a prescription
for those?
Jackie: This outfit is very
representative of Jackie
because it's a little retro,
but has a little bit
of that modern twist.
RuPaul:
Miss Bouvier, you stay.
Carson: Oh, bee-hive now.
RuPaul: That's a reach.
I'll leave the way I came in.
Nicky Doll.
Carson:
I've heard of feathered hair,
but never a feathered bosom.
Nicky: My runway look tonight
is iron, metal-like feathers.
Vixen makeup, bad bitch that
you don't want to mess with.
And I'm here to con-kere.
Con-kere?
Conquer. Conquer.
I'm here to conquer.
RuPaul: Mask for mask.
Widow Von'Du.
Oh, damn!
She's ready for takeoff.
Michelle: She is.
Nicki: I love the earrings.
Obsessed.
Widow:
My drag is in your face,
like you can't help
but look at it
and that's what
my sparkle look is.
It's what Judy Jetson
would wear
after she took over
the company.
Now she saying, "Bitch
better have my sprockets."
[laughs]
RuPaul: It's like
the Sydney Opera House.
It is.
Why go all the way there
when you can just look
at her shoulders?
RuPaul: Yeah.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Welcome, ladies.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques,
starting with Brita.
Hello, Brita.
Hi, nice to meet you.
The thing that stands out to me
about you is your energy.
You seem inviting.
That's really, really
a good thing in show business.
Your looks in the fashion show
were both very beautiful.
You know how to shape your body.
I can tell that just from
seeing you on one episode.
This runway look
certainly is sparkly,
but what I'm really appreciating
are all the details.
You're creating a narrow waist
with the peplum flare.
You look like a pro.
Thank you.
Your lyrics didn't really
tell me much about you
except that you want to win.
And what I love
about what we're doing here
is we're taking the time
to really get to know
each and every one of you.
Because when
you're all crammed together,
we don't get as much time.
But when we want to get to know
you, we want to get to know you.
100%.
I know they said
you didn't say too much.
But as a rapper, to me,
what you said about yourself
was that you're cocky,
you are optimistic,
and you don't doubt yourself.
And when it comes to rap
or show business,
I think those three things
are actually really, really
freakin' good!
Thank you so much. Aah!
Up next, Crystal Methyd.
Are those boots Prada?
No.
It was The Devil Wears Prada
joke. Anyway...
Just note to the director.
Put some laugh track
under his last statement.
[all laugh]
My favorite thing
that you did
was that Freddy Krueger fashion.
It was very gorgeous,
very chic.
The bandages, the hair,
genius idea.
With your rap, I love that
you said "Make my mama proud,"
because ultimately,
that's what we all want to do.
I mean, that's what I wanted
to do when I started rapping.
So, tch-tch,
good job with that.
Tonight, she's cute,
she's costume-y.
I can't wait to see what else
you got in your wheelhouse.
Thank you.
Up next, Gigi Goode.
Your fashion show choices
were fantastic.
You love a helmet, too.
Three out of four looks
have incorporated helmets.
I do love a helmet.
[all laugh]
What I loved the most
about your rap
is that you had
a double entendre in it.
I'm just here to win
and leave a bitch on read.
Literally,
I would steal that line.
Like, that's a real rap line,
and I want you
to really understand
that's a real rap line.
Because you're talking
about reading a bitch
and also leaving them on read
on your phone.
So when I saw
that you said that,
I was like, who the fuck
is this bitch?
[all laugh]
Up next, Heidi N Closet.
-Heidi N Closet.
-Yeah.
What made you choose that name?
I was from a very small town
and there's
a lot of straight men
who would always try
to get my goodies.
So basically it was
a lot of undercover brothers
trying to holler at you
where you from.
Oh, all of them.
Heidi N Closet,
What was your second choice?
Sasha Nicole Fierce,
but you didn't--
[laughs]
-No.
-Okay, this is
where I'm gonna press
the trap door button.
Aah!
Where are you from?
Small-town girl, you said.
I'm from Ramseur,
North Crack-i-lacky,
and we're outnumbered
by chickens.
B-b-b-b-b-bawk.
[laughs]
In the fashion show,
you know, you had a moment
with your headpiece falling off.
You did pick it up and carry on,
so I want
to applaud you on that.
Thank you.
And then this look
on the runway,
it's opalescent oppalance.
But I hate, hate, hate
your hair and makeup today.
The wig and the makeup
could have enhanced
your face even more
to match this beautiful gown
that you have on.
What's your experience like
in this challenge?
It's been crazy.
Last night
I got back to the hotel
and just welts and hives
just started down my arms
and down my legs,
and I had to go to the ER.
Wow.
So you had
an allergic reaction last night?
Yes, I did.
We narrowed it down
to the hotel's detergent
or something that I may have ate
for the first time, kale.
That'll do it.
Kale will not do that, no.
Goddamn kale.
I'll never eat kale again.
Don't--oh, my goodness.
Never!
If you were hospitalized
last night
and you came out here
and did the performance you did,
you are a superstar
and you have a very genuine
spirit and your spirit shines.
Up next, Jackie Cox.
Salaam, RuPaul June.
Sounds delicious.
I'll have two.
I want to talk about
your fashion looks right away
because they were
some of my favorites.
I loved the Spring.
it was very sixties, very
Laugh-In, very Oleg Cassini.
And I love this look.
Your rap was so fantastic.
I really got to know
who you were from that.
I love that you said
"Just like my girls, Laverne,
Deb, and Courtney."
And I love that you rhymed
naughty with Courtney
because most people would have
had the obvious rhyme scheme
for a word like naughty,
you know.
I love that you're
a proud Persian queen.
One thing
that I am going to tell you
because you are of Persian
decent and your hair is dark,
we're already seeing
the bleed-through on the beard.
This is going to be
the bane of your existence.
But if you need help
with something,
now is the time to look around
and say "I love
the way you do this.
Can you give me some tips?"
You got it, Michelle.
All right, we've got another
Nicky in our midst, Nicky Doll.
Hi, RuPaul.
Let's talk about
your fashion looks.
That beautiful kind of hasidic
meets Jean Paul Gaultier,
which was really chic.
This look is something
that like Pink or Robyn
would wear on a tour.
Like, it is stunning.
Your face is just
shutting everybody down.
You look like a Barbie
out of the box.
Thank you so much.
I wanted to let you know also
that I named myself
Nicky Doll after you.
Well, you are doing me proud.
Tonight in your performance,
I felt you a little bit
unsure of yourself.
What was going on with that?
I just feel like
I've been watching the show
for so many years overseas.
And standing there
in front of all of you,
it was just overwhelming.
You never have
to second guess it.
The reason you're here
is because Ru picked you.
So just let those voices go away
'cause they don't matter.
How do you say saboteur
in French?
-Saboteur.
-It's a French word.
[mouthing]
Oh, you knew that?
Put the laugh track in
over that.
I got it. I laughed.
Up next, Widow Von'Du.
I love the Missy Elliot
kind of reference
with the neoprene neon.
You put your thing down,
you flipped it and reversed it
with that hood action.
Ooh, going there.
Yeah, you know I'm into
a little bit of rap myself.
[all laugh]
What I loved most was your rap
and the performance.
It was some next-level shit.
Thank you.
Lyrically, Miss Lady,
when I heard the line,
"'cause they rub together
like they harmonize,"
I was like in here screaming.
I was just like,
yes, thank you!
RuPaul: Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
Now, while you untuck backstage,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right,
now just between us Barbs,
what do you think?
Brita.
I mean, I just like her energy.
She's so positive
and has a joy about her
that I kind of
want to see more of that.
When a person
can make you feel happy,
that transference of energy,
like that goes a long way.
Crystal Methyd.
I get a little bit worried
when they pigeon-hole themselves
into one specific thing.
'Cause she had the same makeup
on for the fashion show.
If she can step up
with the fashion and the makeup
and match that
with how funny she is
and how charismatic she is,
then she is going to be
like such a big threat.
Gigi Goode.
She nailed it
on a different level
with that green and the latex.
Oh, my God.
And it looks like she has
a personality under that, too.
'Cause a lot of times,
fashion queens will come on,
they're like,
"I'm fashion, I'm fashion,"
and there's
no personality there,
So to have her like that with
a personality is very exciting.
Heidi N Closet.
It is my job to convince her
to change that name.
Worst name ever,
but in the performance,
I mean, she was like reenacting
Death Becomes Her.
Her head was like everywhere.
When you can perform like that
while still lip syncing
and like slay-ana all day,
like that in itself is a show.
I think Slay-ana is a better
name then Heidi N Closet.
[all laugh]
Absolutely.
Jackie Cox.
Well, I love all Cox.
-Same.
-Especially Jackie.
She's very smart.
Her lyrics showed that.
She's in on the joke with us
and like knows how to play to us
without playing to us.
I like that.
She gets fashion.
She gets period fashion.
She gets fashion, period.
[all laugh]
Nicky Doll, en francais.
Her performance
in and of itself was good.
But when she was doing
the group parts,
I saw her kind of really
laying back and being insecure.
So I worry about that.
But something about that accent
just gave me everything
I didn't know I needed.
Like, coupled with the fact
that she was more laidback
in the performance
to me made her now turn into
this mysterious Paris girl.
She knows how to do
her own makeup,
she knows high fashion,
and she's
drop-dead beautiful, period.
Widow Von'Du.
Her Spring runway was fun.
It was like this is bad-ass.
When you put her on that stage,
she shines.
And that's what we love,
seeing people perform.
At the end of the day,
you can wear a beautiful dress,
beautiful this, beautiful that.
But we like attitude
and charisma on the stage
and energy and fun,
and she brought all of that.
I want to see more, more, more.
I want to see what
the Widow's gonna Von'Du!
Up in her!
Now, Nicki, I'm curious.
What would your I'm That Bitch
rap sound like?
Okay, I would say
something like this.
♪ First, I'm that bitch,
Imma only say it one time ♪
♪ I body all these bitches
with just one rhyme ♪
♪ Chew 'em up, spit 'em out
like it's gum time ♪
♪ Chinese bangs,
ponytail in a bun time ♪
♪ Fat ass and my titties
stay perky ♪
♪ Bad ass, but I'm still
a little quirky ♪
♪ American Express in my Burqy ♪
♪ If he got a real big P,
he could hurt me ♪
♪ Real rap
we don't with the sides ♪
♪ Came from nothing
I beat the odds ♪
♪ Pretty queen thing,
but young Nicki Minaj ♪
♪ Queen RuPaul, Carson,
and Ms. Visage ♪
-Yes!
-I love it.
I love it!
Yay, Nicki.
That's what I would say,
something like that, yeah.
Well, that's why
you're the queen.
Thank you.
All right, silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Brita, grab a pen
and sign yourself up
for another week.
-You're safe.
-Thank you so much.
You may step
to the back of the stage.
Jackie Cox.
You've got real Persian-ality.
[all laugh]
You're safe.
Thank you.
Crystal Methyd.
You've got great style,
but remember,
the devil's in the details.
You're safe.
Nicky Doll, the first rule
of Drag Race
is do not second-guess yourself.
You're safe.
Thank you.
You may join the other girls.
Heidi N Closet.
Your performance
gave us a severe reaction.
You're safe.
You may join the other girls.
Thank you.
I'm in the bottom?
I am trying so hard not to cry.
I want to throw some shit,verify
but I can't
because ain't nothin'
close.subtitle
I don't even know what to think.
Did I really do that bad?
Gigi Goode and Widow Von'Du.
I'm sorry, my dears, but you...
are the top two queens
of the week.
[applause]
[laughs]
This week, no one's going home.
But there will be one winner.
Two queens stand before me.
Prior to tonight,
you were asked to prepare
a lip sync performance
of Starships by Nicki Minaj.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me,
earn the first win
of the season,
and a cash tip.
$5.000.
Child.
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing] for your life!
Girl, I'm revving my engine.
Fucking Nicki Minaj
is waiting to see meverify -
Shit, or Fuck.
lip sync to her song.
Oh, trust,
I am not losing this, bitch.
'Cause I'm about to wear you out
like good beef.
[snaps fingers]
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
[music plays]
One moment.
[all laugh]
♪ Uh, let's go to the beach
each let's go get a wave ♪
♪ They, they,
what they gonna say ♪
♪ Have a drink, clink,
found a Bud Light ♪
♪ Bad bitches like me
is hard to come by ♪
♪ The patron own,
let's go get it on ♪
♪ The zone on,
yes, I'm in the zone ♪
♪ Is it two, three?
Leave a good tip ♪
♪ Imma blow off my money
and don't give two ♪
♪ I'm on the floor, floor,
I love to dance ♪
♪ So give me more, more
till I can't stand ♪
♪ Get on the floor, floor
like it's your last chance ♪
♪ If you want more, more,
then here I am ♪
♪ Starships were meant to fly ♪
♪ Hands up and touch the sky ♪
♪ Let's do this one last time ♪
♪ Can't stop,
we're higher than a mother-- ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ We're higher
than a mother-- ♪
Gigi: My favorite thing to do
when I lip sync
is just be so seamlessly
gorgeous and fashion.
♪ We're higher
than a mother-- ♪
And then flip it around
and turn it into comedy.
♪ Now everybody let me hear you
say ray, ray, ray ♪
♪ Now spend all your
money 'cause today payday ♪
♪ And if you're a G,
you a G-G-G ♪
♪ My name is Onika,
you can call me Nicki ♪
♪ Get on the floor, floor
like it's your last chance ♪
♪ If you want more, more,
then here I am ♪
♪ Starships were meant to fly ♪
♪ Hands up and touch the sky ♪
♪ Let's do this one last time ♪
♪ Can't stop,
we're higher than a mother-- ♪
I can tell that Miss Nicki
is getting
her motherfucking life!
♪ Higher than a mother-- ♪
If you ever need a bitch
in a video, call a ho ♪
♪ Starships were meant to fly ♪
♪ Let's do this one more time ♪
♪ Hands up and touch the sky ♪
♪ Let's do this one last time ♪
♪ Can't stop,
we're higher than a mother-- ♪
♪ We're higher
than a mother-- ♪
[cheers and applause]
Epic-ness!
O-M-G!
Wow. That was
a fantastic lip sync.
And I've made my decision.
[exhales]
Widow Von'Du...
you're a winner, baby.
[applause]
Epic, epic, epic, epic,
epic, epic, epic.
It means so much.
Con-drag-ulations.
You've won $5.000 provided
by Bubly Sparkling Water.
Thank you.
What? [laughs]
Gigi Goode, you were fantastic,
and you are safe
to slay another day.
Thank you so much.
And con-drag-ulations, ladies.
But don't get too comfortable,
because there are more queens
clocking in soon.
What do you mean, Ru?
No more ho's!
I'm not letting them take
my spot in this competition.
And remember this,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an "Amen" up in here?
-Amen!
All right,
now let the music play!
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪register
to vote
RuPaul: Next time
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
Welcome to the second premiere
of RuPaul's Drag Race 2020.
-Mm!
-You're a feast!
[all laugh]
Are you ready
to meet the other queens?
Bitch, what?
-What's going on?
-What's happening?
I hope these bitches are
ready to eat the leftovers.
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ I am American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪
♪  Am-Am-Am-Am-American,
American, American ♪
♪ I am American, American ♪
♪ The red, white, and blue ♪
♪ Just like you, too ♪