This is
an impressive first showing.
This is not a makeup
that works.
You're all my children now.
Previously on Face Off...
16 artists arrived
in Los Angeles
for a life-and-death
final audition.
- None of you are on the show yet.
- Oh, dear.
Dina's wood nymph
brought her the win...
Thank you so much.
But Scott and Gabby
did not make the cut.
14 artists survived.
Face Off!
And tonight, they will take on
their first spotlight challenge.
Each of these items represents
an actual gangster.
And though
many will struggle...
We're in trouble.
...one will snuff out
the competition.
Absolutely stellar makeup.
It was a poor idea.
In the end,
only one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- Wow.
- Oh, wow.
- This is crazy.
- We arrive at the house.
And it's gorgeous.
- Whoa, no way!
- Yeah!
I can't believe
we're staying here.
The house is amazing.
- Ping-pong table!
- Wow.
I see photos of makeup
from previous cast members
representing life and death.
There's this koi pond
and a pool outside.
We are gonna have
an awesome time.
Face Off!
Whoo-hoo!
Today we get
to Universal Studios.
Oh, look.
A sweet dodge.
We're looking at all of
the buildings and all the sets,
and it's unbelievable.
I see McKenzie down there,
and she's standing next
to peanuts and bananas,
and there's a big tuna.
This doesn't really
make any sense.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
Welcome to New York Street,
here in the heart
of Universal Studios Hollywood,
home to one of the most
historic back lots
in the film industry.
Countless Oscar-winning
films were shot here,
including The Sting
and Dick Tracy,
which are both widely regarded
as classic gangster films.
From Scarface
to Sammy The Bull,
old-school gangsters often
took on colorful nicknames
that represented their
appearances or dirty deeds.
Films like Dick Tracy
and Sin City
took these nicknames
and used them
to inspire
their over-the-top makeups.
So in this spotlight challenge,
you will create your very own
over-the-top crime boss...
inspired by the nickname
of a real-life gangster.
- Awesome.
- I'm really thrilled
that we have this challenge,
because I'm a huge fan
of Dick Tracy.
Those characters
are so far out there.
Each of these items
represents the nickname
of an actual dead gangster.
Working in teams of two,
you'll choose one of these items
and use it to inspire
your character.
All right, guys, your randomly
assigned teams are...
Gwen and Drew,
Rachael and Vince,
Doc and Stella,
Barry and Sasha,
George and Cig,
- Dina and Jason...
- Awesome.
Keaghlan and Damien.
Go ahead and stand
with your new teammate.
Gwen and Drew,
you have first pick.
- Go ahead.
- Shark.
All right,
in honor of Sharknado 2,
which airs tomorrow night
on SyFy,
you chose
Michele "The Shark" Sindona.
Rachael and Vince.
Typewriter.
You have Charles
"The Typewriter" Nicoletti.
- Doc and Stella.
- Needles.
Leonard "Needles" Gianola.
- Barry and Sasha.
- Clock.
Allie "Tick Tock" Tannenbaum.
- George and Cig.
- The tuna.
- Tony "Big Tuna" Accardo.
- Yes.
- Dina and Jason.
- Peanuts.
John "Peanuts" Tronolone.
Keaghlan and Damien.
All right,
we're gonna go with the truck.
You have
Opal "Mack Truck" Long.
Now I have a special surprise
for you.
I've brought someone
who knows gangster movie makeup
better than anyone else.
He won an Academy Award
for his innovative makeups
in Dick Tracy,
and he also won two Emmys
for his visual effects work
on Battlestar Galactica.
- No way.
- Please give a warm welcome
to the incredible Doug Drexler.
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
Whoo!
I'm a huge fan of his.
I watched Dick Tracy
so many times as a kid
that the tape wore out.
Oh, boy.
Wow, wow.
Doug will be joining us
on the reveal stage
- to give his final thoughts.
- Oh, I can't wait. Oh, boy.
What advice can you give
these guys?
The important thing to remember
is if it's too on the nose,
it probably
isn't interesting enough.
It has to be a turn of the screw
into fantasy.
But you don't want to take
your makeup so far
where people can't
relate to it.
That's fantastic advice.
Thank you so much
for being here today.
My pleasure.
All right, guys, I want you
to get started on your designs.
When you're finished,
go check out that lab.
Yeah.
My dad and I will be by
later on
to check in on your progress.
Good luck.
Definitely some big, like,
bruiser knuckles and stuff.
George and I got
Tony "Big Tuna" Accardo.
He should have a cigar
stuck in his fat wrinkle.
That would be cool.
We don't want to make
a straight fish guy,
so we give him
fishlike features.
And his bio says
that he was notorious
for using a baseball bat.
So we think it'd be really funny
if we switch out
the baseball bat
and he just kills people
with a giant tuna.
He's sleeping
with the fishes, see?
We got to play up on that.
He ratted people out
when he got caught.
Sasha and I have the clock.
And our gangster is
Allie "Tick Tock" Tannenbaum.
He was a stool pigeon.
He was a rat.
So I want to incorporate
that idea into it.
I really don't like rat makeup.
So are we good
with this direction?
Like a rat face?
No, because I kind of
love mine.
I have this idea
to make
this awesome grandfather clock.
We have to represent
a gangster.
Like, where's
the gangster element?
That's the evil face.
And the mustache
is the hands on the clock.
I don't think Sasha's concept
is very gangster,
so it's not gonna work.
Stella and I have
Leonard "Needles" Gianola.
Needles.
Kind of like when a porcu--
How a porcupine spikes.
We're thinking let's do
something with the hair.
Also, he is an assassin,
so let's have some sort of slit
in the fingers,
and these needles would come out
as his weapon.
For the hat,
we can get a fedora.
And then if we get a feather,
it'll represent a fin, you know?
Gwen and I decide to take
the shark's jaw.
I have this really cool idea
for this shark guy.
He should have
really sharp features.
And since our object
was the teeth,
I decide that we should make
these really awesome shark jaw
dental appliances
so that he'll actually have,
like, the mouth of a shark.
This guy's like a monster.
Hey, everyone,
let's go check out the lab.
We're leaving
to head to the lab,
and we decide to do
Barry's concept of the rat.
This isn't the direction
I would have gone,
but I just want to work well
with a partner.
Barry seems to really know
what he's talking about,
so I'm going to trust him.
To the lab!
Oh, man.
Oh, dude, we're here.
- Oh, radical.
- This is it. This is it.
- Yeah!
- Awesome.
We get to the lab
for the first time,
and it has everything I could
possibly ever want to use.
Wow.
The first thing that stands out
are the rainbow colors
of Kryolan.
I'm really stoked to use those.
So we pick our models,
and it's time to get started.
So it's day one in the lab.
We have six hours.
And Gwen and I know that we need
to get the face done and molded.
First thing I sculpt
is the shape of the gums
onto the life cast.
I'm doing the cowl.
I want this guy
to be top-heavy,
like a shark who doesn't really
have shoulders.
Lettering is kind of
important, because it has to be
sort of like it's from
a machine, it's typewritten.
Charles "The Typewriter"
Nicoletti
is our real-life gangster.
Our concept is
this big, brute boxer
with these typewriter
brass knuckles
and the names of his victims
carved in his head.
Glenn, Neville,
- um, Ve, and Lois, right?
- Yeah, I like it. Yeah.
Our makeup will require
a lot of skin detail.
It's gonna be
really time-consuming,
so I'm hoping
that we can pull it off.
Movie magic.
I start blocking out the cowl
while George starts
blocking out the face.
What do you think of this
so far?
Yeah.
We really want to make
a badass makeup.
I can't wait to have
Doug Drexler look at it.
And I hope he doesn't
tear it apart.
If we have the head tilt,
which way do you think
it should tilt?
This way?
Our gangster's name
is John "Peanuts" Tronolone.
And he was
very greed-oriented,
so we want to bring that
into our makeup.
So Jason and I are going
to make the top of the head
more fantasy by giving it
a peanut texture.
We're gonna keep
the peanut shell open on top
and throw a bunch of jewels
and money up there
to show that he's
a flashy, sleazy kind of dude.
Well, I was gonna go
for, like, the venting,
like, on the side of that car.
Our real-life gangster
is Opal "Mack Truck" Long,
who was built
like a mack truck.
So Keaghlan and I
decide to create
a half gangster/half truck
hybrid.
We want to do four headlight
appliances on a hat,
a hood emblem on the collarbone,
as well as a face appliance.
How can you have a gangster
challenge without a dirty rat?
Concept is a dude
with really big ears,
reminiscent of rat,
but still have
a human anatomy going on.
Sasha's working on the face,
and I'm on the cowl.
Making the face pristine
takes away from it, you know?
I think we can come together
and make this work.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
Oh, my God.
Michael Westmore is here.
How are you?
We get our first one-on-one
with Michael Westmore.
He's worked on countless films,
and I'm uber-worried
about what he's got to say.
So our guy was an assassin.
And the way
he assassinates people
is he will take the quills
from his head.
And then tomorrow
we're going to fabricate,
like, an actual
poison dart system.
If you actually incorporated
maybe these
into just little finger cups,
that way it's just, hello, bam.
Okay.
This is the peanut inside?
Yeah, yeah.
Your paint job is gonna
be extremely important,
because you have to try
to sell the idea
this is a peanut,
not a broken egg.
- Yeah.
- Right.
Tell us about what
you're doing conceptually.
Yeah. How are you working
the clock into your sculpture?
Well, we're actually doing
a ratlike character.
Um, another element
of the real person
was that he was a rat.
You've been given
a challenge...
- Yup.
- ...and it isn't here.
How does this really represent
the clock?
I don't know
how to answer that.
We are in trouble.
Now I'm actually
a little bit worried.
Coming up...
I totally screwed the pooch
on that. Shit.
We're screwed.
I really like your character.
You've got some serious issues.
How does this really
represent the clock?
It's day one
of our gangster challenge,
and Mr. Westmore isn't fond
of our idea.
You've been given a challenge,
and it isn't here.
We don't see how the clock
really ties in with your makeup.
I don't know
how to answer that.
Okay. If you put a time bomb
on him or something...
Something to incorporate
that idea.
But you need to sell
the idea of the clock.
- Okay.
- Okay. For sure.
- We'll make sure we do that.
- All right.
- Thanks so much.
- Thank you.
Now we're trying to figure out
how to work in a clock.
He's a ticking time bomb.
We can make dynamite sticks.
I can do fabrication
to get, you know,
get it attached to him.
I really want
to do Barry's vision,
so whatever he's saying,
I'm just gonna really try
to work with it.
- We'll see what happens.
- Okay.
We picked typewriter,
and there's gonna be words
branded into his head.
He's also got brass knuckles
with letters on them.
You're gonna have to make
your letters
or your exclamation points
and things like that
very legible.
- Yeah.
- Good-bye, everybody.
- Bye.
- Good luck, guys.
- Thank you.
I don't think
I have enough time to mold this.
No, you know what?
I'm gonna do it right now.
Do it.
Run, run, run.
You make a mold by layering
a plaster-like substance
over your sculpture.
Once the mold hardens,
you clean it out
and you pour in foam
or silicone,
which will eventually become
your prosthetic.
There'll be
some lettering here.
I was hoping to get
the face molded today.
But we're running out of time,
so we're going
to mold it tomorrow.
I decide to make a stencil
for the names
so that the writing looks like
it's from a typewriter.
We'll go in and make incisions
where this letter should be.
But it's extremely
time-consuming.
I can't believe you're cutting
all this shit out.
You and me both.
All right, guys.
30 minutes left.
All right, start scraping.
Ten minutes, guys.
- Fuck.
- These are cool.
All right, everybody.
That's time.
It's the end of the day, and
I'm feeling a little frustrated.
I'm disappointed that we didn't
get to do any of the moldings,
and I'm feeling
a little nervous.
We have a lot to do tomorrow
so that we don't fall behind.
- Yes.
- Yay, yay, yay, yay.
Whoo!
It's day two
of the gangster challenge,
and we have 9 1/2 hours
in the lab.
That's cool.
I didn't get to see
the whole back half yesterday.
What we have to do today
is finish the headpiece
and figure out some way
to incorporate poison
and get his actual weapon
incorporated into the makeup.
- All of this?
- Yup.
Mr. Westmore said
he would like to see
the needles come out
of the character's fingers,
and that's when I decided
to life-cast my fingers...
We're doing these two, right?
- Yup.
- So we could sculpt on those
and create some type of
finger cup for needles to wear.
Let me know if there's anything
I can do with one hand.
Symmetry,
that isn't too important.
- We can adjust it.
- It looks fantastic.
Our big task today is getting
the chest sculpture completed.
As Keaghlan finishes up
the smaller pieces,
I start sculpting out
some more headlight details.
Once I'm done molding
all of our smaller designs,
we can both start tackling
this big chest mold
that we have to get done.
That looks good.
I like that.
This is perfectly jolly.
The foam piece fits perfectly
on the cowl,
so we just start molding that
right away.
So while George is doing that,
I foam-fabricate
the fat suit.
It's really important
to keep the proportions correct,
so it'll look like
a realistic big, fat tuna man.
On the neck,
a very visible spot.
You know, maybe this side.
So this morning there's
a lot of details to work out,
and we don't have
a lot of time.
Stella, there are two Ls
in your name, right?
Yeah, baby.
Rachael and I thought,
wouldn't it be cool
if the victims' names were also
some of the cast members' names?
I'm carving the names
into the cowl,
and Vince is doing the same
for the face piece.
We need to get this done
as quickly as possible,
because we have
to start molding.
We should texture this,
just take the sponge
and chip brush to it.
Dina and I have to finish
sculpting the cowl and the belly
as fast as possible,
so we can get the molds
ready for foam.
We have a lot
to get done today.
I am so happy.
We see that the face
lines up with he cowl.
So I don't have
to fix anything.
It's good to have that weight
off of our shoulders.
It slopes down. We're not gonna
have any problems with that.
- I was so worried about that.
- Yeah.
We've refined the concept
a little bit
by adding a time bomb
with a clock.
So I'm really excited
to do my clock and not a rat.
I make a whole bunch
of sticks of dynamite,
and I'm gonna attach
a whole bunch
of complicated-looking
electrical cords.
I'm feeling a little better
about this situation.
We've finally got
a cohesive thing going.
Better late than never.
Fat suit's ready to test out.
Oh, shit.
I go to check out
Cig's fat suit,
and it looks awesome.
Oh, yeah.
Who's gonna be sleeping
with the fishes?
It's a lot of fun,
and I'm just excited
to show the judges.
- Beautiful.
- Nice.
No.
Jason and I are trying
to get our mold apart,
and it's stuck in there.
_
I'm on top of the table
holding the mold,
and Dina's trying
to pull that core out.
Oh, shit.
_
The bottom of the mold cracks.
If it completely breaks,
then we're screwed.
Oh, shit.
It's broken here.
It's day two
of our gangster challenge,
and Jason and I are trying
to get our mold apart.
But it's cracking.
If it completely breaks,
we're screwed.
- It's coming.
- It's coming? Yes!
Thank God.
We're gonna have
a pretty bad seam,
but hopefully
with all the textures
going on in the peanuts,
it won't be that noticeable.
Ow.
I need to make the shark teeth.
I use
a thermo-sensitive plastic.
It comes in little pallets,
and you put it in hot water,
and it melts
and becomes pliable.
And then you can shape it
into whatever you want.
I want to fabricate
a working cigar.
So I have the idea
to put a LED light
in the end of it.
I want to make it smoke too,
so I'm gonna take
what's called a bulb syringe
and load it up
with baby powder.
The model can give it a little
puff, and it'll just... whoo.
- Oh.
- Looks good to me.
Vince and I
took too much time sculpting,
so we're behind schedule.
It's really important to get
these pieces finished today,
because we don't want to have
to run our cowl in poly foam.
- Damien, do you have time?
- Yeah, a little bit.
Thanks.
All righty.
We have a lot of clay
stuck in our cowl mold.
And we have to be really careful
when removing it,
because there's so much detail.
If anybody's not doing nothing,
Vince and Rachael need help
cleaning their mold out.
We're getting down to the wire.
- How long do we have?
- About 20 minutes.
The mold is just grabbing
this clay and not letting go.
The clock is ticking, and we're
taking the clay out as fast as we can.
We need paper towels!
Everyone's helping
get these things clean,
and I am so grateful.
All right, good.
That's time, everybody.
- Blood, sweat and tears.
- Yeah.
All right, high five.
We get our molds done.
I'm concerned,
because Rachael and I
still have a lot to do.
So tomorrow is gonna be tough.
So it's application day,
and we have four hours
in the lab
and one hour at last looks.
The first thing I do is start
seaming that chest appliance.
And Keaghlan starts finishing up
other little things,
like the hat.
Oh.
Our cowl is a mess.
There are steam packets
everywhere...
Fuck.
And the seam is pretty bad.
So we need to trim that up
and patch it,
get it nice and smooth,
so it won't be so obvious.
- I'm Doc.
- What up, Doc?
Going down? Nice.
_
- Oh, sick.
- Yeah.
Our plan for application day
is to tag-team everything.
So Sasha puts
a bald cap on him,
and I start seaming the cowl.
There's a little bit of damage
around the seam,
but once I glue it back down,
it's not gonna be too much
of an issue.
The first thing that we do
is Stella applies the face.
In the meantime,
I paint the headpiece.
Let's talk about this hair
one more time.
You want to just do
brown washes over it?
Yes. Brown washes.
I do a white stipple.
And you'll really see that
come through
once you start layering
other colors on it.
While Vince is starting
the paint job,
I need to make
these brass knuckles.
So I take L200,
which is
a soft fabricating foam,
and start cutting out shapes,
trying to imagine
what it would look like
if I were making real ones.
I'm not super happy
with the brass knuckles.
I wish I had a couple more hours
to spend on them,
because they're such an
important part of our concept,
but they will have to do.
One hour, guys.
The beast is heavy.
Stella and I realize,
with the headpiece,
the edges on it
are pretty rough.
I think we should cut this
to a sharp line.
The edges are so thick,
it's gonna look like big blobs
of goo on his head.
So I decide to cut it,
make it a hard edge.
It looks lumpy,
but we're gonna just use it
and whatever happens, happens.
I totally screwed the pooch
on that.
Gwen and I have to get
his teeth in.
How's that feel?
He doesn't have
as much mobility with his mouth
as I was hoping,
but they look badass,
so that's all we care about.
While Dina's throwing down
some flesh tones,
I go ahead
and start hot-gluing
all the jewels and poker chips
inside the peanut head.
We tried as best we could
to clean up all the seams,
but it's still bugging me.
I'm not sure where we stand.
I think it all depends
on how last looks come together.
I'm keeping the hair
super sparse over here,
because hair doesn't really grow
on skin this damaged.
Barry started the detail work
with the paint,
while I lay the hair.
This is not my best work,
but I'm just rushing,
because it's better to have
the whole head covered in hair
than only half of the head.
He can look ratty.
He's a rat, right?
- Yup.
- Guys, that's 15 minutes.
That's gonna have
headlights on it.
This edge on the hair
looks really stupid.
And, quite frankly,
I'm worried.
I think we should bring
a little shading in here.
I need this paint job
to sell this piece.
That's time, guys!
I don't know that we're gonna
pull it together in last looks.
Coming up...
We're painting like crazy,
but I don't think
we're making it look better.
I'm really concerned
about how dark our paint job is.
I'm not fond of this makeup.
This is a great idea.
It cuts a striking figure.
All right,
we have the latex out.
- That should be, like--
- It should be in the bin.
We have an hour in last looks.
We have got all the quills in.
Everything's ready to go.
The only thing left to do
is add the wefts on top
of the hairpiece
and glue on the quills
to the fingers.
Take care of the mouth,
I'll take care of the hands.
Right away
I start airbrushing in
all those final little details.
And I'm really happy
with how it's looking.
Jason and I are just trying
to get everything done.
So we're painting like crazy,
but I don't think
we're making it look better.
The rat face is
a grayish skin tone,
and now I'm concerned
how dark that paint job is.
All I can do is lighten it up,
but I don't think
it's gonna look
the way I had it in my head.
Ten minutes, guys.
Gums in.
That's time, everyone!
I'm not happy with this makeup.
There's a great concept
inside there.
But Sasha and I just didn't
put it together.
All I can do is just hope
for the best.
Welcome
to the Face Off reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
First, let's say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening.
- Hey.
- Hey, Glenn.
Oscar-winning makeup artist
Lois Burwell.
Good evening to you.
- Hey, Lois.
- Hi, Lois.
And creature and concept
designer, Neville Page.
How are you doing, gangsters?
We are thrilled to welcome
back Oscar-winning makeup artist
and 17-year Star Trek veteran,
Doug Drexler.
It's great to be here.
And I can't wait to see
what you guys have come up with.
Okay, before we get started,
I need to let you know
that in keeping
with this season's theme
of life and death,
the judges will again have
a one-time special immunity.
They can use it at any time
to give you a second life
when you would have otherwise
been eliminated.
That's really cool,
because even
a great artist could just have
a really bad week.
All right,
this week's spotlight challenge
was to create
an over-the-top crime boss
inspired
by the colorful nickname
of a real-world gangster.
Let's take a look
at your creations.
Gwen and I are both
really, really pleased
with the way that this makeup
has come out.
And we think he looks badass.
I'm very disappointed.
He looks muddy,
but my bomb looks really cool.
It is a little bit flat.
I'm a little bit nervous
about the paint job
reading from afar.
I'm really happy
with our character.
You don't get
more truck-like
than having exhaust pipes
coming out of your face.
I'm pretty embarrassed.
This isn't the character
that I wanted to see onstage,
but hopefully it's good enough.
I was a little nervous.
But I think from far away
he looks kind of cool.
I am psyched.
He has a perfect profile.
Yes! It looks great.
All right, judges,
it's time to take
a closer look at our gangsters.
The blend's pretty nice from
the headpiece into the cowl.
Can you open and close again?
- That's really good.
- Yeah. It really is.
The paint is on the muddy side.
It sure is.
It's all just one color.
Needs something to punch it up.
- Somehow, it got lost.
- What about the prop?
I see that
I must have been hit,
and I think Neville's been hit.
_
You know what's cool about it?
It looks like they're supposed
- to be keys on the typewriter.
- Yes.
Thank you.
If you were watching
Boardwalk Empire
and Nucky went to see the wiz,
this is what it would look like
in that world.
_
I do like the painting.
Yes. Thank you.
Wow. What did they
sculpt it with, a hammer?
I'm very worried now.
The judges are noticing
the bad seams,
and that's going to put us
on the bottom.
Who made your favorite
over-the-top crime boss?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
Wow. What did they
sculpt it with, a hammer?
The seam is pretty bad,
so I will be potentially
going home.
I really like the face,
but this is so literal.
It looks like a swimming hat.
Although nice job
on making the quills.
- They look like quills.
- Yeah.
The placement of the weight
around the torso,
this is really well done.
There's just an overall
nice continuity in everything.
That's hilarious.
Okay, the judges have scored
your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Gwen, Drew,
Keaghlan, Damien,
congratulations, because
you guys are safe this week.
You can head back
to the makeup room.
All right, the rest of you
were the best
and the worst this week.
The judges would like to speak
with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Doc and Stella,
please step forward.
Explain the idea
behind your makeup.
We got
Leonard "Needles" Gianola,
so we incorporated quills
into the hair.
Also, he was an assassin,
so we incorporated poison
to the fingers.
Doc sculpted the face,
and I worked on the headpiece.
I also made
all the poison vials.
The techniques in the face
are very well thought out
and successful.
But I feel like just because the
word "needles" is in his name
spiking his head like that
is too literal
with that one aspect
of the challenge.
I think the face
is very promising,
and the hand is intriguing.
But the hair looks like a hat.
Overall, I really like
the character.
- It's a cool makeup.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Doc and Stella,
please step back.
Sasha and Barry.
Tell us the idea
behind your character.
Our gangster is
Allie "Tick Tock" Tannenbaum.
He was a rat who ratted out
many, many gangsters.
And he's a mad bomber.
He's had a few of his bombs
go off in his face,
and his ear is
a little bit damaged.
I'm not particularly fond of--
of this makeup.
Who did what?
The concept was Barry's.
We both sculpted.
I did the hair.
Barry painted it,
and I made the bomb.
There are just certain things
that aren't up to snuff.
Like with the sculpt,
I wasn't certain
if it was a rabbit or a rat.
Just having the ear
drop an inch below
the other ear
does not connote damage.
And it is
such a muddy paint job.
My favorite part of this makeup
is the clock.
Yeah, it's the prop
that makes him who he is.
You want people to be able
to look at a character
and suss out the story.
Unfortunately, your makeup
doesn't really do that.
Sasha and Barry,
please step back.
Cig and George, you're up.
Tell us about the concept.
Well, we got
Tony "Big Tuna" Accardo.
He was notorious
for using a baseball bat,
so we changed the baseball bat
for a fish.
And it says "Good Night" on it,
because that's the last thing
you see before...
- you're sleeping with the fishes.
- You're sleeping with the fishes.
I blocked out the cowl,
and he blocked out the face.
I foam-fabricated
the fat suit,
and George laid all the hair.
This is great thinking
and a really good execution.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
The gills/rolls of flesh
and using the jowls
as a fish mouth
makes this
that much more impressive to me.
The other thing
that is really remarkable
is the body suit.
It's all this guy.
The sense of weight that it has
carries right from the top
of the head,
right down to the tips
of the feet.
- Thank you.
This is
absolutely the catch of the day.
Yes!
I love the hair.
He looks wonderful in profile.
You should be
really, really pleased.
- Thank you.
- Thank you guys so much.
Cig and George,
please step back.
Good work, big boy.
Good job.
You guys rocked it.
Thanks.
Dina and Jason.
Would you tell us
about your guy here?
This is
John "Peanuts" Tronolone.
He ran a bunch of gambling
and bookmaking operations,
and he has money,
poker chips, jewels, and stuff
up in his peanut cap.
I sculpted the face.
Jason blocked out the cowl.
I did some detailing on that.
I feel like
there's a disconnect
between the cowl and the face.
And it also falls down
as far as the paint goes.
The peanut part
is very boldly painted,
while there's very little
painting on the face.
If you bring one skin tone
against another,
it should look like
the skin tones belong together.
But the hands are just
the model's own hands.
This is just a peanut
on a guy's head.
It certainly doesn't have
a Dick Tracy feel,
and the face does not flow
into that cowl at all.
Dina and Jason,
if you'd please step back.
Rachael and Vince.
Let's start with concept
and how each of you participated
in the creation of this makeup.
So our gangster is named
Charles "The Typewriter"
Nicoletti.
He bludgeons his enemies
with brass knuckles.
In addition, he memorializes
his victims in his skin.
I blocked out the cowl
while Vince sculpted the face.
Conceptually,
this is a great idea.
Love what you guys did
with the typewriter aspect
of your character.
- Thanks.
- With a tighter paint job
and a little tweak
to the sculpture,
this could have been
an absolutely stellar makeup.
Thank you.
I probably would have
punched the paint job up more.
Rings under the eyes,
some beard shadowing.
The face really
is begging for that.
But it cuts a striking figure,
and I think that
you're really successful there.
Rachael and Vince,
if you'd please step back.
- Thank you, guys.
- Thanks.
All right, guys.
The judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they make
their decisions.
All right, judges, so let's talk
about tonight's makeups.
Why don't we start with
Doc and Stella?
The treatment of the face
felt like it was right direction,
right world.
- It's a strong character.
- It is.
I think they had a nice idea.
All right, let's move on
to George and Cig.
The distribution of weight
on this thing...
***
that the suit wouldn't collapse
in the wrong areas.
What was wonderful is that
the weight in the makeup
and the face carried through.
And there were
some lovely little details.
I mean, there's dribble
hanging there perfectly.
All right, judges, let's
move on to Rachael and Vince.
Rock-solid idea.
Very, really, really wise.
And the execution
of the type in the head,
that was all
really, really good.
I love this idea.
I love taking the typewriter
and just going straight
into the makeup itself.
All right, judges, let's
move on to Barry and Sasha.
I really dislike this one,
and it doesn't satisfy
the challenge.
It was a poor idea
picked up and run with.
It never would have
occurred to me
that a bomb went off
in his face.
- I didn't get that at all.
- Nor I.
I was serious when I said
that the prop was the most
successful part of this,
because it is
the only thing that,
when you look at the character,
says, "Tick Tock."
All right, let's move on
to Dina and Jason.
I just think there's so many
other intellectual ways
to have approached
the peanut aspect
other than sculpting a planters
peanut guy on top of his head
and then putting pearls
and chips in it.
The problem with it
is that it's too on the nose.
- It's not clever.
- And you look at the painting.
They had one solid color,
with a bit of dark thrown into it.
All right, judges.
Have you made your decisions?
- We have.
- Let's bring them back out.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about tonight's top teams.
Actually, there's one makeup
that is vastly superior
to the rest.
Glenn, tell us
about the top teams.
Actually, there's one makeup
that is vastly superior
to the rest.
George and Cig's Big Tuna.
- Thank you.
Your clever ideas,
world-class teamwork
and great technique made for
a stunningly successful makeup.
- Thank you.
Cig and George, well done.
But as you know,
we can only have one winner.
Glenn?
Without the construction
of that fat suit,
the makeup would not have been
as successful on the whole.
So, Cig, you are our winner.
Thank you.
_
It feels really good to win.
It's just so exciting.
Cig, congratulations.
You, George, Doc, Stella,
Rachael and Vince,
you're all safe and can head
back to the makeup room.
Unfortunately, that does mean
the rest of you are
on the bottom this week.
And one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom teams.
Barry and Sasha,
we appreciate that you tried
to be clever with your concept,
but your character
just didn't capture the essence
of your gangster's name.
Dina and Jason,
while we liked some things
about the face,
your uninspired concept
sabotaged the makeup.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Barry.
The character was flawed
in many ways,
and it seemed to us
that you were the driving force
behind it.
Barry, I'm so sorry,
but that does mean
you have been eliminated.
Dina, Jason, and Sasha,
you're safe and can head back
to the makeup room.
No worries.
I feel certain there is
a future for you in makeup,
and we wish you well.
Thank you so much.
Barry, thank you
for being here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
- and pack up your kit.
- Thanks, guys.
Worked so hard to get here,
and just to go home so soon,
it's such a bummer.
- No, man!
- Aww!
I don't think
that this one challenge
represents me as an artist.
This is definitely not
the end of the line for me.
I'll never be done
making creatures.
It's what I do.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net