This is great thinking.
I'm not particularly fond
of this makeup.
Sleeping with the fishes.
Previously on Face Off,
the 14 surviving artists
teamed up
for their first
spotlight challenge.
Cig's outlandish tuna
brought him his first win...
Thank you.
...but Barry's creative flaws
sent him packing.
Now 13 artists remain.
And tonight, they will take
monumental inspiration
to create
out-of-this-world makeup.
That's right. Aliens.
Yes.
My brain is like, "Yeah."
I've never seen
anything like this.
But some will never
even get off the ground.
Well, that's
your first mistake.
And I'm just at a standstill.
In the end, only one
will win a VIP trip
from
Kryolan Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Looks like a spaceship.
We're walking
by this gigantic pyramid,
which is really cool.
We see Glenn and McKenzie, so we
have no idea what to expect.
Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- Hey, McKenzie.
Welcome to the Walter Pyramid
at California State University
Long Beach.
For centuries,
historians, architects,
and engineers have marveled
at incredibly advanced
ancient wonders,
like the Pyramids of Giza
and Stonehenge,
which were built
long before the age
of modern
construction techniques.
While most experts insist
that these remarkable structures
were manmade,
others are convinced that
something not of this world
must have had a hand
in their creation.
That's right. Aliens.
- Oh.
- Yes.
My brain is like, "Yeah."
I imagine aliens just as
silly and awful as we are.
So I'm all about it.
While this theme has been
explored in movies like Stargate
and Indiana Jones And The
Kingdom Of The Crystal Skull,
alien theorists take
the theme a step further,
suggesting that
these extraterrestrial visitors
may have also left clues
about their own civilizations
within these ancient constructs.
For your first individual
spotlight challenge,
you will select
an ancient construct
to inspire
your very own alien creation.
Yes.
Aliens are a tall order
for one person to do
in 2 1/2 days.
All right, let's take a look
at the ancient sites
and cultures
that you all have
to choose from.
We have the Giza Necropolis
in Egypt,
Easter Island
in the South Pacific,
Stonehenge in England,
Machu Picchu in Peru,
Pyramid Of The Sun in Mexico,
Peruvudaiyar Kovil Temple
in India,
and Angkor Wat in Cambodia.
Yes.
All right, guys, once
you've decided on a location,
you can stay here
to work on your designs.
When you're done, head back
to the lab and get to work.
See you later.
Good luck.
Thank you.
I'm here on Face Off
to kick-start my career,
so I'm really, really gonna
try to push myself creatively
to come up
with really cool ideas.
I choose the Giza Necropolis
in Egypt.
The aliens
that I'm creating are dying,
so they decide to pass on
all their information
to the Egyptians
so that their way of life
doesn't just die with them.
Then the pyramids were built
to emulate
the way the alien looked.
So I really want to keep
a really sharp, angular design
to really make it pop
and speak out as Egyptian.
So I got Angkor Wat.
Since Angkor Wat is dedicated
to Lord Vishnu,
a Hindu deity, I'm gonna
sculpt my interpretation
with a blue exo suit
with two extra arms,
but I'm definitely
biting off a lot,
so hopefully it
doesn't bite me in the ass.
I selected Peruvudaiyar,
and Lord Shiva is depicted
throughout the structure
with a closed third eye.
So my alien is
Lord Shiva's mate,
and Lord Shiva starts
mating with all the natives.
My alien gets very angry,
and she opens her third eye,
turns them all to stone,
and erects Peruvudaiyar
as a warning to never
mate with the natives.
The construct that I chose
was Easter Island.
The Moai statues are known
for having fish lips.
So I'm gonna go
with this fish-type alien.
I think I'm gonna own
this challenge,
and it's gonna be
really fun to do.
So I've picked Machu Picchu.
I'm thinking
this telepathic race of aliens
that communicate
through frequencies.
So this alien
is gonna have a long beak.
So I need to make
a giant headpiece
and a modest face piece.
I am doing the Giza Necropolis.
I envision my character
as the princess
of an alien royal family,
and I'm going to incorporate
a feline aesthetic
into my alien because I see
a lot of those elements
in Egyptian artwork.
This will be the first time
I've ever had to do something
so grand by myself,
so I am definitely nervous.
Hey, guys,
let's go back to the lab.
We get to the lab,
and we have five hours
to get started
on our alien makeup.
I'm a giant nerd,
and I get to make aliens,
and I'm super stoked.
I choose the Pyramid Of The Sun
because I've actually
been there,
and I feel like that
would give me an advantage.
My concept for my alien
is based on one
of the Aztec gods associated
with the Pyramid Of The Sun,
Quetzalcoatl.
He is a snakelike god
with feathers,
and it will translate really
well into an alien society.
First thing I do
is start sculpting the cowl.
Since I love India
and I choose Peruvudaiyar,
I decide to blend
Indian culture into my alien.
So I'm gonna incorporate
the building's wavy shapes
into the cowl.
I'm trying to work with
the features of my model's face
and do a very aesthetically
pleasing shape to the head.
Where is he gonna see out of?
He's gonna have eyeholes
covered up with a pattern
that resembles
what the Polynesians wear.
- Oh, cool.
- I chose Easter Island.
These aliens taught
the Polynesians
that working together,
you get a lot more done.
So the Polynesians erected
these statues
that look like the aliens
as a thank-you
for what they taught them.
I'm going to change
the proportions of the head
by making the nose longer,
flattening the forehead,
and making the jaw huger,
so my alien will resemble
the look
of an Easter Island statue.
That looks fun.
I like it.
I think the biggest thing
is I don't want it
to look like a dinosaur.
No, your concept's solid, man.
It's awesome.
I end up getting Stonehenge.
So my concept is
an aquatic alien who convinces
the locals to build her
this magic temple.
I definitely want to go,
like, older woman.
I'm thinking
about a face piece and a cowl.
I'm hoping that I'm gonna
have time for hands,
but I'm not banking on it.
I have to say
my favorite alien is Predator.
It is pretty awesome.
My ancient structure
is also Stonehenge,
and the movie Predator has
that warrior type of tone,
which I love about aliens.
I'm thinking well, maybe
I could utilize some of that
to make my character
more barbaric,
more humanoid.
Just create the monsters, dude.
Take that.
Hello, everybody.
- We're here to check on you.
- Hello.
- How are you?
- Hi.
- Hi, Dina.
- How are you?
- Good, how are you?
- Hi, how are you?
- Good to see you.
Okay, so tell us
what you picked.
I picked Pyramid Of The Sun.
The people who built the temple
built it for the Sun god,
and he carries fire on his head.
So instead of having my alien
hold a fire above his head,
it will be
a mind-control device.
I'd also go ahead
and give yourself
a small piece down here,
just to be able
to carry your texture.
- Okay.
- Why did you pick Machu Picchu?
Machu Picchu's just
a very interesting location.
Machu Picchu was built
for the Incan god of creation,
and I wanted to incorporate
elements of that god
into my alien design.
They're said to have a headpiece
that's like a sun,
so I was gonna cut
this top piece off,
put some LEDs and stuff
underneath.
It should represent sunlight.
What we did
on The Borg Queen was
we literally picked out foam
from the inside
almost to the surface
and laid LEDs in there
and siliconed them in.
Great idea.
Let me turn this a little bit,
so I can see it.
Okay.
The construct that I chose
was Easter Island.
So I'm thinking
go with something amphibian,
like sympathetic,
older creature
from another water planet.
Okay.
I don't feel Easter Island.
This was my vision
from the get-go,
and now I'm just confused.
These images here
were made by the people
in the semblance of their god.
If they saw this guy,
they wouldn't be making these.
I have no idea what to do.
I'm just extremely worried.
Coming up...
I'm not saying,
"Don't listen to Mr. Westmore."
I should go out
this way, right?
I don't really know
how to do this.
- This is very unsuccessful.
- I love it.
I don't feel Easter Island.
I'd really get in
and do a little bit rethinking
on the nose and the brow ridge.
Okay.
I just think it should
be maybe a little higher.
I would maybe fill this in.
Bring your lower lip out
a little bit.
But it could be a little flatter.
It's day one
of the alien challenge,
and Mr. Westmore has
a bunch of different changes
that he thinks I should make,
and that takes all the wind
out of my sails.
I'm really confused.
I don't want to go
against what Mr. Westmore says,
but I didn't want
to go too literal.
So now I have to regroup
and figure out
how I'm gonna save this makeup.
There's a bull
that guards this tower,
and he's got this big,
ornate neck piece on.
So I was thinking of doing that
but starting it at her lip.
That would be great.
My concern is
she's not gonna be able
to move her neck.
When you get this piece out,
from the back side,
you tear out
some ridges across it,
and that allows them
to do this.
Okay.
I am creating an alien queen.
I've been utilizing
Nefertiti's headdress.
- It's a good profile.
- Thank you.
Yeah, but what's really
going to make this for you
is gonna be your paint job.
So make sure you leave yourself
enough time...
Absolutely.
...to really do
a beautiful paint job.
I'm really excited that
Mr. Westmore has come in
because he is really
the king of aliens.
He's worked
on so many Star Treks,
it's ridiculous.
So I cannot be more excited
to get his input,
and I'm definitely
gonna be taking his advice.
All right, we're heading out,
everybody.
- Good luck, to everybody.
- Thank you.
I look around the room,
and I'm super nervous
because this is the first time
I've ever sculpted a cowl,
and it just looks
so much smaller and wimpier
than everyone else's.
Damn.
He's crazy.
Oh, I know.
I'm hoping that
it's just my nerves,
so I'm just gonna keep going.
Mold, mold, mold, mold,
mold, mold, mold.
So I finish up my face
fairly quickly.
I have only about an hour
left in the day
to start molding it.
I would just really like
to get this out tonight,
so I have something
to go off of tomorrow.
It's only me and Rachael
back in the mold room
getting our faces molded.
♪ I'm a-molding,
I'm a-molding ♪
So I'm feeling like I'm in
a really good spot for the day.
I feel like I'm kind of ahead,
and I like the direction
that it's going.
I like having the face done
on the first day.
It feels good.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I'm not saying,
"Don't listen to Mr. Westmore,"
'cause obviously
that's always a bad idea.
Yeah, I know.
But I think just taking it
super literally and putting
an Easter Island head
on a dude is gonna be weird.
I'm trying to walk
that fine line
between what Mr. Westmore said
but still keep my own concept,
and I'm just at a standstill.
- You think this looks wonky?
- Uh...
I think--
I don't know.
I have no idea what
I'm gonna do at this point.
And every time
I look up to the clock,
it's just burning and burning,
and I realize I'm just
wasting too much time.
I've got to refigure out
the cowl, finish it off,
and at least get the face
where I'm happy with it.
Time is winding down,
and the more I sculpt,
the more I'm just having a hard
time seeing the character.
I think the scales
have tipped a little bit
on my confidence level.
- Okay, guys, it's time!
- Whoo!
That will have to wait
till tomorrow.
At the end of the day,
I'm really kind of concerned
because I've already been
bottom look,
and I'm just not feeling
so great about this.
I need some time
to step away from it
and just get my thoughts
together and come back.
It's day two
of our alien challenge,
and we have 9 1/2 hours
in the lab,
and I have the opportunity
to get a set of fresh eyes
on my sculpture.
I'm feeling
more confident today.
So I change out the nose,
and I've got the mouth
turned down a little further,
like Mr. Westmore had wanted.
So it's kind of
less fish-like
what I had
originally anticipated,
but I really can't spend
any more time on the face
when I need
to also give attention
to the cowl
and get two molds finished.
I start sculpting out
the neck piece,
and I know that I don't
have enough time to sculpt
individual jewels
into this piece.
So I find whatever jewelry
I can in the lab,
and I push them all
into the neck piece,
just so I know how
it's all laid out,
and I know exactly
where to put them back
once I get this face done.
I finally finish sculpting,
and I realize doing a mold
as big as I have to do is crazy.
I'm really nervous
about this mold.
I think my sculpture was at
a good place maybe an hour ago,
and I'm a little pissed at
myself for not molding earlier,
so I am trying to mold
as quickly as possible.
- Left side, right side.
- Oh, yeah.
Definitely a lot better.
Today, I feel really good.
I'm feeling better
about my concept.
As I'm sculpting
the chest and the back,
I see more of the creature
coming out.
He's alien, but I wanted
to create the anatomy
where it's just a touch
out of the humanistic realm.
I was like, "No belly button.
That means
you are definitely an alien."
I'm feeling
really confident now.
I can work with this.
- Looks good.
- Cool. Thanks.
So I finish
my first cowl sculpt,
and I'm gonna go start
my first two-piece cowl mold.
I really have not that much
experience making molds,
so I'm completely confused.
I should go out
this way, right?
Yeah.
I don't really know
how to do this.
And I'm starting to panic.
It's day two
of our alien challenge,
and I'm doing
my first cowl mold.
I should go out
this way, right?
Yeah.
But I don't really know
how to do this.
I feel like I can pick up
on things really fast,
so Dina seems like
she's done this before,
and I just start doing
exactly what she's doing.
And I'm just gonna
hope for the best.
I go and I pop my face mold,
start cleaning it out.
I stipple in a bunch of latex,
let that dry.
I pull it out, and then I have
kind of a Halloween mask
so I can lay that up
onto the face
that my cowl is sculpted on,
and I can make sure that
all my lines that I designed
are gonna line up correctly.
I'm a firm believer that aliens
should have no human features,
because fingers look
like a human in makeup.
I have this idea
to do basically squid hands.
So I cut this L200 foam
in certain shapes,
and it looks great.
So I sit down,
and I try to open the mold.
I'm down there on the floor.
I'm tugging on it.
Don't know if this mold's
even gonna open.
How's it going, Sasha?
Yay!
It finally opened,
so I'm actually feeling
a lot more confident.
- 19 minutes!
- Okay.
It's hard to run
with heavy things in your hands.
So I see most of the people
are running around
trying to get
their cowl molds done,
and...
I'm basically getting ready
for tomorrow's application.
I'm trying
to mentally get there.
I think if I have
a better plan,
it will be better for me.
And I won't have to be running
around like a crazy person.
I really want to give
this character four arms
because Lord Vishnu
always has four arms.
So I get the idea
to joint the arms,
and I'm gonna use monofilament
and attach it to his wrists,
so when he raises his arm,
the arm would raise
with his arm.
Yay, they work.
Everybody, that's time.
Coming off a win,
I feel like the judges
are expecting more of me.
So I want to make sure
I don't disappoint.
So it's application day.
We've got four hours in the lab
and one hour in last looks.
How's everybody's stuff look?
It's mostly fine.
My foam came out beautiful.
I have no problems.
It's all coming together.
All right.
Hey, how's it going?
- Iris.
- Jason.
So you're gonna be an alien.
We have
a pretty bad situation here,
not good at all.
I had a really big plan
for application,
but my foam chest piece,
it's just bad.
Not doing so well right now.
The foam has
collapsed on itself,
so it has these air pockets
just sitting there.
This is gnarly.
So I have to figure out how
to salvage this chest piece.
This is part of my character.
I need to have this chest.
You look like an alien,
I swear to God.
Keep going, keep going.
Almost there.
_
I start applying, and
my only concern at this point
is that the cowl
is a little big,
so he's got
this large, bulbous head,
which isn't quite the look
I was going for,
but I know I can leave it loose
and then glue it down
in last looks.
All right, let's start
putting this on your face.
Whoo!
I decide to go with a yellow
and green color scheme
because usually
the dangerous snakes have
the brightest colors.
So I do my base color,
and then I airbrushed
some detail signs.
And then I used a stencil
to get the green patterning
on the skin, and I really
like the direction
that it's headed in.
I start painting,
and then I realize
how much work I have to do.
It's a big piece.
It's 360 degrees around.
So I just let the colors fly.
A lot of Egyptian artwork,
it's lots of golds and blues,
so I really want to stick
to those colors.
So I start painting my piece,
basing out with gold,
which I'm really,
really happy with.
You are golden, literally.
I get some of the blue put on,
and it's starting to get
kind of muddied up.
So I try going back
to kind of cover up
with a little bit of gold,
but it's not really helping.
So I'm really
stressing on my paint job,
and it's too late to turn back.
- What's the time?
- 1:16.
All right.
This is just trashed.
I spend three hours just trying
to patch and fix this thing,
and my paint,
I have to kind of sacrifice.
Everything that could
go wrong is going wrong.
30 minutes, guys!
That's time, guys!
- Ooh.
- Hoo!
All right, let's go.
My heart's just falling.
It's kind of like watching
the car crash happening
while you're in the car.
When I have to try to pull
a really good paintjob
to salvage this piece, but,
things aren't looking good.
Coming up...
I get my airbrush out,
and it's completely clogged.
It's gonna take a miracle
for me to be safe.
This is
a beautiful-looking piece.
Did you get lost time-wise?
It's really quite remarkable.
- Let's go to work!
- Where my alien at?
We have one hour at last looks,
and I get my airbrush out.
Oh, come on, airbrush.
And it's completely clogged.
So I start hand-painting it.
Just making it work.
I try and spatter
some black on him,
you know, kind of break up
some of the gray.
Turn your arm over.
Everything that I would see
on the statues is there,
but I'm still on the fence
with how it's gonna look
to the judges.
I'm gonna attempt
to put this thing
on the front of you.
I put the costume on,
and it's a little bit better.
It helps hide
some of my mistakes,
but not all of them.
It's just a gnarled mess.
It's gonna take a miracle
for me to be safe.
I stick on the bindi,
and I hang chains from her nose.
It looks alien-like,
and it looks Indian-like,
so I'm pleased.
This side is just
not staying down.
All right, guys, it's time!
Yeah!
Whoo!
Welcome
to the Face Off reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
First, let's say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve
Makeup Effects Studio,
Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening, guys.
- Hi, Glenn.
A big welcome back
to Oscar and Emmy-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
I missed you last week, guys.
I can't wait to see
what you have for us.
We missed you too.
Say hello to creature and
concept designer Neville Page.
- Hello.
- Hi, Neville.
And Oscar-winning
makeup artist Lois Burwell.
Good evening, everyone.
- Hi, Lois.
- Hi.
All right, guys.
This week, your first individual
spotlight challenge
was to choose an ancient wonder
and create the alien species
who might have helped build it.
Let's take a look
at your otherworldly beings.
The paint's not really
popping like I want it to,
but there's a lot of things
I like about it.
I'm really hoping
I'm safe at this point.
His overall presence
is really cool.
I'm really proud
of my prosthetic.
Hopefully, that'll
be enough to save me.
I'm not really happy at all.
I really hope the judges see
the amount of time I put in
to try to make this thing work.
It's exactly
what I pictured in my head,
but I think the wardrobe
might have been
a little too crazy.
I look at my character,
and he looks pretty cool.
It's kind of creepy and, like,
very, very alien to me.
I'm proud of it.
I think she looks beautiful.
I created exactly
what I wanted to see.
She looks amazing.
I was able to show
what I'm truly capable of.
I think it's pretty cool.
This totally looks like
an alien that could've inspired
the creation of Angkor Wat.
I wish I had given her
a prop, but overall,
I'm impressed with the amount
of stuff I got done.
I really like
how she looks overall.
Hopefully, the judges notice
all the work I put into it.
I'm not super happy with it.
It's not what I envisioned,
but at this point,
I'm just hoping for the best.
I'm not 100% happy with my
paint job and some of my forms,
but with the time that I had,
I'm proud of it.
I took a risk
by going very minimal,
and I'm hoping that
the judges think less is more.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look at our aliens?
- Look at that edge.
- Yeah, wow.
There's a lot more paint
on the body
than there is the face.
There's not really
a focal point.
We have to ask
where it comes from.
Okay.
He got a little crazy
with sponges and maybe
a stencil or something.
He kind of ruined it
with the paint.
_
I'm nervous that
my incomplete paint job is going
to kick me in the balls,
and I'm gonna end up going home
because of it.
What do you think
of tonight's designs?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
He ruined it with the paint.
I'm freaked out.
All the parts came together
except the paint job.
At this point, I'm worried
that I could be sent home.
- I really love the mouth.
- Yeah, that's great.
Thank you.
It's using
the Egyptian headdress...
Mm-hmm.
...and the traditional
goatee shape.
I think that's very wise.
I love the reference.
Thank you.
This is cool.
There are some real
adventurous forms on this face.
- Yeah.
- I really love this collar.
It just doesn't feel
like this wise alien race.
It feels so sad and destroyed.
_
He's sparkly.
To put these shapes on the
face makes no sense whatsoever.
_
Thank you.
It's terrific 'cause she has
such a nice, little,
narrow chin.
Just really helps that whole
shape really be very effective.
_
Continues the shape,
gives it femininity.
It does.
Come back around?
All right.
All right, the judges
have scored your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Sasha, Doc,
Stella, Gwen,
Damien, Keaghlan,
you were the best
and the worst this week.
That means the rest of you
are safe and can head back
- to the makeup room.
- Thank you.
All right, the judges would
like to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Sasha, you're up first.
Tell us about this character
and how your location
inspired your design choices.
This is Shiva.
She came to Earth
because she's
an animal species collector.
She built a shelter,
and when she left,
everyone used the shelter
as a temple and worshipped her.
It's really quite remarkable.
Thank you.
It is instantly recognizable
as having Indian influence,
and you kept the form
so nice and tight
to accentuate
those big, beautiful eyes.
Thank you so much.
I really compliment you
in regard to her head
because you created proportions
that feel not even achievable,
and I like that.
I love the use of the jewelry.
It's something that
obviously is traditional.
- Very wise choices.
- Thank you.
Sasha,
if you'd please step back.
Doc, you're up next.
Tell us how you let
the Moai statues
help you create
your alien today.
I wanted to create something
that alludes
to what the Moai statues are.
That's why he's got the kind of
squared off front of his head
and the longer face
and then the downturned mouth.
I'm sorry, Doc,
but I think this makeup
is very unsuccessful.
The paint job itself is
just completely monotone.
You've created this
sympathetic look that allows
your character to do nothing
but look sad.
And the sculpting
on the bottom of the face
is very strange
around the mouth.
You chose to cover the ears.
Why is that?
I wanted to go amphibian
with more
of a fish-type character.
It doesn't
communicate your intention,
so it feels concept-less.
Okay.
Doc, please step back.
All right, Stella, you're up.
Oh, God...
So tell us about the concept
and how the cultural influences
inspired your creation.
This is Lord Shiva's mate.
Shiva started to mate
with the natives,
and he had 250 sons,
and she was so angry with him
that she opened her third eye
and turned them all to stone
and erected this building
as a warning
to never mate
with the natives again.
You're doing some things
with forms
that just shouldn't work,
but it does.
The way you brought
the cheeks down
towards the corner of the mouth
is beautiful.
It is a very successful makeup
and character.
Thank you.
I like the color choice
of the contact lens.
I like the way you put henna
on the back of the hands,
and the collar is fantastic.
Thank you.
I've never seen
anything like this,
so I think you succeeded
on an extremely complex
and advanced level.
Thank you so much.
Stella, please step back.
Gwen, please step forward.
Tell me about the concept
and what you're trying
to tell us.
When my character
came to Earth,
he gave the Viking people
mathematics, the Sun,
and Stonehenge.
The Viking people
showed him how to survive,
which made him more savage
the longer he stayed.
He looks pagan, not alien.
Did you get lost time-wise?
I spent a lot of the time
trying to patch and maintain
the chest piece
because I wanted to show
that he is
a little human-esque.
One of the worst decisions
you made was sculpting out
a whole chest and doing almost
nothing with it to tell us
that it's an alien.
With better use of color,
you could've salvaged it.
Gwen,
if you'd please step back.
Damien, please step up.
Please enlighten us as
to how you utilized the location
that you chose
to motivate your makeup.
So my alien finds Earth
and decides to give them
his knowledge,
and in honor of that,
humans decided to build
monuments in his likeness.
I think pulling the pyramid
shapes down onto the face
has no basis
in anatomical reality.
It's just rough forms
with color on it.
Damien, did you start
with the blue or the gold?
I started with the gold.
Well,
that's your first mistake.
You didn't start with a color.
You started with a highlight,
and I'm not really happy
with the blue.
I mean,
nothing looks organic on him.
I understand.
Damien, please step back.
Keaghlan, you're up.
Tell us how the pyramids
inspired your alien.
She landed on the planet
and brought the cat species,
and then her form inspired
the Egyptian culture
to adorn their royalty
with those features.
This makeup is much prettier
up close.
I love the way
you used the gold
and made really subtle accents.
- Nicely done.
- Thank you.
Strong silhouette.
Even the subtle graphic
design of the pale face
to the yellows and oranges
within that headpiece is great.
Thank you.
Keaghlan,
if you'd please step back.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
All right, guys,
the judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
All right, judges.
Let's talk about the looks
you like the most this week.
Why don't we start with Sasha?
She allowed
the model's features
to drive the beauty
in this makeup.
And doing so little,
always risky,
but I think she knew
her limitations.
I loved the color choice
of the contact lens
and the blue stone.
How about Stella?
The neck piece-- beautiful,
multicultural references.
Even those petals
on the back of the head.
It was just one more thing
that was so spectacular.
She does have an eye
for shape and form,
but the real skill set
is bringing it together.
And what about Keaghlan?
I think it's a great makeup.
It fits into the ideology
of the Egyptian pantheon.
I was surprised
at how great the paint job was
when we got a little bit closer
to it.
I liked the balance
of the ears.
All right, so before we talk
about the looks
you like the least,
I want to remind you, you do
have that special immunity
available if you
would like to use it.
All right,
let's talk about Doc.
This lack of symmetry
and the shapes around the mouth
was just so sloppy and clumsy.
If someone that depressing
arrived and that gray,
it would make me lose
the will to live.
If he actually stepped out
the craft, you'd be likely
to club him to death rather
than take him and build a--
But he knew it was a lemon.
And what about Gwen?
Did not satisfy
the challenge at all.
We ended up with
this cromagnon-like character.
And I think she wasted
so much time trying
to patch up her chest,
which she covered up.
And what do you think
of Damien's work?
In this challenge,
it felt totally off the mark.
And the fact alone that
he started with that gold paint,
you're doomed right there.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- Yes, we have.
- Let's bring 'em back out.
So, Glenn, tell us
about tonight's top looks.
Sasha, you did
a great job embracing
your model's features,
and the Indian influence
was so present in your work.
Stella, we loved
some of the unique shapes
in your character's face,
and the overall image
was quite powerful.
Keaghlan, this character
had a bold, graphic quality,
and we love
how you incorporated
recognizable
cultural references.
So who is the winner
of tonight's challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
So who is the winner
of tonight's challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
Stella.
Thank you.
There were so many things
that should not have worked,
yet you managed
to pull together
all of these disparate elements
into an incredibly
successful makeup.
- Very cool.
- Thank you.
I win.
This is an amazing feeling,
and I proved to myself
that I can do this.
- Stella, congratulations.
- Thank you.
You, Keaghlan, and Sasha can
head back to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Unfortunately, that does mean
that the three of you
are in the bottom this week.
One of you will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about tonight's bottom looks.
Doc, your struggle
to nail down some of the aspects
of your makeup was undeniable,
and that was notably apparent
in your sculptural forms.
Gwen, not a lot about
your makeup worked tonight,
but perhaps the biggest misstep
was the fact that
it looked more like a tribal
demon than it did an alien.
Damien, we thought
that there were
some fairly significant
sculptural misfires
in your makeup,
and your paint job
only served to enhance them.
So who's going home tonight?
The person going home tonight is...
Gwen.
You clearly suffered
some major technical setbacks,
but it was your inability
to adapt to them
that ultimately
was your undoing.
Gwen, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
That means, Doc, Damien,
you guys are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Gwen, I know
you're a talented artist,
and I can't wait to see
what you do in the future.
Thank you.
Gwen, it's been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- Thank you guys.
- Good luck.
Going home this soon
is heartbreaking.
Who is it?
- Gwen.
- No.
Being here has shown me
that I can move forward
with my art.
I love makeup a lot.
I love designing new creatures,
so this is just the beginning.
I have got
a lot of bumps and bruises,
but I'm not gonna give up.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net