The winners of this challenge
get to go to the finale.
To make it this far
is just unbelievable.
There's only three people
standing between me
and 100 grand.
This is the last chance
to show that I have
what it takes.
In a season of life and death,
four artists have thrived.
But which three
will keep the dream alive
and make it to the finale?
Don't hold anything back.
- So much to do.
- Yeah, right.
All aspects of this makeup
have to be perfect.
The worst foam in the world.
- You have a lot of work to do.
- Ew!
I bit off more than I can chew.
I've got several surprises
in store for you tonight.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- What's happening?
- I don't know. What is this?
We show up to the studio,
and we're walking through
all these different sets.
And I have no idea
what's going on.
Oh, God.
Oh, creepy.
Every ten feet,
it's like you're
in a different world almost.
- Weird office or something.
- Yeah.
I'm confused.
We get to this elaborate
courthouse set,
and at the end of the walkway,
there's McKenzie.
What?
I'm super excited.
There's a newsstand.
And the newspapers
have all of these
really sensational headlines.
- What the hell is a Yeti Crab?
- I don't know, but I love it.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Welcome to DC Stages
in downtown Los Angeles.
This location and its massive
variety of standing sets
has been featured in dozens
of films and television shows,
like Alias, X-Files,
and Iron Man 2.
Cool.
Now, you're next
spotlight challenge
is inspired by two infamous
movie monsters
that made a name for themselves
destroying some of the world's
most recognizable skylines.
Are any of you Godzilla
or King Kong fans?
- Yeah.
- Of course.
Now, Godzilla and King Kong
are forever associated
with iconic buildings
like the Tokyo Tower in Japan
and the Empire State Building
in New York City.
Each of these newspapers
features a bold headline--
an image of a famous landmark
that's been devastated
by some type
of monstrous creature.
So your spotlight challenge
is to choose
one of these newspapers
and use its headline
and imagery as inspiration
for your very own giant monster.
Yes! Yes!
I love giant monsters!
I am ecstatic.
This is like a dream challenge--
to get to make a giant monster.
I gotta calm down. I'll pass out.
All right.
So our headlines are...
"Yeti Crab Crushes Kremlin,"
"Giant Sloth Slashes Shanghai,"
"Mantis Preys On Paris,"
"Deadly Squid Destroys Dubai,"
and "Taj Terrorized
By Pterodactyl."
All right, guys, I want you
to choose carefully,
because this is your last chance
to show the judges
that you are capable of earning
a spot in the finale.
This is dream come true.
I've always wanted
to make a giant monster,
but I am terrified,
because I just need
to get the spot in the finale.
- Dina.
- Oh, God.
I'm gonna do this.
Cig, you're next.
I don't know. I'm gonna go
with Yeti crab.
- Ah!
- Squid.
- I'm going with the sloth.
- All right.
All right, guys, I have
an exciting surprise for you.
I want to introduce you
to a very special guest.
He's starred in dozens
of hit films,
like Star Trek, Capote,
Traffic,
and appropriately
for today's challenge,
Guillermo del Toro's
Pacific Rim.
Please give a warm welcome
to Emmy-nominated actor
Clifton Collins, Jr.
has done a lot of productions
with makeup effects
and especially giant monsters.
So I'm stoked to see him here.
- Hi.
- Hi. Thank you so much
- for being here.
- Thanks for having me.
- I'm a big fan.
- I should also tell you guys
that Clifton will be joining us
on the reveal stage this week
to see your final makeups.
So, as one of the stars
of Pacific Rim,
you've seen your fair share
of giant monsters.
- I have.
- What do you think it is
that gets the audience
so excited?
For me, it's, like,
the nostalgia.
Having grown up on, like,
big, giant robot or Godzilla
or any of these monster movies,
to become an adult
and see these creatures
brought back to the screen
is just a great time.
What are you gonna be looking
for in their final creation?
I'm gonna be looking
for originality
and attention to detail.
I think, as a character actor,
I'm always hunting
for those minute, little details
- that make the difference.
- Very cool.
Thank you so much.
All right, guys, it's time
to get started on your sketches.
And remember,
don't hold anything back,
because it's now or never,
if you want to prove
to the judges
that you belong
in the final three.
See you later on at the lab.
Good luck.
Good luck, guys.
I got
"Mantis Preys On Paris."
The cool thing
about praying mantises
is the females actually eat
the heads of their mates.
So my concept
is she ate tons of them
and grew into a giant monster.
I have to do wings, face,
cowl, arms, legs,
and then they have this
whole lower body part
that I'm probably gonna have
to fabricate.
I have to just go all out
in this challenge.
I want the judges to see that
I don't just do pretty things.
I can do creepy.
I like sloths.
They're real stupid
and slow and cute.
So it's gonna be fun
trying to take that
and transform it
into a hideous, scary monster.
My concept for my giant sloth
that destroys Shanghai
is an ancient,
forgotten creature
that has been brought
to the modern world
and basically just goes crazy.
So he's gonna have longer arms
with really long claws,
some sparse hair,
and shortened legs.
I'm not holding anything back
this time.
Like, it's a monster challenge,
a giant-monster challenge.
So I'm going giant monster,
all the way.
- How's your squid monster?
- It's a squid man.
Yeah?
Let me see.
My concept is this
radioactive mutant squid.
The squid is growing
bigger and bigger,
until he goes on a rampage
in Dubai.
They're all soft and squishy,
except for this big,
bad-ass beak
that can just, like,
rip apart Dubai, apparently.
I think I'm gonna put the mouth,
like, on his chest.
- Cool.
- How's your Yeti crab?
It's gonna have, like,
Yeti face
and, like, carapace going back.
- That's cool.
- And then it has, like,
big forearms.
So my story is that
the Yeti crab
is actually a mutant byproduct
of the Chernobyl disaster.
And the Russian government
captured it,
but it's too strong,
and it breaks out.
Now it's just pissed off, so it
just starts crushing the city.
- So much to do.
- Yeah, right.
Hey, guys.
Let's go back to the lab
and start our monsters.
Yeah.
It's day one of our
giant-monster challenge,
and we have six hours
in the lab.
So much to do.
I'm on Cloud Nine.
I get to make a giant monster.
I'm gonna sculpt a cowl
and a face piece.
Then I'm gonna try to fabricate
an entire creature suit
that ends in crab claws
and have, like, armored plates
all throughout.
I start with just
the basic ape sculpt,
and add some other stylized
elements into the gorilla face.
It's a monstrous amount of work.
The mantis eyes are, you know,
on the side of its head.
So I find these giant,
plastic half globes
that are perfect for its eyes,
so stick those right
into my sculpt.
And then I'm gonna try to hide
my model's eyes in the nostrils,
so I start working on the face
and the cowl at the same time
because it needs
to match perfectly,
or this is not gonna work.
All right, this is
my fourth bag of clay.
What are you making there--
- chest piece?
- Yeah.
A squid is not all that scary,
just this gross, slimy thing.
So I start sculpting
this big, thick beak
right in the center
of my model's chest,
with all these rings
and spikes.
The beak's gonna look like
it can destroy a whole city.
Got to just be a pit
of destruction in its chest.
It's gonna sell
the scary aspect.
Do you like him?
Yeah.
I love sloths.
It's like, they're adorable.
What can they possibly do?
I'm spending a lot of time
trying to make sure
I don't go too sloth-y,
which will just turn out
to be a giant cute monster,
so I'm spreading out the eyes
so that he's still
sort of dopey and cute-looking,
but also somewhat menacing
and more like
a giant, scary sloth.
Hey, guys.
We're here to check in on you.
- Hey, George.
- Hey, how are you?
- Good. How you doing?
- Hi, George.
- Good to see you.
- All right, so you have
- "Deadly Squid Destroys Dubai."
- Yeah.
So I'm gonna have these
giant eyes and the face split,
and these will blend into
the tentacles that are his arms.
And then the beak
is gonna be on his chest.
What about color now?
The paint job is the thing
I'm most looking forward to.
Tans with some, like,
blue spotting
and patterns
and stuff around it.
Well, you don't want
to get muddy either.
- No.
- When you talk about tans,
you don't want to,
all of a sudden,
start to shade
and get it too dark.
Octopus and squid, you find reds
and blues and purples.
- Mm-hmm.
- So you can easily work those
- into your shadows around there.
- Yeah.
All right, so remind us
what you chose today.
"Mantis Preys On Paris."
- That's right.
- I like your face.
Should I white
her eyes out maybe?
No, I wouldn't whiten them,
'cause that's gonna pop
right out.
If anything, bring your shading
all the way through here
and really just go
all the way down
- with the aqua color plus...
- Yeah, yeah.
'Cause it'll last,
and then take a black pencil
and do the table of the eye
to get rid of any pink
- that's in there.
- Right.
So, yeah, here he is.
I'm trying to change
the silhouette
so that he has a wider,
like, stockier head, basically.
Mm-hmm.
Since you are so thick here,
score it from the inside,
before you put it on him,
- so it'll bend.
- Okay.
In fact, I would even,
with this one here,
so he could get more of that,
would be to literally
tear some out.
Score it and tear some
out of it,
'cause then
it will have something,
you know, to fold into.
- Okay.
- All right.
So you got
"Yeti Crab Crushes Kremlin."
Yep. I thought that no
collection of giant monsters
would be complete
without a simian-esque monster.
So I'm gonna make
the overall look very apelike...
Mm-hmm.
...with the carapace
and exoskeleton of the crab.
- Uh-huh.
- This is gonna look like
- a gorilla in a crab costume.
- Mm-hmm.
I was really happy
with the face.
But this is definitely
a wrench in the gears.
It'd probably be a good idea
to sell a little bit more crab
in the face
so it isn't all simian,
you know,
really tie the two together.
- Okay.
- You have a lot of work to do.
- Good luck, guys.
- Good luck.
Thank you.
Fuck. I want to take
Mr. Westmore's advice
to sell the crab more,
but I'm not sure
what I'm gonna do with the face.
I don't know.
I'm not seeing it.
I don't have time
to be thrown off,
because I have to still
fabricate
an entire creature suit,
so it's really frustrating.
But at this point, I just have
to walk away from it.
Coming up...
What the fuck?
At the end of the day,
there's gonna be one person
that's gonna be sent home,
and it's nerve-racking.
So, I think it's
a very successful makeup.
I struggle with this.
I appreciate
your swinging for the fences.
Fuck.
It's day one of our
giant-monster challenge,
and I'm nervous because
I'm running out of time today,
and Mr. Westmore said
that I really need
to sell the crab more,
which I definitely agree with.
But I'm not exactly sure
what it is about the face
that's not really
coming together.
I'm thinking crabs
have these really long antenna.
So that gives me an idea
to put antenna
coming off the side of the face,
and have them hang down.
That's very
old-school monster.
- It's got antenna.
- Yeah.
I get my face sculpt done,
and I'm going to start getting
this thing molded.
I just need to finish
the face today,
'cause it needs to match up
with the cowl
so it looks like one
cohesive head.
Ten minutes.
One thing that's sort of looming
over me still
is how I'm gonna make
these hands and these claws.
Otherwise,
it's not gonna read as sloth,
and it won't read
as a giant monster.
Hey, guys, it's time.
The other thing
that's looming over my head
is the amount of hair work
that I'm gonna have to do.
It's gonna be
sort of a daunting task
to get all of these things
finished on day two.
Whoo-hoo!
So, it's day two
of our giant-monster challenge,
and we have nine
and a half hours in the lab.
This thing is, like,
barely cooked.
My chest piece
isn't completely cured.
I'm squishing the beak,
and it's just--
my fingerprints are staying
in the foam.
It's totally distorting
what I sculpted,
and it's pretty much ruined.
I need to figure out
something else to do.
Ew.
It's creepy.
I have a very long list
of things to do today.
I need to finish my cowl.
I started sculpting a butt
for the insect that I need
to get finished and molded.
Then I need to, like, fabricate
some wings and some legs
and a bunch of blender pieces,
so I have a lot to do.
My chest piece is so thick,
it didn't get baked.
Weird.
Since my chest piece wasn't
baked all the way through,
I'm gonna run the chest mold
with polyfoam.
But polyfoam's
a lot more rigid,
so I'm pretty sure
it's not gonna come out
as nice as I would like it to.
But I have to get something.
I pop open my face mold,
clean the clay out.
It looks great.
Now it's time
to jump on the cowl.
I decide to put
some more spikes on it
and detail it out a little bit.
I'm feeling a lot better
this morning.
I'm ready, I have a direction,
and I'm running at it.
- Ew. Look at his little ears.
- Aren't they gross?
They're really gross.
I have to get the cowl
sculpture completely finished,
and then
I have to get it molded.
I'm not the fastest mold maker
in the world.
So I know that
that's gonna take up
a chunk of time in my day,
and I still have to get
these sloth gloves made.
It's a ton of work,
and in a challenge this far
along in the competition,
you have to do every step
of the process justice
and give it the attention
that it deserves,
or else it can bite you.
It's time to start
on the creature suit,
and I'm designing
as I'm putting pieces on.
I just grab some couch foam,
and I wrap it in a shape
that creates my understructure,
and from there, I'm going
to cut out segments of L200
and actually layer them
on top of each other.
I just keep layering them and
standing back and looking at it.
There's no time to waste.
I'm just going.
The arms I'm fabricating
are gonna extend my model's arms
almost two feet,
so I want them
to be very long and creepy.
It's just gonna add
the giant factor to her.
So I decide to take some foam
and roll it up
into a cone shape.
I want to add as much texture
as I can,
'cause I don't want it
to just look like
a piece of rolled-up foam,
because praying mantises have
tons of little, like, spikes
at the end of their arms.
So I'm cutting spiky shapes
out of foam,
gluing them on.
Then I make a piping bag
out of some wax paper I find
in the lab and add silicone.
Piping bags are used
in cake decorating
to pipe frosting onto cakes,
so I feel like
I'm back at the bakery.
I have to fabricate two gloves,
get them painted, then get hair
laid all over them
before the end of the day.
- You like?
- Yeah, it looks cool.
Yeah, I got to get
the hair on there.
I'm doing hair
because he is a sloth,
and they are hairy creatures.
But it has to be
really well done,
or else it's not gonna do
my makeup justice
and I'm not gonna make it
to the finale.
I need to get
this whole bodysuit fabricated
in...
way less time than I need.
I'm realizing that I bit off
way more than I can chew.
Every new thing
that I put on this suit
just kills me inside.
I don't really want to be
in this position
this far into the competition.
This isn't the type of work
I want to represent myself with.
I'm not all that proud
of this makeup,
and it's gonna suck
if I go home.
So it's day two
of our giant-monster challenge.
And I realize that I bit off
way more than I can chew.
Fuck!
So, at this point, I just start
throwing paint at it.
I'm hoping that my paint work
and some of my finishing work
can pull it all together,
but it's starting to worry me.
So, down to, like,
30 minutes left in the day,
I get enough hair laid
on the first glove
that I have to move on
to the second one,
and I just don't have time
to do that.
I make a snap decision, instead
of doing fur on both sides,
I'm gonna incorporate
a burn makeup on the other side.
It will add another layer
of information to the character
so that it becomes
a little bit more interesting.
So I mix up some gelatin
and then start laying that
on the other glove.
The way that I'll work this
into the story
is the armed forces
are shooting fire at him.
I'm really happy with how
the paint job is coming out.
The stomach's looking
really creepy.
So I'm starting to think
that I'm going
in the right direction.
Hopefully, everything will come
together in application.
- That's fucking crazy, dude.
- I did all of this today.
You're completely insane.
- All right, that's time!
- Whoo.
Even with implementing
this burn makeup,
I feel like, at this point,
this makeup is gonna turn out
to be silly.
It's a giant sloth monster.
- How do you feel?
- Like a zombie.
It may or may not work,
and that worries me.
We get back to the house,
and we're all exhausted.
This was a crazy challenge.
Dead.
Nobody has any energy at all.
I think we're all
a little worried.
Only three of us are gonna be
in the finale.
And so this
is a really important challenge,
and it's really weighing on us.
Oh, man.
Did everyone finish
everything they wanted to?
- Not even close.
- No.
At the end of the day,
there's gonna be one person
that's gonna be sent home,
and it's nerve-racking.
Let's eat, kids.
Okay.
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab
and one hour at last looks.
Foam come out?
It's pretty good--
a few bubbles.
Mine came out
really, really nice.
Ew!
What the fuck?
My foam piece has a lot
of microbubbling on the cowl.
Hooray for the worst foam
in the world.
I have to figure out a way
to make these work,
which sucks.
Seriously?
- How are you?
- Great!
- Hey, man.
- Good to see you.
Whoop!
Oh, no!
I'm trying to, like,
work as fast as possible,
but the bald cap
is just not working out.
Oh, crap. Okay. So I guess
we have to take it off.
I'm freaking out.
I don't have a lot of time.
So I just run and get a cap,
and I throw it on her.
Hopefully, it'll be okay.
Yeah, that's better.
The foam's sort of rough
this time.
I realize that the microbubbling
is on the burn-makeup side.
It's gonna be covered up anyway,
so that's not that troubling.
But I'm worried
because all aspects of this
makeup have to be perfect
because this is the last chance
to show the judges
that I have what it takes
to be in the finale.
The first thing I need to do
is hose down my bodysuit
with crystal clear,
which is an acrylic
that will make it
a little bit glossy.
See if we can get you
into that shirt.
Now I need to get my actor
in the top half
of my bodysuit.
And that's
a pretty big challenge.
- Are you in the sleeves sort of?
- Kind of.
It doesn't want to bend.
It's like wrestling,
trying to get him
into this suit.
Here, bend forward.
There you go.
I hear people laughing.
And for a second,
I'm relieved of all this
pressure and stress
- from the finale.
- It's so ridiculous.
But only for a second.
So all my pieces
are applied and steamed.
Now it's time to start painting,
which is my favorite part,
'cause painting it
brings it to life.
I want the face
to be very gorilla,
but with accents
of the crustacean.
So I base the face out
in light flesh tone,
and over the top of that,
I start stippling
different alcohol colors,
like reds, whites,
yellows, browns
to do the break-up and
make it look like realistic skin
rather than a foam piece.
They brought me in
for questioning?
I'm 3,000 feet tall.
I need to make these eyes
look like bug eyes,
so I cut a square of mesh,
and I place it
over the eyeballs,
and I airbrush right over it,
and it's gonna give the illusion
of praying mantis eyes.
I keep looking
at the hair glove
and how terrible
the hair looks.
I want you to start tearing
the fur off of that glove.
Get all of it off of there.
That way,
Lois won't bitch me out
about terrible hair work again.
I make a decision
to carry this burn makeup
onto both arms,
because it's gonna save me
from having to put horrible
hair work onstage
in this really,
really crucial challenge.
Oh, come on.
15 minutes, guys.
- That's time, guys!
- All right.
It's my last chance
to show the judges
that I have what it takes
to make it to the finale.
High five.
I'm looking at my makeup,
and the decision
to lose the hair
could either win this for me,
or it could sink me.
Coming up...
I'm not gonna make it
to the finale.
I'm really worried
about the tentacles.
Everything's so well executed.
He just bit off
more than he could chew.
I really like this character.
We have one hour in last looks,
and I'm just doing
whatever I can
to get this character done.
So I'm just painting
like crazy.
I'm so close at this point,
if I don't make it,
I would be
incredibly disappointed.
Is it okay if I glue some of
this stuff over this edge here
so it doesn't look like shit?
I'm moving lightning fast.
I get the black burns
all glued down,
and I finish the burn makeup
with some K-Y jelly,
which makes it look like
the burns have started
to ooze a little bit.
This makeup has to be spot-on,
or else I'm not gonna make it
to the finale.
You can hunch
the shoulders forward.
Can you pull them up?
I need to get the pants on
and get all the pieces
to the body blended together.
You look like squid Elvis.
But everything
from the neck down looks hokey.
So the main thing I'm worried
about is the tentacles.
The problem is there's
this giant cowl piece
and these hanging antenna
that are gonna have
to come through the suit.
So I have to reach in there
and guide the cowl through.
Then all of a sudden,
the suit pops on.
Ta-da!
And I'm thinking,
"This is awesome.
He's a giant monster."
Keep your eye closed
for a second.
15 minutes, guys.
All right, that's time!
Thanks, dude.
- Give me some claw.
- Yeah.
At this point,
I'm hoping that somebody else
messes up worse than I have.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated,
and three of you will earn
your place in the finale
to compete for the VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
First, let's say hello
to our talented judges--
owner of Optic Nerve
Makeup Effects Studio,
- Glenn Hetrick.
- Hi, guys.
Hi, Glenn.
Oscar-winning makeup artist
Lois Burwell.
- Good luck, all of you.
- Thanks, Lois.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
Hello, guys and lady.
Hi, Neville.
And joining us again tonight
is Emmy-nominated actor
Clifton Collins, Jr.
How you guys doing?
Welcome back, Clifton.
You ready to see some monsters?
Yeah.
All right, guys, this week
your spotlight challenge
was to use a dramatic
newspaper headline
and imagery as inspiration
for your very own
giant monster.
So, with only three finale spots
on the line,
let's take a look
at your monsters.
I am proud of this makeup,
and I'm thinking this
could get me into the finale.
There's a giant monster
standing in front of me.
Even if the judges hate it,
I'm happy,
because I got to make
a giant monster.
My squid walks out onstage,
and I think he fits
the challenge,
but I know
that it's not my best work.
I'm starting to get nervous.
If the judges
don't like the way
that I've approached
the burn makeups,
then I'm
gonna be really screwed.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look
at our monsters?
The coloring is lovely.
I like the teeth
and the patterning on the eyes.
It's just one of the few times
that an eyehole does not really
feel like an eye hole.
- Yeah.
- I love the incorporation
- of the mantis's camouflage.
- Yeah.
- It's really beautiful.
- Thank you.
From the front, it's a unique,
interesting Yeti-type face.
It's from the side that you
really see the crab.
- It's a good shape.
- Yeah.
_
The fact that he was able
to do all this
is fascinating
and intriguing to me.
He doesn't look happy, does he?
These things were,
in Japanese cinema
around the '60s, very hokey.
I think he was going
for that feel.
I like the nostalgia
of the old Japanese,
'60s throwback.
Can you turn around for us?
- It's not a bad side view.
- Yeah.
You never know what the judges
are gonna like
or what they're gonna hate.
And we're so close
to the finale.
It freaks me out
just thinking about it.
Which three artists
do you think will make it
to the finale?
Tell us on Twitter,
using #FaceOff.
I kind of like the transition
into the mouth
and then down to the shoulder.
That's an interesting idea.
I'm not feeling great,
but I'm hoping that the judges
at least like
how I did the cowl.
Thank you.
I like
that he just went right--
"I've got a sloth head,
sloth hands."
Then the rest he just made up
just to keep moving.
It's a good sculpt.
Sloths are silly-looking
characters and cute.
There's no getting around it.
- He's very appealing, isn't he?
- Yeah.
I think there's some really
nice paint textures
going on here--
simple, quick, but broken up.
Thank you.
The judges would now like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Drew, you're up.
Drew, tell us about
your giant-sloth character.
He was brought to the mainland
as a zoo attraction,
sort of like King Kong,
and he broke loose
and started destroying
and going crazy
on downtown Shanghai.
They tried to fight him off
with flamethrowers,
and his arms caught fire,
so that's why the burns
traveled up his arms
and on to the sides of his head
and to his chest as well.
You've created something
that feels successful
within this challenge.
I love the combination
of techniques,
both in your painting approach
and the overall fabrication.
I just think
you could have handled the burn
- with greater finesse.
- Thank you.
I really like this character,
I have to say.
It was a wise decision to go
for the hands and the head.
I think it's a very successful
makeup this week.
I don't get the sense
that you've modified
the physicality
to accommodate gigantism.
But the way the sculpture
and the design
sustains the character is what's
really beautiful about this.
Thank you.
The sloth face
is just so real-looking.
- I love where your head's at.
- Thank you very much.
- Drew, please step back.
- Thanks, Alex.
Cig.
So what can you tell us
about the Yeti crab?
He was a mutant byproduct
of the Chernobyl disaster,
and the Russians
discovered him,
but he couldn't be controlled,
and he busted out,
and he starts crashing
through Russia.
There are some elements
within this
that are absolutely lovely,
particularly the face.
Could you turn sideways?
Thank you.
When we see him in profile,
I think it works
exceptionally well.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
There are some great forms
in that face.
Where I struggle with this
is I don't see much
of the crab aesthetic happening.
That feels more like
a bumblebee,
and that is a subjective thing,
so don't take that too much
to heart.
I totally get
what you're saying.
I love what's going on.
I love the shadows,
and I really like the mix
of fur and shell on the back.
- You did a pretty sweet job.
- Thank you.
Cig, you can step back.
Thanks, guys.
George.
George, tell us
about your giant creature.
He's based
in the city of Dubai,
which is kind of known
for their excess.
So they had the biggest zoo
in the world,
where all the animals
were genetic experiments,
and this guy was the biggest,
and he broke out and then went
on a rampage in Dubai.
Where I think
you've really succeeded
is particularly in profile
with the head.
That's the George
that we've come to know,
'cause you're
a pretty fantastic sculptor
- and technician.
- Thank you.
The color work makes it
feel a little playful
- and less of a threat.
- Mm-hmm.
It takes me back
to my childhood.
I remember the squid monsters
and big giant robot
and things like that.
- So thank you.
- Thanks.
I'm heavily approving of
the sarlacc pit of the stomach
that you built.
Like, it's a really great idea.
I appreciate your enthusiasm
and that you were swinging
for the fences.
Thank you.
George, please step down.
Dina, you're up.
Please step forward.
Hey, Dina. You want to tell me
a little bit about mantis?
She is a praying mantis
who really had a taste
for the heads of her mates,
so she ate tons of them,
and to satisfy her hunger,
she worked her way up
the food chain to the big city,
where there are thousands of men
for her to feast on.
Really blown away
at the detail.
The head's really beautiful
and the detail in the eyes,
I love just looking at her.
Good job.
Thank you.
I really do love
the model's eyeholes.
Feels completely part
of the head.
- My goodness, I really like it.
- Thank you so much.
Everything is so fitting
and so well executed.
Every square inch
has been addressed in some way.
- I love it.
- Thank you.
Dina, please step back.
Good job.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you please head
back to the makeup room
while they decide
who will move on to the finale.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, guys.
All right,
so the question at hand is,
whose monster helps secure them
a spot in the finale?
So why don't we start
with Drew's sloth.
I feel like he spent
all his time on the head.
The expertise really showed.
I mean, the head
was almost close to perfect.
The problem is he gave us
a really nice sloth head
and some really nice
sloth claws,
and then
not-so-good burn makeup.
I do think the burn makeup
is disappointing.
It could have been
more proficiently expressed.
Absolutely.
So I'm on a fence
about Drew, honestly.
All right, let's move on
to Cig's Yeti crab.
He chose to do
a literalized "Yeti meets crab."
I happen to not like that look.
But it not only feels like
a Japanese giant monster,
it actually feels Japanese
in its design.
So, for this challenge,
I love it.
The thing that I really
enjoyed was that samurai look,
particularly around the face.
The guy's just so at home.
He clearly loves
Japanese monster movies.
All right, let's move on
to George's squid.
The form language on the head
is a standout on the makeup.
You can see the elegance
that George possesses.
I'm very fond of it.
He looks as if he's a plaything
from Doctor Who.
And there's something
so delightful about it
that I've sort of forgiven
the fact
that it isn't well executed.
He just bit off
more than he could chew
because he wanted it
to be amazing and big.
When he chose to tackle
the eight tentacles,
I think he just went south
really fast.
All right, let's move on
to Dina's praying mantis.
The most impressive thing
is the fact
that every square inch
of this character
has been addressed.
Yeah, that color, the shape,
the sculpt through here--
I mean, it's lovely work.
And think
about the actual surface area
that she had to paint.
- The painting's beautiful.
- Yeah!
I mean, granted,
it could have done
with maybe a little bit
more variation in color.
But that is really
just a bonus.
All right, judges,
so have you decided
who should move on
to the finale?
- I think we have.
- Excellent.
Well, Clifton, thank you so much
for being here with us tonight
and helping us
select our finalist.
Thanks for having me.
I had a blast.
All right, well,
let's bring them back out
and award some finale spots.
I just like the fire.
There's fire!
We walk out onstage,
and there's swords and torches.
I don't know what's going on.
Oh, God.
Welcome back.
As you can see,
I've done a bit of redecorating.
- It's lovely.
- Now, the things you see
around you are related
to our finale challenge.
Before I can tell you more,
you need to earn your spot.
So let's find out
who is moving forward.
Glenn, who is the winner
of this challenge
and the first person
to make it to the finale?
The first person joining us
in the finale is...
All right, Glenn, who is
the winner of this challenge
and the first person
to make it to the finale?
The winner
of tonight's challenge
and the first person
joining us in the finale is...
Dina.
Yes!
Thank you.
We would have been happy
with your mantis
if two people
would have worked on it.
So the amount of success
that you achieved by yourself
is all the more impressive.
Thank you so much.
Aah!
Holy crap.
Me?
The first week I was here,
I didn't think I measured up
to anyone,
so this feels so amazing.
- Dina, congratulations.
- Thank you.
You've earned the first spot
in the finale.
Yes!
Thank you.
All right, Glenn,
who is the next person
to make it to the finale?
The second person
that will be joining us
in the finale is...
Cig.
Whoo!
We loved the throwback nature
of your concept,
especially in profile.
The striated edges
were a really great way
to show off the crab aspect.
Thank you guys so much.
I honestly didn't think
I was gonna make it this far,
and now I'm in the finale.
Like, this is amazing.
Congratulations, Cig.
You've earned the second spot
in our finale.
All right,
we have two artists left
and only one spot.
So, Glenn, who has
the final spot in our finale?
Here I am, almost at the end.
I can see that $100,000.
Being eliminated right
before the finale
would be devastating.
I want to be a finalist, and
I think I deserve to be there.
The last person moving on
to the finale is...
Drew.
- Drew.
- Oh, my God.
Thanks, George.
You made a very smart decision
to focus on the sloth elements
of your character,
which gave you the time
to deliver
a very successful sculpture
- and a beautiful paint job.
- Thank you.
Congratulations, Drew.
You've earned the last spot
in the finale.
Thank you so much, guys.
I'm dumbstruck.
Being a finalist is beyond
what I'd ever hoped for,
and I'm so happy and so grateful
to have this opportunity.
Unfortunately,
that means, George,
you have been eliminated.
George, you can't get
too down on yourself
for making it this far.
You have delivered some amazing
makeups this season.
Unfortunately, this week
you just weren't up to the work
- of your peers.
- Yes.
George, it's been so great
having you here with us.
But if you would please head
back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thanks, guys.
Good luck, George.
I'm out!
I'm pretty disappointed,
but I've done some work
that I'm really proud of.
I got to make 13 monsters.
That's really cool.
I love doing
this stuff so much.
So I'm gonna go back
to my house,
finish building my shop,
and keep making monsters.
Only one challenge remains
between one of you
and our grand prize.
Oh, God.
We will end the season
the way we began--
with life and death.
And I've got several surprises
in store for you.
Oh, my God.
Without a pause for a breath
we're going straight
into the finale.
Shit!
Oh, God.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net