It is a gorgeous sculpt.
To me, this looks
like Teen Wolf.
Previously on Face Off...
Ten artists journeyed
into Wonderland.
Dina's flying monkey
stole the show,
and Jason was sent home.
Now nine artists remain,
and tonight's challenge reveals
a special surprise.
Oh, my God.
This is good.
For some, this is a dream
in the making.
But others will be haunted
by its results.
Damn it.
This is a big problem.
It's just so poorly executed.
In the end,
only one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Aah! Shit!
Oh!
Hey, whoa! Whoa!
I'm just--
Leave me to my perch.
I'm gonna get the girls.
- Huh!
That was pitiful.
- You guys ready?
- Yeah!
- Ooh-ooh!
- Whoa!
Spooky!
So we walk into the lab,
and it's all foggy and dark,
and McKenzie's standing there
next to a mirror,
and it's definitely
creeping me out.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey!
Let's talk about this week's
foundation challenge.
It's inspired
by an urban legend
of a female figure
so terrifying
that it's been used as a basis
for films like Candyman
and Paranormal Activity.
She's been described
as everything
from a corpse to a witch,
but no one knows
what she really looks like.
Oh, my God.
They call her "Bloody Mary."
Yeah!
Now, according to the legend,
if you say her name three times
while looking into a mirror,
you may never live to tell
anyone about it.
So why don't we try it?
- Oh, God.
No, I don't want to.
I refuse.
I know better.
That is a whole bag
you don't want to get into.
Bloody Mary.
Aah!
Creepy.
Oh, my God.
That's so cool.
All right, now that
I am thoroughly creeped out,
let's just move on
with this challenge.
As you may have guessed,
your foundation challenge
is to create your very
own version of Bloody Mary.
- Cool.
- Nice.
We get to make up
what Bloody Mary looks like?
This is awesome!
Your judge
for today's challenge
won an Emmy for her work
on Buffy The Vampire Slayer
and has been nominated twice
on the critically acclaimed
HBO series True Blood.
Please welcome
Brigette Myre-Ellis.
I'm a huge True Blood fan,
so this is awesome.
Hello. Thank you
so much for joining us.
It's a pleasure to be here.
- Hi, guys.
- Hi.
I know you're hard at work
on the final season
of True Blood.
- How's that going?
- It's insane.
It is an epic body of work
that I've been
so proud to work on,
and I think we've outdone
ourselves this year,
if you can believe it.
Now, you obviously
have a ton of experience
with supernatural characters.
What are you gonna be looking
for in their final makeups?
Ultimately, I want you guys
to scare me.
Not easy to do
after the career I've had.
The winner of today's challenge
will earn immunity and cannot
be eliminated this week.
You have two hours
for this challenge.
Good luck, guys,
because your time starts now.
That's fine right there.
I'm Keaghlan.
I'm actually gonna
run some tubes
that will pump blood through,
and it will look
like you're crying blood.
My original Bloody Mary
has been taken to Hell,
and then the forces of Hell
make her appear in mirrors
and drag other people to Hell.
We got to get messy today.
So I made some pieces.
I'm gonna try to get,
like, some glass shards
all over your face.
My Bloody Mary bursts
through the mirror,
and she's gonna
be eating people
that she sucks back in.
And she's gonna have
really nasty blood
dripping down from her mouth
and everything.
I want really
disgusting-looking blood
for my Bloody Mary,
and my concept is
she's a baby snatcher.
This is your bottom lip.
I found these
really cool horn shapes
that I'm gonna make
her mouth out of,
so she's got this beak
that helps her eat the baby.
I love these horns.
_
My Bloody Mary
wants to scare you
into taking your own life,
and I'm actually extending
her mouth down
to give her a really creepy
elongated face.
I'm doing a Bloody Mary
who steals faces,
so I lined slit throat pieces
all around her head
to make incision marks.
It's a little freaky,
but she looks very beautiful.
You got 10 minutes left!
That's it, guys!
Brushes down!
Time's up.
All right, so tell us
about your Bloody Mary.
She was just obsessed
with being beautiful,
and when she couldn't reach
the level that she wanted,
she actually killed herself
in the bathtub.
The color red that you chose,
I feel like, is very accurate.
Mm-hmm.
But I would just
consider next time
blending her little edge
right there.
Mm-hmm.
What did you use
to create the scarring?
Those are big neck pieces.
I enjoy your use of veins
coming up the neck, too,
to tie it all together.
You see the beauty in her,
and you see the horror.
Thanks.
So this is my Bloody Mary.
Her job is to claim your soul.
- Oh! Oh, my God!
- There it is!
I was so worried!
I know, right?
Where's the blood?
Here it is.
Really good job.
I look around the room,
and everybody's got
some awesome makeups.
There are so many
great artists left
in this competition,
and any one of these guys
could knock me out.
So, Brigette,
what do you think?
I'm really impressed
by your work today, you guys.
Thank you.
So who created
your favorite looks today?
Rachael...
I loved the way
that you took the incision
all the way around her face.
The whole concept
of how she stole faces
just creeped me out.
- Good job.
- Thanks.
Drew, to use a blood tube
was very daring
and very original.
- Very impressive.
- Thank you.
All right, Brigette,
who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of this challenge is...
Rachael.
All right!
Thank you.
You not only made her
absolutely beautiful,
but absolutely creepy.
- That is Bloody Mary.
- Congratulations.
You have earned immunity
and cannot be eliminated
in the next
spotlight challenge.
It's awesome to win immunity.
I can't wait to see
what the next challenge is.
I want to go crazy.
I will see you later tonight
to tell you about
your next spotlight challenge.
- Good-bye.
- Bye.
Thank you.
Uh-oh.
- I'm scared.
- What is happening?
We are at Universal Studios,
and it is really spooky.
Oh, shit!
Standing in the distance
is McKenzie
and this huge lit-up marquee.
"Universal Studios
Halloween Horror Nights."
What?
I knew it was gonna be spooky!
Horror challenge!
This is amazing.
Welcome back to the incredible
Universal Studios back lot.
This week's spotlight challenge
taps into one of the most
timeless forms of advertising--
movie posters.
Movie posters must capture
the essence of a film
in just a single glance.
Posters in most genres
tend to showcase
either the handsome hero
or the beautiful starlet.
But horror-movie posters
tease us
with only mysterious images
or taglines about
their villainous stars.
So your spotlight challenge
is to choose one
of these original movie posters
and use the imagery, title,
and tagline
as inspiration to create
its villainous lead character.
- Sweet!
- Yes!
I'm a huge horror-movie fan.
This is definitely my element.
So your options are The Cloven,
"It was too hot in Hell."
Bone Appetit,
"Dinner is served."
The Trophy Room,
"It's hunting season."
Bonnie and Cyanide,
"A toxic romance."
Homecoming Scream,
"Save the last dance."
Buzzcut,
"Just a little off the top."
We Met Online,
"There's no escape key."
The Second Chumming,
"Swim at your own risk."
And Axe Girlfriend,
"Breakups can be hell."
Stella, you get first pick.
The Trophy Room.
Homecoming Scream.
Bonnie and Cyanide.
Bone Appetit.
Cloven.
We Met Online.
Buzzcut.
Axe Girlfriend.
Second Chumming.
Now, to tell you more,
please welcome
the creative directors
of Universal Studios
Halloween Horror Nights
in Hollywood and Orlando,
John Murdy and Mike Aiello.
These guys are the big bosses
from the Halloween
Horror Nights,
so this is super exciting.
- Hello.
Good to have you guys here.
Fantastic being here.
Universal Studios
Halloween Horror Nights
is the nation's premiere
Halloween event.
We combine
movie-quality sets
and award-winning
makeup artists
all together
into a haunted maze
to bring our guests'
nightmares to life.
Nice.
All right, now,
there's a major prize
on the line this week.
Oh-ho.
What?
This is good.
Coming up...
Ugh. The design
is just not working.
Guys, stop messing
with the wigs.
Hats off to you.
This looks like a ton of work.
There's a major prize
on the line this week.
Oh-ho.
What?
For the first time ever,
both parks are featuring
the best makeup
from all prior seasons
of Face Off...
- Awesome.
- Very cool.
Including the winner
of this challenge.
Wow!
To see a creature
that I have made
in Halloween Horror Nights
would be, like,
one of the coolest things.
Now, there are very few people
in show business
that can scare a crowd
like you two.
What advice do you have
for the contestants?
When John and I are
translating a horror property
into a haunted maze,
we've got to look
at every single detail,
so I encourage you
to do the same
with your movie posters.
Find that small detail,
because sometimes
they tell the best story.
Thank you again so much
for being here.
Thanks for having us.
All right, well, the time has
come for you to start working
on your designs.
- Good luck, guys.
- Thank you.
- Good night.
- Thanks, guys.
My poster is Homecoming Scream,
and my killer is
a 1950s homecoming queen,
so I decide
to do a grayscale makeup,
because I really want this
to be reminiscent
of a B horror movie
from the 1950s.
She is the victim
of a tragic senior prank,
where she breaks her neck,
and now her head
is facing straight,
but the rest of her body
is backwards.
Beautiful,
but really dark and twisted.
I'm so stoked
for this challenge.
I get The Second Chumming,
and the tagline is
"Swim at your own risk."
I get the idea to do
this salty old sea captain
made of chum.
I'm planning a cowl
that also incorporates
the bottom the jaw,
and then I'm gonna do
a face piece
that incorporates the tongue
and the top of the head.
I'm worried this time
I might be biting off
more than I can chum.
So my movie is Buzzcut.
The tagline is
"Just a little off the top,"
and I'm getting really excited
that I can maybe create
some kind of psychotic doctor
that's going around
scalping people.
I'm going to actually make
some silicone scalps
and take them and put them
on his head.
And I want to put lots
of, like, slime in there.
So, when he peels it back,
it's really stringy and gross.
I chose We Met Online.
The tagline is
"There's no escape key."
I like the aesthetic
of this creepy weirdo
on the other end
of a chat line,
who tricks these girls
into meeting him
and ultimately eats them.
I picked Bonnie and Cyanide,
"A toxic romance."
What I decide to do
is make Bonnie this woman
who's been poisoned
by her husband,
and she built
this arm contraption
that takes the poison
out of her veins,
then she can inject
the poisonous blood
into other people.
All right, guys,
let's head home.
Dude, that sketch is badass.
He's a cannibal.
- Whoo!
- Yeah, let's get started.
It's the first day
of our Halloween
Horror Nights challenge,
and we have six hours
in the lab.
The poster I pick
is Axe Girlfriend,
"Breakups can be hell."
So my character's
a jilted mistress
who was shot in the head
by her lover.
Now she's back from Hell,
wielding this axe
to seek vengeance.
So I'm sculpting
a big gunshot wound to her face.
I'm gonna cast it in silicone,
because it moves more realistic
than any other appliance
material that we have.
You're going goat, right?
I'm going deer.
Oh, that's right.
I forgot.
You're doing reindeer.
I end up picking The Cloven,
"It was too hot in Hell,"
so my first thought is
a demon reindeer
Santa sent him to Hell
for torturing the elves,
but it's too hot
in Hell for him.
- Are you gonna make antlers?
- Yeah.
I've never really sculpted
anything like this before,
but I'm hoping
this will come together.
Don't look so excited.
My movie poster
says Bone Appetit,
and "Dinner is served"
is my tagline.
I come up with this
cannibalistic baroness idea.
I definitely want to do
an old-age makeup on the face,
but I also want to have her
eat people
with a mouth stomach.
_
Creepy.
I chose The Trophy Room,
"It's hunting season."
My character is a hunter.
Whenever people encroach
upon his hunting grounds,
he kills them
and cuts their head off
and mounts them on their wall.
He's inbred and was born
with facial deformities,
so his head is really swollen
on one side,
and he's got a cleft palate.
It's disturbing.
- That's a good one.
- Yeah.
I look like I work
at a video store.
Yeah, an adult video store.
Oh, God.
Hey, George,
can I borrow your pick?
You guys are making it hard
for me to work next to you.
Guys, stop messing
with the wigs.
Really, we need to be working.
I'm sorry.
No more funny business.
I have no idea what I'm doing.
Ugh.
Sculpting a deer face
on a human form
is really difficult.
It's not
a reindeer/human hybrid.
It's a reindeer.
If it was a hybrid,
I think I would have
a much easier time,
'cause I could incorporate
some of the human forms
into the deer forms,
but I'm going straight reindeer.
Oh, God.
I just feel like
it's getting worse and worse.
This is the first time
where I felt like
the design is just not working.
Come on, man, I need this.
This is a big problem.
Oh, damn it.
So it's day one of our
Horror Nights villain challenge.
I'm just having
a really hard time.
Sculpting a deer face
is really difficult.
- Cat.
- But I don't think it's--
Cat.
It doesn't look like a deer.
It looks like a cat.
Ugh.
So I kind of, like,
just give up.
_
I know.
And I mold it,
because I have no other choice.
- What are you making?
- I'll make some fingers.
My villain keeps trophies
from her kills.
She cuts off their ring fingers
and makes a necklace
out of them.
So I use alginate,
which is a seaweed-based
impression material,
to make a mold.
Go for it.
Within ten minutes or so,
it sets up into this gel,
so I pour platinum silicone
directly into the mold
so it's a easy way of making
silicone body parts
and things like that.
So creepy.
30 minutes, guys.
So I need to fabricate
my hair transplant
surgeon's skullcap.
So I start
with the vacuform machine,
then try to figure out
the right size.
Nope.
That one's too small.
Finally, I get the exact size
that I need.
No, actually,
that's pretty good.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
That's time!
So at the end of the day,
I got my scalp completed
in time.
Tomorrow I have to get veins
and hair laid on it,
as well as sculpt and mold
my cowl,
so there's a lot to do.
It's day two of our Halloween
Horror Nights villain challenge.
We have 9 1/2 hours in the lab,
and I have to finish my torso,
and I'm really paying attention
to anatomy,
because my homecoming queen
is twisted and mangled.
It needs to read
like a back on the chest
and a chest on the back,
so I want to make sure that
I do it as perfectly as I can.
So today I need
to sculpt my hooves.
I definitely need
these hooves on my makeup,
because the movie poster
has a hoof
coming out of the ground.
So, hopefully, they'll turn
out better than the face.
My cowl's done,
so I need to mold it.
It's a pretty big mold,
so it's gonna take some time,
so I'm trying to get that done
as soon as possible,
because I still have to sculpt
more chummy bits
'cause there's a lot
of surface area to cover.
I am working on the face,
and I'm not used
to old-age makeup,
so I'm taking my time
with the sculpt.
Just because I have immunity
doesn't mean I want to make
a crappy piece.
What is all this shit?
Ha!
Mad science.
The idea of these arm weapons
is that she can push out
the poisonous blood
into her victims.
So I take plastic tubing
and inject neon colors in,
because the poison has altered
the color of her blood.
I've never fabricated anything
like this before,
but I feel confident
that it's gonna look cool.
Really cool.
It's so good.
My villain keeps heads
mounted on a wall,
so I want to make
a separate head for him.
So I pour up a latex face,
find a styrofoam head,
pin it into place,
and hot-glue the wig
into place,
and I have
this awesome severed head.
All right, everybody,
that's time.
Whoo-hoo!
Well, all my pieces are done,
but I have an insane amount
of work to do tomorrow.
Man.
There's a lot
of surface area to paint,
and this is probably
the most appliances
that I've ever applied
on a single person ever,
so that has me worried.
- Let's do this.
- It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab
and one hour in last looks.
Let's see it.
It's not terrible.
Thank God.
- Morning.
- Hi.
- You're giving me the finger.
- Yeah.
Your veins are, like, neon.
Can you lean your head back?
I need to apply
this face piece,
and the thing with silicone
is it's so heavy,
so I need to recline her back
on the chair.
If I were to apply it
with you upright,
it would all stretch down
by your cheeks
and wouldn't really be the way
I sculpted it.
The mouth looks awesome.
I think this stomach
is probably my favorite thing
I've created
in this competition,
and I am really excited
to present it to the judges.
Cool shit.
I like it.
He's the bubble-gum monster.
When I paint gore,
I base everything out
in a bubble-gum paint,
because when you put
the other colors over that,
it really sells the gore.
It looks really funny at first,
but I know where
I'm going with it,
so I'm not worried.
You're gonna get
gummed to death.
Ohh!
Okay, and then flip.
I'm gonna get the top, yeah.
I'm trying to do veins here.
Oh, this is terrible.
But this is not veins.
They're not looking realistic
or convincing at all,
and I really don't know
how to make this better.
Ten minutes, guys!
That's time, guys!
It's good.
You're beautiful.
I am so disappointed in myself.
It's just not very good.
I don't want to go home,
but I really don't know if
I have enough time to fix this.
Coming up...
I don't know how to apply
this stuff.
- It's taking forever.
- Ha, ha!
I'm really worried
that I might be going home.
- It's great fun.
- I love all of that.
This is not your best work.
There it is.
We get to last looks, and
I got a lot to do in one hour.
I don't even know
how to apply this stuff.
I need to cover the entire thing
in blood.
It's taking forever,
and I'm starting to regret
the decision
to make an entire chum bag.
I still have to add
neon colors to the veins
and attach the arm weapons.
I really don't know
if I have enough time.
I need to dry off your teeth.
All right, you ready for this?
It just needs some blood.
I want to make her
adequately bloody,
but not overly bloody--
just some accents of blood.
You're very, very creepy.
Yeah!
Ha, ha!
You're disgusting!
I get the sash on
and splatter blood head to toe
slap my hand.
I love her.
I think she looks so creepy.
I'm worried about this makeup.
The hair is awful.
The face sculpt is bad.
I'm not happy with anything.
15 minutes, guys.
Time, everybody!
Yeah.
My makeup's not near
as good as anyone else's.
I'm just so mortified
right now.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
First, let's say hello
to our talented judges--
owner of Optic Nerve
Make-Up Effects Studio,
Glenn Hetrick...
- Good evening, guys.
- Hi, Glenn.
Oscar-winning makeup artist
Lois Burwell...
Evening, all.
- Hi, Lois.
And creature and
concept designer Neville Page.
Hello, everyone.
- Hi, Neville.
This week
your spotlight challenge
was to select
a horror-movie poster
and use it as inspiration
to create its villainous
lead character.
The winning makeup
will be featured
at Universal Studios
Halloween Horror Nights,
Hollywood and Orlando.
Let's take a look
at your fear-inducing creations.
My villain
looks really awesome.
I'm really stoked
that my character
came out the way it did.
My reindeer from Hell
does not look scary at all.
I might be going home
for this one.
The sculpting
is really not good.
The veins
don't look convincing.
It just looks like a joke.
He is a giant chum bag,
and I think I have a really
good shot at winning this.
I think this is a solid makeup,
and I'm proud
of the realism aspect.
It's really everything
that I could have wanted.
I think my character
is really creepy,
and he looks gross
and villainous
and very scary.
Suddenly I realize
that my homecoming queen's sash
is on backwards.
It definitely defeats
the illusion.
I think my baroness
looks awesome.
I just made
a really cool piece.
I love my creepy character,
and I feel great
about this makeup.
Judges, why don't you
take a closer look
at our horror villains?
There's an interesting detail.
Oh, yeah, there we go.
Oh, that is so juicy.
That is juicy.
Oh, yeah.
That's good stuff.
Thanks.
Ooh. Without those horns,
this is a pig.
Nice delineation in the paint
going on into the hoof.
Yeah.
I assume it's meant
to be veins.
Yeah.
It looks as if someone's
just gone mad.
I'm so upset
that they have to look
at this terrible makeup.
I think it looked better
from farther away.
Yeah, real far.
I know that I messed up,
and I could absolutely
be going home.
Who made your favorite
horror villain?
Tell us on Twitter,
using #FaceOff.
I'm so upset that the judges
have to look at
this terrible makeup that I did.
I can't imagine them
liking anything.
Will you turn to the side
for us?
Let's see you open and close
your fake jaw.
It's a cool idea.
We've never seen
this done before.
No, it's very smart.
I like the fingers.
Yeah, it's really horrible
in a good way.
Yeah.
Oh, it's a great mouth.
But it's just a face
with boils on it.
There's not much more
going on than that.
Thanks.
- I think this is the spine...
- That's the vertebrae.
If you wouldn't have said that,
I wouldn't have known.
It's overambitious.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's creepy.
This is such a cool idea.
I want there to be a story
that explains this.
I really do love
the forms on this.
Great pear head shape--
very hillbilly mutant,
- very successful.
- Yeah.
Okay, the judges
have scored your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Stella...
Drew...
Damien...
Congratulations,
because you are all safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you.
The rest of you were the best
and the worst this week.
Now, the judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Rachael, please step up.
Tell me about the process,
how you went from the poster
into a makeup.
I had Bone Appetit,
so I thought, "Feast."
This is my baroness.
She throws these crazy, big,
wild parties,
and what the people don't know
is that she's actually a demon
feeding these people
other people.
I have to tell you
that I'm really impressed.
The mechanism in the chest
is really inspired.
This is
a wonderfully unique way
to have handled
the subject matter.
Thank you.
I like the tummy teeth,
but I think to actually
make it more into a mouth,
it needs to be
more moist looking.
This chest reveal,
conceptually,
I think is pretty compelling,
and I think that the animation
is so good.
I think this is
a successful character.
Rachael, please step back.
Dina, you're next.
Tell us about the character
you've created.
The poster I chose
was The Cloven,
and this is
my outcast reindeer,
who loves torturing elves.
It misses the mark.
I can't get past the concept,
and although it's a reindeer,
it looks a very piggy reindeer.
The problem is
that the face is lacking
in the detail department,
and this is The Cloven.
This is about the hoof.
It doesn't look like a hoof.
It feels like it could be
some kind of a vegetable
or a different creature,
like a crab claw or something.
This concerns me.
Dina,
if you'd please step down.
- All right, let's talk to George.
- All right.
Tell us which poster you got
and the resulting character
you designed.
I chose Axe Girlfriend,
"Breakups can be hell."
She was the mistress
of a rich man,
who popped her in the head,
so there's an entrance wound
over on this side,
and it came up
and through her face
and blew all this nastiness
all over.
I do like the character
head to toe.
The precision
that you've achieved
with the exit wound is great.
Thank you.
I think that you used
a really nice,
realistic approach--
the silicone piece--
and you exercised
a lot of restraint.
Instead of trying to put
holes all over her,
just one wound,
which is telling your story.
I love all of that.
George, you can head back.
Good job.
Keaghlan, please step forward.
Tell us what movie poster
you chose.
I chose the Homecoming Scream.
She is a victim
of a senior prank
where she is pushed
off of bleachers
and breaks her neck and
twists her head halfway around.
It doesn't visually
communicate what your intent is.
Her breasts
are on her back, correct?
Yeah.
So her face needs
to be facing that way.
And then shouldn't
the "Homecoming Queen" banner
be on the other way too?
That was a mistake.
There's a lot of them.
Lois deciphered
what was going on.
I didn't know till she told me.
Hats off to you
for attempting something
so difficult,
but I don't like the sculpting.
That kind of blank full head
is neither here,
there, nor anywhere.
Keaghlan, you can step down.
Cig, please come forward.
Tell us how your creature
comes from the poster.
I got The Second Chumming.
There's
this salty old sea captain,
and the crew hates him,
so they kill him
and put him in the chum barrel,
where he fuses with the chum
and becomes a chum bag.
I think it's great fun.
Using the chin as the tongue
is a very clever thing.
I've never seen it before.
This looks like a ton of work.
There's a lot
of purposeful texture in there,
and I'm really impressed
with your time management.
Thank you.
Cig, please step back.
Sasha, please step up.
Hi, Sasha.
Tell us about your poster
and the character
that you designed.
The poster I chose
was Bonnie and Cyanide.
Bonnie has been poisoned
by her husband,
and she built these tools,
and she can stick the poison
into other people.
Um...
It doesn't look anything
like what it is
that you were trying to do.
The veins are a disaster.
It's as if you've never
seen a vein before in your life.
I understand
these engorged veins.
I get the concept,
but it's just
so poorly executed.
This is not your best work.
Sasha, you can head back.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
All right, judges,
why don't we talk
about the looks you liked
the most this week?
Let's start with Rachael.
- Big idea.
- Yeah.
Done so well.
Her greatest success is
that she looked at this poster,
and she pulled out
very creative visual cues.
That's what this challenge
was all about.
Let's move on to Cig.
It was a huge amount of work.
There were some nice touches,
like that lovely skull detail
on the shoulder.
And it was such a cool idea
to make his lower jaw
stabilized by the chest
so that he could use
his head movement.
It's not been done
on this stage before.
Okay, let's move on to George.
The color painted
on the silicone appliance
looked really good.
And even though
it was a bloody character,
he did not pour gallons
of blood over the hair,
and that restraint shows
an advanced type of approach
to makeup effects.
All right, judges,
so before we move on
to the looks
you liked the least,
I just want to remind you
that you do have
that special immunity
available to save somebody
to see some more of their work.
Let's move on to Dina.
This was not
a successful makeup.
I'm very concerned
how it illustrated
her lack
of anatomical knowledge.
And the sculpt of the deer head
and the cloven hooves--
none of it was good work.
All right,
let's move on to Keaghlan.
I wish more detail
had been spent on the face.
It became stone
rather than monochrome.
Having the vertebrae
in the front
and the breasts on the back,
that's fine,
but the sculpture
of those two elements
was so soft and vague.
Let's move on to Sasha.
There was clearly
an apparent lack
of cardiovascular knowledge.
It looked like a child
with crayons on the wall,
and that concerned me,
because she is
so much better than that.
I just think
she was completely lost.
All right, then, judges,
have you made your decisions?
We have.
Let's bring them back out.
Glenn, tell us
about the top looks.
Rachael, we really liked
your character's backstory,
and we were particularly fond
of the way
that you rigged the mouth
to your character's chest.
George, your villain
was definitely
one of the most realistic
makeups out there tonight,
and it was incredibly
well suited
to your film poster.
And, Cig, we love
that you embraced
a gloriously gory concept,
and we were really impressed
with everything
that you were able to get done.
All right, who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
All right, Glenn, who is
the winner of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
George.
Yes!
Finally got one.
It means a lot.
We think your villain
was spot-on for this challenge,
and we can easily envision
her scaring people
at Universal Studios
Halloween Horror Nights.
- Great job.
- Thank you.
This is my first win.
It feels great.
People are gonna pay
to be scared by my makeup.
That's really cool.
George, congratulations.
Your makeup will be featured
at Universal Studios
Halloween Horror Nights,
Hollywood and Orlando.
You, Cig, and Rachael, can head
back to the makeup room.
Unfortunately,
that does mean the three of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
If you'd please step forward.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Dina, we get that you wanted
to do something different,
but this was
a horror challenge,
and there's nothing scary
about your makeup.
Keaghlan,
it was a valiant effort,
but it was just too much work
with the timeline
for this challenge,
and that showed
in your final work.
Sasha,
between the poor sculpting
and the bizarre
paint decisions,
we really struggled
to find something
about this makeup
that we liked.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Sasha.
We had a really hard time
understanding
where it was you were going
with this character.
It didn't work for us
on any level.
Sasha, I'm sorry,
but that means
you have been eliminated.
Dina, Keaghlan, you are safe
and can head
back to the makeup room.
Sasha, we really like
some of the work
that we' seen from you
in the past,
and we all know
that you're very talented...
Thank you.
...which is precisely why
we've decided to use our
special immunity and save you
from elimination this week.
Ahh!
Me?
You.
You went way off
the rails this week,
but we know that you
are capable of much better work.
So, show us an amazing
makeup next week!
I promise so much.
I'm gonna make
something really good.
Good. Pull your socks up
next week.
My socks?
Oh, it's an expression.
Put socks on,
then pull them up.
Okay, I will pull my socks up.
All right, Sasha, that means
you are safe this week.
You can head
back to the makeup room.
Thank you.
- Good luck.
- Ooh!
- Don't fall.
I won't fall.
I can't believe they saved me!
This is so awesome!
I was saved!
The save is gone,
and I am so focused now.
Welcome back!
I'm going to prove
to the judges
that they saved me
for a reason.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net