Welcome to the Face Off
season finale.
Face Off!
Tonight, this season's
epic battle
of life and death
becomes an all-out war.
I have got several surprises
in store for you.
- Guys, come on out.
- Oh, my God!
And only three artists
remain in the fight.
It's so good
in so many different ways.
It's absolutely horrific.
I just wanna constantly
make monsters, so bring it on.
Dina, I know that you
decorate cakes for a living,
but I think you
might have found
your true calling in makeup.
If I win Face Off,
that would validate
me switching careers.
Everything about it
was extremely well done.
I have a one in three chance
of winning this thing,
and it's insane.
- I'm in panic mode.
- Watch as they strive
to overcome obstacles.
This needs some changes.
I have to rethink
my whole concept.
Wait, what the fuck am I doing?
I just don't have time for this.
On their way to the biggest
clash in Face Off history.
Let the games begin!
In the end,
only one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan Professional
Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Only one challenge remains
between one of you
and our grand prize.
And I have got several surprises
in store for you.
Without a pause for breath,
we're going from the last
spotlight challenge
straight into the finale.
I have no idea what
the challenge is going to be,
but the stage has been
completely transformed.
There's all these swords and all
these medieval coat of arms.
So I can't wait to see
what's in store.
Your final spotlight challenge
taps into one of the oldest
and most popular characters
in fantasy film history...
Oh, God!
- Knights.
- Yes!
Cool.
I'm... What, seriously?
I love medieval times.
I love, like, knights
and chivalry.
I couldn't have asked for,
like, a better finale challenge.
Now, whether it's
the ringwraiths
in The Lord Of The Rings
or the knights
from Game Of Thrones,
knights can represent
both good and evil.
So we will end this season
the way we began.
With life and death.
Your final spotlight challenge
is to create
two fantasy knights of your own,
one that is heroic
and embodies life,
and the other a villainous
knight embodying death.
Awesome.
Now, there's a lot
at stake here,
so you obviously are gonna need
a little bit of help.
Guys, come on out.
Hi!
You'll each get to choose
one of your former competitors
to join your team.
Drew, you're up first.
George.
Yes!
- Cig.
- Sasha.
And, of course, Dina.
- Stella.
- Yay!
- We've won one before together.
- I know!
Let's do it again.
I'm sure you're
probably thinking
you might need some more help,
right?
- Yeah.
- Well, don't worry.
I've got a few more artists here
to help you
who know exactly what it takes
to win Face Off.
Take a look.
Oh, my God!
- No way!
- That's right.
Each of you will also have help
from one of these former
Face Off champs.
Rayce, Face Off
season two champion,
Nicole,
our season three winner,
and Rashaad,
last season's champion.
Holy crap.
These are three amazing artists.
They've done this before.
They've been through it.
So it's nice to have someone
on our team
who can help us
get through this.
Welcome back, guys.
It's great to have you here.
- Good to be back.
- You ready to show these guys
- how it's done?
- Yeah!
I'm very happy to be back.
I'm excited,
and whoever I'm paired up with,
I'm gonna give them my all.
Now, to keep things fair,
we've randomly assigned
one of our champions
to each of you.
So, Dina, you have Nicole.
- Hey.
- Hey, girl!
Let's win this thing.
Drew, you're paired with Rayce.
- Nice. What's up, dude?
- How you doing, Drew?
- Good to meet you.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Of course, that means,
Cig, you have Rashaad.
Now, regardless of whether
a knight was good or evil,
they always wore
a unique coat of arms
as a symbol of their allegiance
during battle.
Each of you will pull a sword
from a stone
to select one of these coat
of arms and use its symbols
and colors to inspire
your final knight makeups.
- Dina, you're up first.
- Awesome.
There's this really cool
aquatic-looking coat of arms
with an octopus wearing a crown.
So I'm going for aquatic.
Drew, you're next.
I've always been drawn
to the imagery of deer.
So I want the coat of arms
with the stag's head.
- Cool sword.
- Yeah, it is.
And lastly, Cig.
I always wanted to do this.
I'm gonna do it! I'm gonna pull
a sword out of a stone!
Yes!
Cross that off the bucket list.
Well, I can't wait
to see your creations.
But what good is a knight
without putting him to the test
in a battle?
Each of your characters
will partake
in a fantastical
knight's tournament
complete with jousting
and an epic sword fight.
- Oh, my God!
- That's awesome!
Why don't you all head back
to the house and get some rest?
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
- Tally ho!
- I'm so excited!
It's day one
of our finale challenge.
And we have nine
and a half hours in the lab.
Let's do it.
We pick our models
and start sketching away.
Ah! This is so exciting!
To win Face Off would literally
change my life.
So I really want to win this.
And I'm pulling from
all the things
that are on on the coat of arms.
I have gargoyles, a crescent
moon, and a couple stars.
Dark, we could go really
skeletal armor.
My death knight is gonna have
a very evil, gargoyle face,
and I want to fabricate
an entire suit of armor
that looks very skeletal.
And Rashaad
is a genius fabricator.
His fireman robot was one of
the best characters I've seen,
so I'm just gonna trust him
fully with any fabrication.
What do you think
about the good guy?
I think some filigrees,
and, like, really regal,
refined.
Sort of beginning transition.
I'm not sure what I'm gonna do
with the life knight.
I'm toying with the idea that
they're a race of gargoyles,
and when they die
they become evil.
I'm just setting Rashaad loose
on sculpting.
And then we'll keep
conceptualizing
as we're moving along.
So we're looking
at our coat of arms,
and we're doing something
very aquatic.
And everything they're wearing
is gonna be from things
found under the sea.
I'm thinking,
for the death knight,
sort of a king crab crustacean.
And he's actually dead,
but he's brought back to life
by these electric eels.
So he'll be kind of zombified.
- For the good guy...
- Yeah.
...we should do something
a little more beautiful.
A mermaid actually
gave my life knight
the ability to live underwater.
So he's gonna be this fish-man
with all this armor
from the sea.
That's, like, exactly
what I'm thinking.
Nicole is such
an amazing artist.
She's really good at beautiful
and creepy makeups.
So I'm really excited
to work with her.
If you wanna start maybe
on the fish guy...
- Okay.
- ...then I can start
- on this crab dude.
- Okay.
Do you want the hybrid at all?
Yeah. Based on
our coat of arms,
my concept is two
dueling factions
of woodland elf creatures.
The light race,
they are more perfect forms.
So the light character sort of
this beautiful cedar
with features of deer anatomy.
And the death character will have
deer-like forms
that have become overgrown.
You start blocking out
the cowls.
- Okay.
- You and I will start
on the faces.
I wanna get the faces
mostly done today.
Rayce is a genius
conceptual artist.
And he's really awesome
with paint work
and an amazing sculptor.
He's getting all
of these gnarled scars
and really cool wrinkle lines
into the face design.
I'm really, really stoked
to be working with him.
Your sculpting skills
terrify me.
- I'm mediocre at best.
- You shut your mouth.
Awesome.
So I have Nicole
working
on the good knight face,
and I'm starting
on the bad knight face.
Midway, we switch.
'Cause I want a hand
in everything that we do.
- I'll make it bigger.
- All right.
Stella has the starfish
blocked out,
wrapping around him,
protecting him.
We're gonna use it as armor.
Stella, I'll come and pipe
and you can mess with these.
- Okay.
- I actually do some
finishing touches on it
with some piping.
I just pipe all the little dots
onto it.
- Dina?
- Yes?
- It looks amazing.
- This?
- It does.
- Oh, my God.
- Hey, guys!
- Hi!
To stay with the theme
of our challenge,
I'm wearing the Westmore
coat of arms.
Over 100 years old.
All right, so tell us about the
coat of arms that you picked.
It has gargoyles,
and in the middle,
there's a black crescent moon
and three stars.
So these knights get cursed.
So anytime they die, they come
back as these gargoyles.
I'm gonna take some
of that bone structure
and subtly put it over here.
You have to be careful
that they both
- don't look too dark.
- True.
I think you need
to lighten his features.
Okay. It didn't really occur
to me before,
but the life character
is definitely snarly
and creature-esque,
so that definitely
makes me reconsider the face
for the life character.
- That's a good point.
- It is.
Our concept
is two battling races
of elfin fawn people.
How is your thickness
on this one here?
It's very thin underneath
the major emote areas.
In being so thin, I would say
get that nose anchored first
because these are gonna
be very difficult,
being as then as they are,
to get them placed.
- Yeah.
- So the octopus is the king
and these two were serving
under him.
We're doing kind of
a crustacean.
He was dead, but then some eels
wrapped around him
and their electricity
shocked him back to life.
In your coat of arms,
you had an octopus
- and you're doing a crab.
- Yeah.
- Why?
- Well, the octopus is actually
wearing a crown, so we were
thinking he's just the king,
and these are the knights
under the king.
- Hmm.
- This is the finale challenge.
And Mr. Westmore's not liking
what I'm doing.
This is a big problem.
I would add something into this
that's octopus-y,
because it's an element
of your coat of arms
that you're literally missing.
Yeah, very.
Oh, God. Now I have
to rethink my whole concept.
I'm just completely lost
and overwhelmed.
Coming up...
I'm in panic mode.
We're running out of time.
Wait, what fuck am I doing?
I just painted these pieces
the wrong frigging color.
This is for
the whole enchilada.
The winner of Face Off is...
I would add something
that's octopus-y into this,
because it's an element
of your coat of arms.
- That you're literally missing.
- Yeah, very.
It's day one
of our finale challenge,
and I have to rethink
my whole concept.
- This needs some changes.
- We're doing two characters
and I don't have time
to rethink everything.
So I'm just completely
freaking out.
- Good luck to everybody.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
I'm feeling pretty down
right now,
and my team can see it.
_
Dina's really worried,
so I'm just gonna
be that voice of reason,
help figure out how
to incorporate that octopus.
I'm trying to think.
What if we put the tentacles
hiding underneath the shell?
Nicole suggests that
instead of the eels
bringing him back to life,
the octopus crawls
into the head of our crustacean,
kind of controls his brain
with his tentacles.
_
_ _
Okay, George,
I think it's ready for you.
- Okay.
- We get the faces finished,
and George has actually
volunteered
to be in charge
of all the molds.
He's not only really good at it,
he's really fast at it.
So while I am picking up
where George left off
on the light creature's cowl,
Rayce is sculpting
the dark creature's cowl.
My team is playing into
each one of our strengths,
and it's sort of running
like a well-oiled machine.
Yeah, that's already
more elfin.
It's towards the end of the
day, and Rashaad's sculpting
this great face
for the life character.
But it still just
doesn't feel right to me.
It's time, guys.
My plan is to sleep
on the life character
and hopefully a brilliant idea
will come to me.
My brain hasn't let me down yet.
So it's day two.
We have nine and a half hours
- in the lab today.
- Nice.
Looks real good.
We have to finish
these cowls today
because I really wanna
start pre-painting tomorrow.
So I'm focusing more
on the death knight cowl,
and Nicole is working
on the life knight.
And Stella starts molding
the chest piece.
_
Gotta go with my gut
on this one.
I was able to sleep on it,
and now I have
a really solid story
for both of my characters.
Instead of having
the life knight
starting to turn
into a gargoyle,
I wanna take a chance and do
a human silicone makeup.
So I have to start over
from scratch.
While I'm sculpting it,
Sasha is going to
finish the details
of the collar piece.
I'll have Rashaad
fabricating armor.
- Georgie?
- Yeah?
It's ready.
We get the light character's
cowl finished,
but the dark character's cowl
still needs a lot of work.
It has a lot more texture
and detail.
So Rayce and I decide to start
tag-teaming that sculpture
together.
I like it.
One hour, everyone!
I'm, like, in panic mode.
We can do it.
We can do it, we can do it.
We're running out of time
and I really need
to get both of these molds open
and cleaned out
- by the end of the day.
- Ooh!
So we open
the death knight's cowl,
and we start power washing that.
I don't think we're
gonna have time
to get the other cowl
open today.
There's just no way.
But Nicole is gonna
try to go for it anyway.
_
- We have four minutes.
- Four?
All of a sudden, George
and Rayce and Drew walk out
with our life knight mold.
I just can't even believe
they're helping us out.
This is the finale.
It's so awesome of them.
Just tie it on. Just tie it.
- Done!
- Yeah!
We get it done.
It's unbelievable.
All right, that's time!
I love you guys!
There's no way we could
have got both of those cowls out
- without their help.
- Whoo!
- This is gonna put us
in a really awesome spot
tomorrow.
- Thank you guys so much.
- Yeah.
It's day three
of our knight challenge,
and we have eight hours
in the lab.
- That's so awesome. High five.
- Yes.
So today, Rashaad's gonna keep
trucking along
on both the life
and death armor.
Do your thing, Rashaad.
And Sasha is going
to start sculpting these
accented filigrees
for the life knight.
I'm definitely behind schedule,
and I need to get
the death cowl finished
and molded as soon as possible.
I'll do the arms.
You do the chest.
I'm really putting Stella
and Nicole to work today.
I have Stella starting the arm
pieces for the death knight.
I have Nicole start
the chest piece.
We wanna incorporate some fish
bones into our design as well.
So I start sculpting
the fish spine
that we're gonna use
to go over the chest plate.
Looks really good
with your beard.
I know.
I think that the flesh
needs to be lighter
because I was envisioning, like,
dead, dry mummy skin almost.
Rayce is pre-painting
the death knight,
and I notice that a lot of grey
is getting worked
into his paint scheme.
That makes me really nervous.
I'm worried that
it's gonna get so dark
that there's no contrast
and nothing reads.
I don't think I'll
go much lighter than this.
All aspects of this makeup
going into this finale
have to be perfect.
If we don't get this paint job
completely dialed in,
it could sink me.
I think that the flesh
needs to be lighter
because I was envisioning, like,
mummy skin almost, you know?
It's day three
of our finale challenge,
and Rayce is pre-painting
the death knight,
and I notice that a lot of grey
is getting worked
into his paint scheme.
I'm worried that it's just
gonna get so dark
that there's no contrast
and nothing reads.
I just don't want it to get...
_
- It won't be.
- The magic word.
But Rayce is the champion
of season two,
and really awesome
with paint work.
So I know that he'll be able
to make something pretty sweet.
All right, I trust you.
- That's time, guys!
- I kind of love him.
He's absolutely beautiful.
Thank you so much.
We have about 15 pieces
to apply tomorrow.
It's absolutely insane.
So sleeping tonight
is gonna be very hard.
We get back to the house,
and I'm completely exhausted,
and so is everyone else.
Oh, man! What?
I see my mom and my boyfriend.
Oh, my God, this is so amazing!
Hey, come here, guys!
I see my girlfriend, Randy,
and my mom.
It's making me teary-eyed,
and I'm, like...
If I blink, I'm gonna cry.
Give me some love!
My parents are two
of the biggest-hearted,
most supportive people ever.
So do you guys get to stay
for the whole thing?
Oh, my God!
But the fact that they're here
to support me,
it's an amazing gift.
- I have...
- Couldn't be prouder.
- Grandpa's ring.
- Oh!
I wear it
for every spotlight challenge.
Winning Face Off
while my parents are there
to watch it happen would be
the highest point of my life.
Oh!
I've been trying
to work on my confidence
since I've... yeah.
_
I'm really proud of you.
We're just overwhelmed.
This is
the energy boost I need.
I wanna do, like,
the best makeup possible
so that my mom and Michael
can see me win this competition.
I just wanna make them
really proud.
This whole thing
has been so amazing
and crazy at the same time.
I know you're
gonna do 'em proud.
I knew you were gonna
make it to the end.
I did,
but no matter what happens,
I'm really proud of the things
I've done here,
and I can't wait
till you guys can see them.
- I know.
- You're a winner in my eyes.
Thanks, mom.
Seeing my loved ones,
I realize there's a lot
at stake here.
Like, this could change my life.
- There we go.
- Oh, boy.
- You guys ready?
- Yeah, I'm ready.
We're on location
for the finale
at this incredible
equestrian center.
There's an arena.
There's horses and stables.
This place is huge.
This is the culmination
of everything we've
been working for.
This is for the whole enchilada.
So bring it on.
All right, here we go.
- All right.
- Here we are, guys.
We have four hours
of makeup time,
and one hour of last looks,
all on location.
- Hello.
- Hey, how's it going?
- Good.
- Drew.
- Tony.
- I'm applying the face to you.
I'm gonna let Sasha
take point on the silicone face
and I'm gonna tackle the
application of the death knight,
and I'm gonna set Rashaad
on the armor.
- Hey, Cig.
- Yeah?
- Check him out.
- Love it.
It's time to start sticking.
I'm gonna be applying
the death knight.
George will be applying
the life knight.
And Rayce is going to finish up
the life knight's armor.
- Imagine those copper?
- Yeah.
Can you bang this out fast,
though?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Pull this on like a shirt.
Yeah,
that's looking really cool.
So I get the face applied
to the death knight,
then I jump on painting
the life knight.
I'm taking a risk doing
this minimalist makeup,
so I really wanna take my time
and make this really good.
You think...
_
- You can miss it?
- Yeah.
Our models will be participating
in a medieval battle.
So we have to be really careful
about how we're gonna stick
the antler pieces
into both makeups.
If one of these antlers
does snag on something and
tear a chunk out of the cowl,
it's pretty much done.
So instead of going, like,
straight up and giving
the antlers height,
we're going back at an angle.
It makes the antlers less
likely to get knocked off.
Oh! Stop lifting.
The arm pieces that we sculpted
don't curve
around the actor's arms.
So we're having a hard time
getting those edges down.
I used the Pros-Aide
all over his body.
It's just the arms
that it's doing this.
We tried every adhesive,
and nothing's really working.
So the parts that are lifting
we're covering with moss
and seaweed so you can't
see those seams.
And then reinforcing it
with some rope.
15 minutes, guys.
Hey, guys.
So you have one hour left.
- This is last looks.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, McKenzie.
I have a lot of little pieces
that I need to add
to the death knight.
Some really cool mandibles
and fish spines.
But they just don't look right.
So we're just gonna scrap those.
I'm getting the copper color
painted over the life knight's
armor pieces.
Wait, what the fuck
am I doing? Am I drunk?
But I just painted these pieces
the wrong frigging color.
They're supposed to match
the silvery plate.
Idiot.
I just don't have time for this.
To really sell the knight look,
I was envisioning lots of armor,
and now I'm realizing
there's so much space
that just doesn't have anything.
It looks incomplete.
I'm running out of time, so I
just start ripping up fabric
and tying it around him
as if it was wraps.
15 minutes, guys.
That's time, guys.
Yes!
- Do you love them?
- Yeah.
I can't believe
how much we got finished.
I'm still extremely nervous.
I've just worked my butt off
to get here and this is it.
I just wanna win so bad.
Coming up...
Welcome to the Face Off
season finale.
My stomach's in knots.
The winner of Face Off is...
Good evening, everyone,
and welcome to the Face Off
season finale.
We will be transporting you
to another time and place,
where knights are locked in
a bitter life and death battle.
You will witness
their epic clash,
and then we'll crown a brand-new
Face Off champion,
right here, tonight.
Now, who better to choose
our winner
than our talented
and accomplished judges?
First we have the owner of Optic
Nerve Makeup Effects Studio,
Mr. Glenn Hetrick.
Oscar-winning makeup artist,
the lovely Lois Burwell.
And creature and concept
designer, our very own
Neville Page.
Okay, let's take a look at our
finalists' amazing creations.
Our first pair of knights
is from Cig.
I'm really proud of my team.
The death knight looks great.
The life knight is so well done
that it just looks
like his face.
Did I even do a makeup
on that guy?
I feel like I might
have a shot at this.
Yeah!
They look so cool,
and my death knight
looks like a badass.
I'm just so happy
for me and my team.
I couldn't be prouder
of these two makeups.
I can't believe the amount
of insane work
my team and I have managed
to pull off.
All right, guys, it's time to
put our knights to the test
in battle.
Let the games begin!
Oh, my God!
- Yeah!
Oh!
_
That was amazing!
You guys like the battle?
Thank you, everyone,
so much for being here
with us this evening.
But the time has come
for our judges to take
a closer look at the makeups
and deliberate in private.
Thank you again so much.
Have a good evening, everybody.
Here we go.
That battle was so cool
and now it's time for things
to get serious.
My stomach's in knots.
I'm nervous.
But at this point,
I've given everything I got.
So, hopefully, it's good enough.
Who made your favorite
life and death knights?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
This is the culmination
of everything we've been
working for,
and this is such, like,
a crazy, emotional moment,
but whatever happens, happens.
I'm trying to figure out where
he ends and the makeup begins.
- That's a good thing.
- Yes.
- Yeah, it is.
- The silicone certainly
- is well done.
- Really amazing.
- I love the armor.
- The armor's fantastic.
And this area here
is really very nice.
The surface of this,
this scale, is spot on.
It's rather lovely, and I
love this collar going around.
Look at the sheer amount
of detail all over this thing.
- It's bloody fantastic.
- It's screen ready.
I love the way the arms are.
It's just wonderful.
This is really nice,
natural looking makeup.
I love these subtle
color transitions.
This nose and cheekbones
are all that it took
to convey that it's stag-like.
There's some really beautiful
character design,
this kind of slash
through the lip.
- It's very well done.
- I absolutely love
the arrangement of the horns
on the top of the crown.
Thank you.
So judges, what do you think
of tonight's makeups?
It's a phenomenal amount
of work to have accomplished,
and even more impressive
was how each and every makeup
withstood the test of battle.
Well done.
Thank you.
All right, guys,
the judges would like
to hear from each of you.
So, Cig, explain
your concept to the judges.
So my life knight
is a part of these crusaders
bound by honor to protect
the realm from themselves.
And they come across this tribe
that ends up cursing the knights
so that when they die, they come
back as these gargoyles.
The more of them that die,
the stronger
the darkness force grows.
Regarding
your good life knight,
the silicone piece
is absolutely gorgeous.
The edges are
almost nonexistent.
I really appreciate that you
went with a character makeup,
hyperreal silicone
on your life guy,
and then went crazy monster,
very orc-ish
on your death knight.
Great conceptual work there.
- Thank you.
- I particularly liked
your dark knight's sculpt.
Some lovely forms,
and great paint work.
Well done.
- Thank you.
- Great characters.
They really complement
one another.
The head sculpt
of the dark knight,
you really retained
the proportion so well
- that it remains really heroic.
- Thanks.
So it's a beautiful piece.
As a team, you've really
done quite well.
Thank you.
Okay, Dina, you're next.
There is this octopus king,
and him and his army have been
sinking ships for years.
The octopus sends
his squid minions
to crawl into the corpses
from these ships
to control their bodies.
That's where this guy
comes from.
And my good knight
was actually a victim
of one of these ship attacks,
and a mermaid gave him armor
from sea life
to help him defeat
these crustaceans.
The overall vision
is exemplary.
Thank you.
I absolutely adore
your dark knight.
The color is marvelous
and the chin is excellent.
I'm very impressed by it.
With your good knight,
I like the way the shapes
and the colors merge
and yet stand out.
- Very well done.
- Thank you.
Your concept is so good
and so courageous
that I really want
to applaud you.
- How was the starfish done?
- Stella sculpted it
and then I piped
all the little dots on there.
It's a crazy amount
of work to try
for one element of your makeup.
The detail on both
of these makeups is astounding.
That's the kind of thing
we're looking for in a finale.
Thank you so much.
- Drew.
- These are the leaders
of two warring sects
of elfin cedar people.
The guardians of life
protect the forest
from evil necromancers
who have embraced the power
of death.
So it's a constant battle
between life and death
trying to overtake one another.
These two work so well together.
They feel like they're
in the same world,
yet they are divided enough
in their aesthetic
to feel independent.
And the nuanced stag features,
- done so well.
- Thank you.
They very much feel
like they belong in a fantasy,
medieval world,
and that death knight,
you guys killed it.
That character's gorgeous.
Not just the sculpture,
but the paint job.
So well done.
Well, I think that
you've done exceptional work.
And they complement each other
superbly well.
- Thank you.
- All right, guys.
Could you please head backstage
while they deliberate
and decide who'll become
this season's champion.
All right, judges. So we've
seen some great makeups tonight.
And you definitely have a tough
decision ahead of you.
- Why don't we start with Cig?
- When you were watching
all of them fighting,
his death knight character
- really stuck out.
- There was some really
beautiful sculpture work
in the death knight's face.
The paint work,
the multi layers of metallics,
was so beautiful.
I'm just not sure
about the good knight.
I think it had
some quality work,
but I don't feel that
he really pushed the character.
We were clearly looking
for something more than just
a silicone sculpture face.
Well, I think that Cig's done
some remarkable work
throughout the series.
There was
the big fish character.
There was the dark water
creepy clown.
That work was lovely.
His makeups have been
some of my favorites.
Let's move on to Dina.
It's quantity and quality.
It is a massive amount of work,
and every piece
is beautifully detailed.
Her death knight is gorgeous.
It looks like a finished,
ready for film makeup.
It didn't feel as if there
were three people
- working on an idea.
- Absolutely.
It was...
What's the Japanese phrase?
Itai doshin--
many in body, one in mind.
- It was that.
- But there's a disparity
in the different
design elements
- of the life knight.
- Yeah.
She has created some of
my favorite makeups on Face Off.
From the praying mantis
to the Greek goddess,
it's hit after hit.
These are the types of designs
that get you jobs.
All right,
let's move on to Drew.
These two fulfill the fantasy
knight element the best.
What a wonderful way to realize
that fawn-cedar-pan-like makeup.
They really were
the ying and the yang.
They belonged together
and they were opposite.
Both designs were simple
and elegant.
For example,
on the death knight,
the sculptural work
in the cheeks,
that was so well done,
when you scrutinize it up close.
Beautiful. And actually,
I think the shape of the helm
was amazing.
But the hair on the face
takes it down a notch.
I completely agree, actually.
He's done some amazing things
all season long.
Incredibly realistic makeups.
This is one of the toughest
neck-and-necks
that I've ever seen
on the show.
- This is really hard.
- It is.
Judges, have you decided who
will become our next champion?
We have, but it was not easy.
All right then,
let's bring them back out
and crown our winner.
All right, you guys, one of you
is about to become
the winner of Face Off.
Glenn, tell us about
tonight's makeups.
Cig, we truly appreciate
the bold conceptual choices
that you made and the armor,
as well as the face,
of your death knight
were both fantastic sculptures.
Dina, the swing for the fences
volume of work
was only outshined
by your incredible detail
and your paint job,
particularly on the crab cowl.
Drew, your knights really
screamed fantasy to us
and we loved how harmonious
they were with one another,
both in terms of style
and palette.
All right, Glenn,
who is the winner
of Face Off?
The winner of Face Off is...
All right, Glenn,
who is the winner
of Face Off?
The winner of Face Off is...
Dina.
This is such
an amazing feeling.
- I can't even describe it.
- You did it!
I took a huge risk coming here.
I quit my job.
I came with very little
experience.
And I made it to the finale
and I won.
It's mind-blowing.
I can't believe it.
Here are the keys
to your new car.
Oh, my God...
Oh, my God!
I can't be upset.
An amazing artist
won Face Off season seven.
Just because it's not me
doesn't mean that
the right person didn't win.
I'm proud of everything
that I've done here.
I had a blast doing it and
that's the biggest win for me.
You haven't seen the last
of Cig Neutron.
Everybody, come on over
and congratulate her.
Family, come over.
Winning Face Off is completely
gonna change my life.
I get to do what I love now.
That's the grand prize.
I'll bake cakes once in a while,
but yeah, I'm pretty sure
that's out of my life for now.
Thank you all at home
for watching us tonight.
Join us in January
as the next season of Face Off
kicks off with a big twist.
Good night.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net