You really knocked
this one out of the park.
Somehow, it's just
all gone a bit mimsy.
Previously on Face Off...
Dina's serpentine sniper
- blew the judges away...
- Thank you.
And Keaghlan was sent home.
Now eight artists remain.
Tonight they will face
their darkest fears.
This is going
to give me nightmares.
I'm about to peel it off.
And for some, the challenge
won't be a laughing matter.
I'm really not happy with it.
It doesn't feel
like a solid vision.
In the end, only one
will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Wake up, kiddies.
Wake up.
What is that?
We're hearing laughter
and some disembodied voice.
I don't even know
what time it is.
Everyone's waking up,
like, "What the hell is that?"
Come on, kiddies,
get dressed and make
your way to the lab.
Don't worry.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Oh, my God.
What just happened?
We're all incredibly
freaked out.
We have no idea
what's happening.
I don't want to even leave
my room,
let alone go to the lab.
I can't even see the door.
Where am I going?
What is that?
Oh, no, no.
Oh.
We're half asleep,
and we're walking around
in a pitch-black lab.
I don't know what's coming.
I'm feeling around,
in case I hit something
or someone tries to attack.
Hello?
Ooh, what's that?
Oh.
I don't like this.
For your next spotlight
challenge,
you'll experience one
of the most powerful
human emotions.
It's what you're feeling
right now...
Fear.
This is going
to give me nightmares.
I didn't know McKenzie
could be so terrifying.
While some fears evolve
as you grow into adults,
childhood fears,
like being afraid of the dark,
can last a lifetime.
This week, you're going
to venture into the world
of a character
that is mostly regarded as good,
but has also instilled fear
in thousands of children
and adults in films
like Poltergeist, Saw,
and Stephen King's It...
Clowns.
So your spotlight challenge
is to create
your very own
evil-clown character.
This challenge
is gonna be a lot of fun.
I'm really excited,
because back home,
I'm known
for doing scary clowns.
And, of course, you know
it won't be that simple.
Before this challenge,
you were all given a survey
with various questions,
but one of them was about your
own darkest, childhood fear.
Creepy.
George, you wrote "Worms."
Dina, "Tornadoes."
Cig, "Dark water."
Damien, "Spiders."
Sasha, "Old dolls."
Drew, "Spiders."
For Stella, it was
"Monsters under the bed."
And, Rachael,
you said "Cockroaches."
Yeah, I did.
You will each use
your own childhood fear
to inspire
your evil-clown character.
Of course,
there's just one more thing.
Your makeups will be applied
on real clowns...
...who will put your makeups
to the test on the reveal stage,
featuring a flurry of juggling,
slapstick routines,
- and unicycling.
- Sweet.
I want your designs
to really capture your fears.
So I'm going to leave you here
in the dark to work on them.
Good luck.
Oh, my God.
So let's go find
our sketchbooks.
Over here?
It's pitch-black
in the room again,
and we all feel around
for our tablets
and start sketching.
Sitting in the dark
is really helping me channel
my childhood fear,
which is monsters under the bed
that would reach up
and grab me.
So my evil clown is dressed
in these oversized pants
made out of bedsheets,
and he's gonna have
all these hands coming out.
Spiders have always
creeped me out.
I hate them.
I start designing a clown face
that has spider eyes
across the forehead,
and the cranium comes back
into this big arachnid butt
that's basically an amalgamation
of everything about spiders
that used to terrify me
as a kid.
So it's gonna look
like a spider,
but it's gonna have the color
palette of a twisted clown.
I think he feels like something
straight out
of my own nightmares,
and it's kind of cool.
So right now I'm kind of
going with the idea that, like,
my clown ate a bunch
of spider eggs,
and now he's got all these
tiny spiders crawling out
all over his face.
My childhood fear was that,
you know, a spider
could crawl into your mouth
while you're sleeping
and lay its eggs inside of you.
And then you have all these
baby spiders hatching
inside of your body.
So right away I really wanted
to just get the gross-out,
like, ugh factor, 'cause I hate
little itty-bitty spiders.
So my childhood fear
was tornadoes.
I don't know why.
I think maybe I watched too much
Wizard Of Oz.
So I'm doing, like,
a twisted face.
I'm, like, bringing it up
into the hair,
making the hair actually
look like a tornado.
We'll see if I can pull it off.
It's gonna be a tough one.
The lights come back on.
We have six hours in lab today.
We pick our model, and
it's time to start sculpting.
When I was a kid,
my dad and I took a clown class.
I wasn't really the coolest kid,
but I'm hoping that'll give me
some kind of edge
in this challenge.
I am really afraid of worms.
I feel like they're gonna burrow
up into my shoes and get me.
So my character
is gonna be a big,
segmented worm head
with a floppy stocking cap,
and I would love to just cover
this whole makeup
in some super slime.
But if he's gonna be dancing
around or juggling,
it can't be slippery at all.
So I have to keep
everything minimal.
Hey, Sasha.
Tell me why you're afraid
of old dolls.
When I was little,
I was scared of old dolls,
but now
I love old creepy dolls.
My grandmother has so many
of them in her house,
and I've always had a hard time
sleeping at her house
because of these dolls.
I decided I'm gonna take
a different approach.
I'm not making a clown.
I'm gonna make a cracked doll
that has clown makeup.
I know I'm taking a risk
by not making a clown
and going with the doll
concept, but I like it,
and I'm gonna make sure
it looks good.
- Did you get a haircut, George?
- No.
You look kind
of different today.
I trimmed my beard a little.
- Is that what it is?
- I think it is, yeah.
There's something different
about you.
I knew it.
My childhood fear
is cockroaches.
My concept is a cockroach hybrid
who is pretending to be a clown.
I'm sculpting the face to look
like the segments
of a cockroach's body,
but I also want to bring
a little bit
of a clown aspect to it,
so I'm actually sculpting
clown-like lips
and a clown-like brow.
Cig, you have
hydroskourophobia.
"One that is afraid
of dark, murky water."
I used to have these
reoccurring nightmares
where I would fall
into this giant pool
of, like, black, tarry water,
and these, like, skeletal,
creepy creatures
would try to drag me under
and eat me.
So I'm actually going to sculpt
one of these creepy creatures
that I used to see
and turn it into a clown.
As I'm sculpting, I'm realizing
that a lot
of my stylistic choices
come from these nightmares
that I used to have as a kid,
and I didn't realize
it until this challenge.
It's like I learned
something about myself.
Imagine that.
So this long nose, Cig,
is gonna be a spider's leg,
but there's gonna be, like,
little hairs and stuff
sticking out of it.
It's gonna be gross.
For my spidery clown face,
I work out this weird structure
for the nose,
and then I figure out
a really cool arrangement
for the spider's eyes
coming off the browridge.
And I really like the shapes
and forms of the face,
and I think that he's gonna
look really cool.
I'm looking at my sculpture.
I got it almost ready to mold,
and I realize
that this character
is just a bunch of blobs
of clay.
It literally looks like poop.
For the first time,
I'm seeing a makeup
that could send me home.
There's eight
really talented artists left,
so there's no room for error.
I don't know if there's enough
time to rip it all apart
and start all over,
but I really don't have
a choice.
Coming up...
- I think it's a stretch.
- Yeah.
It's hard to do a good makeup
when your heart's
just not in it.
- It's horrific.
- I love it.
It just left me a bit confused.
So it's day one
of the evil-clown challenge,
and I'm really, really unhappy
with how the sculpture's
coming out.
It looks just like my sketch,
but this is bad enough
to send me home.
My best option is just to tear
all that clay off
and start fresh.
So you took the whole face off.
It just wasn't looking right.
The thing was, like,
two inches thick in some spots.
That's a mask.
That's not a makeup.
Even though I'll be behind,
it's the best option.
But now I need to figure out
a much better concept
very quickly.
Isn't the rule for the monster
if you have your
feet under your covers,
you're fine?
My mother tucked me in like
a mummy every night
so the hands couldn't get me.
The clown is gonna be made up
of things that you would
find under the bed,
like lost toys.
So I'm going to take this
bouncy ball that I found
and use it as the clown's chin.
I come up with this concept
of a serial-killer clown
whose essence possessed
all these worms,
and now, they have reformed
into a killer worm clown man.
I wasted a few hours,
so I'm gonna have to bust my ass
to finish this.
Hello, guys.
- Hey.
- Here to check in.
Mine was dark water.
It's gonna be really wet,
and I'm gonna use
the Kryolan aqua colors
and actually
paint the clown makeup
and then use a spritzer bottle
and then melt it off.
I'd suggest doing
some tests on it first...
- Yeah.
- Because if it doesn't work,
- it's gonna be hard to go back.
- Mm-hmm.
She's gonna have these cracks
all over her,
and I want it painted
like a porcelain doll.
You might age it a little
teeny bit of brown, yeah,
because if you paint it
pure white,
it's gonna look
like it's brand-new.
Okay.
Tornadoes were my fear.
His hair was gonna actually
be the tornado,
and it's kind of pulling
his skin up into it.
It's a different thought.
It's not one
that I would think of.
- I think it's a stretch.
- Yeah.
Mr. Westmore's not completely
comfortable with my concept.
It's not helping
with my confidence.
Make sure it tells the story
right away of what you're doing.
I'm focusing on all
of the things
about spiders that scare me.
So he has six eyes
instead of two now.
This is actually going
to transform
into a spider's leg.
There's so much spider
you have coming out.
Be careful with the paint job--
that it isn't too bright.
All right, everybody.
We're heading out.
- Bye-bye.
- See you.
Bye.
I don't have very many
references for cracks
for my doll's head,
so I am just taking pictures
of the cracks in the pavement.
I want to make every little
detail perfect
because I want to prove
to the judges
that they saved me
for a reason.
You son of a bitch.
- What?
- Are you molding already?
Yeah.
I got a lot of spiders to make.
It feels really good being
the first one in the mold room,
but it also makes me
second-guess myself.
Did I go too simplistic?
Everybody else is spending
a lot more time
on their sculptures,
but I'm just gonna focus
on putting on
a really clean makeup.
Hopefully, that's gonna do
the trick.
Ten minutes, guys.
I know it's boring.
I'm still a little worried
about my concept.
It's hard to do a good makeup
when your heart's
just not in it.
That's time, guys.
I'm feeling a lot of pressure
to tweak my concept.
I have no idea
what I'm gonna do,
but hopefully I can figure it
out before tomorrow.
So it's day two
of the evil-clown challenge,
and I have a ton of work to do.
Originally, I designed
this giant spider butt
for the back of the head,
but I realized that our makeups
have to withstand a professional
acrobatic performance,
and that giant spider butt's
probably gonna be in the way.
So I shrink it down
quite a bit.
Hopefully, it works.
I have a big chest cavity
I need to sculpt,
two big arm cavities,
and lots of little baby cavities
to really complete the idea
that these spiders
are just eating him from within
and not just coming out
of his face.
Last night I was thinking
that I need have
a little more fun
with this design.
So my new concept is the clown
got stuck outside
at a birthday party
during a tornado
and impaled
with birthday-party debris.
I definitely feel a lot better
about my concept now.
It tells a story,
so I'm excited.
George thinks that it
would be really comfy
to wear shorty-ass shorts,
shorter than any man
should ever wear.
You're distracting me.
I didn't have a whole lot
of fun in the lab yesterday,
and I wanted to get
some fun going,
and I wanted everyone
to look at my legs.
I could feel the eyes
on me all day.
I mean, it's hard not to look
at perfection.
George, you want to grease
up your arms?
Sure.
Stella's been staring
at my awesome thighs all day,
so she wants to see
if I got awesome arms as well,
which I do.
My evil clown needs to have
arms coming out of his body,
so I have George put his hands
in alginate arm molds.
It's not as nice as my thighs,
but I do have good arms.
Algin is basically
made out of seaweed.
It's what they put in your mouth
when you go to the dentist
and get your mouth molded.
Awesome.
Once it's set up, I can pour
poly foam into the mold
so that I can make as many arms
as I need to.
Do a quick test.
I need a hell of a lot
of spiders
'cause there are gonna be
a bunch of them
crawling out all over his face.
My first idea is to dab
a bead of hot glue
and pick each little leg out
with a little string.
Not working.
So I tried sticking little bits
of wire in it.
Use this.
Then I would try to thread
some wire into some beads,
but the legs aren't staying
where I want them to stay.
Ay-yi-yi-yi-yi.
I'm getting really frustrated
that I can't figure out a way
to make these damn spiders.
My character is a spider clown.
If I send him out there
without any spiders,
I know that
I'm gonna be going home.
I tried, like,
30 different things.
I'm about to fucking give up.
So it's day two
of our evil-clown challenge,
and I want to put these nasty,
rotted baby spiders
crawling all over him,
but I'm getting
really frustrated
that I can't figure out a way
to make these damn spiders.
I tried, like,
30 different things.
I'm about to give up.
If I send him out there
without any spiders on,
I know that I'm gonna be
going home.
I hope this works.
I finally start taking
four pieces of wire
and then taking a little string
of duct tape
and wrapping it
around the center
and then just bending
and posing the leg.
I spray 'em black.
Clear coat 'em so they're nice
and shiny and gross-looking.
They look really good.
I remember being creeped out
by the heads of the dolls.
Their hair-- it almost
looked like bad hair plugs.
So I start punching hair
through a cowl
and make this really creepy wig
that just looks like
the doll's head.
Are you gonna see an edge
of this in the front?
No, because the face covers it.
I'm totally happy with it.
- That's cool.
- Thanks.
Since I'm only
doing a face and a cowl,
for my evil clown, the paint job
has got to be really good.
So it's really important
that I test this out.
I get a premade appliance,
and then I paint
the aqua colors over the top.
And I hold it up, and I spritz
it with a water bottle.
That works.
It looks all drippy and gross.
It runs through the cracks.
So I'm actually really excited
about application day.
I want to make giant worm arms
by tying thread
around a soft foam and covering
it with silicone.
If I cover it in silicone,
I'll get the sheen
and the glossiness of a worm
without having to make
my performer all slimy.
It can't be slippery at all.
It could ruin
the whole performance.
Oh, my gosh.
That's disgusting.
Hey, guys, one hour left.
I start fabricating antennae
for my creepy cockroach.
I'm using foam tube
and armature wire
so I can bend them back
and make sure
that they won't interfere
with the performance.
It's looking really cool.
I'm really excited
to put this on my model.
That's time, guys!
It's the end of day two,
and I am happy
with everything I've done.
I think it incorporates
my childhood fear
and the clown element,
but I was in the bottom
for the last three weeks,
and I'm really hoping
that it comes together nicely
on application day.
It's application day,
and we have four hours in lab
and one hour in last looks,
and my foam looks great.
- That's some good foam.
All my edges are paper thin.
- It's great.
- Some good seaming.
Yeah.
Those pants are ridiculous.
Oh, I hope she can dance
in that.
Clowns.
Hi.
I'm Rachael.
Nice to meet you.
- I'm Damien.
- Demetrius.
Demetrius, nice to meet you.
- No problems?
- No, I don't think so.
Okay.
I want to try these worm arms
on you.
These guys--
they're not our regular models.
They're used
to just being silly.
And I notice as soon
as they get into the lab,
the whole atmosphere
is just lifted
'cause these guys
are so much fun.
So perfect.
You think you'll be able
to juggle in those
- with some white gloves on?
- No problem.
Okay.
Cool.
I get the cowl on, and I notice
that there's a little bit of
space in the back of the head,
and it kind of wobbles
a little bit.
Does it feel okay?
Everything comfortable?
_
_ _
If she's doing flips
and jumping around and dancing,
the wobble could potentially
tear the whole makeup off.
So I stuff the back so it fits
a little bit more snugly
and it's not wobbling
around so much,
and hopefully it'll work
in my favor.
Can you move your head
and everything?
- Yeah.
- Cool.
The pieces are fitting
together really nicely
except the neck isn't hitting
his actual anatomy
all that well.
So I get it to stretch across
in a decent-enough way
so that it looks pretty good.
Try not to move
your neck too much.
I want to create muscle
and the skin flap
and, like, the inside
of his skull.
So I use Kryolan Artex,
which is a two-part,
like, on-skin silicone.
And I sculpt some lines into it
and try to make it look
like muscle.
It's actually looking
pretty cool.
Shit.
It's just not wanting to stay.
I'm having a lot trouble
with his chin area.
His edges around his mouth are
starting to break down again,
and I just don't know what it is
that's causing these problems.
Here, I'll show you where
it's coming off at.
I still have to do all
this paint work and glue on,
like, 150 spiders, so I'm really
starting to freak out.
It's that mouth for some reason.
I don't know why.
Hey, guys.
Ten minutes left.
That's time, guys.
Once I kind of see it together,
I notice that his arms
and his face
aren't the same color,
and that's not good.
So now I have one hour
to fix this.
I have to even up my paint job,
and I still have to paint him
to look like a clown.
This could get me in trouble.
Coming up...
I still got a lot shit to do.
I'm worried my clown
is not "clown" enough.
Take it away, guys.
There's no words
to describe it.
All right. Awesome.
Let's just do the bench.
We have one hour at last looks,
and my clown's mouth
is falling off his face.
I grab some telesis
and slather it on
and hope
that it's gonna stay down.
I got a lot shit to do.
It feels okay?
All the painting's done,
and now I start spritzing it
with water
to make it look runny.
I'm only gonna have
one chance at this.
If it doesn't look right,
I don't think
I'm gonna have time to fix it.
I'm painting as fast
as I can because his face
is really red,
and his arms are really purple.
So I need to even out
the color of skin.
I am really nervous
my clown is not "clown" enough.
I hope that I can pull it off
with my paint job
because everyone else's
looks pretty clown-y.
15 minutes, guys!
I'm running out of time,
so I need to finish the makeup
around the eyes and the mouth,
and I'm also worried that
that big hair is gonna fall.
- Who's got hairspray?
- Damien.
Throw it over.
I got right here.
All right, that's time!
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Time's up, and I didn't get
the chance
to add spider-leg details
to the nose,
but I'm hoping
that it still works.
Whew.
Welcome to
the Face Off reveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
First, let's say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve
Make-Up Effects Studio,
Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening, guys.
- Hey, Glenn.
Oscar-winning makeup artist
Lois Burwell.
Hello, all.
- Hi, Lois.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
- Hi, guys.
- Hello.
This week
your spotlight challenge
was to use
your own childhood fear
as inspiration
for an evil-clown character.
My evil twin also told you
that your characters
would be tested in a performance
here on the reveal stage.
First, let's take a look
at your evil clowns.
Even from far away,
my clown's terrifying.
It looks like it just stepped
right out of my nightmare.
My clown probably
looks better up close
than he does from far away.
So, hopefully,
the judges will notice
how much I actually did.
Everyone's laughing at her.
She's hilarious and creepy
and terrifying
at the same time.
I'm not happy with it at all.
If I go home
on a clown challenge,
it's gonna feel
really embarrassing.
This makeup is terrifying.
He's very spider-y.
He's very creepy.
I really enjoy watching him.
I took a risk by going
with the doll concept.
I love my makeup,
but I just don't know
if the judges are gonna like it.
I feel pretty good
about this makeup.
I think it's definitely gross,
and that's what I was going for.
I'm not sure if the judges
will get it,
but it creeps me out.
So I like it,
and it's disgusting.
All right, it's time to see
your evil clowns in action.
Take it away, guys.
There's no words
to describe it.
Everyone's makeup
held up really well.
I didn't see any foam latex
flop on the stage
or any of that stuff.
So I think it was a success
across the board.
All right, judges,
it's time to take a closer look
at our clowns.
- Oh.
- These shapes are amazing.
It looks so wet and drippy.
It really is good.
Oh, look at this.
Beautifully executed.
The way that this is painted
to look like worn makeup...
- Yes.
- Really well done.
I really like how
the eyelashes are sculpted in.
- It's clever.
- This is weird.
Is it a dog toy?
It just doesn't make sense.
Oh, golly.
This is such a known approach
to the makeup.
It feels like the joker.
At least bring out
the sternum here a bit.
Thank you.
These eye shapes
should have proceeded up
- along the side of the head.
- Yes.
I think the judges are talking
about how tightly clustered
the eyes are,
and I'm starting to think
I might have made a mistake.
So I'm freaked out.
Who made your favorite
evil-clown character?
Tell us on Twitter,
using #FaceOff.
It's neither spider nor human.
The judges go up to my makeup,
and I see them gesturing
to the sides of the head,
and I'm starting to think
I might be in trouble.
You've got what looks
like a finger nose, maybe, or--
- I don't know what that is.
- I don't know either.
Thank you.
I like the way it looks
like some of the painting's
coming off and cracking.
This specific hair punching
that you'd see on a doll.
Oh, that's fantastic.
Around the eyes, there's not
a whole lot that's been done.
I kind of wish
he would have kept
the sausage-casing coloring
to the face
'cause this is wretched
in the best way possible.
It's a cute idea.
I'm just not sure we got
to a place where the roach
and the clown came together.
It's almost
a cartoon version of both.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Okay.
The judges have scored
your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Stella...
George...
Rachael...
Congratulations,
because you guys are all safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you, guys.
- Thank you.
Good luck, guys.
Now, the rest of you
were the best and the worst.
The judges would like to speak
with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Dina, please step up.
Tell us about your fear
and how you integrated that
into your clown character.
My fear as a child
was tornadoes.
My clown was at
a birthday party, performing.
A storm hit, and he got impaled
by a bunch of party debris.
How do you feel
about your creation?
I think it's a fun concept.
I think you should be
extremely pleased.
It was exceptionally difficult,
but you struck
the perfect balance for me
between the fantastic
and realism.
I like the blood.
I love the piece of skin
coming up,
and I absolutely adored
the balloon animal.
It's really very good.
I have to kind of disagree
with the two other judges.
They like it.
I love it.
I think it's really
well sculpted,
really well painted.
I'm starting to really see
a whole new tier
to your skill set.
Thank you so much.
Dina, please step back.
Thanks.
- Good job.
- Thanks.
Drew, please step forward.
Tell us about your childhood
fear and your makeup.
My childhood fears
were spiders.
The things that scare me
the most about spiders
were their furry, hairy bodies,
their spindly limbs,
and their webbing.
So I tried to incorporate
all of those ideas
into this makeup.
This, for me, doesn't work.
If you'd taken the eyes
and placed them on the sides
of the forehead,
then the eye makeup
and the spider's eyes
would actually have complemented
each other.
What were you going for
with the nose?
Is it supposed to be,
like, a little finger or--
- it was actually the segmented
end of a spider's foot.
Unfortunately,
I wasn't able to complete it.
When you have a complex idea
like that
and you don't get
to complete it,
it affects the overall feel
of the makeup.
It just left me a bit confused.
Okay.
Thank you.
Drew, please step back.
- I thought it was amazing.
- Thank you.
Cig, please step forward.
Tell us about your fear
and the resulting design.
My fear was dark water,
and as a kid,
I would have these nightmares
that I would fall
into this dark, tarry water,
and these sinewy,
skeletal creatures
would try to drag me under
and eat me.
So I created
one of those creatures
and turned it into a clown.
It's so good
in so many different ways.
It's absolutely horrific.
The asymmetry of the paint job
on the front
applied
to this grotesque skull--
this is awesome.
There's something
very childlike
about the color palette
that you've used.
It's scary, but you've got
humor there as well.
Thank you so much.
The paint techniques
that you used
on the back of that head
is phenomenal.
That's what I would want it
to look like
coming out of my shop.
- You should be very happy.
- Thank you.
Cig, you can step back.
All right,
let's talk to Damien.
Tell me about your fear
and how you integrated it
into your character.
My fear as a child was spiders.
So this is Webbles The Clown,
and he's a sideshow performer
who would pop a spider
in his mouth
and pop it out as a gag.
And while he had it
inside of his mouth,
it actually laid its eggs,
and he swallowed them.
So now
they're eating him alive.
As much as I love your idea,
there's so many other ways
to have done that, man.
As it stands, there's not
a whole lot to the fake depth.
It kind of feels glued on top,
and this has so many
expected lines and shapes.
It's just not
your strongest work.
I agree 1,000%.
It looks very sort
of Halloween-y costume
this week.
Here's what I love
about it, though--
the definition happening
with the painted part
of the makeup.
I think that we needed
to see more of.
It's just too much of the
classic evil-joker look to it.
I agree.
Damien, thank you very much.
Please step back.
Sasha, you're up.
Sasha, tell us
about your makeup, please.
My fear was
old porcelain dolls.
I took a different approach
with not making a clown.
I made a doll, and I painted
the clown face on.
I absolutely adore it.
Thank you.
I like the cracks.
I love the highlights
on the lips and on the nose,
but best of all,
the dolly plugs in the hair--
- absolutely brilliant.
- Thank you.
It's beautiful.
It's the overall silhouette
that gives you a strong,
memorable character.
Thank you so much.
The way
that you applied the paint
to the doll-shaped face
fulfills the clown aspect
without going over the top
and still makes it feel
like a creepy antique doll.
Thank you so much.
Sasha, please step down.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
All right, guys,
the judges have heard
what you have to say.
Please head back to the makeup
room while they deliberate.
Thank you.
All right, judges,
let's start with some
of the looks you liked the most.
How about Dina's work?
I really love
everything about it.
I like the wounds, and I like
the contrast between one side
of the face and the other.
I also think
that the paint application
was handled extraordinarily well
because it felt like a real
horror prosthetic makeup.
Yeah.
All right,
let's move on to Cig.
Ugh.
A dark water clown?
That's extraordinarily difficult
to concept out,
and it's all there.
The exposed skin so clearly
reads as a waterlogged corpse.
That melted makeup
was beautifully handled.
It's really gorgeous
from the profile as well.
All right, how about Sasha?
The technical work
not only in the sculpt
but in the painting-- I mean,
that's beautifully painted.
She did such a good job
with a makeup
that I've seen done
many, many times.
That's phenomenal.
She felt she was taking
a risk by putting clown makeup
on the doll.
That's exactly the decision
making that wins challenges.
All right, judges,
let's move on to the looks
you liked the least.
Let's start with Drew.
This one failed miserably,
in my opinion.
The eyes should go up
the side of the head,
and the nose is one of the worst
noses on a makeup ever.
Unless we knew it was a spider,
there's nothing there
that would give you
that information.
We got too many things
happening,
and therefore, we can't figure
out what it's supposed to be.
All right, let's move on
to Damien.
It is the lowest-hanging fruit
imaginable in the clown
department of makeup.
It's the elongated chin.
It's just so uninspired.
It was as if he had thrown
it all together,
and at this point
in the competition...
- That's right.
- ...that's no place to be.
All right, then, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- Yes.
- Let's bring them back out.
All right, Glenn.
Tell us about the top looks.
Dina, we loved the way
that you juxtaposed
fantasy over realism.
Cig, your clown
and that paint job of yours
was absolutely phenomenal, man.
Awesome.
Sasha, your decision
to explore a different path
was clearly worth the risk.
All right, Glenn, who is
the winner of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
All right, Glenn, who is
the winner of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
Sasha.
You took a big creative risk
tonight,
and you delivered
an outstanding makeup.
Thank you for reminding us
why we saved you.
- Well done.
- Thank you so much.
I won the challenge.
This is one of the best days
of my life.
I have so much more confidence
in my skills,
and I feel like I belong here.
Sasha, congratulations.
You, Dina, and Cig can head
back to the makeup room.
Unfortunately, that means
the two of you
are on the bottom this week.
One of you will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Drew, some of the paint work
was actually quite good,
but the design, particularly
in the center of the face,
was just far too busy.
Damien, you did
some cool painting,
but there was nothing
that really surprised
or intrigued us
about your makeup.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Damien.
It was just too expected
of an approach
for a challenge that begged
for out-of-the-box thinking.
Damien, I am so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
It means, Drew,
you are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Damien, I hope you find
that this experience
has been encouraging,
because the three of us
have really enjoyed your work.
Thank you.
Damien, it's been so great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thanks, guys.
- Good luck to you.
- Good luck.
Take care.
I really expected to do
a lot better this challenge,
but I made it this far,
so I can't really
be upset about that.
- Clowns sent me home.
- No...
Competing along side these
other artists has meant the world to me.
This has been
a complete blessing.
I feel even more capable than
I did when I first came here.
So, I'm really excited
to go home and
make my dream of
doing this every day come true.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net