I love it.
I've never seen
anything like this.
Previously on Face Off...
Stella's incredible alien
brought her to victory.
- Thank you.
- And Gwen was sent home.
Now, 12 artists remain,
and tonight,
they'll face
an extraordinary twist.
There is one more thing
you need to know.
Oh, my God!
But not everybody will thrive.
I started noticing some cracks.
This is the end
of the line for me.
It's a triumphant victory
if it was
for an office Halloween party.
In the end, only one will
win a VIP trip
from
Kryolan Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
So what's it like to win?
- It's pretty awesome.
- Yeah?
Mm-hmm.
I'm not gonna lie.
I was just glad to not be
in that bottom circle again.
- Yeah, it sucks.
- Finally.
I've been on
the bottom a couple times.
The last makeup was
safe, which is good,
but I definitely want
to show everyone
that I can do better than this.
- Oh.
Ooh!
We're walking into the lab,
and all the models were
standing up on these pillars
in really elaborate costumes
and capes,
and we're
all really, really excited.
Well,
as you've probably guessed,
today's foundation challenge
is all about superheroes.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Before I give you the details,
I want to introduce you
to one of the biggest names
working in makeup
and special effects today.
He's helped create
some of Hollywood's biggest
superhero movies,
like Fantastic Four,
X-Men The Last Stand,
and the movie that nabbed him
an Academy Award nomination,
Hellboy II.
Yes.
Please give a warm welcome
to Mike Elizalde.
I'm freaking out.
Like, I am
a huge, huge Hellboy fan,
and then, for him to walk in,
I am super stoked.
Great to finally
have you here on Face Off.
- It's great to be here.
- All right.
Well, some of the most
classic heroes of all time
are intrinsically linked
to their capes and costumes.
What they wear really
defines who they are
as superheroes.
That brings us to
today's foundation challenge.
You'll each choose one of
these incredible costumes
and create
the superhero that wears it.
- Nice.
- Yeah.
So Mike, what are you gonna
be looking for
in their final makeups?
I want to see integration
with the costume
that they're working with.
Put your best effort into
telling a complete story.
All right, guys.
The winner of this foundation
challenge will earn immunity.
On my "Go," I want you
to choose your model
and get to work.
You have two hours,
and your time starts now.
Hi.
Let's go get you
superhero-ed up.
Right here.
I go right to these
knee-high glitter boots
and hot-pink cape.
My superhero's name
is Deadly Diamond.
She is hard and
beautiful as diamonds.
The piece doesn't
fit her face exactly,
so I rip parts away from it
and start creating
some of that diamond-shape
and that cracked pattern.
Perfect.
I look at my model,
and the most prominent feature
on her costume is
the huge protrusion of feathers
sticking out of
the shoulders of her cape,
and I find this really cool
feathered bird mask.
And I realize that with the way
that the piece is designed,
doesn't look like
it should be a part of her.
So it works perfectly.
It's a mask.
I want that immunity real bad.
I'm really excited because
I'm a huge comic book nerd.
My character's an alien assassin
who comes to Earth
and falls in love
with earthlings.
I'm using this skullcap
and this cotton underlay
to create a new head shape.
He's Intensitron.
Part man, part machine,
all intensity.
I'm gonna bring
the color scheme up,
do some metallics
and some blues.
Intense.
Just something
about the purple man
that appeals to me.
So my superhero
is The Camo-Lord
he can change his skin
to any color or texture.
I use Kryolan Aqua Colors
on the face as a base
and then some airbrushing.
Two hours goes by
really frickin' quick.
You got 30 minutes,
we're at the 30-minute mark.
That's it. Time!
Brushes down.
- Hey, Doc, how are you?
- How's it going?
Hi, Doc.
All right, so tell us about
what direction you went in
with your superhero.
All right,
so this is Paul Fincher.
He is zookeeper by day,
birdcage by night.
It feels to me like
he's wearing just a mask.
It should carry over
into his skin as well.
But other than that,
I think your paint job's
really well done.
That means a lot.
Huge fan.
I really like what you did
with the layering of color.
It looks like you took a lot
of time in creating depth
to a very dark makeup.
I might have done a little
bit more with the lower half
of the face, but I think what
you've done looks very nice.
- Thank you.
- So this is Karma.
She's an assassin
on her home planet.
This is really, really elegant.
I think your use
of contouring is beautiful,
and the lashes look great.
Thanks very much.
I was inspired by the collar
to do the head shape.
Also it symbolizes cat ears.
I think it's
really, really beautiful.
It's tough to do black makeup,
and I like the way that you
augmented the highlights
by using silver,
that's a really nice choice.
There are really some
amazing superheroes
in the room.
It would be so cool to win,
but everyone's is
really amazing.
It could go either way.
All right, Mike.
How do you think our
artists did today?
I think they did
an amazing job.
Thank you.
Okay, so who created
your favorite makeups?
Vince, I really love the way
that you used layering
in your airbrushing to give
your character an organic feel.
- Thank you.
- And Rachael.
Very seductive design,
beautiful contouring,
and good choice of colors.
Very well done.
Who is the winner
of today's challenge?
The winner of today's
challenge is...
Rachael.
You've created
a complete character
which told me a story
which I believed.
- Well done.
- Thanks very much.
Rachael, congratulations.
You have earned immunity in
the next spotlight challenge.
I am really excited to win.
Mike was so nice!
Just having his feedback
on my piece is really great.
I will see you tomorrow for
your next spotlight challenge.
- Bye.
- Thanks, guys.
- Nice to meet you.
- Thank you.
- We're back.
- Whoo!
We walk into the lab,
and we see McKenzie
with this huge tree.
I take a lot of inspiration
from nature.
So I'm pretty excited
to see what's in store.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
Let's get to this.
Films like Lord Of The Rings,
The Wizard Of Oz,
and The Evil Dead
portrayed trees
as intelligent beings
that possess humanlike traits.
This week's spotlight challenge
is to create
a larger-than-life
tree character
inspired by
a unique tree species.
That's cool.
I'm absolutely freaking out.
I've been wanting to make
a tree character
for a really long time.
All right, so we have
banyan tree,
a sequoia tree,
weeping willow,
white birch tree,
bristlecone pine tree,
and silk floss tree.
For this challenge,
you'll be working together
in teams of two.
This time, you get to pick
your own partner.
Ooh.
Go ahead and stand
with your new teammate.
Yeah, sure.
_
Jason and I have both been
either safe or in the bottom
on every challenge, so we're
gonna combine our forces
of being terrible
and make something awesome.
All right, time
to pick the trees
that will inspire your designs.
Doc and Jason?
- Bristlecone pine.
- Sasha and Stella.
The white birch tree.
- Vince and Damien.
- Giant sequoia.
- Yeah.
- Dina and Rachael.
The banyan.
George and Keaghlan.
The silk floss.
There is one more thing
you need to know.
Ooh.
In each of the movies
that I mentioned earlier,
the trees were
either evil or angry.
So I want you to turn
your characters
into twisted trees.
- Nice.
- Yeah.
Now to help guide
your dark transformations,
you've each been assigned
a common malady suffered
by trees.
Oh, that's cool.
Doc and Jason, your malady
is the lightning strike.
Cig and Drew,
your tree has pests.
Nice.
Dina and Rachael,
your malady is fungus.
Vince and Damien,
your tree has rot.
Sasha and Stella,
you've got burl.
This is so cool.
George and Keaghlan,
your malady is choking vines.
- Yeah.
- Cool.
Keep in mind that the judges
will be looking
for both the tree
and the malady
to be reflected
in your final makeups.
So select your models and get
started on your designs.
I'll be by later on with my dad
to check in on your progress.
- See you later.
- Thank you.
Bye.
- Bristlecone pine.
- Hell yeah.
Jason and I picked
the bristlecone pine.
Our malady is lightning,
so we've got the coolest tree.
We probably have
the coolest malady,
and we're gonna create
something awesome.
Maybe one big knot
going off to the side.
So we decided to have him be
the guardian of the desert.
And he's very old
and grumpy and lazy.
Whenever he's not doing
his job right,
the elder gods will strike him
with lightning.
I definitely think-- just
keep going more asymmetrical
- with the profile.
- Okay.
This is, like,
my dream challenge.
I love incorporating nature
into my makeups.
We get the banyan,
and our malady is fungus,
which is amazing.
Since these are supposed
to be twisted trees,
maybe we include
an aspect of twisting.
Oh, yeah.
The fungus will be coming out
of cracked bark,
kind of moving with the flow
of the tree, so...
Yeah.
This is gonna be beautiful.
Sasha and I pick
the white birch tree,
and our malady is burls,
which are, like, tumor growths.
So I start on the face,
and Sasha starts on the cowl.
Our concept is a sacred
Native American tree
that is sad
that the white man scared
all his people away,
and he starts growing
all these burls
because of that.
Also, birch trees have eyes
and are known
as the watching trees.
So we want to put eyes
all over his body
as if he's always watching.
I love these branches so much.
I think it's kind of sick.
All right, I'm gonna get
a block of clay
and start carving this out.
I don't really have
a solid concept
for a head or a face
on this tree.
So I give Vince the go-ahead
to start designing
that aspect of it.
We picked
the giant sequoia tree,
and our malady is tree rot.
I would really love
to make a zombie tree.
The top of his head is gonna
have a really angry face on it,
big hands with huge,
you know, bent fingers,
and his feet are gonna
be also giant
and, like, big stumps.
That's cool, man.
Hey, guys. We're here
to check on your trees.
- Hello.
- How are you?
- Hi.
- Hello.
He is this twisted,
broken tree who's in pain,
so we are trying to show
the twist of how he's grown.
You know,
when I first looked at it,
I thought it was vines
or a fire.
It's like different
directions going everywhere.
I am totally freaking out
right now.
We just spent hours
sculpting this thing,
and I was excited about it,
and now we have to start over.
I'm worried because Rachael
has immunity,
so if we are on bottom looks,
I could be going home for this.
Coming up...
It's breaking.
The more we pry,
the more cracks we're getting.
- Is it fixable?
- Nope.
- I'm fucked.
- I actually enjoy it immensely.
It's devoid and crippling.
It's like different
directions going everywhere,
which isn't really
what your research is.
Mr. Westmore tells us
that our design
doesn't really resemble
a banyan tree.
I thought
it was vines or a fire.
We put a lot of work into this,
but if he doesn't think
it looks like a banyan tree,
then the judges
aren't going to.
We have to start over.
All right,
so you have the silk floss.
We have the silk floss.
And the malady
is choking vines.
Choking vines.
So explain the concept.
Our character was
an environmentalist
perched up in the top
of this tree
to stop it
from being chopped down.
So when the tree fell,
her and the tree
combined and grew into
this warrior of the forest.
So the face-- we wanted
to incorporate the spines
into her face and kind
of create a brow with it.
Try to just take a little
bit of the human out of it.
Maybe filling in
a little under here
so it doesn't have
the sharp jaw sticking out.
Okay.
So you picked
the weeping willow.
Yes.
And it's infested with bugs.
So our story is that
it was an earth spirit,
and she became infested
with these bugs.
She's all draped
in these leaves,
and people hear someone crying,
so they come up to the tree.
She snatches them up,
and the bugs come out
of all her holes.
And then they're eating
the people.
To show the bug,
are you gonna
have actually little holes?
'Cause the bugs are, you know,
like termites.
Yeah, I was just started
to put in some divots.
- Yeah, make 'em big enough.
- Yeah.
We have a big, big sculpture
that sort of resembles
the sequoia,
but then the face itself--
it's got the rot on the face.
When you get this out in foam,
pull a little foam out of it.
It'll give the model
more freedom
to be able to twist their head.
Yeah.
The bristlecone pine's got
these amazing trunks
towards the bottom,
so we've come up with these
cool boots to go over top.
The bristlecone pine--
there's just so much more...
- Jagged edges.
- ...going on with it
than what I'm seeing
what you're doing.
Yeah.
You haven't gone far enough
for your design.
All right.
He's kind of
an old, craggy man.
You know, you're
getting real human in this.
You don't have to show
a mouth so much
or even the nasolabial folds.
It's not a person in a tree.
This is the personification
of a living tree.
Okay.
All right, everybody.
- Good luck with your trees.
- Good luck.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
- Bye-bye.
Our malady is bug infestation,
and Mr. Westmore mentioned
that we should put
some of the evidence of the bug
infestation on the sculpts.
So I'm gonna sculpt bug trails
into the chest area
while drew is sculpting
the texture slab
that we can use
for the arms and the legs.
And then, we really need
to get started fabricating
the willow branches, which
is really important
because we've got to figure out
how to distribute
the weight properly.
I like 'em.
Let's look at this again.
I think Dina's very nervous
about the immunity,
and now,
we are completely redesigning
every aspect of
what we've been working on.
_
My first face had a lot
of horizontal designs,
but once we got that curveball
from Mr. Westmore,
I decided to change
that completely
and have
vertical branches instead.
- This is really depressing.
- I know, I know.
I was hoping
I could get it finished today,
and then, tomorrow,
as soon as I get here,
- we can open it.
- Dude, just--
- as thick as you can make it, and then--
- That's what I'm trying to do.
At the end of the day,
I'm pretty worried
the leg mold
is not thick enough,
and I know I'm gonna have
to come back to it tomorrow.
Okay, that's time.
We're now behind for day two.
I have been in
the bottom every challenge.
It's just not
a good spot to be in.
I'm starting to get
extremely worried.
Oh, it smells like
foam latex in here.
Sweet.
It's day two
of our tree challenge,
and we have ten hours
in the lab.
Yesterday,
I re-sculpted the face,
so today, we're gonna have
to finish sculpting the cowl
and maybe do some hands,
chest piece,
and we'll see about a neck.
We have a lot of work
to do today.
Yeah, we need to add
something here.
- How's it looking?
- Fine and dandy.
How's our face?
Edges look really nice,
- that's for sure.
- Yeah.
We have our foam latex pieces
that we sculpted yesterday,
and they look beautiful.
So now, we have all of
day two for fabrication.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna
start cutting up
some flowers
while the latex dries.
All right.
The tree-- it has
this very, like,
feminine kind of curve to it,
so we were gonna fabricate
this pencil skirt out of latex
to do this.
I sculpt--
it's called a gang mold.
So that I have
a mold of, like, 30 spikes,
and I can just pass latex
in that.
And within 10 minutes,
I've got 30 spikes
that are ready to go
wherever they need to.
Can you think of anything else
that's more pressing?
Um, I don't know.
Maybe just dance.
Doc is finished
with the leg mold,
and I get the chest, back,
and cowl finished.
It's the biggest sculpture
I've ever done, and now,
I have the biggest mold
I've ever made to make.
I'm probably gonna need
your help moving the mannequin.
While I'm molding the chest,
Doc is molding the arms.
We're both a little bit
worried about time management,
but hopefully,
we can get it all done.
Hey, Drew.
I think it's ready to go.
Let's do it.
The stone on the bodysuit mold
has completely hardened,
and it's ready to open.
Fuck.
I broke it.
We're having a lot
of trouble getting
the mold actually popped open.
We started noticing
some cracks...
Shit.
And we start noticing
some more cracks.
What the fuck happened?
The more we pry,
the more cracks we're getting.
- Oh, oh.
- What's happening?
It's breaking across the chest.
I'm getting
worried at this point.
If we don't get this mold open
and ready for foam today,
we won't have anything.
Why are you stuck?
We're in a lot of trouble.
It's breaking.
It's day two of
our twisted tree challenge,
and me and Drew are having
trouble opening our mold.
- All right. Stop.
- It's stuck here somewhere.
I'm starting to get
a little worried right now
because we really need
to get this mold
popped and get right
to fabricating willow branches.
Look at that.
Finally get the mold open,
and it's definitely a relief.
But we've lost a lot of time.
All right, you go fabricate.
- I'll handle this.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- All right.
- Very sure.
I immediately get started
on fabricating the branches
of the weeping willow tree.
I'm going to make
four large branches
that are gonna protrude
from the prosthetic in the back.
Once you see it start
to kind of,
like, wiggle on you,
that's your best point.
Birch trees have bark
that peels off like paper.
To create that look,
I'm taking L200,
and I cut some shapes into it,
and I curled them
with the heat gun.
Look, Sasha.
Oh, my God!
We also have to make hands,
so Sasha makes burl hands out
of poly foam.
_
There's no way that they're
gonna come off the hands
without us completely
tearing them apart.
This is not good.
_
I'm very frustrated,
but I'm just gonna have
to figure something out.
Yeah.
- Okay.
- Ooh.
See, that right there is almost
just perfect for this
reddish color that's in there.
_
That's why I'm mixing
other colors in it,
and this is why I said
it was not the exact.
Damien definitely wants to go
more sequoia red color with it.
Our malady is tree rot,
so I want to go
a little bit more grayed-out,
dead zombie tree.
It just needs to get
a little bit darker.
But it dries a different color
than what you're looking.
We're not quite in sync,
so I'm a little bit
worried about it.
It could make or break us.
I decided to carve my hands
out of mattress foam.
It's not looking beautiful,
but burls aren't beautiful.
And at least now I feel
like I'm on the right track.
I'm gonna keep going.
Hit me.
Aww.
Time is just whittling away,
and I go to open the first arm.
I try and lift, and--
Oh, come on.
It's just breaking
along the edges.
And there it goes.
It just completely breaks
into, like,
four different pieces.
We might not be
getting the arms.
- Why not?
- They just keep breaking.
This is just a mess.
That's time, everyone!
Brushes down!
- Eh?
- Eh.
This is the end
of the line for me.
- I'm out.
- No, it's not.
Time runs out,
and at this point,
I'm already packing
my bags in my head.
We don't have the arms.
That was my responsibility.
I sculpted those.
I molded them.
I broke the mold.
It's my fault.
- Go on ahead.
- Go, go, go, go.
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab
and one hour at last looks.
Things are gonna be crazy.
Okay, that can be glued.
A little bit of a tear,
but that looks pretty good.
Look. Check it out.
What's that?
We have a very bad second skin
on our cowl.
Second skin is where
the outside
of your foam piece
isn't attached,
but it really resembles
the rot texture
that we sculpted
into our cowl originally.
- That actually looks good.
- Yeah, like rot.
You could do
the rot right there.
Oh, yeah.
So we decide to turn
all of our second skinning spots
into rot, which I'm hoping
doesn't come back
to bite us in the ass later.
- Cool. Yeah. Right on.
- That's awesome.
- I'm Vince.
- Cig.
So you're gonna be
the silk floss tree.
George and I have
to apply the skirt,
apply the latex patches
from her shoulder
to her fingertips.
We also have to apply
our face piece
and head dress as well.
I look around,
and everybody has
very, very different
makeups than ours,
but I'm hoping that it makes
us stand out in a great way.
If I got to go home,
I want to go home
on a makeup that
I had fun with,
and I've had a lot of fun.
Me, too.
This really looks
like peeling birch.
- I love it.
- Yeah, it really does.
We used brown as our base color
and then dry-brushed white
all over.
Our tree is
totally coming to life.
The colors in it
and the eyes are popping--
like, really looking awesome.
Doc and I get the cowl
and torso on our model,
and I take a chip brush
and just start
brushing
on that brown base coat
and then come up
with the lighter brown
highlights on top of it.
And 'cause the arms
did not come out,
we have to find
a way to cover everything.
But luckily, I have a robe
that I can cut up
and glue down on top of him.
The sculpt bulks out.
The arms are covered.
He looks cohesive.
I just hope it's good enough.
_
How much time?
Ten.
Oh, fuck.
Time's almost up.
We have all of our prosthetics
applied and painted.
So when we get over there,
we're gonna attach
your branches, and they're
gonna come out above you.
Guys, that's time.
- Brushes down.
- Yeah.
It's a risk for us
to apply at last looks,
but without the branches,
she won't read
as a weeping willow at all.
So we have to make sure
that we get 'em done
and done right.
Coming up...
We need to focus on the paint.
It's looking very hokey.
Stay together, girl.
I don't know what happened.
It's awe-inspiring.
There are so many
missed opportunities here.
Let's go. Let's go.
We get to last looks,
and we have an hour left
to complete our tree.
They should come out
in a two-top.
Okay.
Drew's putting on the branches
while I'm touching up the paint.
I'm worried that if we don't
get this tree canopy,
there's nothing about
the makeup
that says "weeping willow."
Perfect.
_
We notice that some
of his legs were showing.
- What do you need?
- The big piece of pine needles.
So we bring in some more
of the green pine
to make it look like
it's all intentional.
And I'm just thinking,
"Oh, my God.
We may have pulled it off."
_
I'm still questioning
the hands in my head,
but the character looks amazing.
We need to focus around
the costume,
getting it all black.
We're frantically painting.
Time is running out,
and it's just too bright.
It looks very hokey.
So we start darkening that dye
with some blacks
and some browns.
- It popped way better like that.
- Did it?
So we're looking pretty good.
All right, guys.
15 minutes.
Time, guys.
- Awesome, awesome, awesome.
- Kick ass.
At the end of last looks,
I cannot believe that Cig and I
have managed to create
not just a tree creature,
but a tree.
I think we've got
a really good chance
of hitting top looks
with this makeup.
Please,
just stay together, girl.
Yeah, right?
Welcome to
the Face Off reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
First, let's say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve
Make-Up Effects Studio,
- Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening, guys.
- Good evening.
- Hey, Glenn.
Oscar-winning makeup artist,
Lois Burwell.
Good evening, all of you.
Hi, Lois.
And creature
and concept designer,
- Neville Page.
- Hello.
- Hi, Neville.
- All right, guys.
This week, your spotlight
challenge was to create
a twisted tree character based
on a unique tree species
and malady.
Let's take a look
at your creations
while the audience
at home tweets
about their favorites
using #FaceOff.
I'm loving
how interesting he is
and how he doesn't look
like any other tree.
I wish there was a little
more variation in the color,
but the makeup is
pretty complete.
He stomps onto the stage.
He looks amazing.
I'm really hoping
that we get top looks.
I think he looks great.
I think he's got
a strong profile
and a strong silhouette.
It looks like a tree character.
Our banyan tree
doesn't look good.
I'm definitely expecting
to be on bottom.
There are no branches.
What the fuck?
When we finished last looks,
it was all put together,
but now, it's not.
I don't know what happened.
Judges, it's time to have
a closer look at our trees.
It's really well-rendered.
- And I like the bark here.
- Yeah.
I love this.
- Full head-to-toe coverage.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Wow, there's
a lot of work here.
The strangling vine idea
seems placed on
as an afterthought.
Thank you.
I don't get it.
I think it's
the stump at the top.
There's a lot of things
well done,
but it's flawed.
The hands are really good.
Yeah.
Thank you.
This is stunning,
the way that it trails off
in one direction.
I love the clarity of the face.
Thank you.
This pattern here doesn't
say "tree bark" at all.
It doesn't say it anywhere.
As Glenn is gesturing,
I'm starting to notice
all the things that
we should have done.
Looks like fungus
wasn't the only malady.
I have immunity,
so I am gonna be
really, really upset
if Dina goes home.
Who made your favorite
twisted tree character?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
Oh, lord.
I'm starting to notice
all the things
that we should have done.
Looks like fungus
wasn't the only malady.
I am gonna be really upset
if Dina goes home.
Thank you.
The arms seem so undone,
and the colors don't even
really tie together.
It feels to me as
if there's something
elaborate missing.
Okay, the judges have
scored your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
George and Keaghlan,
Dina and Rachael...
Congratulations,
you are all safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
That means the rest of you
were the best
and the worst this week.
The judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Doc and Jason, please step up.
Tell me about the tree
that you selected
and how it influenced
your makeup.
We got the bristlecone pine.
Its malady
was lightning strike.
Since the bristlecone pine
is a Western tree,
we made him the guardian
of the desert.
I sculpted the hands,
chest, back, and cowl.
Doc blocked out
the face and the--
And the stumps.
The form language is exquisite.
Oh, my goodness.
You're doing highly
advanced creative thinking.
The shapes actually inform
the visual experience
for the audience.
It's quite awe-inspiring.
Thank you so much.
I like all the small details.
I love the way you've even done
the knees and the feet.
I think it's excellent work.
Thank you.
On the malady front,
I don't really know if
it's supposed to be
on fire
or it's just extinguished.
I would have chosen
one way or the other.
Yeah.
But the finesse in
the cheek area is so good.
Doc and Jason,
please step back.
Thank you, guys.
Good job, buddy.
Good job, man.
Good job, guys.
Cig and Drew, please step up.
Tell us about your tree.
We got the weeping willow.
It has bug infestation,
and the only way
that she can get
the bugs to not eat her
is to give them
something else to eat.
So she sits under the willow
branches and grabs passersby.
Then, the bugs come out,
and they feast on the person
while she's weeping
in their face.
I don't want to lead you
with anything,
but is there anything missing?
She was draped
in willow branches.
I'm not really sure,
but I think our model
had a last minute
weight issue with them.
Even taking that into account,
I feel as if there are so many
missed opportunities here.
There's something about
the way the color is done.
This seems to be so uniform,
and the sluggy bugs
don't make sense to me.
There's some really nice
fine detail work
up in the face,
but it turns
to mud rather quickly.
Who's responsible
for the different aspects
of the makeup?
Cig sculpted the body,
and I did the face
and fabricated the branches.
So you're taking
full responsibility
for engineering
whatever I'm not seeing.
That's brave of you.
I'm sad it didn't work out.
- Me, too.
Cig and Drew,
if you'd please step back.
- Thanks.
- Thank you, Iris.
Sasha and Stella,
please step forward.
So tell us about the tree
that you chose
and how the malady inspired
this design.
Our tree is
the white birch tree,
and it is sacred to
the Native American people.
He is upset that his people
were driven from his land,
and because of that,
he started growing burls
all over his body.
I'm pretty well impressed.
It is so well-rendered
and so clear that it is birch.
Then, I see these boxing gloves
that are so wrong.
I wanted to do away with them.
Oh, you didn't like them?
I said, "Can we
please get rid of them?"
It's a little late now.
Are those just gloves?
Can you take one of them off
so I can just see his form
without the--
If his hand was just white,
it's a gigantic leap forward,
but overall, the paint job is
absolutely gorgeous.
I enjoy it immensely.
- Thank you.
- I really like this makeup too.
I particularly love
the crumply knees.
Just a nice touch.
It's really, really good.
Thank you.
Stella and Sasha,
please step back.
Damien and Vince.
Tell me about the tree
that influenced this makeup.
Our tree was the giant sequoia,
and its malady was rot.
Somebody chops him down,
and that's how
he gets infested with the rot.
Vince sketched out
a profile of him
and sculpted the face.
I sculpted the hands,
and we both had hands
on the cowl and the feet.
I think it's
a triumphant victory
if it was
for an office Halloween party.
It's just not sensible to
have started
with the trunk on his head
because it's so limiting
in terms of what you can do
for the rest of the body.
It really is like he's rushed
into the forest
and pulled something over
his head as a disguise.
There's something
not cohesive about it.
There's some gorgeous
work here.
The giant hands,
well-sculpted,
but his left eye--
What is that supposed to be?
It's just a dead eye,
just like the rot in--
that's infesting him.
Don't understand that,
and conceptually,
it's devoid and crippling.
Vince and Damien,
please step back.
Thank you.
All right, guys.
The judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the make-up room
while they deliberate.
All right, judges.
So why don't we start
with the looks you like
the most this week.
How about Doc and Jason?
I thought it was gorgeous.
There's little
that you can do to screw it up
once you've got the forms
that right-on,
and I think that
was mostly Jason.
The way that
the expression comes through
and the clever use of
that red under the eye
to give that haunted look.
I really loved it.
The distance read had
a lot of information
that was interesting,
and up close,
there was a lot
of tight detail.
All right, let's move on
to Sasha and Stella.
That thing read instantly
that it was American-Indian,
birch, and there was something
fantastical about it.
- The coloring was superb.
- Yeah.
I don't know that you could
have nailed
the texture color any better.
It's just wonderful.
I loved it.
Let's move on to
the looks you like the least.
Cig and Drew.
It's a shame
because it's so hard
when part of the makeup isn't
actually there in front of you,
but we can't judge something
that isn't there.
The fact that they're
not clever enough
to have engineered something
in the time
that they had to carry
that weight,
that's
a decision-making problem.
So even though Drew
dropped the ball
on the most important part,
he was responsible
for the face,
which is the best part.
- Yeah.
- All right.
Let's move on
to Vince and Damien.
It is devoid of a concept.
I don't think Da Vinci
himself could have made
anything happen with that idea
of a tree mask
with his eyes and mouth showing
through on his head.
And what about Vince
and that eye?
That was one very,
very specific region
that had
the greatest opportunity
to design, sculpt,
and sell character.
Yes.
A complete missed
opportunity there.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- We have.
- Yep.
Okay. Let's bring them
back out.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about tonight's top teams.
Doc and Jason,
there was
some elegant flowing lines
in your sculptural work,
and we thought that you made
all the right choices
in your paint job.
Stella and Sasha,
your birch texture really
came through,
and we absolutely adored
the way
that your malady drove
the sympathetic nature
of your character.
All right.
Which team came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
All right, Glenn.
Which team came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Doc and Jason.
Looking at that makeup,
you would never know
that the two of you guys
started off the day thinking
that you were in trouble.
It is a remarkably strong
piece of work.
Thank you.
Jason and Doc, congratulations.
As you know,
we can only have one winner.
Glenn?
Our winner tonight is...
- Jason.
- Oh, my God.
There was true beauty in some
of your detail work tonight.
What a comeback.
Congratulations.
Thank you guys so much.
I actually won a challenge,
and it feels great.
No matter what happens further
in this competition,
I have this win, and they can't
take that from me.
- Jason, congratulations.
- Thank you.
You and Doc, Sasha,
and Stella are all safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Unfortunately, that means
the rest of you
are on the bottom this week.
One of you will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
All right, Glenn.
Tell us
about tonight's bottom teams.
Cig and Drew, we thought
the face was quite nice,
but the missing willow canopy
just left your makeup up
a river without a paddle.
Vince and Damien, there were
some well-done pieces
of the makeup,
but the crippled concept
was just too prevalent
in the end result.
So who's going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Vince.
Most of our major issues
were the shapes
of the head and cowl.
They just left no where else
for the makeup to go.
Vince, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
That means
Damien, Cig, and Drew,
you guys are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
You've got great talent,
and I hope in the future
we meet up again.
Thank you.
Vince, it's been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- Good luck, Vince.
- Thank you.
I'm bummed
that I didn't get a chance
to compete in other challenges.
Who is it, guys?
- Vince.
- Oh, Vince.
I have a lot of ideas
that I wanted to show.
My only regret, I guess,
would be that
I didn't think more
about the concept,
but makeup effects,
it's my first love,
and I still love doing it,
and being able to do
that is pretty great.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net