I think it's amazing.
I loved the character.
- Whoo!
- Watch your face.
Previously on Face Off...
Damien's ambitious
animal hybrid
earned him his first win,
and Doc was eliminated.
Oh, boy.
Now just ten artists remain,
and tonight they'll take on
a wonderful twist of whimsy.
This rainbow is an homage
to one
of the most legendary films.
Ugh!
But for some,
it will be just plain wicked.
- Cheer up.
- It just not looking great.
I'm hypnotized
as she stares at me.
It's so freaky.
In the end, only one will win
a VIP trip from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
It's a breakfast feast.
Wow!
Oh, he's so beautiful.
Pshew!
I woke up this morning
really, really excited.
I mean, I'm feeling
very confident.
I have now had three top looks
in spotlight challenges,
and I'm ready to do something
really awesome.
Let's go.
What do you think
the challenge is gonna be?
Better be something pretty.
Oh, boy.
We are walking
in Sony Pictures,
and we see this giant rainbow,
and I'm instantly excited.
Ooh, are we talking whimsical?
Please tell me whimsical.
Oh, please don't be whimsical.
Most people are afraid
of creatures and monsters,
but I hear "whimsical,"
and that's scary for me.
There's McKenzie.
Hi.
Look at this.
Looks like a crazy tea party.
That's so cute.
McKenzie is set up
with a tea party.
It's really, really adorable.
I'm a little bit nervous
to see what's in store,
but it's gonna be fun.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi!
Welcome
to Sony Pictures Studios.
Soaring 94 feet into the sky,
this rainbow, created by
renowned sculptor Tony Tasset,
is an homage to one
of the most legendary films
in cinematic history,
which is celebrating
its 75th anniversary this year,
The Wizard Of Oz.
I am in heaven,
because The Wizard Of Oz
is my favorite movie.
The film is based
on the classic children's book
that created some of
the most memorable characters
in popular culture,
Frank Baum's
The Wonderful Wizard Of Oz.
And for today's
spotlight challenge,
you'll be bringing
some of the book's
iconic characters to life.
Awesome.
Now, this is a team challenge,
so before I tell you more,
go ahead and choose a partner.
You and me.
Let's do it.
- Yeah.
- Let's do it.
- Sasha?
- Yes.
Jason likes monsters
and horror,
and I like
bright, pretty stuff,
so I hope we can pull off
something crazy
with our different styles.
Now, since I've been talking
about The Wonderful
Wizard Of Oz,
you may be wondering
why I've invited you
to The Mad Hatter's tea party.
Well, of course, that's because
there's a big twist
to this challenge.
- Oh, my--
- Of course.
Your spotlight challenge
is to reimagine a character
from The Wonderful Wizard Of Oz
as though they've fallen
down the rabbit hole
into the fantastic world
of Alice's Adventures
In Wonderland.
- Oh, fuck!
- Yes!
Merging Oz into Wonderland
is gonna be really fun.
With all the trippy colors
and surrealistic aspects,
I think we'll be able
to do something
really creative and outside
the box with this makeup.
On the bottom of each teacup
is the name of a character
from Oz.
Oh, my God.
When I call your name,
pick one to find out
which character
you'll be transforming.
George and Drew,
you're up first.
- Yeah!
- Ooh.
Wicked Witch Of The West.
Dina and Stella.
Winged Monkey.
Cig and Damien.
The Scarecrow.
Uh-oh.
Rachael and Keaghlan.
Tin Woodman.
Jason and Sasha.
Cowardly Lion.
Okay, you're all set.
Get started on your sketches.
- Good luck, guys.
- Thank you.
I'm so stoked for this.
So we're definitely
going green, right?
Yeah.
Our Wicked Witch Of The West
was flying in a tornado
on her broomstick
and ends up in Wonderland
by getting blown off course.
All of her features
become super exaggerated
as Wonderland fuses with her.
She's actually gonna have
a spiraled hairstyle
so that when she takes
her hat off,
we'll have the reveal
of this cool, like,
twisted tornado of hair.
I really like that idea,
actually.
He was burlap in Wizard Of Oz.
So maybe he fell down
the rabbit hole,
and he lost stuffing.
He was always, like,
falling around
'cause he doesn't have bones.
We decide
that our Scarecrow embraces
the madness of Wonderland.
We'll still have some burlap,
but we were gonna incorporate
bright polka dot
and striped patchwork.
And then if we build up
fake shoulders,
we could do that head gag,
where it looks
like his head falls off.
- Like, mm, mm.
- Yeah. Yeah.
I think
that's a great idea, dude.
We need to figure out
his character.
Okay.
I read the description
of the Winged Monkey,
and it says that
he's very mischievous,
and he likes
to play tricks on people.
So how does he mess
with people?
So maybe he's the joker.
- Oh? That's actually...
- Right?
He's the joker
of the Queen's court.
That's smart.
So our concept is
that our Winged Monkey
is going to be the jester
for the Queen Of Hearts.
What if his wings were made
out of a deck of cards?
We could.
That could look
really interesting.
Rachael and I
are really excited
about creating a character
that fits in both these worlds.
The Queen Of Hearts
is always yelling
"Off with their head."
Who better to carry out
that request
than the Tin Woodman
with his ax?
So, basically, like,
he falls in down the rabbit hole
and is immediately forced
into the Queen Of Hearts' army.
Mm-hmm.
In refusing to act
as her executioner,
he realized that he had
a heart after all.
I like that.
He's that kind of character.
Yeah.
What's your idea?
Couple ideas.
Well, okay,
the Lion's in Wonderland.
Right.
I figured maybe the Queen
turns him into her soldier,
but he's cowardly,
so he doesn't want to fight,
so she beats him
and starves him,
so he's all withered
and lacerated.
I like creepy and gross stuff,
but that's not
what we're supposed to do
for the challenge,
and I don't want the same thing
that happened with Barry
to happen now.
You've been given
a challenge...
- Yep.
- ...and it isn't here.
We need something colorful.
You know, the Cheshire Cat's
purple and pink stripes.
I don't know.
I kind of want to go with cool.
We just came off a challenge
where we were doing
whimsical makeup,
so I'd really like
to make something
a little darker and scarier.
Um...
I don't know if that's right,
but I don't like confrontation.
I'm so bad at it.
So we're gonna go
with a creepy lion, I guess.
All right, guys,
let's head back to the lab.
All right.
Whoo!
It's nice and cool in here.
We come back to the lab.
We have 6 1/2 hours today,
and the first thing we do
is select our models.
Then we start sculpting.
I'm gonna block out
the cowl for Tin Woodman,
while Keaghlan
starts to block out the face.
Do you like kind of
the shapes I'm going with?
I do.
What if the ears were, like,
in the shape of a joker hat?
Of a joker hat?
Oh, yeah!
Would that be kind of cool?
Stella and I are mixing
inorganic and organic.
We're doing the jester hat
out of skin.
Once we have our concept down,
then we start sculpting.
I get started on the face,
and Stella starts
blocking out the cowl.
I'm gonna make it
a little ear shape
at the bottom, I think.
Okay.
George and I are working
really well together.
We're on the same page
conceptually and technically.
I'm still musing on how
to make her more Wonderland,
'cause I'm worried
that she's just gonna be
too straightforward
Wicked Witch.
The nice thing about Drew
is that he has no trouble
saying what's on his mind.
We could make
her teeth rotten and gnarly.
Think we could paint them up
like playing cards?
Yeah.
- I don't like that idea.
- Okay.
- Sorry.
- It's fine.
Since Jason has this idea
for this makeup,
he starts sculpting the face,
and I start sculpting the cowl.
I want to do exaggerated ears
to make it more whimsical.
Jason, what do you think
about the ears?
Uh, not too big.
Lion ears are small.
I'll make them more realistic.
I definitely am not happy
with the direction
of our makeup at all.
Cig and I are sculpting
our Scarecrow's cowl and face
really, really quickly.
I'm gonna go back there
and start cleaning
this bad bitch up.
We don't have to spend
any time detailing the sculpts,
because we're going
to actually sew fabric
into the foam pieces.
So about two hours in, we have
the face done and the cowl,
and we're ready to mold.
It feels really good
being the first ones
in the mold room.
We want to get these
ready for foam tonight,
so we can spend
all day tomorrow fabricating.
Hey, guys.
Here to check on your work.
- Hi.
- Howdy.
- So you got the Wicked Witch.
- Yeah.
What are you going to do
with the mouth here?
We want to have
a curled-under sort of look.
One thing you can do
would be to make
your upper lip
a little thicker.
It's gonna make that
fall back in.
Yeah.
We were thinking
about building these ears up
like a jester's hat.
Are you gonna use any hair
or any fur on it at all?
I really don't want to.
- Are you a little nervous?
- I know you don't.
Little bits wouldn't hurt,
even if you lay a little bit
on the chin,
just very whimsical
little things,
'cause you could do that
on the back of the hands too.
Mm-hmm.
We have the Tin Woodman.
I like the way
you straightened all this out.
- Yeah, this is great.
- Yeah.
But all of a sudden,
I'm looking at a seashell
over here.
- It need more planes to it.
- Okay.
Make it a little sharper?
Sharpen the leading edge
and then round into it.
Okay.
We have the Scarecrow.
Are you talking
about making him patchwork?
Mm-hmm.
The thing is,
don't get really crazy and busy
overly doing it,
making the face disappear.
Yeah.
As soon as the Lion
gets to Wonderland,
the Queen is the first person
that finds him
and beats him up a little bit.
So he's like
one of her soldiers?
Yeah.
It needs to be bolder.
It's reading kitty-cat to me,
not a lion.
You need to get
a little whimsical
into this character.
I said to Jason from the start,
it's got to stand out
and be interesting.
This is wonderland.
This is not quite coming up
to what everybody else
is doing.
I'm really worried now.
If I don't take his advice,
they could end up sending
one of us home.
Coming up...
Only thing that worries me
is the movement.
It's gonna put our heads
on the chopping block.
It's a little bit stiff
and masklike.
That is confounding to me.
It needs to be bolder.
This is not quite coming up
to what everybody else
is doing.
It is day one of our Wizard
Of Oz and Wonderland challenge,
and Mr. Westmore doesn't think
we're going whimsical enough
with our creepy Cowardly Lion.
I'm kind of already scared
at this point.
Color-wise,
what do you plan on doing?
Applying colors
like the golds and the browns.
But that's really
not what the challenge is.
I said that to Jason
from the start.
It's got to stand out
and be interesting.
This is Wonderland.
Think happy and colorful
to mesh both worlds together.
Good luck.
Thanks, guys.
Maybe now we can make a makeup
that I really would
love to make.
All right, guys, good luck.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
♪ making witches ♪
What's the matter, Dina?
He still looks
a little too happy.
Oh, yeah.
We want a very mischievous look
on our monkey's face,
like he's smirking at you.
Dina can't seem
to get the expression right.
You want to switch?
Yeah, we can switch.
I just kind of
push her clay around
until I get it
to where it looks perfect.
Yeah, I think
he looks creepier.
- Like that? Okay.
- Yeah.
Good. It looks good.
So we want to do, like, a...
Pfft.
Like, a collar thing, right?
Yeah.
For the gag to work
to make it look
like our Scarecrow's head
falls off,
Damien and I have to build up
the shoulders
so that when his head drops,
the perspective
is that his shoulders
are still in place.
So maybe, like, build it up
with couch foam first
and use that
as, like, an armature
to shape the L200 around.
I get this couch foam,
and I start carving out
a collar shape that we'll put
under his wardrobe,
and when he drops his head,
the shoulders look
like they stay in place.
- Unh!
- Yeah.
Mr. Westmore tells me
to incorporate elements
from the Cheshire Cat
into my sculpture,
but it's frustrating having
to change your sculpt
after you've been
working on it all day.
So I'm just trying to bulk
the face out
to make it look
like a lion snout.
Hopefully,
that'll help the design.
Jason's
just moving clay around.
He hasn't done anything
to make our Cowardly Lion
more whimsical.
It was really frustrating,
but I just sit there
in my own world,
sculpting my lion ears,
all depressed.
Hey, Rachael, can we have
some of your hair?
You know, just a trim.
We're gonna take
Mr. Westmore's advice
and give our monkey
some little chin hairs,
and Rachael with her big,
beautiful, purple hair
is perfect.
Cut from the back, please.
Okay.
Have you ever cut hair, Stella?
Nope, but I've watched
people cut hair.
You're not making me
feel any better.
We have a piece of Rachael
in our makeup now.
Oh, yeah!
Perfect.
Cig, I'm gonna bundle
all this hay shit together.
I want to see what you think.
Hope it's not gonna
look too hokey.
We're going to stuff
our Scarecrow
with some glittery material,
so you can tell that he was
the original Scarecrow,
but he's been in Wonderland
for a long time,
and he's embracing the madness
a becoming part of Wonderland.
It's definitely
more Wonderland.
It's Wonderland hay.
Wonder hay.
Sasha, babe, cheer up.
I'm very upset because this is
like my dream challenge,
and it's just not going the way
that I would have loved.
I like pretty things.
Look how pretty that looks.
You want to make
something pretty?
We can't make--
It's creepy.
There's so much creativity
that could be put into this,
and I just want to do something
Wonderland-ish.
It's not pretty and creepy.
It's just creepy.
Ours just is so boring.
All right, everybody,
that's time!
Whoo!
I'm just hoping to
come back tomorrow and fix this.
Can you see the air pocket
on the nose?
- Nope.
- Good.
And there's glitter
on everything.
Looks like a fairy just
CENSORED over here everywhere.
There we go.
That's what we're looking for.
It's day two
of our Oz/Wonderland challenge,
and we've got 9 1/2 hours
in the lab.
First thing I'm gonna do
is add the skin across the back.
We start off by finishing
the sculpture for our witch.
I decided, rather than stick
to the strong anatomical
bone structure,
I'm gonna add stretches
of wrinkly skin
in between the shoulder blades.
I think this will be
a lot cooler
than just sculpting
realistic scapula.
It should be ready
for detailing shortly.
Okay.
Do you want to look
this over for me?
If you want to play
with it any, be my guest.
Okay.
Keaghlan asked me to jump
on the face and check it out.
_
And I see some stuff
that really needs to be fixed,
because symmetry's really
important for a Tin Man.
We want to get our molds done
in a couple hours,
so we're trying to step it up
as fast as we can.
I really dig
how beautiful you made him.
I think it's really beautiful.
Thank you.
While Dina is molding,
I get straight to work
on the wings,
which means I have to make
my own deck of cards.
I lay the stencil down,
and I airbrush them.
I glue them to a piece of L200
and cut out each card.
Sasha, I don't really think
I want to do much more to it.
Yeah?
Then I'm gonna mold it.
I'm still not happy
about Jason's face sculpt,
but we got to get this going,
so I start molding it.
I'm trying to stay
really positive.
Later, I'll figure out
how to make this creepy lion
more whimsical.
Oh, that's cool.
_
Cig stitches
the patchwork on our face,
and I really like
the way it's looking.
Only thing that worries me
is the movement.
Yeah.
But it's really losing
a lot of elasticity,
and one of the first thing
that the judges
ask your model to do
is move your face.
Can you move your brow?
Can you open your mouth?
Can you smile?
It feels tight,
like, up to here.
And if our model
can't do any of that,
we're really afraid
we're gonna hear
that dreaded "M" word,
which is mask.
Maybe score it out,
but I don't know if that's gonna
help all that much.
We're gonna
have to make it work,
otherwise, it's definitely
gonna put our heads
on the chopping block.
Only thing that worries me
is the movement.
It's day two
of our Alice In Wonderland/
Wizard Of Oz challenge,
and me and Damien are worried
that our Scarecrow face
is a little too stiff,
so we have to make it work.
If we cut on the inside
from here up
and separate the jaw...
I cut strategic movement points
around the mouth, nose,
and forehead.
Hopefully,
that's gonna fix the problem
of it looking like a mask.
That's a lot better.
I'm excited
about the monkey wings.
I'm just nervous about
how much time it's taking me
to make all of these cards
and put the wings together.
It doesn't really look
like a wing.
Dina's done molding,
and she comes over and sees
that I might
have a problem here.
We can get thinner here.
I've never fabricated wings
before,
so I'm relying on Stella
to build the armature,
and then I'll work on the shape
and gluing them all down.
Maybe it'll come together.
I like some of them
upside down.
Yeah, it does look
kind of cool.
Ugh.
The face is molded,
and now I'm gonna start
the legs and arms.
Awesome.
I decide that
I'm going to make a lion suit
and stripe it
like the Cheshire Cat.
I'm hoping that this is gonna
turn our makeup around.
I decide to do fur transfer,
so it moves the way
a human moves,
rather than just a fur suit.
So I'm taking fun fur,
sticking masking tape on it,
I shave off the fabric
that it's attached to,
and I spray glue
and stick the fur down
and pull the tape off.
And it looks like the fur
is really stuck into the fabric.
You can't have a Wicked Witch
Of The West without a broom,
so I start fabricating
the witch's broomstick.
I'm using PVC pipe
for the handle
and spiraled floral sticks
for the bristles of the broom.
I get it all painted, and,
you know, it looks really cool.
All right, guys,
30 minutes left!
Awesome!
I pop the face mold open to
go ahead and start cleaning it,
and it pulls out perfectly.
Then I go to open
the cowl mold.
I think the core is locked
inside the cowl.
Think there's an undercut
behind the ear.
It looks like when Sasha
molded the cowl,
the plaster actually went
behind the ears
and locked the core
inside the mold.
I'm so sorry.
If we don't break
the lock on this mold,
then we're screwed
for tomorrow.
It's a miracle.
Yay!
You got it?
- Yeah.
- Yay!
The mold's definitely
busted up in a lot of spots,
but it's not gonna be
a huge issue,
because we're just gonna
lay hair on the edges anyway.
That's time, guys!
End of day two,
me and Sasha are definitely
feeling a lot better.
We're ready to come in
on application day
and knock this out.
Whoo!
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab.
I have to spray-paint
our boots,
finish our ax,
and spray-paint the cloak.
While I'm doing that,
Keaghlan is cutting off
the seams of our pieces,
and then we have to apply
everything to our model.
Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
- I'm Sasha.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
So let's have you
put your outfit on first.
We put on our spandex bodysuit
that has all the Wonder hay
and the mushrooms
growing out of it,
and then cut it up so that
the hay and the mushrooms
grow out from the right places.
That's cool.
There we go.
The cowl goes on just fine,
but we notice that
the face has a little dent,
so Dina adds some cotton
so that the forehead
can go right over it
without it being dented.
That's better.
Should we fill that
or pretend it's a dent?
Dent.
We are trying to create
a really realistic Tin Woodman,
so we base him out
entirely in gray,
and then we dry-brush silver
to get a good depth.
He looks like a Tin Man.
He does.
And then we add some black
in the creases
to pop that color even more.
We start painting,
and I'm trying to follow
Jason's directions,
but he really didn't come up
with a plan
for what color
we're gonna paint this.
We're just messing
with different colors.
We're using purples and browns
and not going
in any specific order,
and it's kind of a mess.
Oh, careful!
That's a lot of yellow.
Think lion, Sash.
I don't even know
how I'm feeling.
I'm just, like, trying
to get through this.
It's just not looking great.
15 minutes, guys!
We got
two different underskirts,
and we have a full hoop skirt.
Okay.
Our wardrobe looks really cool,
except the hat doesn't have
very much space on the inside
to actually build
our spiral tornado hairstyle.
We're not gonna do the blah...
Oh, we're not gonna do it?
It won't fit under the hat.
All right, guys, it's time!
Our Witch isn't
as Wonderland-y as the rest,
so scrapping the hair
could be the wrong choice.
Coming up...
We have to re-haul
the color scheme.
The huge mash-up of color
might get us in trouble.
It's a lovely idea.
So freaky.
We can't find a makeup job.
We get to last looks,
and we only have one hour,
and the first thing I do
is make sure that our cape
has the red heart
from the Queen Of Hearts
so that the backstory
is tied into our character.
Sasha and I still have
a lot of work to do,
and I'm really worried
'cause the lion's
still really reading
kind of brown and werewolf,
so we have to majorly re-haul
the color scheme in an hour,
and that's just
not a lot of time.
This looks great.
George and I decide
to scrap the cyclone hairstyle,
but we still want her to have
some thin, wispy, witchy hair,
so I start
the hair-laying process,
while George paints
layered age effects
with light and shadow
on our model's hands.
Does that work for you?
- Should we go longer?
- Yeah.
Stella starts adding hair
to the chin,
and as she's doing that,
I'm adding Rachael's hair
to the monkey's hands.
It's real hair,
so it's awesome.
Ten minutes, everyone!
All right, guys, it's time!
Cig and I are a little worried.
Our Scarecrow's a huge mash-up
of color, which is great,
but the head gets lost
in some of the costume elements,
and that might
get us in trouble.
Welcome
to the Face Off reveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
First let's say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve
Makeup Effects Studio,
Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening, everyone.
- Hi.
- Hi, Glenn.
A big welcome back
to our three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
I missed you guys.
I'm glad to be back.
Hi, Ve.
Creature and concept designer
Mr. Neville Page.
Hello.
- Hi.
- Hello.
And Oscar-winning
makeup artist Lois Burwell.
Evening, lovelies.
Hi, Lois.
Now, next week,
Glenn, Ve, and Neville
will be competing
against each other
in a very special edition
of Face Off
called "Judge Match."
- What?
- Wow.
And they're going to have
some of the best
former Face Off contestants
to help bring
their original designs to life.
I, for one, cannot wait.
Really?
That's confidence.
Oh! Game on.
I'm frightened.
In the meantime, let's take
a look at tonight's makeups.
This week,
your spotlight challenge
was to reimagine
one of the classic characters
from The Wonderful Wizard Of Oz
as if they'd fallen down
the rabbit hole into Wonderland.
So let's take a look
at your colorful creations.
She looks great, and
she totally sells the makeup.
We're just so happy.
We created something that
we truly believed in and loved.
There's fur flying everywhere.
It's so bad.
I'm in deep trouble.
Her color
is really, really nice.
She feels like the Wicked Witch
of Wonderland onstage.
I'm so proud.
I think Rachael and I
created a Tin Woodman
that could step out
of his own film.
I'm a little bit worried,
because from where I'm standing,
I can't see any sort
of facial features,
so I know that the judges
can't see them either.
Judges, it's time
to take a closer look
at Wonderland's newest citizens.
Oh, man.
It's freaky.
It really is.
I like the way the neck
comes down
into these little goodies.
Show us shock, surprise,
and then anger.
That's great.
- Thanks.
- Goodbye.
Let's see this.
It looks like they did
a whole bunch of sculpting
and created a whole piece.
Let's see your chest.
- Show us your--
- Show us your tummy.
- There's no payoff here.
- No.
Wish more time had been spent
on the face.
I'm not really feeling good
about where we're standing.
I know the judges
don't like the makeup.
I'm not sure if this is just
out of the box and loopy enough
to fit this challenge.
Who reimagined your favorite
Oz character in Wonderland?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
Wish more time had been spent
on the face.
I'm not really feeling good
about where we're standing.
I mean, I'm hoping
we can be safe,
but I'm not sure if this is
out of the box enough
to fit this challenge.
Where are its ears?
Oh, they're in here.
I wish these were longer.
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
Can you turn sideways?
It is a gorgeous profile.
Very birdlike.
The head is kind of eggy,
though, isn't it?
Thank you.
Kneel, so we can really look
at your face.
Oh, lovely.
They've done a really good job
of maintaining symmetry.
Yeah, this whole line
right up in here
is really perfect.
- Mm-hmm.
- Thanks.
The fabrics,
although it's a clever idea,
it's too busy.
This is unfortunately
less interesting up close.
I don't even see
what they sculpted.
It's, like, laminated
over the top.
Thank you.
All right, the judges
would like to speak
with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Drew and George,
please step up.
Tell me about your character
and how you integrated
the two different tales
into this creation.
Our Wicked Witch Of The West
was flying in a tornado
and blew off course
and ended up in Wonderland,
and her features
became super exaggerated.
It feels very Wizard Of Oz,
not very Wonderland.
Can you take the hat off?
There's some great technique
going on here,
but it feels like
the makeup ends
right where the edge
of the wardrobe begins.
This makeup could have changed
into a Wonderland makeup
so easily
if you had not painted
her green.
She just doesn't address
the challenge.
I have a question
about the shape
of the top of the head.
What was the reason
behind that?
The hair was gonna
be swooped up
like a big tornado,
but anything we would have done
with the hair
would have been crushed
as soon as we put the hat on,
and you can't have a witch
without a hat.
I think you can,
and I think if you
would have kept the hair,
you would have had something.
It would have been more fun
had you turned the hair
into a heart shape or a crown.
Give her red hair,
anything like that.
It could have
told the story better.
Drew and George,
please step back.
Thank you, Lena.
Damien and Cig, please step up.
Tell us
about your character, please.
We got the Scarecrow,
and he was unstuffed
by the Wicked Witch Of The West,
and he ends up
falling into the rabbit hole.
He decides he doesn't need
a brain,
and he just embraces
the madness.
This is very clever.
Unfortunately,
you have made his face so dark,
we can't even find
a makeup job.
I think it just went amiss
because we really
cannot see him.
He's just
one big patchwork quilt.
I like the colors,
I like that it is muted,
but the biggest problem
is that the face
has no focal point.
Would you mind
taking the hat off?
And turn round.
See that wonderful metal
and how it pops out?
That's a shame that it was
buried underneath the hat,
because it's a lovely idea.
Damien and Cig,
if you'd please step down.
Stella and Dina,
please step forward.
You're so creepy.
Tell us about the concept here.
She is a Winged Monkey.
She flew down the rabbit hole
and ended up
in the Queen's property,
so the Queen decided,
"She's goofy.
I'm gonna make her
my jester."
This is the most
wonderfully realized fusion
of the two worlds.
I'm almost hypnotized
as she stares at me.
It's so freaky.
Good work.
Thank you.
Who came up with the concept
on this one?
It was kind of a joint effort.
You came up with, like,
the jester idea,
and then I came up
with having the head
be a part of the jester hat.
You found your focus
in the merging
of organic into inorganic form,
and that is
what I want to applaud.
Well, ladies, I dig the heck
out of this creepy little thing.
The color, I think,
was a really good choice.
She's devilish and mesmerizing
all at once.
Stella and Dina,
please step back.
Thank you.
All right, let's talk
to Sasha and Jason.
Tell me
about your Cowardly Lion.
When the Cowardly Lion
falls down the rabbit hole,
he is found by the Queen,
and then when she finds out
that he is cowardly,
she starts trying
to get him tough.
And he's also possessed
by the Cheshire Cat.
It might have been wiser
to have more work
been placed into the face.
It's a little bit stiff
and masklike,
rather than
a movable, living makeup.
Why didn't you seize
upon the opportunity
to bring
the Cheshire Cat's colors
and do crazy afro wig
or something?
Any giant mane.
I think we kind of still wish
he was more yellow
in order to read more lion.
Okay.
This challenge begs
for whimsical, cartoony makeups,
and then you ended up going
in a more realistic direction.
That is confounding to me.
Whose idea was this?
The concept was my idea.
It's my fault
for not speaking up
and trying to do something
more whimsical.
It's not colorful enough.
It's not the Cheshire Cat.
It's got stripes,
but they're not the right color.
To me,
this looks like Teen Wolf.
Sasha and Jason,
please step back.
Rachael and Keaghlan,
you're up.
Please tell me about
your design for this character.
We have the Tin Woodman.
He fell down the rabbit hole.
He found himself
in the Queen's Rose Garden,
and in refusing to act
as her executioner,
he realized that he had
a heart after all.
I think
it's very well executed.
I have to commend you
on presenting
super clean, finished work.
I love the colorings.
I love the little rust marks
here and there.
He's not just
a solid silver being.
It's probably one of
the nicest symmetrical makeups
that I've ever seen
on this show.
Thank you.
I really like it
from the side view.
The spiral here
and those tubes coming up,
the hint
of something industrial.
Well done, girls.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
Rachael and Keaghlan,
please step back.
Thank you.
All right, guys,
the judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you'd please head
back to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Thanks, guys.
All right, judges, before
we talk about tonight's makeups,
I just want to remind you
that you do have that special
immunity still available.
So let's start
with Stella and Dina.
I think that they nailed
the synthesis of the two worlds.
I love the way they melded
the hat out of the flesh.
What a great idea.
And it's so well-sculpted,
painted, conceived.
They've created
a very memorable makeup.
All right, how about
Rachael and Keaghlan?
They really clearly knew
how to work
with each other's weaknesses
and strengths.
I think they did
an amazing job.
The paint job was beautiful.
It looked like metal up close,
and the thing was
extremely well-sculpted.
Sculpting symmetry,
it's one
of the hardest things to do.
That's a specific skill.
All right, let's move on
to Drew and George.
I know you guys didn't care
for that witch that much,
but I really liked her.
I think they just didn't
paint her the right color.
There is some beautiful work
on here,
but to say
"It won't fit in the hat,
so we'll just have
a big, green egg for a head"?
It was a lame reason too
to say it's not a witch
without a hat.
Well, it's not a winner
without a concept, mate.
All right, let's move on
to Damien and Cig.
Really cool idea,
and then they put all
that dark fabric on the face.
If only they had applied
the idea they'd done on the back
of the head to the front.
All right, let's move on
to Sasha and Jason.
I think it was clear
that they had no direction
whatsoever.
There was nothing there
conceptually
that was stimulating,
riveting, appropriate.
It didn't reflect Wonderland
or Wizard Of Oz.
I think Jason was confused
in the concept.
And she didn't have
the courage to speak against it.
All right, judges,
have you made
your decisions then?
Yes, we're there.
Let's bring them back out.
Glenn, tell us
about tonight's top teams.
Stella and Dina,
we love the way
that you chose to fuse
the organic with the inorganic.
Keaghlan and Rachael,
your outstanding teamwork
led to a beautifully painted
and very well-balanced makeup.
All right,
which team came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
All right, Glenn,
which team came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Stella and Dina.
What a bounty
of fantastic ideas you had.
She was the perfect synthesis
of Oz and Wonderland.
Thank you.
Stella and Dina, nice work.
But as you know,
we can only have one winner.
Glenn?
The winner tonight is...
Dina.
We absolutely loved the face,
particularly the way
that the ears
flowed into the jester hat.
Congratulations.
Thank you so much.
I'm just crazy excited.
I'm just a cake decorator,
but I want to be
a makeup artist,
and I feel like
I finally proved myself.
Dina, congratulations.
You, Stella, Keaghlan, Rachael,
Drew, and George
are all safe and can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thanks, guys.
- Thank you.
Unfortunately,
that means the rest of you
are on the bottom this week.
One of you will be eliminated.
Please step forward, guys.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom teams.
Damien and Cig,
you let your concept
overwhelm
your decision-making,
which led
to an overly busy character
with no focal point.
Sasha and Jason,
this was another example
of a laundry list of choices
that led to
a completely inadequate makeup.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Jason.
Your concept and color choices
undermined the makeup
from the start.
Yeah.
Jason, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
That means,
Sasha, Damien, and Cig,
you're all safe this week
and can head
back to the makeup room.
Thanks, man.
Jason, I'm so looking forward
to what it is
you're gonna bring
to the community
of makeup arts.
Thank you so much.
Jason, it's really been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back to the
makeup room and pack up your kit.
Thank you guys.
It's been an honor to be here.
Good luck, love.
I think I'm going home
a little bit early.
I just feel like I had
a lot more to prove for myself.
It's me.
Ohh!
This was the most stressful
and intense experience
of my life,
but it was definitely worth it.
I really hope
I made my family proud.
I learned a lot,
so I'm gonna be walking
out of here
with my head held high,
and I'm gonna move on
to bigger and better things.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net