I have to tell you
that I'm really impressed.
I think it's great fun.
- Bloody Mary.
- Aah!
Previously on Face Off--
George's gory villain
brought him his first win,
and Sasha was saved
from elimination.
We've decided to use
our special immunity.
I was saved!
Nine artists remain,
and tonight, they will take on
a real American hero...
- Oh, my God!
- I love this challenge!
But some artists will stumble
on the battlefield.
I'm totally
gonna blow the save.
Somehow it's just all gone
a bit mimzy.
In the end,
only one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Welcome to Face Off.
- Congratulations on...
- Yeah.
- ...your first win finally.
- Yeah, first one.
That's some beautiful makeup.
You should be really proud
of that one.
I'm the only person
who hasn't had a top look yet.
I've been safe
and on the bottom.
It's time to kick the door in
on this competition
and say, "I'm here,
and I'm ready."
I'm hopin' to turn it around.
That is a big ship.
Yeah. So we're walking up
the ramp of a huge battleship.
- Look at those guns.
- It's incredible.
It's humongous. We're all
just itching to find out
what it is
we're gonna be doing.
A lot of secrets
in those boxes.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
Welcome to the battleship Iowa.
This colossal military marvel
served in both World War II
and the Korean War
before it was retired
by the US Navy in 1990.
It's now a public museum
right here in San Pedro.
- It's pretty cool, huh?
- Yeah.
All right,
well, let's talk about
your next spotlight challenge.
From action figures
and comic books
to animated series
and global blockbuster movies,
few brands have had the cultural
resonance and enduring appeal
of GI Joe.
- Oh, yeah!
- Yeah.
I lose it
because playing with GI Joes
was big in my kid life,
so I'm ready for this.
Celebrating its
50th anniversary this year,
the GI Joe universe features
state-of-the-art technology,
highly skilled assassins,
and an array of uniquely
talented and heroic soldiers.
But beyond all that,
Snake Eyes and Cobra Commander
are evidence
of an overlying theme
shared by
its most memorable characters--
snakes.
- Ooh.
- Hmm.
Inside these crates
lies a variety of exotic
- and even deadly snakes.
- Oh.
No.
Me and snakes are not friends.
They are creepy.
They will bite you.
And I want them
to stay away from me.
First we have
- a gaboon viper...
- Sweet.
- Oh.
- Nice.
The tiger rat snake...
- Yes.
- The hognosed snake...
Namibian coral cobra...
- What?
- Green tree python,
the Christmas tree
eyelash viper...
Now, those are cool.
The albino reticulated python,
the Brazilian rainbow boa,
- there's one more...
- Oh.
- Shut up.
- Oh, jeez.
The green anaconda.
- Oh!
- Whoa!
Oh, my God.
I think he's trying to get out.
- That is massive.
- All right,
your spotlight challenge
is to choose one of these snakes
and use it to inspire
your very own
GI Joe super soldier.
- Yes! I love this challenge!
- Cool.
Rachael, you're up first.
Green tree python.
Tiger rat snake.
The hognosed snake.
The gaboon viper.
Christmas tree eyelash viper.
Albino reticulated python.
The green anaconda.
Brazilian rainbow boa.
Namibian coral cobra.
Ugh.
Okay, guys,
I am happy to tell you
that there's
a very exciting prize
for the winner of this week's
spotlight challenge.
The winner will receive
a huge prize package
fill with special edition toys
from Hasbro's 50th anniversary
GI Joe collection.
- Awesome!
- I love toys.
I want this so bad.
I would have the most insane-o
GI Joe parties.
Like, every Sunday, come over,
let's have some battles.
All right, it's time to get
started on your designs.
Now, I've set up some Samsung
televisions at the lab,
so be sure to take
lots of pictures
with your tablets
so that you can mirror them
on the big screens
while you guys sculpt.
I'll see you later on
with my dad
- to check in on your progress.
- Thank you.
Bye.
What's up, dude?
An anaconda is the embodiment
of the super soldier.
It's just a solid tube
of muscle,
and I want to bring that
into my character.
So my character
is Nick Strangle--
code name "Manaconda."
You can just drop him off
in the jungle
and he'll kill everyone.
I chose the green tree python.
My super soldier
is the jungle assassin
who works for Cobra Commander.
He is a green tree python
hybrid,
and I am thinking of
incorporating the scales,
a really wicked green color,
and these unusual
heat-seeking organs
that are all down the face.
I picked the Christmas tree
eyelash viper
because it has scales
that look like eyelashes.
I'm gonna do this
female ninja-esque assassin,
and her code name is "Lashes."
I chose
the Namibian coral cobra.
Looking at the snake,
I noticed that
the scales on the head
look more like armor,
so my character is
this motorcycle chick
who wears this padded
motorcycle outfit
that looks like body armor.
I think I'm gonna stick with
the cobra theme
and make her
one of the bad guys.
All right, everybody,
let's head it back to the lab.
We have six and a half hours
in the lab
and I'm so excited
to start this.
But first, we have to
pick our models.
By the time it's my turn,
all the females get taken
and my concept is
a female character.
So I'm dumbfounded.
I wasn't even considering
male body types or anything.
I see Matt and pick him.
You know, I'm just
gonna go from there.
I'm gonna need to do
some major rethinking.
We get in the lab,
and we have Samsung TV monitors
that mirror what we have
on our tablets.
So it's gonna
help me out a lot.
My super soldier is
a snake-human hybrid,
who used to be human and a Joe,
but was bound by Cobra and
injected with gaboon viper DNA,
and he's now an assassin
for Cobra Commander.
My snake is
the albino reticulated python,
and I want to make
a femme fatale character.
I want her to be transitioning
from a human anatomy
into snake.
I don't really know
the GI Joe world,
because I was a Barbie girl,
so I'm nervous
about this challenge,
but I'm hoping
that I can make it work.
Since the judges gave me
the second chance,
I want to do something
really awesome,
and I want to get a win.
I picked the hognosed snake.
The hognosed snakes
use their snouts
to dig in the dirt.
So I'm making a ninja
that digs holes in the dirt
and jumps out of the holes
and attacks.
I'm not doing a full face,
I'm doing pieces.
I want to make
something different
than what everybody else
is doing
because I want to stand out
from the rest of the makeup.
So rather than
a snake-human hybrid,
I decide to design
a human super soldier
who has used body modification
to become more reptilian
or snakelike.
Instead of
a full facial appliance,
I'm thinking I'll do
small facial prosthetics
and snake scale tattoos
on the neck and face.
I end up with
the Brazilian rainbow boa.
And in GI Joe,
the female characters
are portrayed as really sexy,
strong types,
so I'm gonna make
a super-sexy sniper snake.
My snake has a lot
of consistent scaling,
and they're all pretty much
the same size.
So I grab a popsicle stick
and I carve it down
to the shape of the scale.
And I start, one by one,
putting all the scales in.
My boyfriend, Michael,
is an action figure collector,
so I really want to win
this prize for him.
I block out my forms,
but it's really hard
to make a snake
with this strange nose shape.
It just-- Everything I keep doing
looks so stupid.
It's looking like a duck
or a pig.
And I'm just having
a lot of problems.
_
So I have to ask everyone
for help.
More, like, sleeker or slimmer.
You might want to bring it
all the way back here.
This line should come up.
I tried that.
It looks so weird.
I'm really lost at this moment.
I can't figure this out at all.
It's a complete disaster.
And it would be so bad
to go home
right after they saved me.
Coming up...
You really set a challenge out
for yourself.
Am I making
the right choice here?
Like nothing.
All of your choices
are perfect.
Everything I keep doing
looks so stupid.
It's day 1 of our GI Joe
super soldier challenge,
and I'm having a lot of problems
making a snake
with this strange nose shape.
That looks so weird.
I just keep pushing clay around
and I'm just having
a lot of problems.
I'm really lost at this moment.
I can't figure this out at all.
- Hey, guys.
- Hello.
Dad and I are here
to check in on you.
- How are ya?
- Hey, guys.
- What did you pick today?
- I picked the hognose.
He has, like, a pig nose
and the worst problem right now
is he--
he looks like a duck.
- I need a little bit of help.
- It looks like,
on the end of his nose here, it
kind of comes up a little bit.
- Yeah.
- That you don't have here.
Here you're all rounded off.
You need to add that on there.
Okay. Oh, that's cool.
That looks really cool.
And the snakes--
their look doesn't come out.
- You need to take this down.
- Yeah.
- So Mr. Westmore helps a lot...
- Good luck.
Thank you.
But I've lost a lot of time,
and I'm gonna have to sculpt
a little faster to catch up.
So I got the Christmas tree
eyelash viper.
Originally, I wanted to do
a female,
but I have a male model,
so now I'm going to do
a ninja assassin
that was part of
the Naga ninja clan
I like your sculpture.
Are you gonna have contacts on
underneath?
I was gonna see if I could
maybe put this over
- the vacuform.
- Put a light haze
on the inside of your plastic
and then paint their eyes black
behind it.
Yeah.
So I have
the green tree python,
and he has these fantastic
little, like, heat sensors,
so I'm definitely putting those
into my sculpt.
The side thing is so unique
to your snake.
- Yeah.
- Don't stop these here.
- I would keep going with this...
- Okay.
...because that'll just overlay
on the cowl anyways
when you go to put it on.
Instead of doing
a human-snake hybrid,
I'm doing a human who has used
the art of body modification
to change their features
to look more snakelike.
What your whole project is
going to boil down to
is a painting,
because you don't have
a lot more going on here.
You've really set a challenge
out for yourself.
- Right.
- Good luck.
Thank you very much.
Everybody else is sculpting
these massive
human-snake hybrids.
And I'm the only artist
who's sculpting
these small, delicate
facial pieces.
It's a little scary,
and I'm gonna take that risk,
but I'm thinking, am I making
the right choice here?
Her name is Lady Reticula.
She's an assassin.
And I really like the vents
that go around the mouth,
so I wanted to incorporate
that idea on the face.
Mm-hmm. You need to bring
more snake into it.
- Mm-hmm.
- And you've got eyes here
in the front,
as opposed to out here.
Yeah, okay.
All right, everybody,
we're heading out.
- It's looking good.
- Bye, guys. Thank you.
- Looking good.
- Thank you.
So I finish sculpting the face,
and I get ready to mold it.
I want to get this face molded
by the end of the day
so I can match it up
to the cowl
and hopefully
even pre-paint it.
And I'm feeling pretty good
right now.
I really like my design so far.
30 minutes, guys.
At the end of day one,
I'm worried
after hearing
Mr. Westmore say
that "I don't
see snake enough,"
I mean, that's one of the
biggest parts of the challenge
is your snake species.
Every second I can, I'm looking
back and forth at the snake
and trying to find more
attributes of the snake
to pull into my makeup.
All right, it's time,
everybody.
I've never done GI Joes
or snakes,
and I'm really hoping that
I can dream about my character
and get a little bit
of inspiration overnight.
- Whoo.
- Yay!
Whoo!
It's day 2
of our GI Joe challenge
and we have nine and a half
hours in the lab.
And since I didn't get
a female model,
that really threw me off
a little bit.
But I was able to sleep
on my concept,
and I get the idea
that it would be really cool
if he had these snake heads
as shoulder armor.
Since I have a clear direction,
now I'm just excited.
I'm back in the game, and I'm
ready to get this stuff done.
You're doing the whole cowl
like that, too?
- Yeah.
- Holy crap, girl.
For my cowl, I want to sculpt
individual scales.
I know that I've done
something like this before,
but I'm hoping that if I
paint it completely different
this isn't just gonna be
a repeat of my cat owl.
I'm scrapping my cowl
and just doing a wig.
There's just not enough time
for me to make a cowl,
so I decide to go with
a strawberry blonde wig,
'cause I want to tie the idea
of her being albino
into the makeup.
I'm gonna spray a lot of it
white and leave,
- like, the tips yellow.
- I love it.
After I spend
a good amount of time
finishing up the face sculpt,
I get to work sculpting out
my helmet cowl,
and then I get
totally surprised...
- Hey...
- Hi.
_
What's that?
Oh, my God.
_
Okay.
I find out
that my model is sick,
and now I'll be getting
a new model
who has a much smaller face.
And my only choices
at this point
are resculpt the face
or take a piece that's made
for someone else's face
and try to make it fit.
Okay.
I don't know
what I'm going to do.
Whatever.
It's day two in the lab,
and I'll be getting a new model
who has a much smaller face,
and I'm a little bit uneasy
about how the prosthetic
is going to fit her.
I'm not gonna spend a whole day
resculpting a face.
So hopefully, it'll fit.
I don't have time
to resculpt the face
because I need to get
my helmet finished.
So I have to carry on.
There's no other choice.
An anaconda is just so thick
and solid,
so I know that I want to have
certain muscles accentuated
on my character,
so I need to design and
fabricate an entire bodysuit.
So I sketch out the specific
muscles that I want
on couch foam.
Once I get all my patterns
cut out,
I go to the belt sander
and I start refining them
and smoothing them out.
For never having done
a muscle suit before,
I think it came out
pretty cool.
Do you wanna go to the beach?
Like nothing.
I'm working on the cowl
and I'm not liking
where this sculpt is at all.
But I don't have a lot of time,
and I really need
to get this cowl molded
or I'm not gonna have anything
for tomorrow.
One of my most important
features of the snake
is his fangs.
So I find a set of these
really big, nasty ogre dentures
and clip
all the extra teeth off,
and then I paint it
with alcohol colors
and clear coat with
a Kryolan clear nail polish
just to keep that shine.
I think they're reading
like snake teeth perfectly.
So I finish the cowl
and I have to make a visor
for it.
So I take these round forms
and then I sculpt the visor
shape onto the round form
and vacuform it.
Then I will be using
that plastic piece
as the visor to my helmet.
One hour!
So you're just gonna have two?
- Oh, no. He's gonna have ten.
- Oh, yeah, you got 'em all.
So I get this idea
to make claws.
The claws are sort of
an extension
of the tiger rat snake's bite.
And I take a razor blade,
and I start carving off
shavings of it
and then spray-paint them
with this really nice
metallic spray paint.
And they end up looking like
brushed steel,
and they look really cool.
I'm making some scales.
My character has exposed hands,
so I do need scales
to put on the hands.
So I just make a flat mold
of some scales
that I can kind of
piece together however I want.
- What's that time say?
- 15.
I'm feeling
a little frustrated.
I got both of my molds done, but
I feel like I rushed the cowl.
That time, guys!
I'm worried about application
tomorrow,
because I am not fond
of the things that I've done.
So now it's all about
the paint job.
- Whoo!
- ♪ The Manaconda ♪
So it's application day, and we
have four hours in the lab
and one hour last looks.
I'm just having a blast here,
and I just want to win
the 50th anniversary
GI Joe set so bad.
How'd your pieces come out,
Rachael?
My cowl is a little messed up.
- Here they come.
- What up, dude?
So I got the albino python.
I gotta make sure
everything fits.
All right.
First thing I do is
fit my pieces on my new model.
And now, I gotta find noseholes
for you.
It's way too big for her face.
It goes all the way back
into her hairline.
Her bottom lip and chin
don't fit into the appliance.
I have to figure out how
I'm going to make it work.
Chin down.
Tilt your head back
a little bit. Okay.
I get the face and the cowl on,
and it's just not lining up.
I'm so nervous that
I'm totally gonna blow the save.
This is not turning out good.
_
This entire makeup rests
on application.
It has to be perfect.
And my approach to this paint
job is all spatterwork.
Spatter creates
a really fine mist
of thin, translucent colors,
and it's a very realistic,
believable way to paint skin.
What am I missing?
Yellow.
Okay, that's good.
_
I finally fixed the face,
but the cowl's too big on her.
So I'm not sure
what I'm gonna do.
_
- Yours is looking really cool.
- Thanks.
It's really starting to look
like an action figure.
The coolest part about my snake
is the iridescent sheen
the scales give off
when the light hits it.
So I'm drybrushing pearl
onto the scales.
She's really coming to life.
I think the biggest thing
that I'm freaking out about
- is the transition right now.
- Yeah.
It's just really muddy.
I really don't like this cowl.
All I can see is green.
So I'm a little bit worried
about how I'm gonna break it up.
Don't go white.
Don't do a sharp line.
I hope that I can pull it out
with my paint job.
- Spatter over it...
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- To make it blend in more.
- Yeah.
Ten minutes, guys!
_
As I'm looking
at my overall piece,
I'm a little nervous
that I didn't push the snake
far enough.
All right, guys, it's time!
It's really missing something,
and I'm not really sure what.
I hope that that's not something
that's gonna send me home.
Coming up...
- I hate this headpiece.
- I'm still a little nervous
that they're gonna be like,
"What the fuck is that?"
- It doesn't work.
- This idea is brilliant.
Okay.
We have one hour in last looks,
and I hate this headpiece
so much.
It doesn't fit on her head.
So the first thing I do
is throw this helmet away
and style her hair.
This could be
the biggest mistake.
I just need to get
the rest of your tattoos on
and get your gloves made
and throw your hair up.
Okay.
I'm looking at my model's hair,
and I realize that
it's balding on the top,
so I decide to incorporate
some white hair
to give it more volume.
But at this point,
I really don't know
if I like this character
at all.
What do you think
about the eyes?
I'm looking at the eyes,
and I'm not sure if I like them
- or if I don't like them.
- I think
- he looks better with 'em in.
- Mm.
I'm liking the way
the tattoos are coming along.
They have that faded,
self-applied look
that I really want.
Ten minutes, guys.
Guys, that's time!
Any good?
My makeup is
drastically different
than everybody else's.
I'm still a little nervous
that they're gonna be like,
"What the fuck is this?"
I need a top look
to show the judges
that I have what it takes
to win.
Welcome to
the Face Off reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
Let's say hello
to our talented judges--
owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick...
- Good evening, guys.
- Hi, Glenn.
Oscar-winning makeup artist,
Lois Burwell...
- Evening, all.
- Hi, Lois.
Creature and concept designer,
Neville Page...
- Hello, everyone.
- Hello.
All right, guys, this week,
your spotlight challenge
was to choose a snake
and use it as inspiration
for your very own
GI Joe super soldier.
And tonight's winner
will receive
a prize package filled
with special edition toys
from Hasbro's 50th anniversary
GI Joe collection.
All right, let's take a look
at your serpent soldiers.
I think he looks awesome.
He looks like an action figure.
I created something
really cool.
There's no way to predict
what the judges are thinking.
But I feel really good
about this makeup.
I'm pleased with the amount
of work I got done,
but I'm not happy
with my super soldier.
It reads like snake up close,
and it reads like snake
from far away.
I'm really proud of him,
and I think he looks
like a complete badass.
It looks cool.
It reads super soldier,
and he looks like a GI Joe.
She's super sexy.
She looks like a snake,
and she's just, like,
everything I wanted her to be.
This whole challenge
was one disaster after another.
So I just hope
that this is enough
to keep me at least safe.
It's not my best work.
And it would be so bad
to go home
right after they saved me.
She's not as imposing
as I would have liked her to be,
so I'm really just kind of
holding my breath on this one.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look at our soldiers?
Do you think
really great symmetry
- for something this size?
- Yes.
And look at the lovely makeup
he's done on the arms.
Yeah, yeah.
The color combination, too,
is very action figure.
It's really smart.
No biting.
The color is
pretty spectacular.
Yes, it is.
I really think it is
a refreshing change.
It's got all the components.
It's just lacking a good sense
of primary form.
_
I'm super disappointed,
because I regret some of
the sculptural choices I made.
His head feels a bit bulbous,
- and it doesn't feel like a snake.
- Yeah.
And it'll suck to go home for
something I'm not happy with.
Who made your favorite
GI Joe snake soldier?
Tell us on Twitter using
#FaceOff.
His head feels baboon-ish,
the way
it comes into the muzzle.
- It doesn't feel like a snake.
- Yeah.
I'm super disappointed in
some of the choices I've made.
So I'm just hoping to be safe.
- I'm glad we're seeing fangs.
- Yes.
That's really pretty. I love
this treatment of the neck.
It looks better up close,
doesn't it?
Yeah.
_
Look at the iridescence
coming through.
- Yeah.
- It just gives it some life.
The precision and layout
of these scales
is incredible.
This is a female character,
and I like how small
the shapes are.
- Quite large scale patterns.
- Yes.
The scales feel
more feather-like.
There's something about it
that reminds me of the owl
she'd sculpted.
There's some
nice coloring in here.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
There's something very matte
and dead about the color choices.
The nose is the worst part,
because it doesn't feel
reptilian.
Okay, the judges have scored
your creations.
So let's find out
what they thought.
Stella.
George.
Damien.
Congratulations,
because you are safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Good luck, guys.
The rest of you were
the best and the worst.
The judges would now like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Cig, you're up.
Tell us about your character
and how you integrated
the elements of your viper.
I picked the Christmas tree
eyelash viper.
This is the last remaining
Naga ninja.
And I just wanted
to make something
that I would want to own
as an action figure.
I'll take two,
one to keep in the package
- and one to play with.
- Awesome.
This is the quintessence
of the bold graphic
action figure style.
Really knocked this one
out of the park, man.
- Impressive.
- Thank you.
I like the epaulets
particularly.
I like the color choices, too.
Well done.
- Thank you.
- The form development
on the face is so good
around the cheekbones,
the chin.
- It's beautiful.
- Thank you guys so much.
Cig, you can step down.
Way awesome, dude.
Rachael.
Tell us about your snake
and the makeup.
I chose the green tree python,
so my makeup is based off
combining the snake
with a human.
And how do you think you did
this week?
I don't think my forms
are very good,
and I don't think I did myself
any favors with my paint.
- I agree with you.
- Mm-hmm.
There is something peculiar
about the shape,
because here is too large
and here is too saggy.
Particularly in overall form,
it does get a bit bulbous.
And with regard to the scales,
they're so random.
It's not great.
Okay.
I think the time
that you allowed yourself
on the main forms was cut off
because you were rushing
to get to those scales.
That can never be at the cost
of the primary form.
- Mm-hmm.
- And the paint job
is very blocky because you
didn't give yourself time
to transition the colors.
Rachael, thank you.
You can step down.
Thanks.
All right, let's talk to Dina.
So tell us about the snake
that you got and the design.
I chose
the Brazilian rainbow boa.
She's a Cobra soldier
who is a lead sniper.
Your choices are perfect.
The head shape
and your secondary forms
are so well-balanced,
and the scales are
incredibly well-laid-out.
I think you've done
an amazing job.
You've reached
a phenomenal equilibrium
between the action figure
aesthetic
and a prosthetic makeup
that would work onscreen.
It's an astounding amount
of work,
extraordinarily well done.
And you should be very pleased.
Thank you.
Dina, thank you very much.
_
Drew, please step up.
Drew, tell us about
your character, would you?
I had the tiger rat snake,
so I chose to go with
a more human character
who's an assassin for hire.
He's used body modification
to make himself more like
the tiger rat snake.
This idea of going with
a minimal,
realistic silicone makeup
was brilliant.
You've created a prosthetic
that could very much, on film,
bring one of these characters
to life.
Thank you.
Can you please
take his hood off?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
I really like this,
and well done on the skin tone.
I particularly like the tattoo
pattern coming down here.
Excellent idea.
Very nice.
- Thank you.
- I'm so pleased
that you did something
completely different.
It's intelligent,
and it's risky.
- So congratulations.
- Thank you very much.
Drew, you can head back.
Drew.
Sasha, you're next.
So please tell us
about your snake.
I chose the hognosed snake
because they have
these funny noses that stick up
and they use them
to dig in dirt.
But I ended up having problems
with the shape of the nose,
and it just threw me off
from that point.
I agree with you.
It's disappointing.
Your owl that you did
the other week
was coming back into this
because the sculpt of the scales
look feather-ish.
The overall shape of the head
is a bit too simple.
It's just
this basic round head.
Sorry.
Sasha, you can head back.
Keaghlan, please come forward.
Tell us about the snake
that you got
and the resulting character
you've designed.
I chose
the albino reticulated python.
Her name is Scarlet.
She was kidnapped
and experimented on
to become a Cobra.
I get what
you were shooting for,
but it feels more like
a feline.
You diluted the snake forms
and details where
it's so less snakelike.
Okay.
You needed a contrast.
You need grays in there
to give depth.
It's just all gone a bit mimzy.
There's nothing punchy
about it.
Keaghlan, you can step down.
Thank you.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
- while they deliberate.
- Thank you.
All right, judges, so let's talk
about tonight's makeups.
Why don't we start with
the looks you like the most?
How about Cig?
This could not have been
better fit
for this particular challenge.
- I like the colors, the form.
- This is a character
that ultimately would be
an action figure.
Let's move on to Dina.
The forms were nuanced.
The detailing was superb.
One of the things I enjoyed
was that translucency.
I really thought
it was wonderful.
Everything highlights
and accentuates
and brings you right back
to the gorgeous makeup.
All right,
let's move on to Drew.
It's just
such a wonderful change.
I love the idea
of the implants on the cheeks.
And I love the tattooing.
When they make these types
of brave decisions
to go against
what everyone else is doing
and present their own makeup,
it defines "Artist"
on this show.
All right, why don't we talk
about the looks
you liked the least?
How about Rachael?
I think that
the overall view of it,
it was like a deflated balloon.
The shape was so bulbous,
and even the scales weren't done
with accuracy or definition.
All right,
let's move on to Sasha,
- who you guys had just saved.
- We did.
And I'm very disappointed
with this makeup.
There's a few things about it
that are good,
but she buried them under
heavy-handed detailing
- in the sculpt.
- The scales
looked like feathers
it really did remind me
of her owl.
All right, let's move on
to Keaghlan.
It doesn't feel like a snake.
It doesn't feel like a soldier.
- And the colors are awful.
- It's not a snakelike nose.
It feels more feline.
All right then, judges,
have you made your decisions?
Tough one, but yes.
Okay, let's bring 'em back out.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about tonight's top looks.
Cig, your sculpture
was incredibly symmetrical.
And we really dug that you took
such an action figure approach
to the design.
Dina, we loved how balanced
all of the proportions were
and the incredible detail
in both the sculpture
and paintwork.
Drew, this makeup told
a believable story,
and it felt very current
in the way
that you interpret a cartoon
character for the big screen.
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
- Dina.
- Oh, really?
Between the detailed sculpture
and paintwork,
this creature was jaw-droppingly
beautiful on every level.
What a huge comeback.
Thank you so much.
Dina, congratulations.
You have won
the Hasbro 50th anniversary
GI Joe toy collection.
Aah! Oh, my God!
I'm so excited!
I won a really awesome prize
that I want to give
to my boyfriend.
I feel like I'm finally
on track,
and I can't even describe
how good that feels.
Hopefully, I can keep up
the momentum.
Dina, nice work.
You, Cig, and Drew can all
head back to the makeup room.
I love you.
Good luck.
Unfortunately,
that means the rest of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Rachael, the sculptural forms
of your head went awry,
but we're glad that you knew
where things went wrong.
Sasha, despite decent paintwork
here and there,
the forms of the head
and the profile
were really undercooked.
Keaghlan, your character
concept wasn't bad,
but the colors became muddy,
and ultimately,
it just didn't read snake.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home tonight
is...
Keaghlan.
It came down to two things--
She didn't look like a snake,
and the most GI Joe thing
about her was her outfit.
Keaghlan, I'm so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
That means, Rachael and Sasha,
you both are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
I'm gonna miss you.
Keaghlan, don't let this
make you feel down.
Use this as a platform
to improve.
We look forward
to seeing you again.
Thank you so much
for the opportunity.
It's been the most amazing
experience of my life,
and I'll never forget it.
Keaghlan, it's been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- Thank you.
- Good luck, Keaghlan.
- Bye, Keaghlan.
I'm really proud of every
single one of the makeups
that I got to do.
- Oh, God.
- Who?
- It was Keaghlan.
- Oh, my God.
Being here has made me
just love makeup even more.
I came here to show the world
what I can do,
and I did exactly that.
- It's not the end.
- Oh, no.
It's just the beginning.
At the end of the day,
what matters to me is the love
and the heart
that I put into my art.
If people can walk away
with a piece of that,
then I'm happy.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net