It is amazing.
You've come up with something
that is triumphant.
Previously on Face Off...
Dina's graceful goddess
wowed the judges...
Thank you.
...and Sasha was sent home.
Now only five artists remain,
and tonight,
Mother Nature meets fantasy
in an epic challenge...
Sounds easy, right?
No.
And for some,
the results are disastrous.
Do you really need that?
There's no room for error.
Hmm.
What happened?
I'm feeling really frustrated.
This is
a very beautiful makeup.
It just doesn't
get there for me.
In the end,
only one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- Good morning.
- How's it going?
All right.
I was in the bottom again.
Yay!
Doesn't that feel so good?
No.
Being in the bottom last time
was kind of a bummer.
I thought I did a really
good job with the makeup,
but at least I'm still here,
so that's all that counts.
Final five.
Top five is the way
I like to see it.
- Yeah, that's even better.
- Yes.
The next challenge,
I really have to just bring
everything I've got.
It would be awesome
if we made it to the finale.
That would be amazing.
I made it to the final five,
which feels incredible.
I didn't think I would
make it this far.
The person who got me
into makeup art
is Anthony Kosar,
the season four champion.
I should probably thank Anthony
for pushing me to come here.
I would be proud to go
to the finale with you, Dina.
Same here.
Oh, my God.
Holy fuck.
This looks terrible.
We arrive at Universal Studios,
and there's a plane torn
in three parts,
smoke blowing
all over the place,
destroyed houses.
I'm thinking
it's postapocalyptic.
I have no idea what
this challenge is gonna be.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
Welcome to
the Universal Studios back lot.
This plane is an actual 747,
and the set around us
was built for Steven Spielberg's
War Of The Worlds.
- Awesome.
- That's amazing.
I'll tell you
why we're here in a bit,
but first, let's talk about
your next spotlight challenge.
Let me transport you
to the fantastical world
of a playful,
mischievous creature
that has appeared
in audience favorites
like Peter Pan, Harry Potter,
and True Blood.
Fairies.
Fairies?
Uh, okay.
Everything I make is oozy
and snotty and gross,
so my excitement level
definitely crashed.
Some believe that fairies
are beautiful spirits
associated
with the four major elements.
Fire, water, earth, and air.
So your spotlight challenge
is to create
your own beautiful
elemental fairy.
Nice.
Sounds pretty easy, right?
No.
Yeah, well, of course it's not.
In this case,
Mother Nature has gone awry,
unleashing her elemental power
and destroying everything
in her path.
Spread
throughout this plane wreck
are five monitors,
each one featuring
a disaster scenario
caused by Mother Nature's
unparalleled power.
You'll each choose one of them
and create a beautiful fairy
born from its destruction.
All right.
I've never made
anything pretty before,
and to incorporate disaster
into a pretty makeup,
that scares the hell out of me.
On my go,
I want you to run
into the wreck
and choose
one of the disasters.
Then you can work
on your sketches
before heading back to the lab
to get started.
I'll come by later on
with my dad
to check in
and see how you're doing.
All right, good luck.
Ready,
set,
go!
Aah!
What's that one?
It's avalanche.
Ooh.
Yeah.
Wildfire.
I pick earthquake
for my natural disaster.
So I decide she lives
under the crust of the Earth,
and she comes out
whenever there's an earthquake
to fix all the damage
that the earthquake has caused.
I'm gonna build up
one of the model's shoulders
and have it all cracked off,
so she can sort of lift it
a little,
and it'll look like
a fault line.
I might paint her
in, like, browns and tans
and then bright red,
glowing lava in the cracks,
but, honestly, this is so far
out of my realm,
I'm just guessing
at this point.
I'm making a wildfire fairy.
Her job is to spread fire
and then inspire regrowth.
The top part of her's on fire,
but the bottom is leaves
and grass and flowers.
I'm not sure
how I'm going to achieve this,
but the only thing
I can think of
is to sculpt flames on her
somehow.
My natural disaster is flood,
and my concept is that the flood
washed away the land,
and this new fairy
was born from it.
She's bringing elements
from the flooded land
back to life.
Floodwater is brown,
but I don't want to just cover
her head to toe in mud.
I also want to bring some greens
and blues into it
to brighten it up a bit.
My beautiful fairy
uses her magic
to clean up the oil spill.
She is doused with oil.
She's got rocky, crystalline
formations on her body
to represent the Earth.
It's gonna look like
a high-fashion runway piece.
My concept is, this fairy
got caught up in an avalanche.
She almost froze to death,
but her fairy magic
kept her alive,
and now she's
like an ice fairy.
I have never done
a beauty makeup,
so that's got me worried.
But then I start thinking
of this
more as, like,
a beautiful piece of art,
rather than a beautiful makeup,
and that's kind of helping me.
I'm drawing these big ice wings
and ice spires coming
off her shoulders and her head,
and I think it looks
pretty cool.
Hey, everyone,
let's go back to the lab!
What'd everybody get?
- Earthquake.
- Avalanche.
- Wildfire.
- Flood.
Awesome.
We get back to the lab,
and we have six hours.
We pick our models,
and the first thing
I start working on
is the face sculpt.
I need to focus on the nose,
the chin,
and at the same time,
I start working
on my chest and shoulder piece.
I'm a little worried
about this design.
I don't know
if what I want it to look like
is beautiful.
I get right to work
on the cowl,
and I'm drawing inspiration
from, like, glaciers
and how they form,
and it's very hard edges
and jagged lines,
so I'm trying to sculpt
this cowl and shoulder piece
that resembles ice spires
growing out of someone's body.
Hey, guys, we're here
to check in on you.
Hi there.
All right, so tell us
about your fairy.
Okay, so my fairy rises
through an oil spill
in the ocean.
So she's going to be
very sandy and rocky,
and these rocky elements
enhance her brow
and her cheekbones.
You might even be able
to extend the nose
just a little bit more
to give a fairy look to it.
Yeah, I thought about giving
her slight upturn at the end.
- That's good too.
- Yeah.
- Very good.
- All right.
I heard you guys
have been taking selfies.
- Oh, yeah.
- We need to take one.
I think--
Is this your first selfie?
I think so.
This is my dad's
first selfie, everybody.
Ready?
Nice.
Thanks, guys.
First one, nice, dad.
You did it.
Good job.
It was a good one.
She's kind of like
an ice fairy.
Okay, that's what
this is gonna be then.
This is ice, all right.
What's your thought
with the makeup now?
Well, I've never done
a beauty makeup before.
You know, the thing is, listen,
you know how to shade
and whatever.
I did a whole beauty makeup
with an airbrush one time,
and you can do that.
Just remember to keep
everything soft,
- and you'll be fine.
- Okay.
I want to do, like,
very delicate flames
around the face.
And then the cowl
is gonna be like
wind is blowing
the flame backwards.
Great. You know,
what's gonna help to make it
is your painting.
I wouldn't be concerned
so much with black,
because this is supposed
to be a really beautiful makeup,
and getting too much black
into it
- would be a problem.
- Okay.
I'm thinking of all the things
that you would find
in, like, a flooded river area.
I know this is probably crazy.
I was thinking about covering
her face in sand.
But it has to be very subtle.
They actually have
in the supplies here
- gelatin crystals.
- In the back room.
In the back room
that you could use for that.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Excellent.
- Cool.
Did you get it?
I got earthquake.
She is all cracked up.
This is gonna be a chest piece
over her heart.
Now, with the face here,
it's so thin in areas,
I don't know if foam latex
would go that thin.
Okay.
You might need to do that
in silicone
if you're gonna go
with the whole face like that.
And then in here,
you're gonna paint...
Yeah, this is
all gonna be reds and yellows
to make it look
like the Earth blood,
the magma, and stuff like that.
Do you really need that?
It's going to look like
somebody sliced your fairy open.
Yeah, like, bloody.
Hearing Mr. Westmore tell me
that there are things
that won't work with my makeup
stresses me out.
Your whole fairy
has to be attractive.
We're down to the final five,
and there's no room for error.
I can't make a mistake,
or I'm gonna go home.
Coming up...
I'm gonna have to come up
with another strategy.
I'm feeling really frustrated.
Aw, come on!
It's not very inventive.
It's absolutely stunning.
This is all gonna be reds
and yellows.
Your whole fairy
has to be attractive.
It's day one of
our elemental fairy challenge,
and Mr. Westmore's telling me
there are things that won't work
with my makeup,
and that's very stressful.
- It's going to look like--
- Gore?
- Gore, muscle.
- Horror, yeah.
It could be blood or something.
- Gotcha.
- Yeah.
Do you think
it would be a better idea
to just stick
with Earth colors?
I think so.
I need his advice.
I'm really stuck at this point.
All right, so to recap,
we got nose, chin, nix the red.
And also, I think your cheeks
might be able to use
a little bit more...
- The-- the--
- Yeah, yeah.
- Can I get a picture of that?
- Yeah.
- Oh, you're beautiful.
- Ah.
Everybody's got a great
direction in this challenge.
Keep it up.
- Thank you, guys.
- Good job, guys.
- Bye-bye.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
So after the walk-through,
I completely scrap
the whole magma concept.
And now she's gonna be
mossy and green
in all the cracks to show
rebirth and regrowth.
Plus, she's gonna have
a happy Mr. Westmore smile.
He does have
some good apple cheeks, right?
He actually invented
apple cheeks.
Today, I have to figure out
how I'm gonna create
this oily look
for the body make-up.
So I decide
to do some experimenting.
I start by mixing
powdered gelatin, glycerin,
sorbitol,
and zinc oxide powder.
I think this is working
really well.
It's really looking
like crude oil.
I get it all melted up
in the microwave
and start painting it
on my mannequin
and making these really cool
drips and runs and smears.
_
- Uh-huh.
- Smart.
After I finish sculpting
the cowl for my flood fairy,
I start working
on some blender pieces.
I'm trying to think
of things that
would be mixed up
in that water--
sand and pebbles
and twigs and bark.
I'm trying to incorporate
all of those things
into my makeup.
So I get my face
to a good place,
and now I'm ready to mold.
I'm gonna be casting my face
out of silicone,
and silicone's kind of finicky,
so I need to make sure
that I make
the best mold possible.
The flashing overflow area
that I build up
has to be perfectly smooth
so that when the mold
is actually opened,
it all comes out nicely
rather than catching
on textured areas and ripping.
I'm ready to mold the face,
and I know that molding this
will be difficult
because of all of the shapes
in the flames,
but I figure
if I'm really careful,
it should look pretty good.
Hmm.
I may need to reengineer this.
Halfway through the application
of the gelatin
on this mannequin,
I realize that
this is gonna become a mess.
Hey, guys, that's time.
There's gonna
be logistical problems
with my model living
in this makeup for a few hours,
like going to the bathroom,
being comfortable,
being able to sit.
This really sucks,
because now I'm gonna have to
come up with another strategy.
Yes!
Today's the second day
of our fairy challenge,
and we have 9 1/2 hours.
Yeah, that broke.
None of the flames
that I sculpted on the face
filled with foam,
so now I have to bake it
again overnight.
I don't even know
how to rescue that.
I'm starting
to like this character
a lot more than I thought,
being a fairy challenge.
And I've always wanted to do
and ice makeup,
so it's looking pretty cool.
Since I need to fabricate wings,
I don't want to spend
too much time
finishing out the details
on either sculpt.
I'm gonna do these wings that
are big and spire-y and all.
Kind of heat-form them
a little bit,
so it looks like ice
and probably airbrush
on top of them.
Beautiful.
I realize that I can't work
on the friggin' bodysuit again
until application day,
because I have to have wings,
otherwise, my makeup's
not gonna read as a fairy.
So I find a sheer fabric,
and it looks
like dragonfly's wings,
which is exactly what I want,
and I see
these peacock feathers,
and I attach them to
this sheer, iridescent fabric,
and they look beautiful.
The issues with the face
sculpt and mold means I know
I'm gonna have even bigger
issues with the cowl sculpt.
_
I'm making bigger flames,
much bigger than the ones
that are on the face,
because I have to match
the design,
and I don't have time
to change the whole concept.
_
So I cross my fingers,
and I hope for the best.
One thing I do know
about fairies
is that they're
supposed to have wings,
so I find foam noodle.
I take a heat gun,
and I scrunch it up
with my hands,
so it looks like bark,
and then I find
these giant banana leaves.
So I'm just gonna glue
those all together
and hope it doesn't
look like shit.
I really have to get
this mold open
and cleaned out today.
Otherwise, I'm going to have
to run in poly foam
on application day,
and I've never run a cowl
in poly foam before,
so the idea terrifies me.
Don't break.
There's all this clay stuck
in all of the flame points,
and I'm freaking out,
'cause I can't get the clay out.
And that's exactly
one of the things
I was worried about
with this mold.
Do you need another hand?
Are you good?
I'm just
gonna power-wash it.
Okay.
I've got to go outside
and spray it with the hose,
which I don't want to do,
because I'm going to end up
with a wet mold,
and I could get all sorts
of air pockets.
Aw, come on!
There's just, like,
two that won't come out.
I don't know if I'm gonna
pull this together.
Aw, come on!
It's day two in the lab,
and I'm having
a really hard time
cleaning out my mold.
That won't come out.
I can't get the clay out.
I've got to spray it
with the hose,
which I don't want to do,
because I am going to have
a wet mold.
Typically what you'd want to do
is get all of the moisture
out of the mold
before you would
ever put foam in it.
But I only have
about 20 minutes left,
so I don't have time for that.
So now I'm worried.
There's a chance that I could
get all sorts of air pockets,
and I'm really nervous
about what it's gonna
look like tomorrow.
I have a little more time left
in the day,
so I decide
to start experimenting.
I'm trying to figure out
the best way to make mud.
It has to be wet.
I can't just cover her in dirt,
so I actually find
some chocolate syrup in the lab.
I mix some cornstarch
into it and heat it up,
and it turns it
into, like, a jelly.
In special effects, you don't
really think of using food,
but I think it's gonna work
really well for this actually.
Look at this bitch now.
Oh, yeah!
That's time.
I'm so done with today.
So it's the end of day two.
I have everything
ready to go for application.
I have a lot to do,
but I'm really happy
with it so far.
Hopefully, when I get it
all put together tomorrow,
she'll be a beautiful fairy.
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab
and one hour in last looks.
Oh, shit.
What happened?
The first thing I see
is my cowl.
Are you kidding me?
It is destroyed.
Well, I'm going home.
All of the flame points
have broken off.
Oh, no!
They all ripped off.
It's okay.
You have time to fix it.
I have to patch it,
and there's a lot to patch.
At least the face
came out beautiful
the second time, but
if I don't get this cowl fixed,
then what do I have,
flames on a face?
That's not very interesting.
My foam looks pretty great.
There's a couple rips
in the sides of the face,
but I can make it work.
Everything else looks good.
Now I just have
to get it all applied.
Hi! How are you?
How are you doing?
- Good to see you again.
- How are you?
- Great. How are you?
- I'm good.
I'm having
some technical difficulties.
I've never done
anything pretty before.
I'm happy that I listened
to Mr. Westmore's advice.
The silicone piece
looks pretty cool,
but I'm still
not feeling great.
This challenge, it's just--
It's not me.
I mean, everything looks
kind of like fairy parts,
but I don't even know what
that's supposed to look like.
Whoo.
I decided to put the oil
on a dress
instead of directly
on the body.
I just start carefully creating
the drips and runs
to create
this oil spill couture, hmm?
I really think
this new approach
will make it a lot easier
for my model
to wear this makeup.
- I like her.
- I love it.
There we go.
The paint job
on this application
is really important.
I am painting her
from head to toe,
and she's gonna be
covered in mud,
so I really need
to bring those colors
into my makeup.
If I don't do
a beautiful paint job,
she's not gonna be
a beautiful fairy.
Oil spills have
this rainbowlike effect
on the surface,
so I'm gonna start
with my flat white base,
and then I'm going over that
with pinks and greens and blues,
and then I go
over the whole thing
with Kryolan Aquacolor
and a sponge
to give it this really
beautiful, iridescent sheen.
Looks really pretty,
and it's perfect.
One hour, guys!
Shit, I just started painting.
Awesome.
Everyone else seems to be
almost done
with their paint job,
and I've just started,
so I know I'm in a bad spot.
On the head, I'm actually using
the chocolate
sort of gelatin that I made,
because I know
it'll set up well.
I'm actually having a lot of fun
with this challenge.
And she definitely looks
like she rose up from a flood,
so I'm feeling pretty good.
15 minutes, guys!
Oh, shit!
It's almost the end of the day.
I notice that there's
a really weird wrinkle
at the corner of her mouth.
That's time, guys!
I have no idea
what I'm gonna do
with this giant wrinkle.
Hopefully, I'll figure out
some way to fix it.
Because I've been in the bottom
the two challenges before this,
if I don't do a perfect makeup,
I could be going home.
Coming up...
The edge on the face
is starting to crack.
I think
she's really delightful.
It just doesn't get there
for me.
- Oh, getting wobbly. Getting wobbly.
- Hi, honey.
All right.
I start painting immediately.
I think if I can get it
painted well,
I won't be so embarrassed
the foam came out so horribly.
I'm gonna add some eyelashes,
touch up her beauty makeup
a little more.
Awesome.
She looks exactly
like I envisioned it,
so that's good.
As I'm airbrushing white
around her eyes,
some of the white
stays on the eyelashes,
and it looks
like frosted eyelashes.
Cool!
I'm unintentionally
doing beauty makeup.
Yeah.
Time is flying,
and I have to figure out
what I'm gonna do
with that wrinkle
at the corner of her mouth.
Make it look like her face
is cracked.
Not a bad idea.
Megan, being
the awesome model that she is,
says, "Well, why don't you
make it another crack?"
It looks like a crack,
so I paint it like a crack.
It's not ideal,
but it's way better
than having a wrinkle there.
I'm realizing the edge
on the face
is starting to crack
a little bit.
Placing the edge there
to begin with
was a stupid, stupid choice,
but I'm hoping
that the overall beauty
of my makeup will overpower
that flaw.
Ten more minutes.
It's time, guys!
Cool.
Time's up, brushes down.
I feel like I've at least
satisfied the challenge,
but there are
only five makeups.
For me to have this giant crack
on the side of the face,
maybe the judges will hate it,
but it's hard to tell.
Welcome
to the Face Off reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
First let's say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve
Makeup Effects Studio,
Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening, guys.
- Hi, Glenn.
Oscar-winning makeup artist
Lois Burwell.
Hello, group.
Hi, Lois.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
Hello.
Hi, Neville.
Okay, guys, this week,
your spotlight challenge
was to choose
a disaster scenario
and a create
a beautiful elemental fairy
born from its destruction,
so let's take a look
at what you've come up with.
The shapes look cool.
The flames all have direction,
but I know up close,
it looks terrible.
I'm really kind of surprised,
'cause I thought
it was gonna be,
like, the worst makeup
I've ever done,
but it looks decent.
Seeing her in front
of the background
makes me
a little more confident.
She really looks like she came
from that environment.
She looks high-fashion,
runway fairy oil spill madness,
and I love it.
She's all glittery and shiny
and glowing.
She looks really cool,
and I'm really happy.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look at our fairies?
Why?
You're filled
all the way in with--
You're full up,
covered in prosthetics,
and you drop an inch
right there.
I don't understand.
It's a strange margin
across this bustier.
Yes.
I love the coloring,
especially around the eyes.
Wow.
- Oh, this is lovely.
- Gorgeous.
This paint on the chin,
on the arms,
I mean, it's still
all very connected.
That's the great thing.
Could you move your arm out,
so we can kind of see that
close and open?
Come forward.
That's cool.
Really, really cool.
- Thank you.
That's rad.
Yeah, it is.
This is so nicely done.
I like all the transitions.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Why is that edge in the middle?
I do not know.
Would have been equally
successful under here,
plus it would have allowed you
to have the seam
surfacing all the way down.
It does turn it
into a Venetian carnival mask.
I have a horrible edge
across the middle of my face.
There's only five of us left,
and at this point
in the competition,
any mistake can ruin you.
We want to know what you think
of tonight's transformations.
As it stands,
why are there edges?
It does turn it
into a Venetian carnival mask.
Mm-hmm.
They should have come
down to the jaw.
I really want the judges to see
the overall
fashionable aesthetic
that I've gone for,
but I'm worried
that that horrible edge
across the middle of my face
could possibly send me home.
Gorgeous.
He's using warm tones
to make the coolness
of the eyes pop out.
Really smart decision
instead of going really dark.
These choices
of crystalline form
match with the wings.
It's very complete
form language.
Yes.
Could you turn, please?
I like the wings.
I think the wings
are absolutely brilliant.
Yeah, I agree.
Thank you.
Okay, the judges
would like to speak
with each of you to learn
more about your work.
George,
if you'd please step up.
George, tell us
how you allowed earthquake
to inspire
your fairy character.
I was thinking a fairy
who lives
below the Earth's crust,
and when an earthquake happens,
she comes out to mend
and renovate everything.
I think the facial appliance
is absolutely beautiful.
Thank you.
And you didn't get crazy
with these shapes
and make it cartoony.
It's a very nice balance.
You've done a really,
really nice job this week.
Thank you.
I absolutely loved your fairy.
I think that the use of the arm
was extremely skillful
and clever.
More than that,
the face reminded me
of some of the fairies
from Legend.
Wow.
Thank you.
The face in particular
is captivating.
It's so well-balanced.
You've managed to have
the perfect amount of point
and softness at the same time.
It's gorgeous.
Thank you.
George,
if you'd please step back.
Good job.
Stella, please step up.
Stella, please tell us
about your fairy.
I wanted her to be completely
encased in flames on the top,
and then wildfires
inspire new growth,
so down below, I wanted her
to be full of new growth.
The concept is nice,
but it hasn't been fulfilled.
And the transition
from the charcoal burning
to the appliance itself
is so abrupt.
Had color transition been used,
it would have a different feel.
I think that the overall image
and the palette
is really quite beautiful,
and it does satisfy
the challenge,
but I would say
that it's not very inventive.
It's kind of like the first
thing you're going to think of
for a fire character.
I know you're creative enough
to come up with something
that would have been
more inventive as a concept.
The massive issue for me
is that she needs wings.
Ultimately,
it doesn't feel like a fairy.
It feels like a fire elemental
or something,
but it just doesn't
get there for me.
Okay.
Stella,
if you'd please step down.
Dina, you're up.
So tell us how flood
influenced your fairy.
She was born
in a flooded forest.
A river overflowed
onto the land,
and she rose from it.
I thought I would incorporate
some driftwood, stones, sand,
you know, a mixture
of all things,
you know, water and land.
This is
a very beautiful makeup.
Thank you.
You retained
the model's aesthetic,
but you didn't do it
in such a way
that you made it mask-y.
I really like this makeup.
The subject matter calls
for the mud and the heaviness,
and yet you have managed
to capture the lightness.
You have quite a range
of colors here,
and the transitions
are handled so beautifully.
It's a beautiful makeup,
and everything else
that you've designed,
including the prosthetics,
just highlight that makeup.
Thank you so much.
Dina, please step back.
Thank you.
Yay. Good job.
Thanks.
All right, let's talk to Drew.
Drew, tell us
about your oil spill fairy.
She is an Earth spirit fairy,
who lives in the ground,
and there was an oil spill,
and so she's using her powers
to clean up the mess.
What do you think
of your creation?
I like
almost every aspect of it,
except for my horrible decision
to cut the prosthetic
across her face.
If I had a time machine,
I would go back in time
and smack myself really hard.
Yeah, absolutely.
That should have gone down
to the bottom of her chin,
so you bury that edge.
My other major complaint is,
there's a disconnect
in terms of the dress
into her face and everything.
I think that you could have
added a little bit
by letting the oil
spill out of her mouth
and then have her neck
covered in black
and tying the oil together
in the rest of the body.
I think what is missing
is the gloss that's happening
from the oil dripping down
across her chest--
there's none of that gloss
in her hands.
That would have helped
communicate the story
a bit better.
The thing is that you've
gone for a nice iridescence,
but it would have worked better
had you gone
for dark round the eyes
coming up into the hair,
and then it would have been
a look that would have worked.
Thank you.
Drew, please step down.
Cig, you're next.
Please tell us
about your avalanche fairy.
My fairy was
a mischievous mountain fairy.
Mother Nature sends
an avalanche to take her out.
She almost died,
but her fairy magic saved her,
so now she's imbued
with ice powers.
I think
she's really delightful.
Can you tell me
how you made the wings?
I wasn't sure
if it was gonna work,
but I just cut out
clear vacuform plastic,
and I used a heat gun
and hand-warped it,
and I hot-glued
all the pieces together.
I think
they're exceptionally good.
Awesome.
I can't tell you
how well I think you've done.
It's really
excellent decision-making
in picking the ice,
using that to drive your
decision-making on your shapes,
and it's absolutely stunning.
With the headpiece and the body
and the wings,
you've sustained
a harmony in form
that is so consistent
that this character
feels very whole.
Thank you guys so much.
Cig, if you'd please step back.
Thanks.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, guys.
All right, judges,
let's talk about the looks
you like the most this week.
Why don't we start with George's
earthquake-inspired fairy?
It was
really quite accomplished,
especially the face.
The face was the best part.
I agree.
Beautiful facial makeup.
Beautiful points--
Well-colored, well-sculpted,
good use of silicone.
One of the best I've seen
on the show.
There was a grace
and a beauty there.
I think it was the most fairy
of all of them.
All right,
let's talk about Dina.
She showed such grace
in her application,
keeping the face light
and figuring out
how to transition
from a bunch
of different dark colors
without the entire thing
looking muddy.
It was
absolutely the correct choice
to have a white face.
Dina's visual acuity
is a force
to be reckoned with here.
All right, let's move on
to Cig's avalanche fairy.
That was beautifully handled,
from the lip line to the way
the eyes were applied.
Everything about it
was exceptionally well done.
This super cool idea
for a makeup,
and then he added the wings,
and he knew that that would
bring it all together
and allow it to succeed within
the parameters that we gave him.
All right, let's move on
to the looks you like the least.
Stella's wildfire fairy.
The biggest problem for me
was the lackluster concept.
It felt solid and stiff
and cartoon-like.
She made a mistake
with a design that she
didn't fully understand
this week, I think.
All right, so what do you think
about Drew's oil spill fairy?
What makes it less than perfect
is simply
technical decision-making.
Mm.
He was heading
in the right direction,
but where he let himself down
was the way the edges are,
the choice of color
round the eyes,
and not tying
his elements together.
All right then, judges,
have you made your decisions?
Yeah, we have.
Okay, let's bring them
back out.
Glenn, tell us
about the top looks.
George, we love
the sophisticated alterations
to her nose and chin,
and we thought
that the shattered shoulder
was a super cool way
to represent your disaster.
Thank you.
Dina, you did
an exceptional job
morphing one color
into the other,
and she was still beautiful,
despite the fact that she was
covered in flood debris.
Cig, focusing on the wings
to tell your fairy story
was brilliant.
And her soft,
almost angelic look,
very well handled.
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
Cig.
Whoo!
No way.
Yeah!
She was picture-perfect
with her crystalline wings,
her icy crown,
and a beautiful color palette.
She oozed fairy.
Thank you so much.
That's awesome.
I've been on the top
so many times,
and I just haven't got
my first individual win.
Now I get it
on a fairy challenge.
That feels even better,
because I went
out of my element,
and I did something
that even surprised myself.
Cig, congratulations.
Thank you.
You, George, and Dina can
head back to the makeup room.
- Thanks so much.
- Thank you.
Good luck.
Unfortunately,
that means you two
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
All right, Glenn,
tell us about the bottom looks.
Stella, we thought
you very successfully captured
the essence of your disaster,
but between
the abrupt transitions
and the unfinished paint,
it just didn't come together.
Drew, many parts of your makeup
were on the precipice
of brilliance,
but all of its parts
didn't quite add up,
and it left us
feeling unfulfilled.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Stella.
You had a tough week,
and, unfortunately,
at this stage of the game,
even a tiny stumble is
something that you can't afford.
Stella, I'm sorry,
but that means
you have been eliminated.
However, Drew,
you are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Love you.
Stella, you've done
remarkably well.
There's absolutely nothing
that you should feel
upset about,
and you leave here knowing
how much you've achieved,
and that's wonderful.
Thank you.
Stella, it's really been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head
back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, guys.
- Good luck, Stella.
- Good luck.
I'm feeling a little bit sad,
but I feel like
I've come really far
in this competition
as an artist.
It's me.
Ohh.
Stella.
This experience
truly has taught me
what I am capable of.
Aww.
I know I still have
so much to learn,
but I plan on learning it.
I love makeup,
and I just want to do more.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net