Shockingly awful.
That is the high point
for you thus far.
Previously on Face Off...
Drew's emo faun
gave him his first win,
and Rachael was sent home.
Now just six artists remain.
And tonight,
they'll face a mythical twist.
It's time to make something
just a little more powerful.
But for some, it may prove
to be their Achilles' heel.
Shit-balls.
I'm so stupid.
It has that grand,
majestic nature to it.
In the end, only one
will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Ooh, looks lovely in here.
We get into the lab,
and it's been transformed
by all this Greek architecture,
and it looks like a coliseum.
Hey, guys.
Hi.
Before I give you the details
of today's foundation challenge,
I want to introduce you
to your special guest judge.
Her work has been featured
in major films,
like Oblivion
and one of my favorites,
The Cell.
Oh, my God.
She's also been nominated
for six Academy Awards,
and she won twice for her work
on Dracula and Quest For Fire.
Please give a warm welcome
to makeup artist Michele Burke.
Oh, my God, Michele Burke.
She's done all sorts of makeups,
including one of my favorite
movies, The Cell.
So I really want to impress her.
- Hi.
It's so great to have you
here with us.
Thank you, thank you.
I'm delighted to be here.
All right, guys.
Today's foundation challenge
is inspired
by one of the most recognizable
and feared characters
of all Greek mythology.
Her deadly gaze
will turn you to stone.
Medusa.
Nice.
Oh, nice.
So your foundation challenge
is to create
one of Medusa's victims
who is turning into stone.
Yes.
- Nice.
- Yes.
So what advice do you have
for these guys today?
What I'm really looking for
is how you create stone
and duplicate the textures,
and I'm also looking
for the expression
of when they're frozen,
the fear or the shock
of being turned into stone.
Excellent, thank you.
Okay, guys, the winner
of this foundation challenge
will receive their
very own spray booth,
courtesy of our friends
at Paasche.
That's a big wow.
- Yeah.
- Holy cow.
That amazing booth will help
keep the air in your own lab
clear of any dangerous fumes
and is worth $2,000.
- Wow!
- Nice!
My spray booth is a table
in front of a window
with a box fan.
So I want
that Paasche spray booth
so bad, I can taste it.
All right, you have two hours
for this challenge.
Good luck, guys,
because your time starts now.
Oh, yes!
I envision Medusa's gaze
so intense
that it actually
sears your eyeballs,
so my character is gonna be
shielding his face,
but it's also burning
his fingers.
I grab some clay,
water it down to make a slush,
and then I also tint that
with some of the
Kryolan aqua proofs
and start painting that
on my model.
You're turning to stone, Alex.
_
My victim was sent out
to defeat Medusa
because they thought,
as a woman,
she wouldn't be affected by her.
I have this idea to cut up
cosmetic sponges
into shapes of rocks.
And with the paint job,
it'll look really cool.
I can't imagine having
my own spray booth.
That would be so awesome.
This nose looks
like a beast's nose.
I find this prosthetic,
and it's got mean eyebrows
and a funky lip and chin.
So he's going to be a creature
that has come to kill Medusa.
And I want a paint scheme
to have more color
than just gray and white.
I like that.
My concept is this
protector of the forest
who saw Medusa,
and he's just frozen
for all eternity.
Open and look up.
There are certain things
that happen to stone
when it gets really old.
Like, it gets moss on it,
and lichen,
which is, like, this really
vibrantly colored fungus.
I'm gonna incorporate that
to just make it
a little more interesting.
That looks really cool.
All right, 30 minutes.
That's it, time's up;
brushes down.
- Hi, Sasha.
- Hi.
All right, so tell us
about your Medusa-struck woman.
She's a princess,
and Medusa wanted to rule,
so she turned everyone royal
into stone.
I like the idea
of the ultra-color in the hair.
That's really interesting.
What could have
been done better,
if this line here
was not a straight line,
because on camera straight lines
catch the eye faster.
She was out gathering things
to help feed her family,
and she accidentally wandered
into Medusa's den.
You've really captured
the stone in her face
- and the crackling...
- And the texture.
That you could have showed
complete stone
and lesser stone,
but that's minor.
She is a warrior
sent out to defeat Medusa.
I really like that you gave it
a 3-D aspect to the makeup.
And I think that would translate
very well in film.
Excellent work.
Medusa's stare is so intense,
the heat sears your eyeballs,
so he put up his hand
to block it,
and it burnt the tips
of his fingers.
I really like this idea.
I would have liked to have seen
a little bit less uniformity
around the eyes.
Mm-hmm.
But this is very creative.
He was a woodland warrior,
and Medusa stared him
straight in the face,
so he is entirely stone.
And this happened a while ago,
so I did some moss on the stone.
I love the fact
that you aged him a little
and made him a complete
frozen character.
Because he's young and foolish,
he decided he was just
going to charge in
and kill Medusa with his horns.
I like the fact
that you did use a prosthetic
to give him more dimension
to the face.
The eyes are good
because they're deep-set
and they show a fierceness,
and I like your paintwork.
You did a very good job
with that.
- Thank you.
All right, so, Michele,
who created your
favorite looks today?
Stella.
It was really creative
and different
to everybody else.
Thank you.
And George.
Your back-story
was very, very different,
and I love that
you aged the face.
- So, well done.
- Thanks.
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
It was a very tough choice,
but the winner is...
Stella.
Ah!
You nailed that expression,
and your paintwork
was really good.
Thank you so much.
Stella, congratulations.
As the winner of today's
foundation challenge,
you have won your very own
Paasche spray booth.
Are you excited?
Yes.
I won a spray booth
from Paasche,
which feels awesome, so, yay.
Michele, thank you so much
for joining us today.
Thank you so much.
It was a pleasure.
Good luck, everybody.
It was just a pleasure
to see you work today.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Okay, guys, let's talk about
your next spotlight challenge.
You've already created
the victim of a Greek beast.
Now it's time to make something
just a little more powerful.
While films like
Clash Of The Titans
and Percy Jackson
And The Olympians
feature Greek gods
as powerful immortals,
their incredible abilities
are rarely reflected
in their appearances.
So, with that in mind,
your spotlight challenge
is to re-imagine one
of the Greek gods,
using their own powers
as inspiration
for a supernatural
fantasy character.
- Nice.
- Whoa.
I'm kind of nervous right now.
I really don't know that much
about Greek gods,
so I'm hoping that I'm going to
pick up on it really fast.
Each of the items beside me
represents a Greek god.
We have...
Demeter...
Poseidon...
Athena...
Zeus...
Artemis...
Aphrodite...
Apollo...
and Hades.
Stella, as the winner
of the foundation challenge,
you get first pick.
Yay.
Ah... okay.
Poseidon.
Aw.
Drew.
Hades.
Aphrodite.
Apollo.
Zeus.
Athena.
All right, now that you all
have your gods,
Greek mythology is filled
with epic stories
of heroes and gods
conquering unspeakable monsters.
In keeping with this season's
life and death theme,
you must also create
the severed head
of a mythological monster
conquered by your god.
Yes!
This is awesome,
but it's gonna be
a lot more work,
because not only do you
have to make a head,
but you have to make a makeup
that looks cool too.
All right, guys, you can
go home and get some rest.
When you get to the lab
in the morning,
get started on your designs.
I'll come by with my dad to see
how things are coming along.
See you then.
- Bye.
- Severed heads!
- Yeah!
Yay.
The first time
I've been in top looks
for a foundation challenge.
- Yeah.
- So that felt nice.
Congratulations.
Yeah, good for me.
After being on bottom
last challenge,
it's nice to be
in top looks this time.
I'm feeling really positive
and more confident.
Now I just want to focus
on impressing the judges
with my Greek god
and my monster head.
It's day one in the lab.
We have ten hours to work today.
We pick our models
and start designing.
I chose Hades,
the God of the Underworld.
Because he's been
in the Underworld for so long,
he is starting to shrivel,
like the dead.
So I'm doing
this very desiccated,
leathery, corpse-like makeup.
My idea for the severed head
is, like, an impish,
demonic servant creature
that displeased Hades.
I'm gonna do, like,
really gnarly stringy bits
coming out of the neck.
Like, he didn't just
cut their head off.
He, like, pulled it
off their body.
My character is Zeus.
He's the God of the Sky.
He controls the lightning
and the thunder.
I'm kind of thinking of him
as almost like a--
like a Renaissance oil painting.
So he's gonna have the long hair
and the long beard,
but I want to give him
this ethereal armor.
So the first thing
I start working on
is the face sculpt.
I want it to have
Mediterranean features,
like the nose.
He's gonna look attractive,
but also aged.
I think I'm doing my piece
out of silicone.
Nice.
Zeus banished all the Titans
to the sea
in this underwater prison.
Because of that,
I want my severed head
to be the last remaining Titan
that he didn't quite round up.
My God is Aphrodite,
and she's the God
of Beauty and Love.
And she was actually born
in the sea,
so I'm thinking I want
to add sea elements
into this makeup,
and I'm just gonna do a cowl
and some shoulder pieces.
For my severed head,
I want to do,
like, the ugliest thing
I could think of in the ocean,
which is the angler fish.
Ooh, gorgeous.
I picked Apollo,
and since he's
the God of the Sun,
I really want to play up
the fire element
and design some really cool
fire armor.
So I decided I'm gonna do
a cowl and a severed head.
Since he was the God of Plague,
I want him to have slain
this diseased abomination.
He dips his arrows
in the blood of this beast
to spread plague and disease
among his enemies.
I'm having the hardest time
figuring out
what my concept is gonna be.
My goddess is Athena.
She's the Goddess
of War and Skill,
and she represents the owl,
because the owl
is the wise bird.
But I've done
an owl makeup already.
I can't do another owl makeup.
There's no clay on my life cast
at this point,
and everyone else
is already sculpting.
I can't come up with anything
right now.
Coming up...
Now I have to figure out
how I'm gonna open it
without cracking any of it.
I know it's not the focus,
but it becomes
such a distraction.
Today is day one
of our Greek gods challenge,
and I'm having
a really hard time
figuring out what my concept
is gonna be.
There's no clay on my life cast
at this point,
and everyone else
is already sculpting.
I find that Athena guided
Perseus' hand
to cut off Medusa's head,
so I'm thinking, well, then,
maybe Medusa could be
Athena's severed head.
But she can still
turn people to stone.
So my goddess, Athena,
has been turned to stone
and is being controlled
by the Medusa head.
I hate my concept,
but I just have to go for it.
Hey, guys, my dad and I
are here to check in on you.
- Hello.
- Hi.
So Poseidon was the God
of Seas,
and he created the horse.
So I figured I could do
a really cool,
like, water creature
with a sea horse element.
And I'm gonna do an octopus
for the severed head.
What is your thinking
on the cutting in
along the nose there?
The gills.
- The gills?
- Yeah.
I think you ought
to over-emphasize these,
and then you could even
carry it on down
- into this upper piece here.
- Mm-hmm.
So Hades is the God
of the Underworld,
and the severed head
is actually going to be
one of the Underworld minions
who has failed him.
What are you gonna do for eyes?
I'm actually going to mold it
with those eye forms in
and paint the latex
and epoxy over them.
You've got them centered
straight ahead.
You might just roll them
a little bit,
because your dead eyes
roll up into your head.
Oh, yeah.
All right,
so you chose Aphrodite.
Yes.
She rose from the sea foam,
so I wanted to incorporate,
like, seashells.
That's great.
You might even pull this back
a little further
to be able to put
iridescent shadow on there
to bring this makeup out.
We know you have Athena.
Yes.
I'm gonna have her
holding Medusa.
She turned into stone.
Now Medusa is, like,
controlling her body.
Interesting concept
you're doing,
because you're going a reverse
of what everything else is.
To really pull it off,
your head
- has to have life in it.
- The fake head.
- Yeah.
It can't look like
a silly, cheap Halloween head.
All right, guys,
it's looking great.
Good luck to everybody.
- Thank you.
- See you later.
- Check it out.
- Oh, looks good.
So I get the face done,
and now it's time
to make the mold.
I'm gonna be casting my face
out of silicone,
because if you're
using silicone,
you can just paint
a few light layers,
and you get that translucent
look of skin a lot easier.
But the mold needs to be
as perfect as possible
so that when it opens
it doesn't tear.
I have to get my severed head
molded on day one,
because I want to be able
to slush some latex into it
and allow it to set overnight,
and I can run foam
first thing in the morning.
Mr. Westmore tells me
that I really have
to sell this Medusa head,
so I start sculpting snakes
on a flat board.
When they're done,
I'll mold them,
run them in foam latex,
stick a wire in them,
and paint them,
bend them however I want.
I like it.
But I think he looks
like the alien.
That's what I'm trying
to avoid.
The flames are looking
really cool,
but it resembles something
I had done in a previous
challenge for the alien,
and I don't want to do something
that looks the same.
I just really want
to illustrate fire.
Instead of going for armor,
I envision him more wrapped
in, like, this divine flame.
That gives me even more freedom
to not be in the confines
of just armor.
I know that changing my cowl
is gonna be a lot of work,
but I'm fired up.
30 minutes, guys.
- Do I look like Zeus?
- You look like a hippie Jesus.
Go back to Woodstock.
That's time.
So it's the end of day one.
I've got my mold finished.
I've got my head roughed out.
Ah!
There's a lot that I need
to do tomorrow,
but I feel pretty confident
that I'll get it all done.
How'd it come out?
I don't know how this
could be any better.
So it's day two.
We have ten hours in the lab.
And the first thing I do
is pour my poly foam
in my severed head mold,
I let it completely set up,
and then I pull it
out of the mold,
and there's a couple
of little imperfections,
but whenever I'm painting this,
I'm just gonna turn them
into some scrapes
or old scars or something
so that they make sense.
I'm, like, a zillion times
more excited about this
now that I'm not doing
hard flames.
Good.
Athena is the Goddess of War,
so she needs to have
some sort of armor.
So I decide to fabricate
a helmet.
I take L200, and I shape it
into a helmet shape
with a heat gun.
And then I mix some Ultracal
and drip it on
to create a stone look.
Good job, Sash.
It's cool to get
some compliments,
and maybe today will be
better than yesterday.
I need to finish my cowl.
And because I only have
this one main piece,
I want to make sure
that it's perfect,
so I'm taking the extra time
to mold it properly.
I have so much detail
in my design
that I want to make sure
I have a really great piece
tomorrow.
I need to get my mold
opened and cleaned,
because I really want to start
pre-painting my severed head.
I realize I forgot
to put pry points in this.
Shit-balls.
I'm so stupid.
Pry points help
the mold separate
without cracking the mold.
Oh, my God.
Now I have to figure out
how I'm gonna open it
without cracking any of it.
It's day two of our
Greek gods challenge,
and I'm having
a really hard time
opening my mold
because I forgot
to put pry points in this.
I'm such an idiot.
So I very slowly
and very carefully
got around the whole thing
to chisel my own pry points.
There's a chance
that I could crack it, break it,
and then I'll have wasted
the entire day,
and I'll not have a cowl.
Oh, my God, I did it.
I am so relieved
that it finally opened.
It's got a few imperfections,
and it set me back in time,
but at least my mold is opened.
I have to fabricate armor
for my Zeus character,
so I heat up L200
and use my hands
to press it
over this mannequin shape.
Then I brush five-minute epoxy,
which is a really
quick-setting plastic
that self-levels and becomes
this really smooth
plastic surface.
How did you do that?
Magic.
After that hardens,
I spray-paint all of this
baby blue
to suggest the sky,
'cause Zeus is the God
of the Sky.
It's looking really cool.
I'm happy with it.
Ugh, it's a big, boily baby.
We have two makeups to do,
basically.
And we're not gonna have time
to do it tomorrow
in four hours,
so I think we all
are in the same place,
hoping to get these heads
pre-painted today.
It's definitely weird
seeing everyone pre-painting
on day two,
but we have no choice.
That looks so creepy.
- That's good.
- Yeah.
That's a good thing.
I hang my Medusa head
from the desk
because I want to see
how it hangs.
It's looking okay.
But everything
that I'm adding to this head
is just making it look worse.
So I decide to move on,
because I need to start
pre-painting the face and helmet
to look like stone.
That's time, guys.
Tomorrow I have to
apply the face,
paint her hair
to look like stone,
and paint her whole body.
I'm hoping that I'll be able
to pull something together.
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo.
Whoo.
So it's application day.
We've got four hours in the lab
and one hour at last looks.
The first thing I do
is grab my severed head
and take this black gelatin
and cover whole neck stump
where his head's been torn off.
Then I take the rest,
and I dump that in cold water,
which allows it to form
this stringy, mass-y stuff...
...which is exactly what I want
hanging out of my neck stump.
What's up?
You are going to be Hades,
the Lord of the Underworld.
This is your helmet.
_
I was on bottom last week.
I'm trying to not
have that happen ever again.
I start applying
my silicone piece.
Some of my edges
are a little thick,
but I have a patch paste
that I can smear in there
and blend down to his skin.
I'm really liking
this facial piece.
That looks awesome.
The first thing I need to do
is apply this puppy,
but I realize
when I put the cowl on him
that I had over-sculpted so much
that the face
is overlapping the ears
that I had sculpted on the cowl.
Yeah, that really
overlaps a lot.
So I have to cut
around the ears,
which is going to create
a thick seam between the pieces.
That's really thick edges.
I patch and I seam
and I make sure all those edges
are beautiful,
but I'm running out
of application time.
Better...ish.
To paint flames,
or anytime I do metallics,
I like to base them out
in black first,
because it really makes
metallic colors pop.
So I base the whole cowl
in black.
Now it's time
to start with the golds.
I airbrush on the Kryolan gold,
and it's going down great.
It's really covering the black.
And as soon as I hit
the highlights,
the piece is really
starting to pop.
Looking very godly.
There's some nasty edges
on her neck,
but the shoulder pieces
cover them pretty well.
She's looking very godlike.
She's just so striking,
and I'm liking
the way it's going.
That's beautiful.
I hate you.
Painting's not going well.
Everything's just
not looking good.
I paint her body,
and I'm spattering,
trying to break up the color
to help this makeup
look like stone.
I'm gonna stick some
of the little stones on.
30 minutes.
The day is almost over.
I did not get
nearly enough finished.
I have a ton to do.
That's time, guys.
At last looks,
we've only got one hour,
and I've got probably three
hours' worth of work to do.
It's not gonna come out
as nice as I would like it to.
Coming up...
_
Take it off.
The helmet won't fit.
Oh, God, I hate this part.
It captures
the essence of a god.
That wig's a bit unforgiving.
The sculpt is so good.
Let's do this.
Good luck, guys.
We arrive at last looks,
and we have one hour
to finish our makeups.
I just touch up
her beauty makeup,
give her some nice eyeliner.
I have a lot of gold,
so I want to definitely
bring that into her lips.
Hopefully it will make me
a top look this time.
I get my mustache glued down,
and I'm not happy with it,
but I have to move on
to painting the armor.
It's pretty important
that I get the clouds on it.
Otherwise, it's just
baby blue armor,
and that doesn't make
too much sense.
Good.
You look really cool.
Ten minutes, guys.
Does it kind of hurt?
_
I still have to
put the helmet on,
and I realize it won't fit
because I forgot to factor in
the bulkiness
of the prosthetic and her hair.
- I'll just take it off.
- Take it off.
So I can't use the helmet now.
All right, that's time.
Good job, guys.
I'm very disappointed
in myself.
I don't want to go on stage
with this mess.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
First, let's say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve
Makeup Effects Studio,
Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening, guys.
- Hey, Glenn.
- Hi, Glenn.
Oscar-winning makeup artist,
Lois Burwell.
Hello.
Hi, Lois.
Creature and concept designer,
Neville Page.
Hello, everyone.
- Hi, Neville.
And joining our panel tonight,
he is a Golden Globe
nominated actor
with critically acclaimed roles
in films like
In The Heat Of The Night
and Monster.
But he is perhaps best known
for his portrayal
of Hershel Greene
on AMC's The Walking Dead.
Please give a warm welcome
to Mr. Scott Wilson.
I'm a huge Walking Dead fan,
and I was so bummed
when he got his head cut off
by the Governor.
On the other hand,
who better to judge
a severed head contest
than Hershel?
Thank you.
Thank you so much
for joining us tonight.
It's a real pleasure
to be here with you.
All right, guys.
This week,
your spotlight challenge
was to re-imagine
one of the Greek gods,
using their own powers
as inspiration
for a supernatural
fantasy character.
And in the spirit of this
season's life and death theme,
I also asked that you create
the severed head of a monster
your god had slain.
So let's take a look
at what you've come up with.
My god's backlit
by this beautiful sunset,
hitting those golds perfectly.
I think he looks radiant
and awesome.
Aside from some things
with the hair,
I'm pretty proud of this makeup.
It really reads Zeus.
I'm just so embarrassed.
It's terrible.
I know I'm better than this.
I have such a beautiful model,
and then the head
is so hideous.
I love seeing that contrast.
He's creepy and wretched
and regal,
and the overall effect
of my makeup shows through.
I'm happy with what I did.
I definitely had a vision,
and I saw it through.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look
at our Greek gods?
It's a form language
cornucopia,
which is great.
It's really hard to find
the skull shape in this.
There are some highlights,
though.
- That eye is nice in there.
- Yeah.
_
The silicone on his face
is really nice.
It is.
Just not sure that it works
as a character.
This look gives the feeling
of man-boobs,
doesn't it, really?
Well, I'm just curious
about the decapitation.
If it were a lightning bolt,
wouldn't there be
something burned?
That's a good observation.
Looks like it's a dried clay
more than a stone, doesn't it?
Yeah.
It would have worked better
had the natural skin tone
been on the model
and this been in the hand.
Mm-hmm.
It's lovely.
Yeah, it's stunning.
I love the shell shape.
The blend is good.
The head is amazing.
Yeah, it's a great
creature-y angler fish head.
Thank you.
_
There's always a chance
the judges are gonna
hate the makeup.
So I'm sweating a little bit.
I really hope
they like this makeup,
because there's only six of us,
and at least two
have to be in the bottom,
and those are strong odds.
We want to know what you think
of tonight's transformations.
Tell us on Twitter using
hashtag #FaceOff.
God, I hate this part.
Hey, I love this.
Yeah, that's rather marvelous.
Whatever this is,
is super cool.
_
It looks like he's killed
a fish from Fraggle Rock, right?
It looks and feels
like a potato.
I do like the colors,
and the iridescence
is always fun.
Thank you.
So, Scott, what do you think
of tonight's characters?
They're extraordinary.
I take my hat off to--
Or maybe I should say
I take my head off to you.
Okay, the judges
have scored your creations
and would like to speak
with some of you
to learn more about your work.
Cig, please step forward.
Cig, tell us about
your character this week.
I picked Apollo,
the God of Plague,
and he rides the sun
across the sky
in his chariot of fire
and uses this
slayed pestilent beast
to spread disease and plague
among his enemies.
This is
a very successful makeup.
I think you've done
a wonderful job
of bringing the fire aspect
of him to life.
It captures the essence
of a god.
It has that majestic nature
to it.
Thank you.
The flame on the right side
is really successful.
It looks like a flame licking.
But I wished you continued
the shape,
because it looks at the moment
as if the shoulders are puffed
sleeves on a girl's dress.
This is a really
difficult sculpture to do
because of this three
dimensional filigree shape.
But you've got
an overall character
that reads very strong.
I think the look that you have
is very nice.
I like your explanation
for the way he looks.
It's a wonderful job
that you've done.
Thank you.
Cig, will you please step back?
Thank you, guys.
Sasha, please step forward.
Tell us about your makeup.
My goddess is Athena.
Athena guided Perseus
to cut off Medusa's head.
But even when Medusa's head
is cut off,
she still turns people
to stone,
so she turns Athena to stone
and takes control
over her body.
How do you feel
about the makeup?
I think it's unacceptable.
I think you're right.
It doesn't say "Stone" to me.
Just looking
at the picture behind you,
there's stone.
This looks more like the gravel
than the walls made of stone.
I think the surface
of the skin and everything
should have been more solid,
and her beauty should have been
more apparent
through her turning to stone.
Your second character
looks like
an anime sex doll head.
I know it's not the focus,
but it becomes
such a distraction
that it is the focus.
Sasha, you can head back.
George, please step forward.
Tell us about your character
and your god's attributes
in this.
This is Zeus, and he controls
like, the thunder
and the lightning.
He's also known
for banishing all the Titans
to below the sea.
So I thought for a severed head
it might be cool to have
and undersea
crustacean bottom-dweller.
The face,
the sculpt is so good,
but then you turn it
into a cross-dressing Zeus
with this wretched costume.
He's got cloud man-boob armor.
I would have taken advantage
of your model's body
and used minimal costuming
and let that be part
of your character.
What I'd like to talk about
is actually the facial hair,
because the beard is actually
somebody else's beard
in comparison to the mustache.
The curl is a very Grecian curl.
Had you used that
on the beard form as well,
then it would have worked.
But as it is, they're growing
on separate people.
Mm-hmm.
And that wig's
a bit unforgiving.
George, you can step back.
Dina, please step up.
Dina, tell us about
how you designed your character
based on the parameters
that you were given.
My goddess is Aphrodite.
She was born in the sea.
She's so beautiful
that every living thing
falls in love with her,
including her victim.
How do you feel about
your performance this week?
I'm not very confident,
but I really do
love this makeup.
It is amazing.
Are you joking?
I don't know how you got the
level of detail and symmetry.
It's astoundingly gorgeous.
Thank you.
I think it's a feast,
because you've listened visually
to the form of your model.
You can't ignore
the actor in the chair,
and you've come up with
something that is triumphant.
Well done.
Thank you.
From the bottom of the hem
to the top of the head,
everything is in place.
Everything works.
It all flows together.
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
Dina, please step down.
All right, guys.
The judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
All right, judges, why don't we
talk about tonight's Olympians?
Let's start with Cig.
He really did manage to capture
the glorious nature of Apollo as a god,
and his explanation
of the Plague God as his enemy,
it all made sense.
Yeah.
The relief filigree
is hard to do,
but it really lent itself
to a solid character idea.
The thing that was
disappointing
was the little
tiny puff sleeves,
because it wasn't godlike.
If the shoulders had been
broadened a little,
he would have enhanced it
big time.
All right, let's move on
to Dina.
She told a whole story there.
Right out of the gate,
you know an awful lot
about her.
It's very successful.
Wonderful use of color
and form.
Beautifully done.
Taking the scalloped shells
as a headdress
was a beautifully unique way
to manifest
the aquatic attributes
of this god character.
All right, judges,
let's move on to George.
Fundamentally,
George just missed the mark.
He didn't create a character
based on the god's powers.
That facial hair, honestly.
No one ever takes a beard
out of a box
and just sticks it on a face.
All right, let's move on
to Sasha.
She didn't really
satisfy the challenge.
To have a god be affected
by her creature
- just made no sense.
- No.
Her beauty should not
have been clouded over.
Just because you turn to stone
doesn't mean you turn ugly.
The idea of building
a face out in big, round forms
in order to create
a gravelly texture,
it's just not good enough.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
Yes, we have.
Okay, let's bring them
back out.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about the top looks.
Actually, there is only
one top look this week.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about the top looks.
Actually, there is only
one top look this week.
Dina, you were
head-and-shoulders
above everyone else.
The sculpture
was insanely beautiful.
You lavished that
with a gorgeous paint job.
And then, on top of it all,
you gave us an absolutely
phenomenal severed head.
Truly great work.
Thank you so much.
It feels so amazing.
This is my third spotlight win.
In the beginning,
I definitely did not think
I would make it to the finale,
but if I keep doing
makeups like that,
I think I have a good chance.
Dina, congratulations.
Thank you so much.
You, Cig, Stella, and Drew
can all head back
to the makeup room.
Thanks, guys.
Unfortunately, that means
the two of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Sasha, you started
with a flawed concept,
and then, expectedly,
that led to a rather
underwhelming goddess character.
George, your beautiful
silicone makeup
was obscured
by atrocious hair work,
and we didn't see
your god's powers
clearly reflected
in the character.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Sasha.
Somewhere along the way,
you lost your confidence,
but we believed in you enough
to use the save on you,
so we hope that you leave here
with your head held high,
because you are
a truly talented artist.
Thank you.
Sasha, I am so sorry.
That means you
have been eliminated.
George, you are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Thanks. Give me a hug.
I really appreciate
the opportunity,
and I'm not giving up.
Oh, bless you for that, Sasha.
Sasha, it has been so great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head
back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you.
Good luck, Sasha.
It was a pretty bad makeup,
and I'm not proud of it.
I'm just proud
that I made it this far.
It's me.
- Ohh...
- Oh, Sasha.
I have all the confidence
in me somewhere.
I just have to go find it.
Come in here.
And I'm so thankful
for this opportunity,
because I've learned what it
takes to make this my career.
I plan to be so much more
driven and focused,
so I'm gonna go out
and work even harder.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net