This season on Face Off,
contestants will have to fight
for their lives
in an epic battle of life...
and death.
I'm so excited!
I hope I'm living
and not dying.
And it all starts off
with the biggest twist
- in Face Off history.
- Oh, dear.
We've never seen anything
like this on Face Off before.
I can't wait to see
what kind of freakish makeups
you guys come up with.
Challenge after challenge...
Oh, boy.
...they'll try to climb
their way to the top...
I quit my job to do this.
...and conquer their rivals.
I want this so bad.
There's no room for mistakes.
This is crazy.
It's life or death.
But to make it to the end,
they'll have to contend
with our award-winning panel
of judges...
It's beautiful.
Including our new series judge,
Oscar winner Lois Burwell.
I really like it.
Find out who survives now.
Welcome to Face Off.
This season is gonna be nuts.
Boom.
We walk into this huge,
incredibly intimidating hall.
One side is black.
The other is white.
The makeup stock
is out of this world.
I'm just blown away by it.
Holy cow.
- There's the vacuform machine.
- Yeah.
It looks look like they
brought most of the lab over.
Look who it is.
Oh, my God.
McKenzie's standing
at the head of the room.
I'm like,
"This is really happening."
Welcome to Face Off.
This is
the Vibiana event space--
formerly the cathedral
of St. Vibiana
and the site of countless
baptisms and funerals.
That's why we are here today.
This season of Face Off
is all about life...
and death.
- Yes.
- And this starts right now.
Because none of you
are actually on the show yet...
Oh, no.
Oh, boy.
I'm sorry, what?
Today will be
your final audition.
I'm not even a contestant yet?
I think I'm going to throw up
in my mouth a little bit.
You'll be fighting
for your life
in a sudden-death challenge
to earn a spot on this season
of Face Off.
We only have room
for 14 of you,
which means that two of you
will be eliminated
before ever moving
into the house
or stepping foot into the lab.
I actually quit my job
to be on the show.
So, if I go home now,
I have nothing to go home to.
You will have four hours
to create a character
that represents
either life or death
while showcasing who you are
as an artist.
On my go, I want you to pick
a life or death workstation.
On each is a box
with an item inside
that you must use
in your makeups.
This is your only chance
to earn a spot on the show.
Is everyone ready?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
On your marks, get set,
go.
As soon as McKenzie says "Go,"
everyone's
falling over each other.
- It's absolutely insane.
- Fuck!
I was going to stop and help,
but I was like,
"No, keep my eye on the prize."
Okay.
I open up my box,
and it's this
huge ripped-throat appliance,
so I'm thinking
she was murdered.
It looks like your throat
is gonna be ripped out.
I'm completely self-taught.
When I was 13 years old,
I started doing haunted houses
in my backyard.
I've never been
in a professional lab at all,
so this is really
the opportunity of a lifetime.
Ah, this is what I wanted.
My name is Keaghlan.
I am a freelance makeup artist
from Oxnard, California.
I fell into makeup
through musical theater
when I was in high school,
and it just ballooned
from there.
I love loud, beautiful,
crazy characters,
so I chose the life side.
I want to create a really
ethereal goddess-like character,
and I'm ecstatic
because the prosthetic
that I got is perfect.
That is gorgeous.
_
First, I fall down,
and I don't make it
to the death side.
Now the neck prosthetic
in my box is scarred
as if someone was burned.
How am I gonna incorporate this
into a life makeup?
My name is Scott.
About three years back,
my son and I took
special-effects classes,
rejuvenating the passion
I've had
since I was ten years old.
I hope Face Off will give me
the opportunity
to pursue a career
in special-effects makeup.
I got to make you
some eyeholes here.
Finally, I decide to turn
this neck piece
into a face piece.
You're gonna be
an intergalactic savior.
I may be down,
but I'm not giving up.
Let's see where these
fit on you.
I'm Drew, and I teach
at the Tom Savini school
of make-up effects,
but my end goal is to work
in a shop or on set.
- Nice!
- Yeah.
There are actually
two prosthetics in my box,
so I put the tumor-y face piece
on his chin.
_
I decide that my character
is a foot soldier
from the underworld,
who comes to deal death
upon the living
through disease and pestilence.
All right, I guess
we're going a little tribally.
Okay.
Let's see how this goes on.
Cool.
I decide
to make my character...
♪ the life warrior ♪
You know, life's a struggle.
People have to fight
their way through it.
We're fighting off death,
which is creeping on you.
My name is Cig Neutron.
I'm originally
from New Castle, Indiana.
As soon as I graduated
makeup school,
I flew like a bat out of hell
across the country
and ended up in LA.
I've been making monsters
for about five years now.
Hopefully, my kooky craziness
is going to take me to the end,
because I really want
to win this.
_
What are we going to do
with this guy?
My box has this brown nose,
upper-lip prosthetic,
and I have no idea
what I'm going to do.
And I see this jacket
that goes with the prosthetic
I have.
You're going to be
an elven pirate
that travels the seas
healing people.
I'm Barry, and I'm
a dental laboratory technician.
Making teeth pays the bills,
but my true passion
is making monsters,
so winning Face Off
would change my life,
not just my career.
I have a three-year-old son
at home.
Being able to put
just a little bit of money away
for his college
would mean everything.
I got these cool little tubes,
kind of, like, alien.
So you're gonna be mechanical
on the inside
and live forever.
I'm George,
and I've been a professional
special-effects artist
for eight years.
I've worked on big movies,
but I wasn't on set for them
or designing things.
I was just doing
what I was told.
So I'm still struggling,
but I'm hoping that Face Off's
gonna push my career
into a different level.
Could you imagine the headline?
"Winner of Face Off season 7
directs new sci-fi movie."
That'd be cool.
It's a pretty
gnarly piece here.
Inside my box,
I get bulging nerves,
so I put it on her neck
as some sort of bite wound.
I'm making
some kind of vampire.
Mm.
My name is Doc.
I've been special-effects makeup
for seven years.
My work has been
in theme parks,
but I would like to work
in film.
I've auditioned
for every season.
So to finally get here
and then immediately
McKenzie says,
"You're not on the show yet,"
is just gut-wrenching,
so I'm not taking no
for an answer at this point.
I don't even know
what to do with this.
My name is Gabby.
I'm a self-taught artist
doing special effects
on my own in Ohio.
I don't have a lot of access
to supplies.
I've had to make do with stuff
from the local grocery store,
so using professional makeup
is very exciting.
Stop shaking.
This huge boil-y prosthetic
doesn't fit
this more ethereal character
I wanted to do.
He's a creature that embodies
those self-defeating thoughts
that everybody has.
Now that I've cut up
the prosthetic,
there's no going back
from that.
I have to make it work
for my design.
Ahh.
I'm Sasha.
I discovered my passion
for makeup
when I built life-size monsters
for ceramics class
in high school
and went directly to cinema
makeup school that summer.
Mother Raven, Maven,
that's your name.
My character haunts
the graveyard
where she was attacked
by a whole bunch of crows.
You kill people
that come into your graveyard.
But the mechanical eye piece
in my box
has nothing to do with death,
so I don't want to use it
on the eye.
I'm putting it on her hand
as a piece of jewelry.
This is a huge risk--
disregarding the piece
that I'm supposed to be using
on the face,
but I know that is gonna make
this makeup better.
Dina, did you come across
the wig cap anywhere?
Yeah, it was there
on the bottom.
My name is Dina.
I'm from Chicago, Illinois,
and I've been a cake decorator
for about eight years now,
but I decided
to change careers.
With cakes, I'm limited
with what I am able to create,
but with special effects,
I can create anything.
I had pointed ears in my box,
so I'm making my character
into a forest nymph.
My box had a pair
of monster hands in it,
so my character is gonna be
a harbinger of death.
Man, it's been a while
since I've done this.
I'm so rusty.
I won an Emmy in 1993
working under Michael Westmore
on Star Trek, Death Space Nine,
but I left the industry
15 years ago,
so my wife and I could raise
our family in San Diego.
I'm hoping that this competition
will be a second chance for me.
_
Everybody stop working!
Oh, no.
Now what?
There's another part
of this challenge
that I didn't tell you about.
Oh, dear.
Oh, my God.
No.
Coming up...
Oh, my God.
I'm functioning on panic.
Don't fall.
- It's kind of amazing.
- Oh, man.
I've never been more nervous
in my life.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
We're 30 minutes into
our life and death challenge,
which is actually
our last audition.
Two of us will be eliminated
right away.
It's terrifying.
Everybody stop working!
- Oh, dear.
- Come on over here.
Oh, my God.
No.
And, of course, it's Face Off.
Twists are on their way.
Makeup artists must have
the ability to adapt
to the creative whims
of a producer, director,
and the ever-evolving script.
So I've brought something
for each of you
to incorporate
into your makeups.
But before I give them to you,
I thought I would bring
in an expert on life and death
who could give you
a little bit of advice here.
He's the star
of the upcoming films,
Fear Clinic
and The Last Showing,
and he's a horror icon,
known for his role in the
Nightmare On Elm Street films.
Please give a warm welcome
to Mr. Freddy Krueger himself,
Robert Englund.
Oh, thank you!
Oh, my God.
Robert Englund
had a huge impact on my youth.
It's just a complete honor
to even be in his presence.
You're all my children now.
All right, so, Robert,
what advice
can you give these guys
on creating a convincing makeup?
Pay attention to your model.
Look at his face
and build on that.
I think one of the successes
of the Freddy makeup
was that they kept some
of my own
facial structure there,
which I was able
to animate easier.
Freddy had the awesome hat.
He had the bladed glove.
How do you feel those items
helped create the character
that he was?
Well, you know,
we actors love accessories.
I mean,
I was inspired by the claw.
I was able to use it
an evil extension
of Freddy's own madness.
That's so cool.
All right, well,
here are your items.
Remember,
this is life or death.
So come and get 'em.
- Good luck.
- Bye-bye.
Yes.
What the hell?
I'm Stella.
I just got this diamond broach,
but my character is
a fertility goddess for animals,
so this broach doesn't fit
with my makeup at all.
Oh, this accessory is going
to be the death of me.
I'm 34 years old.
I feel like I've started makeup
really late in life.
I studied drama at NYU
but gravitated towards makeup.
Two years after I graduated,
I decided to do makeup
full-time.
Last year I took second place
at IMATS, London,
which was
such a confidence booster,
but I definitely think
I'm going home at this point,
because I don't know what I'm
going to do with this broach.
Figure it out later.
- Okay.
- I'll get you painted.
God, not what I'm going for.
My name is Rachael.
I'm from Chapel Hill,
North Carolina.
I graduated from
make-up designory in New York
in 2012.
I have Southern sensibilities
with a New York edge.
I like refined things,
but I also have a lot of sass,
and I'm willing to put something
up in your face,
and I think
that's gonna give me an edge
over my competitors.
Close your eyes for me.
My original concept
was a sea goddess
because there were
two seashell pieces in my box.
Now I have to incorporate fur,
which has nothing to do
with a sea goddess.
Fortunately,
I find a wolf nose,
and I change my concept
to a land and sea goddess.
I don't think it's as strong
as it was, so I'm worried.
This just keeps getting
weirder and weirder.
I'm Jason. I'm almost
completely self-taught.
I have my own very small line
of silicone props,
but my full-time job
is running one of
the busiest kitchens in Atlanta.
Ultimately,
I want to do makeup full-time.
This is a puzzle.
There was a tumor-y and veiny
forehead piece in my box,
so I decided to make
a cancer victim,
but now I got to incorporate
this spiky gauntlet,
so I need to change my concept.
I come across a shirt that looks
worn-out and very low-class.
_
I think the gauntlets
work better
with a "medieval peasant
that's been rotting
in the sewers" concept.
It's very weak,
but I don't have a lot of time,
so I just kind of
keep moving along.
_
How are things?
Oh, shit.
You sound like me.
I'm Gwen.
I've wanted to be in
this industry since I was six.
I was terrified of monsters
until my mom had me watch a show
on special effects
to see that monsters
aren't real.
Ever since then,
I wanted to be the person
to make those
terrifying creatures.
This isn't quite working out
the way I wanted it to.
That's okay.
My character
is the personification of death
as he moves through time.
I've already glued down the vein
prosthetic that was in the box,
and I was given bison teeth
as an accessory item,
and I'm thinking, "Yes, doesn't
affect the concept at all."
I'll just use them
as a necklace.
Maybe they're a trophy
that he gets.
One hour left!
Time is flying by,
and I'm trying to work
as quickly as possible.
So I make a piping bag
and pipe on water-type veins.
Maybe my cake decorating skills
will pay off
in this competition.
Oh, my God.
I'm functioning on panic.
He's not looking anything close
to what I want him
to look like.
I'm just hoping
I survive this one.
Ten minutes, everybody!
You got ten minutes!
Now it's starting to get there.
It looks badass.
Don't fall!
Time is up, everybody!
Brushes down!
_
I feel pretty good
about my character,
but there's some really tough
competition here.
I can tell everyone's
still really nervous.
Two people
are going to be eliminated,
and looking around,
I think I could be going
home today.
We're just really relieved
that that four hours is over,
but I can tell everyone's
still really nervous.
This is
a sudden-death challenge,
and two of us are going home.
Why don't we take a look
at your creations?
Let's start
with the life-themed makeups.
I am really happy.
I think I filled my character
concept really well.
I'm very disappointed.
I'm hoping that
they will overlook
many of my mishaps.
She might not be covered
head to toe in paint,
but she is
a full, realized character.
I'm a little worried.
It's an old-age makeup,
but it's also a robot makeup,
and I'm just hoping to God
it all works.
Since I did
his whole upper body,
I feel pretty good
about my character.
I think it looks cool.
I look at my model,
and I think
she's pretty gorgeous.
She really stands out.
I see a full character,
and I'm so proud of something
that I accomplished
in such a short period of time.
This was a brutal challenge.
All I want to be is safe.
Okay, it's time to check out
the makeups
from the death theme.
I like my character,
but I can't stop thinking
about the piece
that I'm supposed to be using
on the face.
My character
does have presence,
but it's not exactly as crisp
as I would have liked,
and I'm kind of bummed out
about that.
It's not great,
but it kind of showcases
who I am,
and I'm happy
with the way it looks.
I'm horrified.
It's an unacceptable makeup,
and I absolutely know it.
I think she really
speaks death,
but two of us are going home,
and I'm really hoping
that I'm good enough
to at least stay here.
From head to toe,
I love the look.
It has the feel of death.
I just hope that the judges
feel the same way.
I think it worked out.
I look at the character,
and I'm thinking,
"He looks pretty evil.
He looks scary."
I think my makeup captures
the death element,
but the makeup's not that good,
and I'm stressed out
about the double elimination.
I'm sure you're wondering
who's going to judge
your makeups.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Guys, come on out.
Hello.
Say hello to our incredibly
talented judges--
Glenn Hetrick and Neville Page.
Hi.
It's incredibly exciting
to see Glenn and Neville
for the first time
and also
incredibly intimidating.
Well, I'm sure you're wondering
where our fabulous Ve Neill is.
She's actually working
on the set
of The Hunger Games, Mockingjay,
but she will be joining us
on the reveal stage tomorrow,
and she has a big surprise
for you.
All right, well,
I'm sure you guys
are eager
to check out the makeups,
so why don't you
take a closer look?
Okay.
What is this in terms of life?
I don't know.
Watching the judges
is very stressful.
Just slapping the fishnets
on the jacket
seems like a complete waste
of that element.
It's very important
that they find
some sort of good in my makeup,
otherwise I'm doomed.
Which group was
your favorite-- life or death?
Tell us on Twitter,
using #FaceOff.
Was this a purposeful choice?
Yeah.
I'm hoping that the judges see
that I tried to be innovative
in altering the prosthetic.
- It's a cohesive idea.
- Yeah.
This I don't like.
Ooh.
Thank you.
This is extraordinarily
complete.
It's kind of amazing.
It echoes the model's beauty.
All right, here we go.
Well, that's a really cool way
to make a werewolf face
not a werewolf face.
Yeah.
What a massive amount of paint.
God, it's everywhere.
Thank you.
Now, this cold blue thing
could look like death--
quite the opposite.
Yeah.
All right, guys. Thank you.
Let's take a look
at the death characters.
The rib-bone idea
is both brave and effective.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
I like the idea
of breaking it up,
but it's just black, blue.
It's weird.
That's kind of
a cool paint job,
and then it just goes to mud
real quick.
Thank you.
Bison teeth--
they're fantastic,
and to just turn them
into a necklace
is a serious lost opportunity.
Thank you.
Super-cool color choices.
It's a head-to-toe
complete package.
- Gear forehead.
- Where's that--
On the hand maybe?
Bingo.
Actually, that's pretty cool.
There's nothing unique
about the application,
- and that's disappointing.
- Yeah.
Thank you, models.
All right, so how do you think
the artists did
for their final audition?
I was pretty impressed.
You guys did a really good job
first time
out of the gate here,
but there were a few
that really fell short.
Okay, guys, the judges and I
will see you tomorrow
on the reveal stage,
where they will decide
which 14 of you will move on
and compete for the VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
I really want to win.
100 grand would be my ticket
out of the real world.
It would be a dream come true.
Why don't you go back
to the hotel and get some rest?
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Good night.
- See you, guys.
It's been a rough
and extremely stressful day,
and now we have to wait
until tomorrow
to see whose head's
on the chopping block.
Welcome
to the Face Off reveal stage.
Tonight 14 of you
will earn a spot on this season,
but two of you
will be eliminated.
You guys had the pleasure
of seeing Glenn and Neville
yesterday
at your final audition,
but let's give a warm welcome
to our Oscar
and Emmy award-winning judge,
Ve Neill.
Whoo!
Yes.
Ve's awesome.
I've always had a great respect
for her and for her work,
and I think what she's done
is brilliance.
Thank you.
Now, I know you're working
on the latest films
in the Hunger Games franchise,
and unfortunately,
you won't be able to join us
for most of the season.
Yes, that's right, McKenzie.
I'm only going to be here
for a couple of episodes,
but you are going to be
in very good hands.
I assure you.
I'm very disappointed.
I love Ve's opinions,
and I was really looking forward
to hearing
what she has to say
about my work this season.
Well, Ve,
you certainly will be missed,
and with that said,
I'm excited to say,
we're adding another talented
judge to our panel this season.
Her resume is filled
with some of Hollywood's
most iconic films,
like The Fifth Element,
War Of The Worlds, and Lincoln.
She also won an Oscar
for her unforgettable work
in Braveheart.
Please give a warm welcome
to Lois Burwell.
Hello.
So great to have you here
with us this season.
Thank you so much.
I'm delighted to be here.
Lois is
an amazing makeup artist,
and I am so excited.
I think she is going to have
some really great advice for us.
Okay, let's get down
to business, guys.
Now, Glenn and Neville have
brought the ladies up to speed,
and the judges have separated
you into two groups.
One group is safe
and has earned their way
on to the show.
The other group represents
the week's best
and worst looks.
Group one is Cig,
Rachael, Stella,
Damien, George,
Drew, Barry,
and Doc.
Now if I didn't call your name,
you're in group two.
If you please go ahead and stand
with your new groups.
The group
that has earned its way
on to this season
of Face Off is...
Group one.
Whoo!
I'm on the show!
That is awesome.
I'm so relieved.
It's on.
It is so on.
Congratulation, you guys.
Group one, you can head
backstage and celebrate.
Group two, the judges
would like to speak with you
before making their decisions.
If you would please join me
over here.
Kaeghlan, please step forward.
- Hi, Kaeghlan.
- Hi.
Tell us the idea
behind this makeup.
I wanted to do a creative muse,
so I made a character
that's an inspiration
behind all creativity.
This is an impressive
first showing.
This feels like you incorporated
not just a goddess,
but something more specific,
which is, like,
the Hindu pantheon.
It's pretty exceptional
for the time that you had.
Thank you.
I think
she's absolutely beautiful.
You made great use
of your model,
and it's
a lovely color palette.
- Nice job.
- Thank you.
I particularly like the way
the headdress looks like a halo.
- Thank you.
- It's lovely.
Thank you very much, Kaeghlan.
If you would please step back.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
Sasha, if you would please
step forward.
Tell me a little
about this character.
This is Maven,
the mother of the raven.
She died in a graveyard
and tells all the crows
to attack
whoever comes in her graveyard.
The main piece
is your gear forehead,
and you kind of ignored it,
but the end result is you have
a nice, solid character.
To me, it works.
It's a striking character,
and it's well applied.
Thank you.
It's not extremely death,
but you managed to put together
a really beautiful character,
- so I think it's successful.
- Thank you so much.
Thank you very much, Sasha.
Please step back.
Scott, please step up.
Begin by telling us
what you wanted to achieve
with this makeup.
He's a celestial soldier
who battles the infernal forces
in order to regain the souls
that are taken by the demonic.
This is not a makeup
that works.
The use of the pieces
isn't that fabulous.
The color is off,
and this is not
a living makeup to me.
My main focus was supposed
to be the scarred-neck piece.
To me,
that didn't really emulate life,
so I constructed
the facial piece
using the neck piece.
That's a loathsome use
of the neck appliance.
I think you should have put that
on the neck
and then come up
with another backstory.
Everything is just so wrong
about this.
I'm really disappointed.
Scott, please step back.
Thank you.
Jason.
How does this character
represent death to you?
She is a well creature
and represents death
by eating her victims.
I'm not really excited
about this makeup.
It's a very muddy paint job.
I think you kind of flunked out
on this one.
I appreciate the fact
that you were trying to use
as much makeup skill
as possible,
but she is not just covered--
she's buried.
Okay.
The form, from the eyes down,
is wretched.
If you would have just stuck
with that forehead,
I think it would have been
rather easy to accomplish
the idea that you have.
It's the cheeks
that throw everything off.
Jason,
if you'd please step back.
Thank you, guys.
McKenzie,
we've actually already decided
on one of contestants
that will be going home tonight.
Okay.
Glenn, who is leaving us?
The first person going home
tonight is...
I'm worried for my spot.
I've never been more nervous
in my life.
I'm terrified.
I'm hoping for a miracle.
The first person
going home tonight is...
Scott.
Oh.
Unfortunately,
we just don't feel
like you're ready to compete
at this level yet.
Thank you very much
for the experience, though.
I'm surprised.
I don't think this makeup
represents my skill
as an artist.
Scott, I'm so sorry,
but you won't be with us
this season.
We all wish you the best of luck
with your career.
Please head backstage.
Thank you much.
- Good luck, Scott.
- Bye bye. See you, guys.
I'm very disappointed,
but being on Face Off gave me
a second chance
to revisit the passion
that I have
for special-effects makeup,
so I will continue pursuing it.
Dina, you're up.
- Hi, Dina.
- Hi.
Tell me about your idea.
I wanted to bring
the whites and the greens
from the set into her makeup,
so I decided to go for,
like, a forest nymph.
This design...
screams life.
It has spring.
It's sprite.
I think you should be really
happy with what you've done.
Thank you so much.
She is a lovely character.
I love the little veining
you did on her arm.
What did you do that with?
I'm a cake decorator,
so I piped it on her.
You seem to be
a very promising makeup artist.
That means a lot.
I really love that you chose
to pay attention to the set
and bring it into the makeup.
- That's really smart.
- Thank you so much.
Thank you very much, Dina.
Please step back.
Gabby, please step forward.
Can you tell us a little bit
about your character?
I kind of wanted my character
to represent
the small passing thought
of, "I wish I was dead,"
and it went horribly wrong.
I had this neck piece,
so I started trying
to make it fit into my theme,
instead of adjusting my theme
to fit the piece.
Okay, well,
that's a bad decision
right off the bat.
That was the whole idea is,
you take what you have
in the box
and you design something
around that.
Top half being blue and
the bottom half being black--
I always like when characters
have an element
of graphic design.
I don't think it's done well,
but the idea is good.
There's something
about the general application
and the use of color.
It's incredibly confusing,
and it's not appealing.
Thank you, Gabby.
If you'd step back.
Thank you.
Gwen, you're up.
Please step forward.
So tell us about your piece.
I wanted to personify death,
so I just decided, "Let's try
to make him, you know,
bubonic plague,
tumors, cancers."
So, if this guy
ever touched you,
you'd just
kind of disintegrate.
I think a lot of that
does come through,
but overall,
there's a muddiness happening.
The boils on the face
felt a little sloppy as well.
Standing back from it,
you get a striking image,
but the closer you get,
the more it falls apart.
Your bison teeth--
probably the coolest thing
you had to work with.
Why not stitch one
on the eye patch?
Yeah, I thought
about doing that at first,
but it would've just kind of
destroyed the whole eye patch.
If you were
that easily deterred
from ripping apart
a 50-cent eye patch...
I hope you get a lot more bold
- in your decision making than that.
- Thank you.
Thank you, Gwen,
if you'd please step back.
Vince, you're up.
So would you like to tell us
about your concept?
My concept
is a mutated zombie demon
who will travel
to another dimension.
Protruding from his cheeks
are rib bones
that serve as antenna.
I really think
that they are very good, indeed.
Thank you.
I like the colors.
I like the shaping
around the eye.
It's a very successful
overall look.
Thank you.
You allowed the pieces to help
you evolve your character
into a much more
complex entity.
- That's awesome.
- Thanks.
I think one of the best things
that you did was the red hair,
because that really presents
this makeup
in such a different light.
Thanks so much.
Thank you very much, Vince.
Please step back.
All right, guys,
the judges have heard
what you have to stay.
Will you please head back
to the makeup room
while they deliberate?
- Thank you.
All right, judges,
why don't we talk about
the looks you liked the most?
Why don't we start
with Kaeghlan?
It was a very big idea--
so many cultural elements
brought into one.
I thought she had
a lovely color palette.
It was a very pretty makeup.
And I'd be intrigued to see
how she's going to progress.
All right,
let's talk about Sasha.
It was such
a complete character.
I'm torn on this one.
It really doesn't visually
say death immediately,
but she produced
a pretty makeup.
All right, judges,
let's move on to Dina.
What a stunning makeup.
That brow piece
is very nymph-like
and beautifully executed.
And those little veins--
that's extraordinary.
She's thinking outside the box
in a purely creative way.
All right, judges,
let's move on to Vince.
If we were just judging
who made the best use
out of the piece
that they had to integrate,
he'd be my winner.
I love the fact
that he made the hair red.
Had it been not that hair
and that color red,
that could have turned
into a clown.
All right, judges,
why don't we move on
to the looks you like the least?
Let's start with Jason.
It failed him in the end,
but he was not afraid to use
all available
bits of rubber around
and try and build
something interesting.
Huge chipmunk cheeks
that go down to a pointed chin,
with a
big bloated forehead--
it's not salvageable.
All right, judges,
let's move on to Gabby.
The craziest thing
about her makeup
was shoehorning an idea
that does not work
with the choices she has.
I actually really admired
her honesty
for knowing how wrong
her choices were.
All right,
let's move on to Gwen.
Her ideas are good.
Her execution's terrible.
She didn't have to put
those other prosthetics on him.
It's better to make
a really cool-looking character
than to stick something
on their face just to do it.
All right, judges.
Have you decided who else
will be joining us this season?
- We have.
- Let's bring them back out.
All right, Glenn,
who is the winner
of this sudden-death challenge?
The winner
of this challenge is...
All right, Glenn,
who is the winner
of this sudden-death challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
Dina.
Thank you.
What an astoundingly
complete makeup.
I know that you decorate cakes
for a living,
but I think you might have found
your true calling in makeup.
Thank you so much.
I'm freaking out.
I'm just a cake decorator,
and I won the first challenge
on Face Off.
It's fucking awesome.
Dina, congratulations.
You, Kaeghlan, Sasha, and Vince
have all earned spots
on this season.
You can head back
to the makeup room.
Great job, you guys.
- Thank you.
Unfortunately,
that means the rest of you
are on the bottom this week
and one of you
will be eliminated.
If you'll please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Jason, between
the droopy cheek appliances
and the lackluster paint job,
it really seems like this one
got away from you.
Gabby, the decision
to keep your original concept
even though your prosthetic
didn't go with it
was ultimately your undoing.
Gwen, while the visual
was fairly strong from afar,
we really wish you would
have taken some more chances
with the items
that you were given.
So who is the last person
going home tonight?
The last person going home
this evening is...
Gabby.
There just wasn't much right
about your makeup,
but we do respect the fact
that you realized
how rough it was.
That means Jason, Gwen,
you have earned your spots
on this season of Face Off.
Thank you.
If you'll please
head backstage.
Thanks, guys.
It's been
an emotional roller coaster.
Going from happy to sad
and then to happy again
is exhausting,
but now I'm on Cloud Nine.
Gabby, thank you so much
for being here with us.
- We all wish you the best of luck.
- Thank you.
If you'd please head backstage.
- Bye, Gabby.
- Bye.
I really hate
that it turned out this way.
The pressure got into my head,
and my makeup was a debacle
but Face Off
has given me confidence.
I'm good enough
that I got here.
I'm not going to stop.
I love it too much,
and I will continue
to get better and better.
So we're officially on Face Off.
Season 7!
Yeah!
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net