Absolutely brilliant.
That's what I would want it
to look like coming out of my shop.
Previously on Face Off...
Sasha's creepy cracked clown
brought her her first win.
And Damien was sent home.
Now seven artists remain,
and tonight they'll
head back in time.
Exactly!
Couldn't agree more.
But some artists will
be schooled by the process.
- George Smash.
- You've got to be kidding me.
They are shockingly awful.
It's a great character.
In the end, only one
will win a VIP trip from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Being on the bottom sucks.
I feel like I've been
putting everything
I've got into my work,
like that nose
on that stupid clown.
Being on the bottom
with Damien was terrifying.
I do not want to be
in that position again,
so I just have to make sure
that I'm making good decisions
and stay out of the bottom
the rest of the time I'm here.
- I really like yours as well.
- Thank you.
- I really liked yours.
And apparently
so did the judges.
I did get three bottom looks
in a row,
and that still
have reign over me.
I've only been either top
or bottom equal amounts,
so I don't know how to feel.
We are in a high school.
- Oh, that's cool.
- Oh, I see McKenzie.
Are those lockers?
Oh, my God.
Just the idea
of being back in high school
makes me a little nervous.
But I'll just suck it up
and deal with it.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Welcome back to high school.
Exactly!
While many films
have depicted all the drama
that comes with
being in high school,
fantasy films
like Teen Wolf, Twilight,
and Harry Potter took things
to the next level,
proving that, even with
the athleticism of a werewolf,
the strength of a vampire,
or even a wizard's spell,
it's still tough
being a high school student.
Now, with that in mind,
your spotlight challenge
is to create your very own
fantasy creature version
of a high school student.
This is my kind of challenge.
I love fantasy, and I can't wait
to bring comedy into my makeup.
The lockers next to me
each feature the name of a type
of fantasy creature.
Goblin, minotaur,
cyclops, and faun.
You'll each choose one
as the basis for your creation,
but no high school
is complete without its cliques,
so take a look
inside the locker
to find out which group
your character belongs to.
Sasha, you're up first.
Cyclops.
Awesome, cheerleader.
Goblin nerd. Yes.
Goblin, too.
Jock.
Oh, clearly.
Faun.
Emo kid.
Cheerleader.
Minotaur.
Emo.
Nerd.
Okay, guys, it's time
to get started on your sketches.
I'll see you back at the lab later
when I come by with my dad.
Class dismissed.
- Thank you.
- See you.
I don't want to be
back at high school.
I didn't like high school
that much.
I was a choir geek,
so I'm thinking I want to bring
a marching band element
to this character.
I'm also drawing inspiration
from my sister
and giving her a really bad perm
and super nerdy glasses.
Goblins have big noses
and big ears,
so I really want
to accentuate those.
Making an emo faun's
gonna be really fun.
I teach at the Tom Savini School
of makeup effects,
so whenever
I hear the word emo,
it always just makes me think
of my students,
'cause that's 90%
of my student body.
So my faun
is this gothy, sad kid
who falls in with the emo crowd
because he feels misunderstood.
He's got black eyeliner,
faun ears, hoofed hands,
and he wants to be an effects
artist when he grows up.
Cheerleader is hard for me
because it's such
a one-dimensional stereotype,
pigtails and pom-poms.
In high school, that was not
the clique I was in.
I was a huge nerd,
and I'm still a huge nerd.
Because fauns have horns,
I definitely want to add them
along with ears
and some goat leg pieces.
In high school, I was
just kind of like the artsy kid
that didn't really fit in
but was friends with everybody.
I was on the video
announcement team.
My character's name
is Manny Minotaurey.
He's super nerdy.
So I'm thinking people get
picked on for being redheaded,
so he's gonna have
ginger skin tone with pimples
and glasses.
People call him a "ginger-taur,"
and they give him
such an atomic wedgie
that he can't get out of it,
so it's like,
"You'll never find your way
out of your underpants,
Minotaurey."
When I was in high school,
I was more obnoxious
than I am now,
which I know is surprising.
This challenge
is stressing me out
because I know nothing
about the whole jock lifestyle.
So I start by sketching out
my goblin character,
and he's got
this big long nose.
He's got tiny creepy ears
and a big pointy head,
but to make this goblin a jock,
I need to give him
a big thick neck and a flat top.
That's all I've got
that screams jock.
Guys, let's pack up
and head back to the lab.
- Let's go.
- Let's do it.
Give me a piggyback ride,
Cigarette.
Oh, God.
Oh, boy.
It's day one of our fantasy
high school challenge,
and we have six hours
in the lab.
We pick our models,
and we get right to sculpting.
I'm gonna make a face, a cowl,
and horns for my emo minotaur.
Since a minotaur is
a bull's head on a man's body,
the female version
of a bull is a cow,
so I'm gonna put a cow's head
on a female's body.
Makes sense to me.
Style-wise I think black hair,
black lipstick,
black baby doll dress.
Basically, Winona Ryder
from Beetlejuice.
I really want
a full-on, like,
evil face because she's
the evil cheerleader bitch.
- Got it.
- I'm the only one with cyclops.
I'm kind of nervous
because I'd like to usually see
what other people are doing
to make sure I'm following
the challenge right.
Everyone knows cyclops
has just one big eye
in the center of the forehead,
but I want this cheerleader
to be interesting,
so I'm going crazy with this.
She has a whole bunch of eyes.
Her skin's gonna be pale blue.
She's going to have a really
awesome cheerleader costume,
and she's just gonna be
the cool girl in school.
The first thing I do
is sculpt the horns
for my faun cheerleader
and mold them right away.
Then I start to make life casts
of my model's ears
so I can sculpt ear appliances
that will fit her perfectly.
I find the silicone negative
of the model's life cast
and brush some Ultracal
in her ear area.
After that sets, I'll be able
to sculpt the faun ears on top
of that Ultracal positive.
This is gonna end up
being a lot of pieces,
so I'm going to have
to manage time well.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Checking on you.
- Hey, Cig.
- Hey, how's it going?
- How are you doing?
- How are you?
Good to see you guys.
All right.
What did you pick?
I'm doing Manny Minotaurey,
and he's a nerd.
He's gonna have
pasty white skin and red hair.
I love it.
Be careful as far as trying
to make it all white when
you're doing your paint job.
Add some freckles across here.
That's what I was gonna say.
An auburn color,
a medium brown, little darker
brown across there.
- That's me in high school.
- Yeah.
I wanted to keep her
a little bit more human-like.
'Cause keeping the pretty in her
is going to be
really interesting.
Now, keeping her pretty--
you've got an expression
built in here--
Well, I want her
to be sort of mean.
Oh, okay.
Because that's how
I remember cheerleaders.
I want to do the flat top,
but what do you think
about this just kind
of peeking out the top
of the hair?
This is what bothers me,
is the peak.
You lose the whole idea
of the flat top.
So maybe just
sculpt a flat top.
Yeah, yeah.
- So I have an emo faun.
- I love it.
I said I was going
to make it look as much
like Glenn as possible.
That's Glenn as a faun.
Are you gonna add
that little goatee?
- Yeah.
- Keep it very sparse.
Because a lot of kids in high
school have just a semblance--
Yeah, I don't want it
to be fully developed yet,
because he's not, so...
I decided to go with band geek.
Band geek.
I love it.
Make sure you don't get into
too many wrinkles or anything,
because this could be
a witch real easy.
I have an emo minotaur,
and I'm gonna make her
overweight.
You need to add
a little more to the head.
So many overweight makeups
go up to here,
and they forget about this.
It just doesn't work well.
Okay.
You have the cyclops
cheerleader, right?
- Cyclops cheerleader.
- Okay.
But I'm confused, though,
because cyclops has one eye.
Cyclops actually just
means "round eye."
Yeah, be careful with that,
because so much
of the great fantasy films,
there's only been one.
One, yeah.
I mean, I didn't think cyclops
when we walked up.
I'm worried
that their saying this is not
looking cyclops enough.
You think I should change?
I'm just concerned
with all the eyes
that you have going on
around there.
All I can think about is,
I don't have time
to start this character
all over.
This is gonna be a disaster.
Coming up...
I don't know what to do.
Things aren't going well
for me.
That puts you in a tough spot.
It's just like,
bam, bam, bam, bam, bam.
It's day one of our fantasy
high school challenge,
and Mr. Westmore says
that my cyclops cheerleader
is not looking cyclops enough.
I'm just concerned
with all the eyes
that you have going on
around there.
- I would have done a larger eye here...
- Oh, yeah. I could do that.
...and done away
with these.
So what if I just made--
- I would make these wrinkles
across here.
- I mean, this is--
- Oh, yeah.
- So you could see through--
- Yeah.
They can be very tight,
where they can just barely
see through them.
- Okay, awesome.
- Good.
Thank you so much.
I will make sure it's a big eye.
Good luck.
Mr. Westmore's right.
I have to make sure
that this reads cyclops,
or I could go home.
McKenzie and I
are going to leave.
- Good luck, guys.
- Bye.
Thank you.
I need to make sure
that I get this cowl right,
so I'm getting rid of some
of the eyes, changing the cowl
so the wrinkles
cover the model's eyes,
and I'm making the center eye
a lot bigger.
I'm worried about being behind,
but I've just got
to push through.
He didn't like the pointy head?
Didn't like the pointy head,
and I want to give him
a big blockhead.
- Yeah.
Mr. Westmore
always has awesome advice.
The head shape I've roughed out
is pointy on top,
and that's not gonna lend
itself well to the flat top,
and as soon as he tells me
to make the head more blocky,
the whole character just starts
unraveling in my brain.
George Smash.
I can see
how the neck muscles are going.
I can see how the head
has to be.
Sort of tells me how the rest
of the character
is gonna look like.
He's a big thick,
just dumb jock.
_
I demold my ears,
and they come out great.
That means
I can use that positive
to now sculpt on their ears.
I really want take the time
and make sure
that this is really symmetrical
and that it reads faun.
30 minutes, guys.
God, I should make this look
as much like Glenn as possible.
I need to take my time
with this facial appliance
because I don't have many
prosthetics for this makeup,
and this one has to be
executed really well.
- He's a goat man.
- He's a goat man, a faun.
- He's so sad.
- He's so apathetic.
I am focusing on sculpting
a thin, symmetrical, balanced
prosthetic for the face
so that my actor
can emote through the piece.
That's time, guys.
Coming off of the bottom,
it's time to start bringing it.
I'm ready to bust
into the winner's circle
and show that I've got what it
takes to make winning makeups.
Day two in the lab,
we have 9 1/2 hours.
I have so much to do.
I have to make sure I finish
my cowl and the shoulders.
I'm hoping that I have enough
time to get both of them molded.
You're gonna do both
in two hours.
Both in two hours.
Does this look fatter to you?
I'm looking at my sculpture
with fresh eyes,
and it's not as full
as I thought it was.
In fact,
it looks a little emaciated.
I'm gonna make
bigger neck rolls.
Yeah, right there.
And now I have to spend
extra time
that I don't have
refining the sculpture
and making it as full
as it needs to be.
Dina, are ours still brother
and sister?
Yeah.
- Nice.
- Meg and Doug?
- Meg and Doug.
- Meg and Doug Oblin.
I just picture this character
saying his own name
like some kind of idiot,
you know, "Doug Oblin."
"Anybody makes fun
my little sister,
I'm gonna pound 'em
like that--
that thing
that pounds stuff."
He's like the super cool
older brother,
but he's really stupid.
"Doug, why does my inhaler smell
like your butt?"
"Why does your bedroom smell
like books?"
They get along.
They don't really understand
each other.
He thinks she's some kind
of bookworm,
but he doesn't really know
what books are.
"How many nerds does it take
to score a touchdown?
A lot.
Doug goblin."
He can't--
- I want to figure out
a cool way to do leg extensions.
I'm actually going to include
the calf in my sculpt,
and I'm going to try to bring in
that double joint area
that the goat has.
I think it's going
to bring a really cool aspect
into my makeup, so it's really
important that I get this right.
Bulls have horns,
so I need to make some,
but I don't want
to make huge horns
because he's still supposed
to be young and in high school.
So I get the ethafoam,
and I take it to the belt sander
and start shaving down
the horn shape I need,
but the foam itself
doesn't hold its shape,
so I put armature wire
through the middle.
Then I bend it
to where I want it,
and I hot glue the tips together
to get that point,
and it looks just like horns.
It's almost the end of the day,
and I've spent all this time
sculpting.
I don't have that much time
for molding,
so I've got to get in there
and get moving.
Everyone has already
opened their molds
and gotten them ready for foam,
but my mold's still damp.
It's got to cure
so that I can crack it open.
Oh, this fucking mold.
If it doesn't cure soon,
I'm in trouble.
It's day two of our fantasy
high school challenge,
and my mold's still damp.
If it doesn't cure soon,
I'm going to have
to run polyfoam tomorrow,
so I need this thing open.
This is literally the shittiest
foam I've ever made.
I roll it outside in the sun
in the hope
that the sun will help dry it.
This one takes the cake.
I'm just waiting.
I'm gonna open it
in the last 10 minutes
and hope
that it's good enough to open.
I don't know what to do.
I guess I just--
I got to come back out
when it's ready.
I love it.
- Hey, come here.
- Yeah.
So I start sculpting
these glasses
because normal glasses
wouldn't fit my goblin nerd's
freakishly large ears and face.
So I sculpt them out of clay,
and then I vacuum form them,
and, you know,
they look pretty good.
I think if they're a little big
that actually adds
to the character.
Whoo-hoo.
They make this look so easy
at Supercuts.
I find this great wig,
and I'm doing the thing where
you hold it in your fingers
and then you cut like this.
I really want him to be
like what was cool in the '90s.
- Like a mullet?
- Yeah.
I realize that this character
will look 10 times stupider
if he has a mullet.
Mullet flat top combo
is gonna give me the W.
That's the way to go.
Wow.
Well, I know my next haircut.
I go with hooves for his hands
because it's gonna reaffirm
sort of the goaty nature.
So I'm making foam hooves
and fabricating hoof pieces
to slide over his fingers
out of L200.
I'm really excited
to put this makeup all together
and to see this character
in action.
One, two, three.
I'm in a time crunch.
There's 10 minutes left.
Fuck.
I have no choice.
I decide I'm just going to crack
it open and see what happens.
Beautiful.
Oh, my God.
The mold opens like butter.
You've got to be kidding me.
I don't even have to spend time
cleaning it,
'cause all the clay falls out.
It's amazing.
That's time, guys!
I'm really glad that
I got this mold out in time,
so I'm feeling good
about tomorrow,
and I just hope
that application goes smoothly.
Whoo!
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab
and one hour in last looks.
Oh, my God.
I look at my face cowl,
and I noticed tiny bubble holes
and air pockets,
like, right here by the nose
and right here on the cheek.
The dampness
from my wet mold created steam,
and the steam
created air pockets,
so there's a lot to patch.
That is going to be a lot
of cabo-patch.
Yay.
Good, how are you?
Just like
the quintessential dumb jock.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
I leave my model a note
that says I'm in the spray booth
to make my horns.
I already started one
yesterday,
and I have to finish
the second one.
I take my two foam
blender strips,
and I attach them to foam cores
that have armature wire inside,
and I spray them
to make them nice and red.
Then I'm gonna apply them
to the wig
so that my model can wear it
without it pulling her hair.
Hi.
Did you get your note?
Really thick at the jaw.
As I'm gluing my face piece on,
I realize that I sculpted my jaw
too far back,
so the jaw actually covers,
like, most of the ear.
So I have to tear pieces away
to make that rounded shape
just before the ear.
I'm just gonna do my best
to make it work.
Still not ideal.
Yeah.
_
The application on the face
and the ears
are taking longer than I wanted,
and I'm gonna have to spend
a lot of time on these edges.
I'm also really worried because
everyone else's characters
are really overt,
and mine's more subtle.
And I'm starting to wonder
if she's going to read the way
I want her to,
but I just have to move on.
Otherwise, I won't get any paint
on my model.
So I finally get
all the air bubbles patched.
I'm painting the face,
and the steam pocket
on the cheek
is creating a wrinkle every time
I get it wet with paint.
I mean, it's right here
on the face.
I'm gonna open it up.
So I have to cut it open
and glue it down.
Probably just made it worse.
I can't spend too much time
on just this one area
because I still have
a lot to do,
so it's time to move on.
All right, it's better.
It's getting there anyway.
Mr. Westmore says
I'm really going to have
to sell the paintwork
when it comes to freckles
and that I should use multiple
colors rather than just brown.
So I go in
with the heavier stipple
with browns, yellows,
and reds to create
the actual freckles.
It's really looking
like freckly skin.
Perfect.
Hi.
I feel
like I'm ahead of the game,
but I have to make sure
this hair works out right.
I've taken inspiration
from my sister.
She had, like, a bowl cut
with a perm, so it was like--
She's just looking super nerdy.
It's really funny.
That's hilarious.
_
My makeup is very subtle.
I don't have big prosthetics,
so application and paint
on this makeup
are really, really important.
I'm taking the colors of goats
and the color of deer
for my color scheme.
I want to go really light
through the center of the face
and then blending out
to darker browns on the outside.
The faun aspects
are coming together,
and after I get the wig on...
Oh, my God.
...the emo character
comes to life.
That's super emo.
20 minutes, everyone.
At this point, things aren't
really going so well for me.
The face is really blocky,
so I'm not happy with it.
- Time's up.
- Yes!
I've already gone
down the wrong path.
My only hope
is that there's somebody else
who went down an even
more wrong path to rescue me.
Coming up...
Son on of a bitch.
This is the worst
I've ever felt onstage.
It's the high point for you
thus far.
For me, it doesn't work.
So we're actually going
to do wardrobe first.
We get to the stage
for last looks.
I only have an hour, so
I first get her in her costume.
I have a lot of details
I have to do still.
Okay.
Airbrushing.
Son of a bitch.
I dipped my pinky
into a different color
on the Kryolan
grease paint palette,
and I end up with this big
red blotch right over his lip.
So I now have to do
a skin layer
and then do a beard shadow layer
just to get it fixed.
I may have
to sacrifice these horns
because there's a lot
of weight,
and even though I adjust it,
it's still too heavy.
Oh, well.
So I'm going to have
to forgo them.
They are important,
because fauns have horns,
but I'm out of time,
and I don't have a choice.
It's 15 minutes, guys.
That's time, everybody.
Nerd.
Time's up, and I'm not happy
with the makeup,
and I'm really disappointed
I didn't get to do the horns.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
First, let's say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve
Makeup Effects Studio
Glenn Hetrick.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, Glenn.
Oscar-winning makeup artist
Lois Burwell.
- Hello, everyone.
- Hello, Lois.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
Good evening.
- Hello.
- All right, guys.
This week,
your spotlight challenge
was to make a fantasy creature
high school student
using a classic clique
as inspiration.
Let's take a look
at your students.
He's totally attitude-y.
He would totally be a student
at this mythical high school.
He's trying to pick out
the wedgie,
and even from where
I'm standing,
I can see that snot
glistening on his nose.
I didn't realize until now
that she's way too alien,
and aliens
was not the challenge.
This is almost, like,
so over the top
that I can't actually imagine
someone being this nerdy.
It's not my best work.
I wish it could be
a little more goblin-y,
but he looks like a dumb jock.
I'm still wishing
I had those horns
and that I had bumped up more
in the faun area.
I'll be really disappointed
if this is what takes me home.
As I'm looking at it,
I'm feeling maybe it's
a little bit too cow
and not enough minotaur.
Judges, why don't you
take a closer look
at this year's class?
Wow, that application's
really clean.
That's one of the best noses
I've seen on the show.
And the hair looks sort
of stuck on, but then again,
so does mine sometimes.
It comes with the look, so...
I love that we're getting
some texture--
some real sculpted texture
that feels genuine.
Even the runny nose
is hilarious, and look,
there's even freckles
on the arms.
I think that's rather sweet.
Could you open your mouth?
Okay, how many eyes
does a cyclops have?
Generally one.
She looks like a space alien
walking around with pom-poms,
not a cheerleader.
- Exactly.
- If you take this away...
You don't know what it is.
...you'd never know.
I can't even watch.
I'm just so nervous.
This is the worst
I've ever felt onstage.
I'm so embarrassed.
Who made your favorite fantasy
creature high school student?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
It doesn't even feel
like a cheerleader.
She doesn't fit in,
and she was supposed
to be the coolest girl here.
So I have a problem.
The one positive thing
is the fact that it's blinded
where the eyes are.
I really love
the oversized scale
of some of her proportions.
It's really cartoony.
I've definitely never seen
anything like it.
Need a little more
skin texture here, though.
This is very, like, barren.
The braces on her teeth
are great.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I don't understand the shapes
at all.
He's just not taking advantage
of any of the visual cues
that would say goblin.
The whole thing
looks like a mask.
Look at the ear.
What the hell?
The decision
to drop your blending edge
right there on the cheek,
it makes it almost impossible
for her to succeed.
That, and the rough texture,
are really working against her.
Where's the ears?
Take a look at one other
detail, which is down here.
It's an interesting idea.
- It's just poorly executed.
- Looks rough.
Mm-hmm.
The application
around the eyes is very nice.
This spotting,
that's a nice moment
as it comes off
of that and fades
into another color.
I like how the nose
and the mouth are,
but then you come down to this.
That's really very elegant.
But it doesn't feel
like a bull.
That's because she's a girl.
Okay, the judges
have scored your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Dina,
Sasha,
Stella...
Congratulations
because you are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Nice work.
I'm in shock.
I can't believe I'm safe.
I feel like
I just pulled off a miracle.
The rest of you were the best
and the worst this week.
The judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Drew, could you please step up?
Drew, tell us
about your character.
This is Devon Faunda,
the emo faun.
And he's emo because nobody
listens to what he has to say,
so he's resorted to dark music
and sad times alone.
This is a new zenith.
It's the high point for you
thus far.
There's something
about his expression
that reminds me of
a specific oil painting of pan,
and to make it
so accurate is wonderful,
and it has your twist on it.
Thank you.
I think
it's extremely well done.
I think the color palette
is extremely good.
The forms are so good
on his face.
The focus is entirely where
it needs to be, so very nice.
Thank you.
Drew, please step back.
- Thanks, buddy.
- Oh, don't touch me.
- Great job.
- Thanks.
Rachael, please step
to the center.
Please tell us
about your makeup.
So this is Courtney Faunda.
She is the most popular girl
in school.
She's a Mean Girls character,
and I actually had horns but
didn't want to add any weight,
so I didn't choose to do that.
There are some things
about makeup that concern me.
The frown shape of the sculpt,
it makes her look
almost demon-like.
I'm curious about the ears.
They seem to be hidden.
Was that a choice,
or how it ended up?
No, it was just
how it ended up.
Yeah, that wasn't
really intentional.
For me, this week,
it doesn't work.
It's so simple conceptually.
It's hard to find the faun
in this.
I think I know maybe
where you were going with it,
but I just can't see it.
Got you.
The ears
I thought were gorgeous.
Unfortunately, I can't even
take that into consideration
because that hair
is so voluminous,
and it is burying
the only aspect of your makeup
that says faun,
and that puts you
in a tough spot.
Yeah.
Rachael, you can step down.
Cig.
All right, Cig, tell us
about your creation here.
This is Manny Minotaurey.
He is the epitome of nerd,
and everyone's favorite joke
to play on them is,
they give him an atomic wedgie
that's so high up,
they wrap it around his horns,
so that way,
"You'll never find your way
out of your underpants, Manny."
It's a great character.
The detailing up close
is also solid.
There's still stuff
to entertain visually.
You've done a great job creating
a really memorable character.
Thank you.
My favorite thing
about this makeup
is the suggestion
of an expression.
This is not
the big inexpression
that we're always
railing against.
It can still move.
It can still perform.
I think a lot of the humor
resides in that expression.
I like the way
you brought the skin tone
down onto the arms,
that kind of,
you know, freckly feel.
But I really love the form
of the nose to the mouth,
and when he does
the "bleh" thing there,
it's lovely.
It's funny, and it works.
So very well done.
- Awesome. Thank you.
- Cig, you can step down.
- Congrats, man.
- Good work.
George, you're up.
George, give us the background
of your character.
So this is Doug Oblin,
and he is the quintessential
meathead, jock goblin.
What you think about this guy
now that you see him
standing here?
I wish I had found an excuse
for some more secondary forms.
I'm not super psyched on him.
I'm gonna agree with you
and up your need for secondary
forms exponentially.
It is blocky.
Not only is it sculpturally
really far away from finish,
it's not communicating goblin.
He's ending up
more of a muppet then a makeup,
and that's a problem.
And you really have
to practice eyebrows,
- because they are shockingly awful.
- Okay.
The whole thing is so abrupt
in the angles in the brow.
It's just like,
bam, bam, bam, bam, bam,
and like the eyebrows
being an abomination,
the ears are equal to that.
Agreed.
Thank you.
George, please step down.
Don't worry.
You'll be fine.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you had to say.
Please have back
to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
- Thank you.
All right, so let's start with
the looks you like the most,
since we do need
a class valedictorian.
You really seem
to like Drew and Cig,
so let's start with Drew.
This is definitely
the high point
of his career on Face Off.
The way he handled the color,
it all just swept up
and brought your eye right
into this beautifully handled,
professionally executed makeup.
I completely agree,
and I think the profile
was rather marvelous.
It's stellar work.
It's pretty damn close
to being a perfect sculpt.
All right,
what are your thoughts on Cig?
This is hilarious.
This may be the funniest makeup
we've had on the show,
but it's more than that.
It's sculpted well.
It's painted well,
and it's applied really well.
One of the things that really
impressed me was the neck.
The hanging weight felt like
a real heavy piece.
That's hard to do.
I think it's out and out funny,
and the nose is just marvelous.
This may be Cig's best makeup
on the show so far.
All right, let's move on
to the looks you like the least.
Let's start with Rachael.
This is
a pretty severe failure.
The missing horns,
missing paint job,
the edge glaringly laying
across the middle of the face,
it's not good enough.
It's missing the go-to points
that say faun.
And technically, I think she
was really under par this week.
- Yeah.
- All right.
Let's move on to George.
This is just horrible
because it's unfinished.
It looks like a muppet.
Well, we're in Q&A,
and he's kind of going,
"Oh, I wish I could have put
more wrinkles."
What it needed were the forms.
I think where he tripped up
was in the whole goblin aspect.
He's thinking
that classic goblin
where you gonna put big pores
in the nose
and wrinkles, et cetera,
but he couldn't because
it's a high school student.
All right, judges.
Have you made your decisions?
Yes, we have.
Let's bring them back out.
All right, Glenn,
tell us about the top looks.
Drew, we love the sculptural
forms of your face,
and this was
the quintessential goth vibe
that you got
with this character.
And, Cig, your minotaur
was absolutely hilarious,
and some of the painting,
particularly up close,
- really impressive.
- Thank you.
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
Drew.
You've chosen a great time
to step up your game.
This was your best makeup yet.
Good job.
Thank you very much, guys.
I win.
I'm the winner.
It's my first win,
and it feels awesome
to have won
with such a really fun,
cool makeup.
- Drew, congratulations.
- Thank you.
You and Cig can head back
to the makeup room.
Unfortunately,
that means the two of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
All right, Glenn,
tell us about the bottom looks.
Rachael, the trick
with the legs was quite clever,
but the only other thing
that was faun-like
were the ears,
and they were buried
underneath the wig.
George, we appreciate what you
were going for with this,
but he ended up looking
more like a Frankenstein
than he did a goblin.
So who is going home tonight?
The person
going home tonight is...
Rachael.
If you're going
to go that subtle
with all of your appliances,
then the application
must be exquisite,
and tonight, yours was not.
Rachel, I'm so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
That means, George,
you are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
There's no shame in getting
this far in this competition.
You've shown us
tremendous work,
and I cannot wait to see
what you do after the show.
Thank you.
Rachel, it's been so great
having you here with us,
but please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you so much
for the opportunity.
This has been a lot of fun.
We've enjoyed having you here.
Okay.
Thanks again, guys.
- It's been an honor.
- Good luck.
Thank you.
The most difficult thing
about going home now is,
it's not my best work by far.
- It's me.
- Oh.
- No.
- Yeah.
I'm just really glad to be where
I am and have gotten so far,
and I'm just really honored.
Love you guys.
This has been a really great
learning experience,
and I will always be
doing makeup,
because I love it.
This is definitely
a top ten experience of my life.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net