Welcome to a very special
episode of Face Off.
Tonight, the tables
have turned,
as the judges compete
head to head
with each other.
It's just an opportunity
to have a great time
and do what we do,
make some really cool makeups.
They'll each lead a team
of Face Off all-stars
and use every ounce
of their industry experience
to come out on top.
Oh, my God,
I've been wanting to see this
every season.
Good luck, guys.
Whoa!
That's a throwdown.
This is cool.
Loving it.
I'm havin' fun now.
Whoo-hoo!
This is tough to manage
symmetry on this guy.
Feel free to critique Neville
while he's working, guys.
Yeah, this is Face Off.
We're not worried.
This is what winning
looks like.
- Oh, her hands aren't painted!
- No.
I want her to have red hair.
Now I'm freakin' out here.
- Oh, my God.
- It's possible.
This is where
we succeed or fail.
Face Off is hard.
The winner of
Face Off, Judge Match is...
Watch it all go down right now
on Face Off, Judge Match.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Hey.
I walk into the shop,
and I'm very excited
to be back.
I'm interested to find out
what we're gonna be doing.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, McKenzie.
Welcome back to Face Off.
I'm sure you guys are wondering
what this special episode
of Face Off is all about.
Well, today, we're going
to do something
we have never done before.
Sweet.
We're turning the tables
on our very own judges,
and they'll be competing
against each other.
- Yay.
- Yes!
This is Face Off, Judge Match.
Oh, my God, that's
what I've been waiting for.
I've been wanting to see this
every season.
This is gonna be incredible.
Please say hello
to our fantastic series judges--
- Glenn Hetrick.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, Glenn.
- Hey.
- Ve Neill.
- Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
- And Neville Page.
- Hello, everyone.
We will be making
a $5,000 donation
in the winning judge's name
to a charity of their choice.
So, judges,
why don't you tell us
who you'll be competing for?
North Shore Animal League.
They use rehabilitation
and adoption efforts
to save the lives
of companion animals.
Ve?
A Window Between Worlds,
and organization that uses art
to help women
and their children
who have been impacted
by violence and trauma.
And Neville?
The Orangutan Foundation
International,
which is
a nonprofit organization
dedicated to the conservation
of wild orangutans
and their rainforest habitat.
Now, the judges can't do this
all on their own,
so that's
where you guys come in.
You talented people
are all here
because the judges
have invited you
to help them compete
against each other.
And as if the satisfaction
of helping
a charity in need isn't enough,
there's a prize on the line
for you guys as well.
The winning judge's
team members
will each receive $5,000 cash.
Hell, yeah.
This is exciting.
That's a pretty good payday.
All right, judges, it's time
to choose your teams of two.
We drew your names at random,
and, Glenn, you get first pick.
Sweet.
Of course, he does.
Now, there are obviously
no bad choices here
with this bunch,
but who is your first choice?
Ohh, it's hard.
What a great group
to have to pick from.
Laura.
Her application
and painting skills
are so phenomenal.
Neville?
I'm gonna go with Miranda.
She can sculpt, she can paint.
She's got raw skill.
And Ve?
Conor.
He's an amazing artist,
an incredible sculptor,
and I'm so happy that neither
one of you guys picked him.
I'd never seen him before,
so I didn't know.
That's true.
He wasn't here Season One.
And I would have
killed you anyway.
Got it.
All right, Glenn,
your second choice.
Wayne.
He has the goods to deliver
massive amounts of quality
in a very short time.
Anthony.
Anthony's highly skilled
conceptually
and very capable as a sculptor.
Good luck, guys.
- Ha! Whoa!
- Ah!
That's a throwdown.
Roy, you're the best fabricator
we've ever had on the show.
Yeah, baby!
He's amazing.
He can fabricate anything
that anybody can think of.
All right, judges,
why don't you go stand
with your new teams?
This is gonna be awesome, guys.
We have
the perfect fucking team.
All right, let's get into this.
Films like
Chronicles Of Narnia,
Charlie
And The Chocolate Factory,
and Pan's Labyrinth
turn the ordinary on its head,
transforming it into something
stylized and fantastical.
That's cool.
Okay. Good.
These chess pieces
are the starting point
for each of your characters
this week.
Hmm.
So we have the king, queen,
bishop, knight, rook, and pawn.
In this challenge,
each team will create
a pair of living chess pieces
that would be right at home
in a colorful,
stylized fantasy film.
Okay. Nice. We can do this.
This is cool. Okay.
I'm ready.
Are you lined up, ready to run?
I am lined up, ready to run.
Are you kidding me?
All right, let's go ahead
and choose which pieces
you will each be working with.
Neville, you're first.
Bishop.
Ve?
The queen.
Glenn?
Knight.
Pawn.
Ve?
The rook.
The queen needs her castle.
I love it.
This is easy enough.
I'll take it.
The king.
Ooh! They got
two big ones.
This is cool.
All right, so before
you guys get to work,
there's one more component
to this challenge.
Of course.
Since this season's theme
is life and death,
one of your characters
must be pure and pristine,
while the other
is evil and twisted.
- Ooh, I like that.
- Yeah.
All right, you guys have
three days for this challenge.
Choose your models
and get started on your designs.
I'll see you in a few days.
Let's go.
Let's go, boys.
First of all,
like, the evil queen
has kind of been done
a billion times recently.
Yeah, true, but she's so good.
I really want to do
a dark, evil queen,
and Conor says,
"Oh, well, there's been
so many evil queens."
There's never
been enough evil queens.
I want to do an evil queen.
You know, we'll
put our own spin on it.
She'll be fabulous,
it'll be different,
and after all, I am the queen,
so let me do what I want.
This guy can be
kind of like a creature
that she's cursed or something.
For the rook,
I want him to look
like he's been in there
for so long battling
that now he's becoming one
with his castle.
He could, like, break apart
and become partially human.
I'm really excited about
competing for my charity,
and I hope I win.
You guys have far more
experience in applying makeup.
No, you have all the experience
in applying makeup.
I have none.
I do a lot of creature design,
but I wouldn't say that
my resume screams of fantasy.
If anything, it screams more
of science fiction,
so I'm thinking there's a way
to manipulate this
in my favor.
If it's another planet,
it can be conceived
that they're aliens.
- Right.
- So one thought is,
let's make our bishop
the bad guy.
We're going to make
the bishop dark,
and the bishop hat is going
to be part of his head.
The bishop is pretty much
the one in charge.
Yeah.
I want to design
the bishop first
and then figure out what
the pawn could be later on.
I think the big thing, too,
is unity,
making sure that they both look
like they're of the same.
Yeah, exactly.
I haven't worked
quite like this before,
but Neville's process
of designing
is really, really cool.
Sweet.
I'm excited.
So our knight is gonna be
our champion,
and the king is gonna be
our evil king.
I know going into this
Neville's going to have complex
and beautiful designs,
and Ve's application skills
are phenomenal.
However, this is what I do
all day, every day.
If I'm not on set applying,
I'm in the studio building.
It is of
the most urgent importance
that my team have clarity
on what it is that I need
to deliver.
With the knight,
let's take the horse head,
but make it on a human body,
almost like a centaur-y
fantasy creature,
but we can do lots of armor
in the sculpt,
so it's not just a horse head.
And the king is going
to be diseased.
He's going to be really,
really sickly, pale skin,
boils all over him.
Instead of trying to cover
huge areas,
we're just going to pick
our battles.
So how long has it been
since you've sculpted, Ve?
30 years.
Under the circumstances
where we have no time,
we need to start right away,
so I started a headdress
for our dark queen.
Okay, here goes nothin'.
I think, well, okay, I better
start doing something
for the rook.
That'll keep him stable.
So I'm gonna do the chest piece
and the face piece
at the same time,
and we'll see what happens.
It doesn't matter in the end
who wins and loses,
'cause we're just here
having fun,
and I'm totally lying.
It always matters who wins.
I'm really trying to make sure
that we compliment
each other's skill sets.
This is a really, really
powerful team-up,
'cause Laura can sculpt
and design really well.
On the other hand, Wayne
is one of the fastest sculptors
I've ever seen.
He's gonna be so big.
It's like, how much clay
can you use?
We're gonna have Wayne
start banging out that horse,
so I give Laura
the king's face to sculpt
while I start roughing in
an armor helmet.
Your charity is...?
North Shore Animal League.
Aw, great.
Don't you have a cat?
Two.
You have two kitties.
I have two cats, and they
are the center of my life.
Aww.
What I'm gonna do is
jump into ZBrush
and start
messing with some forms,
- and then we can apply it.
- Okay.
We decide to do
a parallel track.
While they're building up clay,
I'm going to be doing a digital
version simultaneously,
so that we can kind of start
to see where it's going.
And what I'm observing
in ZBrush, it's feeling less...
- Bishop-like.
It's kind of like a competition
within a competition.
Whoever carves
the most appropriate path first,
that's where we go.
I like that.
Yeah, I agree that maybe
the two reads more demon.
Time's up!
Put your, uh, stuff down
and go home.
Nice try.
We'll stay back and clean up.
Hey, are you fabricating?
Yes, of course. What else
would I be doing?
I start working on some of
the armor for the rook.
Our idea is for the rook
to, like, transform
from the castle
into a guardian character,
and so I've made a harness
out of L200
and then just made
a little hinge
so that the castle
can separate away from him,
and then there'll be armor
and everything underneath
and weapons and all kinds
of cool stuff.
- Hi, dude.
- What's up, dude?
I'm just looking around
at people's stuff,
see where we're all at,
what we're doing,
and jazz like that.
_
Yay.
Why don't we get
massing in on the pawn
just so we can start
to see something?
- So we know something's there.
- Yeah.
We decide that the pawn
is the altar boy
and is slowly being turned
to the dark side by the bishop.
So it's kind of just trying
to get that little bit
graphically to happen.
This is tough to manage
symmetry on this guy.
You know
what's a little odd is,
all of a sudden being
on the other side of the fence.
Hey, Glenn,
do you find yourself
imagining what you would
say to you right now?
Just the critique of,
you know...
Why didn't you do this?
Yeah, what were you thinking,
you fucking idiot?
The kind of stuff
we say to you guys.
I don't think
I've ever said that.
I'm having
a love/hate relationship
with your piece right now.
Feel free to critique Neville
while he's working, guys.
Oh, this is fun.
These guys must feel good
watching us next
and going, "See?
This is hard, isn't it?"
Coming up...
Why does she need hair?
Well, because
I want her to have hair.
I'm, like, freakin' out here.
Is there anything here?
This is
where we succeed or fail.
Mothereffer.
Yeah, this is Face Off.
Fuck.
It's the first day
of our fantasy
chess piece challenge,
and I'm myopically focused
on our bishop.
I'm sculpting little things,
going in there
trying to get it right,
and I look up and I see
Wayne has massed out
this giant horse head,
so I figure
I'm gonna derail him.
Hey, Wayne,
if you could speed it up
just a little more,
I'm sure your team
would appreciate it.
Wayne is fast,
and I'm a little jealous.
Is it supposed to be a donkey?
No, ladies and gentlemen.
Got Glenn to crack a smile.
You know, Conor is so fast,
about 2/3 of the way
through the day,
we're ready to mold the queen.
It feels pretty good
to be the first one
in the mold room.
But then I have Conor.
He's fast.
Tres fast.
So I'm slappin'
that plaster on there,
and I'm confident that we're
in pretty good shape today.
One character down.
And another one about to go in.
Mm-hmm.
I think
we're doing really well.
Laura finishes her sculpture
for the dark king
in an insane amount of time.
I'm extremely happy
with all of the subtle details,
and it looks amazing.
Well, should I go mold this?
Yes, please.
We are going to be casting up
the king's face in silicone,
because we want that pale,
translucent kind of quality.
Let's do that two more times.
Okay, guys, time's up.
- Good job, guys.
- No kidding.
- Bye.
- See you in the morning.
Bye, guys, see you tomorrow.
It's not a donkey.
Well, it's
a terrible camel then.
I actually sculpted
something today.
- Did you?
- Whoo! Whoo!
There's a lot of
awesome shit going on here.
Did you guys actually do
what I didn't do,
which is think
about application,
think about moldings?
Because I kind of figured,
eh, I'll work that out later.
I'm a little worried
just about the massive amount
of mold-making,
'cause I still have
a whole collar
and big shoulder piece.
I think
we've got to go home now
and have a Martini
or something.
Yeah, let's get some sleep.
I need something stronger.
Okay, bye.
Top of day 2, it's all about
time management this day.
Stopping the sculptures
fast enough
to get everything molded,
cleaned for foam in time.
How far are you from starting
to mold that?
Probably a few hours at least.
Wayne, at this point,
firmly in charge
of that knight character.
Meanwhile, Laura's
finishing the neck piece
for the king,
while I'm finishing the crown.
This is
where we succeed or fail
in our ability to fully deliver
both of these characters.
Do you want me
to make these shoulders smaller?
- No, exactly what you have.
- Okay.
We have to do the chest.
Where are you
at with your construction?
I'm working
on the construction.
The goal today,
I'm just gonna make
everything that we do perfect.
I'm gonna start working
on the headpiece.
I want to make sure
that all the horns are filled
and all that kind of jazz.
I also really want to
finish off the chest piece.
You do all the matching.
And then I'm gonna go
check on Roy,
and I'm actually gonna help him
with the fabrication
for the rook.
So what can I do to help you?
Okay, um...
I have Ve Neill,
Oscar-winning makeup artist,
doing grunt work.
I am making castle stones.
I'm a great grunt.
Just tell me what I'm doing.
They're gonna be layered
onto this shape here,
and that's gonna create
our transforming castle.
I'm really excited about
how it's all coming on.
What about you, Roy?
The other two teams
don't have a chance.
Awesome.
That's what I want to hear.
Neville, that's beautiful.
Oh, thank you.
I'm getting a little nervous
about time, though,
'cause I've been treating it
like a real production piece.
Wrong!
Welcome to Face Off.
Right now, the eyes
of the bishop are just holes.
We're all gonna gravitate
towards the eyes,
so that area has to be right.
I think you're in the groove
of the grooves
on doing some of those details
and forms.
I do need at this point
to hand it off
to Miranda and Anthony,
because they're gonna be
quicker at detailing,
so I'm gonna jump
onto the pawn.
Where did you want
the horns on these?
They should try to follow
this shape.
Wayne and Laura
both are definitely
going in a great direction.
I think I have to stop Wayne,
as great as this is looking.
You guys got to start molding.
I don't want to keep sculpting
and then not have
some of the stuff get molded.
Yeah.
Everything just moved
to molding.
Depending on how far
they get with molds,
it'll dictate any time
that we have left today
what it is that we can do.
That's the fun of it, right?
Not knowing.
♪ It's a big-ass mold ♪
What do you think?
Can I mold it?
Yes.
We get our bishop into mold.
How do you want to do it?
Um...
However, what I'm starting
to get concerned with
is the fact that
I'm still getting the pawn
detailed out
and trying to get
the two to feel
like they're of the same world.
Dude!
That has me worried.
We just need to get it done.
Come on.
Today, I want to get that cowl
and that crown finished
for the queen.
We've got a prosthetic
on one of them,
we've got the cowl,
we've got construction,
we have a little bit
of everything.
All of a sudden, I realize,
oh, wait a minute,
it would be awesome
if the queen had
really long red hair.
Why does she need hair?
Well, because
I want her to have hair.
But there's nowhere
to have hair.
Well, there might be.
The only problem is that Conor
sculpted an entire head.
But this whole frickin' thing
has these horns.
I want this to be
a really great beauty makeup.
Not only do I want her
to be evil,
but she should be
very appealing as well.
That's really important for me.
Without hair, that's
kind of almost impossible.
I thought you were gonna do
a bunch of, like, red and black
feathers back there.
Well, I'm gonna do that, too.
I'm trying to figure out
what we can do.
It's just-- I want her
to have red hair.
I'm, like, freakin' out here.
I'm working on the queen,
and all of a sudden, I realize,
I really want her to have
long red hair.
But there's nowhere
to have hair.
Well, there might be.
It's really feminine,
it's sexy.
And if I want to put that hair,
I'll just figure out
some bitchin' way to insert it,
you know?
I could cut this out
right here.
I mean, it's your call.
We can cut a hole.
I decide
I'm not gonna do anything
until I fit it on my model.
I want to see
how it fits her first,
and I'll see how this
is all gonna work.
At the last minute,
I might just say,
"Fuck the hair,
let's go."
Yeah.
Glenn, how much time
do we have left?
About four hours,
just short of.
Okay.
Got it.
That is mighty impressive,
my friend.
I told ya.
We gotta jump on the molding.
We're behind a half-hour.
We keep pushing back,
and all of a sudden,
we kind of realize
there's no more time
to push back.
Oh! Mother of God!
This one is
a much more complex mold,
because it has to be done
in three parts.
Good thing there's three of us.
Down to the last minute, man.
We're running out of time.
Yeah, this is Face Off.
Oh, shit, this is cool.
That looks really great in red.
Thanks, honey.
Loving it.
I'm havin' fun now.
Whoo-hoo!
Damn, that's sick, man.
Everything we have is awesome.
Shapes, profiles,
but when they get close,
we have this to offer,
so that they can look
at some really tiny detail.
Yeah, that's badass, man.
Wayne working on that knight
gives me the opportunity to do
exactly what I wanted to do,
which is paint that face.
It takes time,
so I know I need
a couple of hours
to layer the colors,
experiment with it.
Because my team
is so efficient,
I have the ability to do that.
Oh, my God, dude!
We can help.
He's got it.
"Let me just grab
this 800-pound mold
and move it over here.
It's no big deal."
How's team Neville?
Yesterday was easy
by comparison, man.
The molding has truly become
a critical situation.
This, we're trying
to get out tonight.
It's possible.
We started this thing too late,
so we're just praying.
I really focus
so much on design,
because I typically
hand that over
to someone who has to deal
with my choices,
but now I'm dealing
with my choices.
Here we go.
15 minutes, everybody!
15!
Now we gotta run it outside,
clean it out with just seconds.
Mothereffer.
Oh, I'm scared.
- You got probably two minutes.
- We're not gonna get it.
We're down to the wire.
Let's go, let's go.
- Under there?
- Yep.
- Yes, oh, my God.
- Tape that up.
Fuck yeah!
We put the mold together,
and we have no idea
how it's gonna come out,
so I'm not gonna sleep
as well tonight
as I thought I was going to,
that's for sure.
Very impressive effort,
guys. Thank you.
Bye, honey.
Bye, Glenn.
I think we did great.
Nah, it was a great day.
I'm really feeling good.
I was concerned for you today.
You guys are still
over there sculpting,
the day's half gone,
I'm like...
- "When are they being molded?"
- Uh!
Guys, I don't know about you,
but I'm ready to hit it.
Let's kick some ass.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
- Yeah, groovy. - Bye, boys.
- Good night.
Good to see you today.
- How are you?
- Ooh, look!
Yes!
Come into the lab
for application,
and I really was
expecting the worst,
but our pawn head is fantastic.
It's amazing.
- Yay!
- Yeah.
We're not out of the woods.
There's no way.
We gotta run this bishop head
in poly-foam.
I'm so impressed
that that came out.
We mix it up, we pour it in,
we barely clamp
that sucker together.
The next thing to do
is, historically,
we'd now take
that coffee break.
We're not worried.
This is what winning
looks like.
No. With the sweat
from the previous activity,
we open up the mold,
and it's perfect.
Let's go seam it.
- Mmm! Sweet!
- Yes!
You are the horse,
and you are the evil king.
- How are you?
- Terrified, but good.
Yeah.
Today, I'm in my element.
This is what I'm familiar with.
I do apply, so I start
on the rook's prosthetic
to make sure
that there's no edges,
there's no funky stuff,
and that it looks immaculate.
The boys are in the back.
They have a lot to do still.
But I'm pretty confident
that it'll look
pretty fabulous.
Wow!
Yeah, that came out good.
Oh, God, that's awesome!
Might be cool to treat
this area right in here
with the same colors as this.
The very first thing
we need to accomplish
is getting that knight
out of the mold,
making sure that we have
one great piece,
and by "We," I mean Wayne,
so he's gonna get a piece out,
we can look at it.
Dude, that looks awesome!
- Came out good.
- Yeah, it did.
And, meanwhile, Laura
moves into application
of the silicone face
on the king.
The goal is
to assist her where I can,
because we have
a lot of different techniques
going on in that makeup.
You are in charge of the king.
All right!
- You're the kingmaker.
- No pressure.
Miranda is now applying
and painting that pawn piece,
and Anthony's jumped onto
getting some amount of paint
on the bishop miter.
Anthony had the great foresight
in tinting our latex black
for that piece,
which will make painting
quicker, but the graphics.
It's so important to me
to get those graphics on there,
and I'm looking
at the clock thinking,
we might want to speed it up
at this point.
I want to start working
on the beauty makeup
for the queen.
I decided that I do really want
her to have hair in the back.
My plan is to just
cut the back out,
pop her head on,
and then I'm just gonna
attach the wig in the back,
and it'll be fabulous.
- Good?
- Yeah?
I'm moving forward with doing
black and red around her eyes,
and then I'm gonna go back in
with her foundation
and burnish it in,
make it really look almost
like it has an airbrush quality.
That's something that
I've pretty much perfected
after working
with Tim Burton so long.
Oh, my God, that's beautiful.
It's big.
Wowee!
With Ve, we all knew
what was coming.
She's gonna deliver
an unbeatable beauty makeup,
and that's exactly
what she's doing.
She's clearly going to put up
stiff competition.
Shit, damn, that's cool, guys.
Coming up...
Face Off is hard!
We're down to the wire.
Nobody wants to let down
their judge.
Oh, her hands aren't painted!
Oh, wow.
I am totally blown away.
You will be choosing
the winner of this challenge.
How's that gonna work?
It is application day
of our fantasy
chess piece challenge.
I'm working on the queen,
and I'm having
a really great time doing it.
Roy's finishing up in the back,
and I go back because I want to
see what he's doing.
I just want to make sure
that he can get
Matt in there comfortably,
and that he can operate
everything.
You want some padding
in the shoulders,
or does it feel
kind of comfortable?
I think it feels fine.
So he has a lot to do still.
_
- are going to have to match.
- Entirely.
- Yeah, I think so.
- Okay.
And all I can say is,
I love it when a plan
comes together.
I just hope it does.
I'm working on the pawn,
trying to get everything done
as fast as possible,
but I'm a little scared
right now.
Both Glenn's team and Ve's team
got to pre-paint yesterday.
We don't have
anything pre-painted.
We don't even have
any pieces on our bishop,
so I am pretty worried
about time at this point.
Nobody wants to let down
their judge,
but, also, we don't want
to let down the orangutans.
When we put
the knight's head on him,
it turns out that the armor
has a big gap
in the front of the chest.
So we have this whole--
Is there anything here?
Nope, this right here
is still exposed.
There's a shoulder piece
that was initially
going to end up on the king.
All we have to do
is spin some things around
and think about it
the right way.
Waynester?
Yo? Oh, yeah.
And I absolutely love it.
The shoulder piece
actually looks
like a functioning piece
of armor.
You got to be happy.
I'll be happy
when this thing is done.
I'm a little worried
about running out of time.
We're down
to not just the wire,
but the core of the wire.
It's got me really concerned.
We don't have our staff.
We don't have our incense burner
put together,
and we don't
have things painted.
Okay.
I've never multitasked as much
as I am at this point.
I'm doing the staff.
I'm doing the staff head.
I'm doing costume details.
So I'm all over the place.
How the hell do you do it, man?
I'm making a stick with a thing.
I'm struggling.
It ain't together yet, so...
Hey, guys!
Judges?
Hey, Neville!
Judges!
Yeah!
Last looks.
You got one hour left.
Thank you.
Okay? All right, Neville!
Neville!
I'm just going over there.
Last looks! One hour!
No!
Yes!
Good luck!
- Okay.
- See ya!
All right.
This is weird with them.
Bye, guys, good luck.
- See you soon.
I think we just got
to get them in the outfits.
We don't have the bishop's head
or anything on her right now,
so it's a little scary.
I mean, miracles have happened
in last looks,
so I'm praying that one happens
for us today.
I can also go through
the whole thing
and put some rust,
or should we...
After everything's on--
hair, slime, spider webs
are on--
then that would
be the last thing.
I went for broad strokes
for this.
In these last minutes,
I really have to lean on Laura,
kind of have to keep
pressing her
to not be as good
as she can be,
to let it go.
Glue that on
and start webbing him up
and sliming him up.
And focus on the all-important
finishing weathering touches
for the king.
I got those gauntlets
on my queen,
and I'm tucking the strings in,
doing a couple
of little touchup things,
putting a little pink
around her face
and putting a little red
around her fingers.
I am so excited now.
We're coming down to the wire,
and it's bitchin'.
15 minutes, everybody!
We don't have stuff done.
Paint is wet.
There's just no way.
Got to get
her finger things on.
Where are they, Neville?
They're on the table.
We have so little time,
which is totally surreal,
and you're still doing stuff
that's meaningful.
Dude, that's awesome!
They'll love it.
Well done.
Can you start putting these on?
- Yeah, of course.
- Oh, her hands aren't painted.
- No.
- Oh, my God. Okay.
Hey, Megan, hold on.
You want paint them first?
Yeah, just really quick.
There's about 45 seconds
on the clock,
and I just slather paint
on her hands.
Okay, get the fingers on.
Do you have the incense thing?
- Yeah, it's right in front.
- Okay.
That's it! Time's up!
Oh, yeah, baby!
So this is how it feels.
- Good job.
- Awesome job!
Awesome! Boys!
Oh, man.
Face Off is hard!
Good evening, everybody.
Good evening.
How do you feel
about your makeups?
- Great. Awesome.
- Pretty great.
Awesome. Well, I'm glad
you guys are feeling good
about your characters,
but before we check them out,
I'd like to extend
a very warm welcome
to a couple of familiar faces.
Season Seven judge
and Oscar-winning makeup artist,
the lovely Lois Burwell.
And, of course,
Face Off mentor,
Oscar-winning makeup artist
and my dad, Michael Westmore.
Hi, guys.
It's great to have you both
here tonight.
How are you?
Well, I'm really excited
about tonight.
It's gonna be fantastic,
and I am so relieved
it wasn't me.
Well done all of you.
You ought to be.
All right, judges,
so remind us again
what charities
you're competing for.
North Shore Animal League.
A Window Between Worlds.
The Orangutan Foundation
International.
Now I asked you
to each choose two chess pieces
to use as a starting point
for your characters.
One was to be pure
and pristine,
the other twisted and evil.
And they were all being made
for a colorful,
stylized fantasy world
that we're about to see.
Let's take a look
at your creations.
- Wow.
- Oh, wow.
Very good.
It's so cool to watch
this challenge come together
and see pieces from other teams
standing next to yours.
It's a striking image, man.
I think we've done exactly
what we set out to do.
The king character looks like
it's ready for a fantasy film,
and the sheer size
of that knight character,
it's impressive.
It's a striking image
when you see all of it together.
I'm looking
at our bishop and our pawn,
and I'm so pleased
at what Anthony and Miranda
were able to pull off,
that I was able to contribute
with them.
I'm so amazed
that we finished it.
I am totally blown away.
They're just gorgeous
and stunning
and just scary and creepy
and everything.
I'm just over the moon
about it.
All right, now that
you've seen the makeups,
what do you think?
Truly remarkable.
Well done.
- Thanks.
- Yeah, tremendous creativity.
I agree.
All right.
Well, let's find out
a little bit more
about your makeups.
Glenn, why don't we
start with you?
Tell us about your knight
and king characters.
The dark knight seemed trite
and sort of hackneyed to me,
as did the holy, goodly king,
so I wanted to flip
that on its head a bit,
and Wayne's ability to sculpt
large, massive forms
with incredible speed
is clearly why we designated him
in charge
of the knight character,
and I honestly cannot believe
how big that sculpt is
and how fast he did it.
The other thing that allowed us
to complete
this amount of work
in the time that we had,
Laura's flexibility
allowed us to do this.
She's the backbone
that made it possible,
because anything
I needed done at any time,
I could just turn to her
and go, "Handle this."
Thank you.
I'd like them to hear
what you guys
think about the makeups.
Lois?
Oh, golly.
Well, I'm madly in love
with the horse, of course.
I thought you might be.
- Yes, absolutely.
- We both are.
Everything about it.
I want to take it home.
I absolutely love it.
And as for your king,
one of the cleverest things
was the choice
of the slightly
twinkly cobwebs,
because that just ties
everything together.
Well done.
Well done, the three of you.
What's amazing with these
are the details.
All your groups,
and especially your king there,
you've picked up
all these little nuances
that you could say,
"What more can be done?"
- Nothing.
- Thank you.
All right, Ve,
would you please tell us
about the pieces you chose
and the backstory?
I chose the rook and the queen.
Mm-hmm.
I've been dying
to do a bad queen,
and when we started
the discussion,
Conor says, "Oh, well, that's
like the obvious thing to do,
the bad queen.
We should do a good queen,
and then make the rook bad,"
and I said,
"No, I want to do a bad queen."
I'm glad you did.
"The rook can be good.
Let's make him
kind of like a transformer."
He comes in,
and, boom, he opens up,
and he's a warrior.
I chose the rook
because I had Roy,
because I know that all I had
to do was let Roy go,
and he can build anything.
Conor was sculpting the queen.
I started sculpting
the piece on his face.
And, mind you, I haven't
sculpted in 30 years,
so I thought, I have no idea
what this is gonna look like,
but came out
really good, I think.
Yeah, beyond.
It came out
really cool-looking,
and I was real happy with it.
So, Lois, dad, what do you
guys have to say about this?
It's extraordinary work.
Obviously, we can see
your style there.
How wonderful--
the nails, the fingers,
just beautifully done,
and the application
of the makeup
and the color choices
are superb.
Thank you.
We can see Roy's work.
What's so unique about it
is you've actually made
a third dimensional makeup
with moveable parts.
Wonderful.
It's great.
And, Ve, I think
you did a great job on the face.
It's like that little underlay
there on the cheekbone,
things like that,
it's like it's so subtle,
but it's there.
You know, when you get
on top of it,
- you can see all the work.
- Thanks, Michael.
Your queen is gorgeous, too.
Thank you very much.
And, finally, Neville,
why don't you tell us
about your bishop
and pawn characters?
It's an alternative universe,
and the bishop is
a political, religious figure
that over time has become
more and more evil,
and as a consequence,
his own anatomy
has started to consume him,
and the pawn
is essentially the altar boy,
who is being manipulated
by the bishop,
and as a consequence,
the bony form on our pawn
is slowly taking over
and starting to close in.
And we just basically kept
passing it around, all of these.
I jumped on the clay,
which is kind of scary,
'cause I haven't sculpted
practically in years.
I thought, let's stay
a little bit longer
on the design front,
and maybe that could be
our edge
from a competitive standpoint,
quite frankly.
But then I thought,
yep, might have shot
myself in the foot,
and I'll be carting
out sculpts,
because I spent too much time.
So I was really nervous
that I was actually holding you
guys back for a bit.
We're used to this.
Being held back by me?
Oh, no.
No, just rushing molds.
Get used to it.
All right,
so what are your thoughts?
I think Neville's done
an unbelievable job here
in capturing the pawn
and the bishop.
His backstory
goes well with it,
and I'm really impressed
with making the person blind,
because it's worked so well.
You've brought the pieces
down so far over the eyes
that it creates an illusion
that's very difficult
to get away with.
I love them both.
Lois, what do you think?
I love the shape of the bishop.
You can see the bishop's miter,
and I like the cleft
in between,
the way it's reflected
in the shoulders.
It's really nicely thought out.
And I love the pawn.
There's something
charming about the fact
that it's ecclesiastical,
and yet submarine as well.
There's something wonderful
about the underwater feel
that comes through,
and it automatically takes
you out into space.
It's very nicely done.
All right,
now, this is the part
where we would normally
ask you all to leave
so that the judges
can deliberate,
but we won't be doing
that today,
because you will be choosing
the winner of this challenge.
We will?
How's that gonna work?
You mean we have to think more?
We didn't see that coming.
I'm definitely feeling
some nervous anticipation,
but at the same time,
it's exciting.
There's such amazing work
out there.
All right, so here is
how this is going to work.
You will each get to cast
one vote,
but you cannot vote
for yourself.
You cannot vote
for your own creations.
Now, in the event of a tie,
the three of us will be
the ones to break it.
I think we can do that.
So as a reminder,
the winning judge
will receive a $5,000 donation
for their favorite charity,
and the judge's team members
will also receive $5,000.
All right, everybody,
it's time to vote.
Glenn, why don't you
kick things off?
Hey, Glenn, vote for me.
All right,
it's the moment of truth.
The votes are in,
and I do have to acknowledge
that this was a real close one,
which obviously speaks
to the quality of your work,
which was phenomenal today.
The winner of Face Off,
Judge Match is...
Neville.
Oh, guys.
Congratulations.
I'm truly shocked that we won.
Admittedly, it feels good
to have won, of course,
and to be recognized
by your peers in particular.
Congratulations, buddy.
But I really wanted to win
for the cause,
and I really also wanted to win
for Miranda and Anthony.
I think the $5,000
is just the cherry on top.
Even cooler to win
a chunk of money
for Neville's charity,
and it was so cool
to have been a part of it
with, you know, all of
these really incredible artists.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Great job. Well done.
I'm so happy for Neville,
and I'm so grateful to have had
Roy and Conor with me.
And I hope that people
have learned
a little bit about
A Window Between Worlds
and that it helps a little bit.
One thing I have to say
about my team
is not only did they do
an incredible job,
on top of that, they were
a pleasure to work with.
And although, ultimately,
our team didn't win
the challenge,
I do hope that we've raised
a bit of awareness
for a charity that I feel
very passionate about,
and people should check out
North Shore
and just see
what it's all about.
Thank you.
This entire experience
has been an unexpected delight.
I would definitely
do this again...
just not soon.
I need a little time to heal.
Thanks for the votes.
Don't thank me.
I didn't vote for you.
No, no, I'm not--
Thank you for joining us.
We will see you next week
for an all-new episode of
Face Off.
Good night.
www.tvsubtitles.net