It's quite awe-inspiring.
Previously on Face Off...
The 12 artists paired off
and brought twisted trees
to life.
Jason's beautiful bark
gave him the victory,
but Vince's flawed concept
sent him home.
Now 11 artists remain,
and tonight they'll spawn
an exotic mash-up.
Why don't you follow me?
Oh, my God.
What is it?
But some can't handle
the pressure.
- This is dumb.
- That sucks.
_
- It is exquisite.
- It's, sadly, a mess.
In the end, only one
will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Your beard takes a lot of work.
It does. To look this good,
it's a whole lot of grooming.
Sucked having
your partner go home.
I've been in the bottom
twice so far.
I feel like I haven't really
gotten a chance
to show
what I'm capable of doing.
I got to redeem myself...
again.
You just have to keep pushing.
I definitely feel like it's
time to bring my "A" game.
We're gonna go
see some "aminals."
We're walking up,
and we see the sign
for the wildlife
learning center,
and I'm getting excited
'cause I love animals.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
Welcome to the Wildlife
Learning Center in Los Angeles.
Now, this natural environment
is home to actually
70 exotic species
of rescued
and zoo-born wild animals.
But I do have a special
surprise for you today,
so why don't you follow me?
McKenzie leads us into
the Wildlife Learning Center.
Oh, my God, monkeys.
We're passing monkeys
and big cats.
Look.
Mama, oh, you're--
- I have no idea
what's about to happen,
but I'm just hoping to pet
some furry things.
Well, this is Danielle.
She's one of the biologists here
at the Wildlife Learning Center.
So why don't you tell these guys
a little bit about the center
and its mission?
We are an animal sanctuary.
We provide homes to animals
that don't have
anywhere else to go.
So we do give them
a permanent home here.
All right, guys, well, as you
probably can guess by now,
the exotic animals here
at the wildlife learning center
are the basis for your next
spotlight challenge.
All right,
and who do we have here?
So this is Kingston.
He is a baby squirrel monkey.
So I'm actually
gonna hand that--
and then just hold it
just like that.
Perfect.
Danielle is pulling out
all these animals.
There's an armadillo.
They can actually completely
close up into a ball.
- Wow.
- So scaly.
- There's a porcupine.
- Hey, little guy.
She actually has
30,000 quills underneath.
All these animals
are super adorable and awesome.
Whoa.
This is Delilah.
She is a red fox.
She is an omnivore.
So she'll go for almost
anything that she can find.
This is called a coatimundi.
They're found
in Central and South America,
and that is a tawny owl.
So they are found
in Europe and Asia.
Watch your face.
His eyes are, like,
staring into my soul,
and I realize
how awesome animals are.
So,Clash Of The Titans,
Sharktopus,
and the Harry Potter films
feature unique animal hybrids,
where different animals
have been combined to create
an entirely new species.
Your spotlight challenge is
to choose two different animals
from the Wildlife
Learning Center
and mash them up to give life
to your very own hybrid species.
- Yes!
- Wow.
I'm gonna leave you here
to pick your animals
and work on your designs.
When you're done,
head back to the lab,
and I'll stop by later on
with my dad
to see how you're doing.
Okay, go.
Going with a bobcat owl.
These guys are awesome.
I definitely want to stray
away from any fur
or, like, muzzled creature.
All right.
I see that the armadillo
and also the alligator
is up for grabs,
and instantly
my brain's like, "armagator."
So after everybody
makes the selections,
we sit down
and sketch our designs.
- Did you do the same thing?
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, come on, dude.
- No way.
I see George.
He has the same
armadillo-and-alligator combo.
- Imagine that.
- Yeah.
So we're gonna conceptualize
close to each other
to make sure that we're not
doing the same thing.
I'm gonna make
an "armagator."
They're like super soldiers
that utilize the armor
of the armadillo
and the ferocity
of the alligator.
He's good.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I have to do a hybrid
of a bobcat and an owl,
which can easily be a Furby.
Look at him.
He's so cool.
Well, and their eyelids
have feathers on them too,
which is really cool.
I decide to make this
witch character
that wanted the nine lives
of a cat
and the flight of an owl.
I'm gonna do cat nose
and mouth with owl eyes
and then maybe the cat ears
as well.
I have the red tail hawk
and the fennec fox.
This is the beak of the hawk
and that kind of hawk brow
into these almost bat-like ears
that the fox has.
I'm trying to avoid making
a full set of wings
or having to lay too much fur.
Wings always come out
looking kind of haggard,
and judges hate fun fur.
Tell 'em about the fennec fox.
Their big ears
are their main characteristic
that makes them stand out
from other foxes.
I'm going to use the ears
of the fennec fox,
the coatimundi face,
and coatimundi tail and paws,
and I'm gonna try and bring in
the fennec fox's coloring.
Doing animal hybrids--
definitely a little scary.
There's always a risk
of going too goofy with it,
not going far enough.
I chose the eurasian lynx
and the kinkajou.
My concept
is an escaped experiment
from a biological-engineering
facility.
I want to do big eyes,
but then go
with the lynx coloring
and then take
the kinkajou's nose shape
and then incorporate maybe
some fangs with that as well.
I picked the coatimundi
and the tawny owl.
I'm gonna try to keep
the coatimundi nose
maybe with, like,
an under beak from the owl,
and I really want to do
the big owl eyes.
I'm scaring myself,
because I think
I'm gonna have to do wings.
So I'm really trying to focus
on my design work
and make sure this animal
is going to look like an animal
and not just a person
in a furry costume.
Hey, guys,
let's get back to the lab.
Whoo!
We have 5 1/2 hours in the lab,
and everyone
starts sculpting immediately.
I have the serval wildcat
and the kinkajou.
The concept is that these
two animals are scavengers,
and through the process
of evolution,
they become one animal.
I'm trying
to put the cat nose in
and then the head shape
of the kinkajou,
which is really, really round,
so this should be interesting.
- "Armagator."
- "Allidillo."
I'm doing an allidillo,
which is an armadillo,
plus the alligator.
I want to do a quadruped,
so I sculpt the top of the head
on the back of the model's head
and then the lower jaw
over the model's face.
I'm taking a huge risk,
and if it doesn't work out,
it could be my ass on the line.
♪ Nothing is greater
than sculpts of a gator ♪
- What'd you get, Dina?
- Prairie dog and fox.
Oh, that sounds cute.
My red fox and prairie dog
are both diggers,
so I decide this animal
is basically a miner.
For the face, I'm gonna use
the prairie dog,
and I want to give him
the red fur
and the pointed ears
from the fox.
I'm pretty nervous
about doing a fur suit,
but, you know, I'm gonna try.
These prairie dogs...
they're so goofy.
Hey, guys, we're here
to check on your work.
- Hi.
- How are you?
All right,
so you have the bald eagle
and a squirrel monkey?
Something in flying monkey.
We'll put the eagle talons
down at his feet,
we'll give him
the monkey hands.
Maybe he has,
like, a bomber-type jacket.
I like what you've done with
your nose here and the muzzle.
It's very simian,
which is great.
All right.
So I'm using the overall body
shape of the squirrel monkey,
and I picked the red fox
specifically so that I could use
his fur patterning and color.
I come up with this idea
that if a monkey
and a fox were to come together,
they would be a perfect beast
that has the quick hands
of a monkey
and the sly cleverness
of a fox.
The monkeys do have a round
head, but the foxes don't.
The fox is a straight back
that comes through it.
- Yeah.
- You might even take this out.
- I like that idea a lot.
- Good.
I chose a coatimundi
and a fennec fox.
He's looking very foxy,
to where you're not gonna
really see the blend
of the two together.
The nose is very distinctive,
and don't be afraid
of bringing that out.
Okay.
The top half is on the back
of the head,
and the lower jaw
is covering the face,
so it's gonna look
like he's opening his mouth up.
To me, it looks more like
a prop than it does a makeup.
The anatomy
on both of these animals
is so much different
than human anatomy.
You're taking a big risk,
but it's a beautiful undertaking
you're doing, so good luck.
Yeah, thank you.
I'm having difficulties
with this model's face,
trying to fit it
under animal features.
You have to think
more into the nose.
The nose is wrong.
There is more detail
that comes around
through the nostrils.
- Mm-hmm. Okay.
- You're just missing it here.
I don't understand
why I'm having
such a hard time with this,
and now I need
to resculpt the nose
and bring it further
out of the face.
That is not good.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, guys.
Even as I'm trying
Mr. Westmore's advice,
it still looks stupid to me.
This is dumb.
I don't like this at all.
I'm not happy with it.
Ugh.
I just feel really lost...
and I don't know how I'm gonna
get through this challenge.
Ugh.
Coming up....
If it works it'll be
a fucking miracle.
I don't know
if this is gonna work or not.
This sucks.
My makeup
could be a catastrophe.
This is unacceptable.
I think it's amazing.
I don't think it works.
I'm really lost.
I'm trying fit the features
of the kinkajou
and the wildcat together,
and I can't figure it out.
Ugh.
I hate what I've sculpted.
I really have to, like, settle
on a shape of this face...
If I spend any more time
resculpting this,
I'm not gonna get
anything else done.
I can't do this anymore.
As I'm sculpting the face,
I'm really liking this.
Like, this is the first time
I actually got to do some kind
of creature-esque thing,
and I really like how it looks.
So I'm going to get it molded.
The kinkajou have
these really big, goofy eyes.
So I use plastic vacuform domes
to create the kinkajou
eye shape,
and then I cut them out
and incorporate them
into my sculpture.
I feel good about the direction
I've taken with my concept.
_
I'm molding the face,
which I'm hoping
to get ready for foam latex,
but it's taken a lot longer
than I thought it would,
and I'm cutting it down
to the wire,
but if you try and pull
a mold open to early,
you run the risk of cracking
the mold right down the center.
How much we got left?
11 minutes.
So I decide it is not
worth the risk
of trying to open too early
and not have a piece.
Time is up.
Ooh.
That sucks.
It's upsetting that I have
to eat it for the day
and open it tomorrow.
So I'm extremely worried
at this point,
because I'm gonna be behind
for day two.
Aah!
It's day two
of the animal-hybrid challenge,
and we have 9 1/2 hours
in the lab.
So I have resculpted this face,
and I'm still not happy
with it.
So I decide that since I hate
it so much, just get rid of it.
Just, no.
'Cause I rip off the entire
bottom half the face,
I'm going to sculpt it again.
I'm trying so hard
to figure out
how to put these features
on this man's face,
but I'm so behind, and it's
getting really frustrating.
I know I've lost a lot of time
on day one,
so I've got to get
the cowl done insanely fast.
I'm coming off
of being in top looks.
So this time, I want to win.
I need to get my face
finished and just start molding.
It's kind of a risk
to sculpt feathers,
because they're not gonna move
like feathers.
They're gonna be foam,
but I have a strong feeling
about this,
so I'm gonna take the chance.
That's one nifty-looking owl.
I sculpt the cat nose again.
I've got the wildcat eyes
and the nose.
The tip of the nose
that I sculpt is the kinkajou.
I don't know
if it's a good idea,
but I don't have any choice
at this point,
I just have to keep going.
Hopefully, the extra time
I'm taking on this sculpture
will pay off.
I need to get the cowl sculpt
finished as fast as I can.
The top half of the sculpt,
where the plates are,
is much more armadillo,
but I decide to go with gator,
like, scale-type patterns
on the gullet and the neck area.
I'm having a blast.
This is a challenge
that I was waiting for.
Since I waited till today
to get my fun fur
from the wardrobe room,
there is only
white fun fur left.
So this sucks,
because my fox is red,
and I know there's
a really awesome red fur
that Drew is using.
I feel bad
I used all this fur, but--
It's all right.
So I'm layering up
this white fun fur
with several different colors.
I'm going in with yellows
and browns and reds,
and I'm really trying to capture
that red-fox color.
_
I'm still worried about how I'm
gonna bring it into the cowl,
but I'm happy with the way
it's looking.
It's time to start working
on this fur/feather body suit.
And what I'm gonna be doing
is barge-cementing
all these feathers
and all this fur
to a spandex suit.
I'm really intimidated working
with both of these materials
for the first time,
but I'm really liking the way
it's coming along now,
and I'm feeling a lot
more confident in my work.
I need to make this body suit
now that all my molds are done.
And I can cut this L200 foam
to get what I need.
L200's really nice stuff.
It'll stick together
in a pattern that is really nice
for doing scales
or hard-edged creatures,
and once I get the suit
to a point that I'm happy with,
I get it painted,
and I have to put it on--
part for fun and part
just to make sure that it works.
I can't see it,
'cause it's on the back of me,
but from what people tell me,
it seems to be pretty good.
Yeah, it's fun.
I have the cowl sculpt
completed,
so it's time to mold it.
It's gonna take me
quite a bit of time,
so I decide that I'm going
to make a hydrocal mold.
Hydrocal sets really fast,
but I've never done it before.
- Hey, George.
- Yeah?
When you do
these hydrocal molds,
do you just make them extra,
extra thick on the outside?
You're supposed
to do hydrocal in one batch
- because it can delaminate.
- Oh, brother.
I start panicking
because I've already used
about three different batches.
So now it might delaminate,
which is when the layers
of stone just come apart.
And this is already set
back here.
This is fucked.
This could be really bad,
and there's just no way
of knowing
if this is gonna work or not.
_
It's day two
of our animal-hybrid challenge,
and on this particular mold,
I'm doing hydrocal
because it sets much faster
than ultracal does.
This is fucked.
If my cowl mold falls to pieces
because I did
some silly molding technique
that I've never done before,
it will be a disaster.
If it works it'll be
a fucking miracle.
Now that I have my mold done,
I'm doing a little bit
of fabrication.
The kinkajou
has these really long fingers
that they use to climb trees,
so I take these rods
made from L200,
and I melt them
and form them into shape.
And then I want to paint
the kinkajou eye
to look like the lynx eye.
So I take the domes
and airbrush paint
on the inside.
I test them for a while.
They look pretty cool.
But it all comes down to how
all the pieces fit together.
All right.
I go back to pop the mold open,
hoping it won't break in half
or into a million pieces.
I'm worried
I completely ruined this mold,
and because of that,
the sculpt is ruined as well.
_
All the stone seems pretty hard,
nothing breaks,
nothing falls apart.
Whew.
So it seems
like I'm gonna be okay.
It's almost the end of day two,
and I've only got one
of my legs finished.
It's one of those things where
you're just rushing so fast,
and there's not enough time.
All right, guys, that's it.
Time's up.
Now I have to run
the second leg
on application day.
I won't get to spend
as much time as I want painting
and getting everything
to look right.
This makeup
could be a disaster.
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab
and one hour in last looks.
I get the foam piece,
and it looks great,
but it's a little heavy,
so I have to hog out a lot
of the foam
so that the actor isn't crushed
by 20 pounds of foam latex.
I'm getting excited, and I can't
wait to get the face on.
- Hey. I'm Sasha.
- Hi.
- Good to see you. I'm good.
- How are you?
Hi.
Oh, my God.
My biggest concern
for application day
is that I have to get
the second leg poly-foamed
because I didn't get it done
on day two.
So I get everything ready to go,
pour the foam in.
I turn it upright
and let it sit,
and in the meantime,
I'm gonna meet my model,
check in on my cowl,
check the face.
It's a lot to do,
and time is just
tick, tick, ticking away.
It's weird
that Telesis hurts your skin.
Yeah.
My model is allergic
to Telesis--
the preferred glue
for something like this.
So I have to use another glue
called Pros-Aide,
which isn't quite as sticky,
and if he sweats,
it's gonna fall off.
So I'm definitely worried.
I get my suit off the mannequin
and get it on my model.
- Hey, it fits. Cool.
- Sweet.
It looks really,
really good on her.
She has a dancing background,
so she's doing lots of really
elegant modeling movements.
I'm really, really pleased
with the way it came out.
Go like this.
Cool.
Keep your eyes closed.
Okay, cool.
There's the belly.
Yay!
I love your belly. Okay.
I pull the shirt on,
and it looks really awesome.
I'm gonna have you put
brown leggings on.
But I don't really have feet
for her.
I just have leggings.
This could mean
that I didn't do enough.
Now I'm worried, because
you can make a small mistake,
and it can just send you home.
The color scheme I'm going for
is actually the eurasian lynx.
Their fur is generally white
with black and browns.
It's definitely hard to make
foam latex look like fur,
so I'm hoping that I can blend
the colors from my face
into the fur itself.
It's pretty much
a head-to-toe creature,
and it's a lot to paint,
and so I want to make sure
that all of those details
are added in.
I'll darken that up.
Ten minutes.
I'm gonna put your shirt on.
I put the shirt
on that I made for him.
Yeah, it doesn't match your skin
at all, lovely.
The problem is,
is that I didn't really think
about the paint job,
and the flesh tone doesn't match
the flesh tone of the shirt.
All right, guys, that's time!
Oh, crap.
What am I gonna do?
I'm panicking at this point,
because I only have an hour,
and I don't think
I'm going to be able to fix it.
Coming up...
In addition to everything
that I still have to do,
my model's face is falling off.
I run out of airbrush color.
I cannot finish his face.
This really works for me.
It sadly turned out
to be a mess.
Oh, there you are.
Hey.
_
- Can I steal your gaff tape?
- Yeah, go for it.
We get to last looks,
and I've got one hour left.
In addition to everything
that I still have to do,
my model's face is falling off.
So we're gaff-taping
this back on.
I still need to, like, wrap
them and everything.
I need to get her hands done.
I attach the fingers using tape,
cotton, and latex.
It's a down-and-dirty technique,
but they won't fall off.
Does it feel
like it's sticking?
- Yeah.
- That's 30 minutes, everyone!
I run out of my brown
airbrush color.
I can't finish painting
his face,
so I move on to hair work.
I'm very worried at this point.
I just want to get
out of here alive.
That's time, guys!
Time's up,
and I'm extremely worried.
My character is covered in fur,
and I don't have a lot
of makeup showing.
Freaking me out.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
Let's say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening, guys.
- Good evening.
Oscar-winning makeup artist
Lois Burwell.
- Hello, chaps.
- Hi, Lois.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
- Hi.
- Hi, Neville.
This week
your spotlight challenge
was to choose
two exotic animals,
mash them up, and give life
to an entirely new species.
So let's take a look
at your creations.
He has the color.
He has the body.
He looks exactly
like a fox monkey.
I think my makeup
is too cartoony
for this animal-hybrid
challenge,
but hopefully
I'm not on bottom looks.
The eyes are definitely
the most prominent thing
about my makeup.
Whether that's gonna help me
or hinder me, I'm not so sure.
I love it. It looks exactly
like what I wanted,
and he definitely has a presence
and looks really imposing.
She looks really elegant
but also
very animalistic onstage.
I'm really hoping
that the judges like it.
I know that it's not
my best work.
There is a risk
that his entire face
could fall off
and go plop on the stage.
I really did
an awesome sculpture,
but those leggings--
I can't even look.
The face--
it looks pretty good.
The paint's still not
what I want it to be.
I'm kind of really not sure
where I stand.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm trying to make peace
with the fact
that I might be going
home today.
The tail's not finished.
The feet look kind of janky.
It's not a polished piece,
by any means.
I'm not in love
with this makeup.
I would hate to go home
for something
that I'm not really proud of.
Judges, why don't you
take a closer look
at our brand-new animals?
There's some
really beautiful forms
- happening throughout there.
- Yeah.
These giant bubble gum balls
over the eyes--
it just never works.
It is the opposite
of painted beautifully.
I really like the way
that the main shapes
come from this
really large head.
It's got a nice prompt tissue
of an alligator.
These secondary shapes
are really nice too.
Look how this blends in.
I love that.
The dead, soulless gaze
of just colored orbs--
it's not so distracting to me here.
Way too big of an idea.
I appreciate swinging
for the fences,
but just no time for painting.
There's glue
all around the eye.
A huge amount of sculpture
to attempt.
And the other thing
she's done so well
is combine
the owl and pussycat.
There's a shocking lack of form
all down the side of the face.
Oh, it's insane.
I know I'm going
to be on the bottom.
It's not a good makeup.
I can't watch this.
We want to know what you think
of tonight's transformations.
Tell us on Twitter,
using #FaceOff.
- These hard ridges?
- Oh, it's insane.
I'm so embarrassed.
I know I'm in trouble.
It's just bad.
It looks like he's just
got stitched up
in one problem after the other,
and none of them got resolved.
Okay, the judges
have scored your creations.
Sasha...
Keaghlan...
Damien...
Doc...
Stella...
Cig...
you were the best
and the worst this week.
The rest of you are safe and can
head back to the makeup room.
All right, the judges would
like to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Sasha, you're up first.
Tell us about your approach
to combining these two animals.
Well, she is a bobcat
and a tawny owl.
She was this witch,
and she wanted to have
the nine lives of a cat
and the power of flight.
How do you feel you did in
terms of your success this week?
I don't really like what I did.
The leggings are pretty bad.
Do you know
what I think it lacks most?
Your confidence.
I think it's amazing.
You had phenomenal control
over color placement.
There's a lot
of great decision making,
supported by a lot
of amazing artistic skill.
Thank you.
You looked so worried when you
were saying about the leggings.
What I thought was,
"She used her time wisely,
and the eye goes
to where it counts."
- So, well done.
- Thank you.
What's extremely impressive
is the sculpting
of the feather work.
It works very, very well.
Thank you so much.
- Sasha, you can step back.
- Thank you.
Keaghlan, you're next.
Tell us about your character.
My character is
a eurasian lynx and a kinkajou.
She is a experimental animal
from a bio-engineering lab.
I don't think the paint works.
The color is flawed.
That's the major reason
why I don't like this makeup.
I do really like
the facial forms,
but the lack of detail
in both texture
and especially the paint
is a failure.
For me, it's lack of realism.
It's inappropriately cartoony
for this challenge.
I agree.
Keaghlan, you can head back.
Damien, please step up.
Tell us about your hybrid
and the "consequenting" design.
My two animals
were the tawny owl
and the coatimundi.
I wanted to incorporate
the big owl eyes,
as well as the tiny sharp beak.
This really works very well
for me.
You have balanced a design
head to toe
in shape, form, palette.
You've really showcased
what you're about.
Thank you so much.
Is that the first time
you've done something like that?
Yeah, it's the first time
I've ever done fur or feathers.
It is exquisite.
Thank you so much.
I like the way
that there are feathers
introduced into the fur.
The feather transition
on the arm is a lovely touch.
- So, well done.
- Thank you so much.
Damien, you can head back.
Thank you.
Awesome.
Doc, you're next.
Please step forward.
Tell me how your animals
inspired this makeup design.
Well, I got the bald eagle
and the squirrel monkey.
I wanted to create
a flying monkey.
It's a good idea,
but it is
a completely illegible concept.
How do you feel
about your work this week?
Awful.
I don't know.
I just lost it.
It's very refreshing to see
that you have the perspective
to go, "This is not
what I wanted to do,"
instead of defending it.
The shape of the face
could be there.
It sadly turned out
to be a mess.
The paint is so muddy.
The foundation's there
but none of the finish.
It's a little heartbreaking.
Sorry, man.
Doc, would you please
step back?
Stella, please come forward.
Tell us about your
two animals, please.
I chose the kinkajou
and the serval wildcat.
These two creatures
became scavengers together
and evolved,
taking on
each other's features.
But I definitely felt lost
during the whole challenge.
It's interesting
you would say that,
because I don't think it works.
My feeling is, you didn't work
to your strengths,
which is choice of colors
and the application
of the paint.
This is completely devoid
of anatomical sensibility,
particularly in the face.
I don't even see the two animals
represented here.
This is an unacceptable makeup.
Stella, please step down.
Thank you.
Cig, please come forward.
Tell us about the two animals
that inspired this concept.
I got the armadillo
and the alligator,
so I made an "armagator."
They're experimental,
amphibious infantry units.
There are some really,
really beautiful forms.
Around the jawline, his mouth,
and the gullet,
those three areas
are beautifully handled as form.
It reminds me
of some of the choices
that Cannom made with Dracula.
See the really big shoulders
and the bigger head,
and then is comes down
to these bunched claws.
- I think that's awesome.
- Awesome.
- Cig, you can step down.
- Thanks.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you would please head back
to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
All right, judges,
let's start with the looks
you liked the most.
Why don't we start with Sasha?
It's so clearly cat
in the lips,
and I think that was
the right place do that.
And she nailed the challenge.
It was the best hybridization.
She's got the eye
and the ability.
It's her confidence
that needs to be worked on.
All right,
let's move on to Damien.
I loved the character.
You would swear
that he has a lot of experience
making feather/fur costumes.
It's his first time.
When he put the feathers
all around the face
and dropped really light colors
on top of those feathers
to break them up,
that's complex,
artistic decision making.
All right,
let's move on to Cig.
It's really got
some gorgeous forms.
I absolutely love the profile
and the straight-on silhouette.
The throat round here--
I mean, all those things,
the component parts
were so good.
All right, judges,
let's move on to the looks
you liked the least tonight.
Why don't we start
with Keaghlan?
It's so cartoony,
and it's so stuffed animal.
I liked the overall sculpt,
just the blocking in,
but the paint
was so amateurish.
All right,
let's move on to Doc.
The paint job
has no definition.
There was no dimension to it.
The form--
there was promise there,
but every decision
was dreadful.
All right,
let's move on to Stella.
It feels like a solid idea
for a paint job
was completely given up on.
I neither saw the kinkajou
nor the wildcat.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
Yeah, we have.
Let's bring them back out.
All right, Glenn,
tell us about the top looks.
Sasha, your character's head
was a true standout,
and you nailed the hybridization
of your two animals.
Damien, you made
some great choices,
and we really appreciated
that you moved so far
out of your comfort zone.
Cig, there's some beautiful
forms in your sculpture,
particularly in profile,
and it really captured
the shapes
from both of your animals.
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
Tonight's winner is...
All right, who is the winner
of this challenge?
Tonight's winner is...
Damien.
You gave us a great makeup,
great fabrication,
and, more importantly, we felt
like for the first time,
your true talents
were on display tonight.
Me too.
This is my first win so far
in the competition.
It feels very much
like a weight has been lifted
off my shoulders,
and I don't need to worry
as much from now on.
It's so exciting.
Damien, congratulations.
You, Sasha, and Cig can head
back to the makeup room.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Unfortunately,
that means the rest of you
are in the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward, guys.
Glenn, tell us
about tonight's bottom looks.
Keaghlan,
we thought your makeup
was pretty rough
around the edges,
and its cartoonish styling
just made it a mismatch
for this challenge.
Doc, we did not see your concept
in the final product,
and the execution
of the painting and sculpting
was quite poor.
Stella, you admitted that you
got lost during this challenge,
and it showed.
We had a really hard time
finding evidence of your two
animals in your makeup.
So who is going home tonight?
The person
going home tonight is...
Doc.
It is crystal clear that nothing
went your way this week,
but it's great
that you're hyper-aware
of the problems
with your makeup.
Doc, I am so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
That means,
Stella and Keaghlan,
you're both safe and can head
back to the makeup room.
- Have fun, guys.
- I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Doc, you have talent.
You have passion.
So the only thing you're
lacking right now is experience,
and that's great news.
- Don't let this be a setback.
- Thanks, guys.
Doc, it's been
great having you here with us.
If you please head
back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- Thanks, guys.
- Good luck.
Good luck, Doc.
And I've spent
3 1/2 years trying,
and I've auditioned
for every season,
and then to finally do it,
and, you know, I made it,
you know,
further than I thought.
- It's me.
- Oh, dude.
To come this far,
I can finally just move on
nd say, "Hey, I was
on Face Off".
I said I would do it.
I did it.
And it's been an
amazing experience.
And it's something I'm
definitely not gonna forget.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net