RuPaul: Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
You'll be starring in movies
for the RuPaulmark Channel.
Ooh, come on, bitch!
- [laughs]
- I am putting a wall factory
where a wall factory
ought to be!
Why did you leaf me
all these years ago?
Denali.
I think you could have gone
way further with it.
- Kahmora Hall.
- You're so buttoned up,
and I feel like
you struggle with that.
- Kandy Muse.
- You were a joy to watch.
But your train look,
it's a little too plain.
Symone.
This has never been done
on a runway.
You are the Soul Train,
I tell you.
You're the winner
of this week's challenge.
[applause]
Denali, shantay you stay.
Thanks.
Kahmora Hall, sashay away.
- Girl.
- [sighs]
So we're back in the werkroom
after Kahmora's elimination.
There it is.
And, oh, I'm devastated
that I had to send
my closest friend home.
"Keep chasing the sparkle.
I love you ladies, Kahmora..."
All: Hall.
Now that Kahmora's gone home,
the competition is feeling
definitely a lot more real.
It just fucking sucks,
because I know every single girl
is now looking at me
as a bottom bitch.
I want these girls' respect
almost as much as I want
to win this competition.
Girl, let me tell y'all,
being in that position
is horrible.
- The bottom three?
- The bottom three.
You know what's even worst?
Lip syncing!
I still don't think you
should have been in the bottom.
I don't either.
Hey, I'm not a judge.
Wait, then, Kandy,
who do you think would
have been in the bottom?
I said earlier I thought Elliott
should have been in the bottom.
Watching it back, I wasn't
laughing, I wasn't kiki-ing.
I thought that her group
was stronger than she was,
and I thought
that Denali and LaLa
were both stronger
in their performance.
Really?
I'm here in this competition
for a reason,
just as well as everybody else.
I was brought back 16 times
for a reason.
So I'm sorry I wasn't
your taste of the week.
[all laugh]
[tongue pop] She is not a judge.
She doesn't get to decide
why I was safe.
My job is to win.
It is not to listen to peasants
and what they
have to say about me.
I was really happy
to be in the top.
Top two, if I say so myself.
But being that close
to "Con-drag-ulations,
you're the winner,"
and not winning,
it's like... I mean, I'm
so happy that my sister won,
because you know, girl,
the bald-headed brigade
is happening.
But right now, Symone
has two wins under her belt,
and she is my biggest
competition here right now.
No, no, no. No, no, no, no, no.
No, no. She's competition.
No, she's competition,
but right now...
But she ain't your biggest.
You ain't seen us yet.
You know what?
But from what I have seen,
my sister's
already won two times.
So for me, she's my competition.
I get it. I get it.
But she's not the biggest.
We all are here.
Well, we're gonna see.
I gotta bring you down
a little bit now.
The only thing that stopped me
from winning this week
was my look, so I know
that next week,
when I come back with my looks
and storm
the challenge once again...
- Okay.
- I can win the challenge.
- And be the winner.
How 'bout that?
If y'all feel that
that is shade to y'all,
saying that y'all
not big competition, baby,
then that's on y'all.
This is my competition
right now.
Okay. Remember you said that.
Just because you did
exceptionally well
in this particular challenge,
now all of a sudden
you sitting beside Michelle.
No, bitch, get back
over here in this line.
You number 12.
Take your original spot
right back over here
with this twisted,
busted wig on your head. Kapow.
We all met, and you said,
"Ooh, this cast is spicy."
Baby, you are the Sriracha,
bitch, okay?
[all laugh] Well...
Sriracha bitch.
Sriracha!
Tamisha works off
of negative vibes,
and Kandy lit that fire for me.
And my thing is
ain't no bitch gonna show me
what you don't know about me.
The pageant has started,
so now we can battle.
Tamisha, just because you've
been doing drag for 500 years
does not mean that
you are better than me.
It's a thin line between
confidence and arrogance,
and I can't stand that,
especially when
you're not on my level.
If she don't shut the fuck up...
She gonna find herself
a new enemy.
RuPaul: The winner
ofRuPaul's Drag Race
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100,000.
With extra-special
guest judge Nicole Byer.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
Aah!
[all laugh]
So it's a new day
in the werkroom.
One girl has officially
left the competition,
and being in the bottom three,
that kinda gave me
a little kick in the ass
to get my shit together.
Because you could easily
be out the door, girl,
in the blink of an eye.
I blink two eyes, but, bitch...
[door opens]
Hello, hello, hello!
[cheering]
Ladykins, guess what?
I'm throwing a birthday party
to celebrate the inner child
that lives in each of you.
Hi, baby!
[all laugh]
So for today's mini-challenge,
you need to shake, rattle,
and roll for Baby Got Back.
[laughter and applause]
You've got 20 minutes
to get into quick baby drag.
Go!
Baby, baby, baby, baby!
These girls look psycho.
RuPaul, you got us doing
some crazy baby shit.
Mwah.
All right, children, remember,
the most bouncin'
and misbehavin' baby wins.
All right, let's get
this birthday party started!
Hit it!
Now, first up, Kandy Muse.
Yes!
Ooh, she's a boss baby.
Now, that's a queen
who likes to pamper herself.
- Aah!
- Yes.
Baby wants a new daddy!
Ooh, who's a big girl now?
Yes!
I don't know why Rosé's baby
is terrifying me.
There's someone on your back!
That's what I call a baby bump.
Ooh, her diaper rash is on fire!
[all laugh]
Ain't nobody told LaLa
that she is three years old.
She is a full-grown woman.
We heard the music,
and she go,
oh, bitch, this is the twerk.
[all laugh]
Her milk bottle brings
all the toys to the yard.
[cheering]
Ooh, Shirley Temple
meets Shirley Temple!
[wails]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
[RuPaul laughs]
Now, you were all
cutie-patooties,
but I really went gaga
for one of you.
LaLa Ri, you are a winner, baby.
[cheers and applause]
You've won a $2,500 gift card
from FierceQueen.com.
- All right!
- Whoo!
Now, queens, for
this week's maxi-challenge,
we're throwing a ball.
- Yes!
- Whoo!
A bag ball.
That's right, you need to serve
three bag-nificent looks.
Now, look number one
is Mixed Bag,
a punny look of your choice
that includes the word "bag"
in its description.
Look number two, Money Bags,
a boss bitch look
that says "I own everything."
Opulence!
[cheering]
And look number three,
from scratch,
you need to design and create
a high fashion,
show-stopping look
that's made
entirely out of bags.
Oh, my God.
As in grocery bags,
sleeping bags,
duffel bags, teabags,
and things of that nature.
Lordy, I am feeling
a little shaken up.
I am not a seamstress,
and I have presented myself
so well on the runway.
And I don't want the look
that I personally make
to not be up to par.
All right, racers,
start your engines,
and may the best bag queen win!
[cheers and applause]
RuPaul: Coming up...
Is it cute?
You kind of look like
Dora the Explorer.
[all laugh]
Bitch.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
This week's maxi-challenge
is the Bag Ball, bitch.
Oh, no! I don't even know
what I have.
They're animals. I'm basically
left with these drawstring bags.
I was not prepared for Drag Race
to turn into fucking WWE
up in this gig.
So what are your ideas, darling?
I originally wanted
to use the pink beanbag.
After Miss Double T jumped in
like a flying squirrel,
almost knocked me over,
I found these bookbags,
and, like, I think
they're just really colorful
and, like, girly
and really playful.
Right now
I'm thinking to myself,
all right, book bags,
really, like, bright colors.
What am I thinking,
what am I thinking?
Hmm, book bags.
School. First day of school.
Ho. First day
of college semester.
Imma be a ho!
I was in the top last week.
I don't wanna be
in the bottom this week.
- Right.
- No, ma'am, I wanna win.
And my look
got me through, so...
- Ooh!
- [laughs]
This ball definitely makes me
a little bit nervous,
because last week on the runway,
my ass got read down
for my fucking dress.
I don't wanna repeat that again.
I definitely
wanna win a challenge,
and if I can win
the Bag Ball challenge...
The ball? Bitch...
Is there anybody
you're worried about?
Oh, yeah, she's incredible.
Olivia also is really good.
- Look, the stakes are high.
- Yeah.
And there's a lot going on,
but just stick to yourself.
You're over here
sewing up a storm.
I don't see much sewing
happening over there, so...
We'll see who's using
hot glue and Jesus.
[both laugh]
Are you experienced
with a sewing machine?
I am not.
If you need any assistance
with the sewing machine...
Well, I need to help
threading it...
Oh, here,
it has an automatic threader.
- Really?
- Yeah, so it comes down.
First you gotta go up into here.
This slant is
where the bobbin goes.
Okay. So we take this off,
this thread off?
Nope, you...
Let's just keep that.
Who would have thought that
this was just this complicated,
to put together
a sewing machine?
[laughs]
Done.
Thank you. Look at that.
- Your first bobbin!
- Oh, my God, I just bobbed!
- You just bobbed!
- Yes!
Come on, Miss LaLa, you bobbin.
Yes, I'm bobbin
and weavin' over here!
I still don't know
what the hell she's doing,
but I'm just acting
like, yeah, girl, thank you.
Just finish this for me
and let me boom, boom, boom.
Next season, girls, if you
need a seamstress, call me.
I'm available.
So I get to sewing, and boom,
bitch, I break the machine.
[sewing machine stops]
Bitch, oh, they're about
to eliminate me right now.
I done broke these people's
nice little machine, girl.
First round, machine.
Round two, let's go.
I don't know what to do,
because this doesn't bend.
- You know what I mean?
- Let me see.
I feel like
you need to cut this off
and then cut panels like this.
And then you could put,
like, rope in between.
Mm, I'm nervous.
I am kind of
spiraling out right now
because I don't have
the sewing skills
to do what I would
actually want to do.
You could do,
like, a panty with it,
and then, like, do, like,
a rope, like, belt fringe thing.
Ooh, that could be a moment.
Symone is stressing out
about this challenge,
which is so weird,
because she is one of
the most beautiful girls
I've ever seen in my life.
She really has
this inner situation
that really gets to her,
and that needs to go.
I just need to get her
back into that headspace
to remember
that she's that bitch.
I feel like we'll just
attempt to sew you into it.
That makes me nervous.
It does, but you're
gonna have to.
It doesn't have any stretch.
You can't slide into that.
I am literally...
I'm scared shitless right now.
I wanna know the tea.
Hold on. Miss LaLa?
- Huh?
- I heard that she was the one
that put you in drag
for the first time.
This is true.
- What?
- Yes, girl.
Miss Tamisha!
She put me in drag
many, many years ago, honey.
- So she's your drag mama.
- Yeah.
But I didn't really
take it serious
until, like, years later.
But she took a tour that day.
Tamisha Iman took me under her
wings, like, a few years back
as, like, her drag child.
But we haven't really
talked in years,
so I feel like
we're both here for a reason.
I feel like that reason
is for us to reconnect.
It was, like, what, five years?
- Yeah.
- A five-year, like, break.
Imans are known for dancing.
You can tell that's an Iman
right away.
While I was getting bucked.
Any time I put a new face
or a new baby in drag,
they become one of my kids,
you know.
So LaLa was an Iman
for that day, you know.
But LaLa
is not an original Iman.
I don't want the kids back home
to say, "That bitch
ain't no Iman."
But she is always
gonna be an Iman at heart,
so I'm still
the first drag mother,
and it's just...
It is what it is.
I'm looking around
at these girls.
I think Symone has, like,
a bra and panty set.
Where's Waldo Girl.
I'm really curious
to see how LaLa does.
I think she had to, like...
She ran out of something.
She had to change something.
So I came up with a plan B.
So I look at the bags,
I said, well, bitch,
you can hot-glue these together
and make, like,
a cute little dress.
So I started to hot-glue
the bags together.
As I'm hot-gluing the bags,
I realize that it's getting
less and less and less.
And I get to a point
where I realize, bitch,
oh, you ain't got enough
material to cover this body.
Aah.
I'm just gonna pray on it.
Lord, bitch... not bitch.
You know you're not
a bitch, Lord.
Lord, girl,
can you please help me out,
because I didn't come here
to be a bottom bitch.
So can you give me
some type of truth or knowledge
to surpass all of these
next challenges?
In Jesus' name, I pray. Amen.
RuPaul: Coming up...
So you gonna bring
two little scraps.
The struggle is real.
I want to be weirder
than Carol Burnett,
scarier than Tim Burton,
and all in one big pblblbl.
Okay.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
So this week's maxi-challenge
is the mother fucking Bag Ball,
and we are all so excited.
So this is gonna be
real interesting.
Anybody got a needle?
Mine just broke.
Is it cute?
You kind of look like
Dora the Explorer.
[laughs]
So, ladies, who's been
to the ball before?
I'm a big fan of ballroom.
Big, big, big, big, big fan
of ballroom.
It's an actual great place
to where
if you don't fit in anywhere,
a ball has so many
different categories
to where they welcome you in.
Girl, I wanna go so bad.
We don't have... like,
we don't have any in my city.
To hear Utica say, "Well,
I don't understand a ball,"
I was, like, okay.
This is my Jack Mizrahi
moment, you know?
Let me bring a little ballroom
to the room.
The category is drag queen.
Bring it to the runway!
[laughter and shouting]
I have admired balls
since before I admired drag.
Catwalk, catwalk, catwalk.
- Werk!
[cheering and laughter]
Because of just the pioneers
of the ballroom scene.
I used to hear a lot
about Willi Ninja and Leiomy.
She was a lot like Tandi.
She had no fear.
[scat singing]
Aow!
That's it?
- I got a bad knee.
- Oh, okay.
Category...
Now, that's a ball.
Now you can't say
you ain't seen no balls.
[all laugh]
Hey, squirrel friends!
- Hi!
Has anyone seen my bag?
- Which one?
- I cut it up.
All right, Kandy and Symone,
come on down.
Hi.
Kandy, you are always
in them short-shorts.
I just love showing off my body.
Okay. So, Kandy, sell me
on your ball presentation.
Well, first and foremost,
I'm gonna be a magician
on the main stage.
I'm gonna be pulling some tricks
outta my bag literally.
Oh, really?
There will be
no undergarments showing,
I promise you that.
Only body.
So now, Symone,
you won last week.
I did.
Are these other bitches
coming for you, because...
- They're coming.
- Are they?
With knives and bats and things.
- I feel it, I feel it.
- [laughs]
But that's all right.
It's a competition.
What can you expect?
- That's what you're here for.
- Yeah.
The only thing I worry about
with someone like you
is how deep your saboteur
might be, you know.
Because it's as clever
as you are,
and that's the part that it sort
of hurts my heart a little bit.
Yeah, it's crazy
that you say that,
because this challenge...
Of course,
I don't know how to sew.
I was like, you know what?
You have to make it work.
You just have to push forward
and do what you know you can do,
and work with what you have.
This is something that
happens in this room a lot,
is the negotiating
the other voice in your head,
and knowing to not listen to it.
The struggle is real,
by the way.
The struggle is real.
What you have to focus on
is what you know
to be the truth.
And I hope
that these other girls
are listening
to this conversation,
because I've been standing
at this table for 100 years,
and it comes up
every single time.
What are your musings
on that, Kandy?
I love it.
[all laugh]
I don't know
what the hell I just said,
but Miss Thing is over here
gagging her life.
That's fine with me.
Let her laugh.
Thanks, ladies.
Thanks, mother darling.
All right, Gottmik and Utica.
Here I come!
Oh, so you gonna bring
two little scraps.
[all laugh] I mean, gorg.
What do you think I'm wearing?
So tell me about
your ball extravaganza.
Do you know how to sew?
I did go to fashion school,
so, yeah.
Really? Where?
Here in Los Angeles?
Yeah, I went to FIDM,
so I have the basics,
but I haven't really practiced
in a couple years
since then, so...
Where does your style
aesthetic come from?
I'm really inspired by art,
and I'm a painter.
I'm inspired by shapes
and rearranging how, like,
the human face should look,
and putting things
where they shouldn't be,
and making it look
all distorted and weird.
Yeah. Is that, like,
a G-string something?
No, it's gonna be
a little, like,
corsetry artistry happening.
Okay.
It's really showing my body,
which I love.
My waist is gonna be so smashed.
I'm just gonna be feeling it.
Well, that sounds fantastic.
And now, Utica, tell me
about your fashion aesthetic.
Weirder than Carol Burnett
and Lucille Ball,
scarier than Tim Burton,
and like a little bit
of Alexander McQueen,
and all in one big pblblbl.
Oh, I love that.
You make outfits professionally?
I do. I make costumes
for fire dancers,
aerialists, contortionists. Um...
So you use a sewing machine.
Oh, yeah. These are actually
the same ones I have at home.
- You're kidding.
- Yeah.
Is that a sleeping bag?
- It's a sleeping bag.
- Uh-huh?
I'm really excited.
I think it's gonna be cool.
It's gonna be a bunch of these
different panels and gores,
and I want it to be as full
and as just delightful
as possible.
I dig it.
- I'm like...
- [laughs]
Well, I can't wait
to see you at the ball.
All right, Joey Jay and LaLa Ri.
- Hi, there.
- Hello!
The bags are in the house.
Where's your style aesthetic
come from?
I've always kind of
leaned towards, like,
edgy, butch queen realness,
sort of a little bit
lipstick lesbian.
- Ooh!
- Little whip crack,
little explosion, dance
mega-mix the house down,
boots back, bareback.
Sure, and those boots back
are scrunch boots, aren't they?
Uh, yes.
- [laughs]
- Yeah, a lot of times.
Are you talking
about this scrunchy boot?
This scrunchy boot
the house down?
You want me to play
the scrunchy boot for you?
I'm gonna start you
- with an IV bag.
- Ooh!
I'm very excited
about that look.
It's gonna be kind of edgy.
Medical meets
futuristic villain.
Well, you had me
at medical, so...
Perfect.
Where does your style
aesthetic come from?
Originally
I was inspired by Beyoncé.
Beyoncé.
And a little bit
of Grace Jones as well.
Yeah, I've heard of her.
And of course,
the girls around Atlanta,
the pageant girls.
You know, Atlanta's big drag.
Oh, when I was there,
it was the mecca of drag.
Do you think you have
this one in the bag?
I hope I have this one
in the bag.
Well, hoping and knowing
is two different things.
I'm gonna give it
the LaLa Ri experience.
- Oh, the LaLa Ri experience.
- Yes.
The LaLa Ri experience,
bitch, is en-tergy from...
Yes, en-tergy from LaLa Ri.
You gonna get a look,
you gonna get a performance,
you gonna get a moment,
you gonna get a feel.
You gonna be thinking about it
days on after.
Like, bitch, that ho
made me feel good.
All right, kids,
I will see you at the ball.
All right, thanks. See you then.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
All right, gather round.
Gather round, queens.
I've got one more thing
to tell you.
To add opulence
to your Miss Moneybags look,
you need to accessorize
using a fabulous
Coach Create bag.
And here's creative director
Stuart Vevers to explain.
Thank you, Ru.
For me, style
is about self-expression,
which is why I came up
with Coach Create,
a special design-it-yourself
experience.
For this week's challenge,
we've taken
one of my favorite designs,
the Tabby bag,
and sized it for a queen,
so you can step
onto the runway purse-first.
Good luck!
[all laugh]
Thanks, Stuart.
Queens, I'll see you
and your Tabby bags at the ball.
So good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
[laughter and applause]
The RuPaul experience is out.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Coming up...
Joey, come here, Miss Thing.
I have the biggest crush
on Joey Jay.
- Is this yours?
- Yes.
- But Joey's taste level...
- I feel good about it.
There's still a few things
that I need to, like, do.
Yeah.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
Ball time!
It is elimination day,
and it is time to get ready
for the Bag Ball.
I'm looking around the room,
and a lot of girls are, like,
doing very draggy silhouettes.
Mine is definitely more skimpy,
fashion-forward vibes,
as opposed to, like, drag-drag,
which makes me
a little bit nervous.
But I feel like I'm gonna win.
Let's go.
- Joey?
- Yes, ma'am?
Come here, Miss Thing.
I don't know
if y'all been catching on,
but I have the biggest crush
on Joey Jay.
Any time he's in the werkroom
I'm like, mm, hi, Joey.
- Is this yours?
- Yes, this is mine.
But Joey's taste level...
I feel like good about it.
There's still a few things
that I need to, like, do.
Yeah.
She seems really confident
with her look.
I'm looking at the costume
a little confused
as to what the hell
I'm looking at.
I know it's not, like,
the most exciting outfit,
but I think that once I can kind
of snip the last few things,
it's gonna be a clean outfit.
Joey, if you wanna quit drag,
we can get married,
I can win the competition,
and I can sustain both of us.
Because...
[laughs]
Oh!
So I have a question.
What's the tea?
So with the whole Black Lives
Matter movement going on,
has anyone been protesting?
Yeah, for sure.
When all the marches
and protests
in New York City were happening,
I made sure I was out there
protesting.
Being an Afro-Latino
from the South Bronx,
when I see Black people
being murdered by police,
it just puts so many things
into perspective.
Fighting for Black lives
is very, very important to me.
Of course, we all know
the George Floyd thing
that really, like,
sparked all this shit.
- Yeah.
- And thank God.
I mean, like, not since that...
It's sad that
that had to happen,
but I'm happy that people
are waking the fuck up,
because it's always been there.
Being Black and seeing
the George Floyd video
being played over
and over and over again,
there's a level of trauma
that comes with that shit.
So even with corona going on,
I felt immediately compelled
to be involved in protests
here in Los Angeles.
Because enough is enough.
Things need to change.
I don't know
if you guys heard about
the whole Rayshard Brooks thing
that happened in Atlanta
that got all of this press.
Well, that actually happened,
like, two minutes away
from my house.
- What?
- Oh, my God, girl.
Like, at the Wendy's
that I go to on a daily basis.
This situation happened,
and it kind of scared me,
because I'm, like,
that could have been me.
- That could have been you.
- Easily. You know what I mean?
It kind of just really hit me
that I could easily
be in that drive-thru,
and there could be a situation
where they pull me over
just because I look like
I don't belong
in that type of car.
It's a fear that a lot of Black
and Brown people live with.
Like, it's not a fucking game
or it's not a joke.
It's really not.
I don't know how it escalated
from him saying that he can
just walk to somebody's house
to him being shot.
That's crazy to me,
how it went from... ooh...
How it went from...
Now I'm gonna cry.
You can just be a Black person
in this world,
and you can just
get killed for nothing.
Like...
It's just... it's scary
that you could just get killed
just because of
the color of your skin.
Like...
The thing about the fight
is Black people been fighting
to show who they are for years,
and it took one incident
for others to realize
that we all are still one.
Oh, yeah.
I think that's
the most inspiring thing
that came out of New York,
is, like, to see the support
to show up,
even during, like, COVID.
You may be scared
to leave your house,
but think about,
like, people of color
and, like, transgender people
who have been scared
their whole lives
to, like,
leave their front door,
to, like, walk down the street.
Yeah, true.
The Black Lives Matter
movement is moving,
but the trans lives,
we losing them left and right.
- Yeah.
- And it's not being recognized,
and it's not being talked about
and covered like it should.
Statistically, Black trans lives
are the most at-risk.
- Uh-huh!
- Yeah, Olivia.
That is true.
I think we're headed
in the right direction,
but I really do think we got
a lot more work to be done.
We have to understand
that we are one,
and we fight as one
and we fail as one.
Well, girls, now we know
what to do when
we leave this competition.
We have to use our voices
and do the right thing.
- Amen.
- Absolutely.
So use that platform wisely.
And get in some good trouble!
[all laugh] Come on!
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
And what?
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage.
Now, if you were a bag,
what kind of bag would you be?
Well, we're in Hollywood,
so I'd be a plastic bag,
darling.
[laughs] Style superstar
Carson Kressley, same question.
Oh, Ru, I'd be a teabag.
Because you like
spilling the tea?
Uh... sure. Yeah,
we can go with that.
[all laugh]
And let's welcome back
the fabulous Nicole Byer.
What kind of bag would you be?
Well, Ru, I'd be a body bag,
because I got
all this body-ody-ody.
Hey! This week,
we challenged our queens
to serve three looks each
to the Bag Ball.
Now, that's 36 looks.
Look, Ma. I can do math!
Just don't tell the IRS.
Racers, start your engines,
and may the best drag queen win!
RuPaul: Coming up...
Ooh, that is one long intestine!
Looks like she got rear-ended.
Lucky her. [all laugh]
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
Let the Bag Ball begin.
First category is Mixed Bag.
First up, Denali,
giving you Airbag.
Michelle: What a dummy!
Denali:
Beep-beep, mother fuckers,
'cause I'm coming through.
I'm a sickening Mugler,
Gaga-esque crash test dummy.
Buckle up, bitches.
[beep, beep, beep]
RuPaul: Looks like
she got rear-ended.
Carson: Lucky her.
RuPaul:
Joey Jay, giving you IV Bag.
Joey: I'm wearing
this rhinestone bodysuit,
and on top of that
I made this syringe armor.
I've got my IV pole,
and it's plugged into my veins.
RuPaul: Yes, she's walking
into the club nurse-first.
[all laugh]
Nicole: Oh, and that poison ivy
got her ass all swollen.
[laughs]
RuPaul: LaLa Ri,
giving you Bag of Bones.
Carson: What a large sack!
[all laugh]
Lala: I am giving you
Voodoo realness, honey.
So the bottom of the dress
is like a burlap sack,
and the bones are coming up
out of the bag.
I've taken the souls
of these men
and put their bones
all over my body, darling.
Carson:
I think I can see her coccyx.
[RuPaul laughs]
RuPaul:
Femur? I hardly knew her!
Elliott With 2 Ts,
giving you Giftbag.
Michelle:
Ooh, girl, she got receipts.
[all laugh]
Elliott:
I'm giving you dollar store,
cheap gift bag,
ready to be regifted, honey,
and once I hit
the end of the runway, bam,
my clutch is the name tag.
Girl, go ahead and unwrap me.
RuPaul:
Off to the gifting suite.
Tamisha Iman, That Old Bag.
Carson: Tamisha Boniva Iman.
Tamisha: My ensemble
is Tamisha Iman,
60 years in the game.
My hair done turned grey,
I still got on my suit
that I made 30 years ago,
and then I'm trying to smile,
but I just remembered
I didn't put my teeth in.
RuPaul: She is living!
Assisted living.
Symone, giving you Fun Bags.
Nicole: Oh, I didn't know
old Michelle came in Black!
[all laugh]
Symone: I'm wearing
this velvet dress
covered in sequins, coming
down to the ground, honey.
Feathered at the bottom,
with the biggest titties
you ever did see.
Of course this is
a Diana Ross reference,
but with a little bit
of a twist to it.
RuPaul: It's RuPaul's
Breast Friend Race.
[pop, pop] Oh!
Carson:
Thanks for the mammaries.
[all laugh]
RuPaul:
Olivia Lux, Punching Bag.
Michelle: What a knockout!
Olivia: I'm serving ginger,
Laila Ali-inspired
boxer couture.
I'm hyping myself up, okay?
We are about to fight.
Ding-ding-ding!
RuPaul: Float like a butterfly,
sting like a bee.
Carson: Or Chlamydia.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Gottmik, Bodybag.
Nicole: Ooh, that
is one long intestine!
[all laugh]
Gottmik: I'm giving you
autopsy of Jane Ho,
and I'm showing you all
that I'm just as glamorous
on the inside
as I am on the outside.
RuPaul: Now, it really
took guts to pull this off.
Rosé, Bagpipes.
Michelle:
Is that a pipe in your kilt
or are you just happy to see me?
Rosé: I'm giving a nod
to my Scottish upbringing,
and I'm also in plaid
as a wee, lovely,
slutty Scottish girl
who just got back
from her bagpipe rehearsal
and is really feeling
like her pussy's on fire
because she's actually a ginger.
Michelle: You like your queens
pipin' hot?
Carson: Oh, blow me.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Tina Burner,
Brown Baggin' It.
Nicole: Ooh! So that's
who was going through
my trash last night.
Tina: I am serving
girl on the go.
When I say that,
I mean I got the liquor,
and I'm ready to go.
I am dressed as
a mother fucking paper bag.
I am wasted with perfection.
Nicole: You know what they say:
recycle, reuse, and be a slut.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Kandy Muse,
Bag of Tricks.
Michelle: Look at all that wood.
RuPaul: Oh, she knows
how to handle a pole.
Kandy: Bitch,
I'm a sex magician.
Boom, bitch.
I'm pulling out a wooden stick
out of my magic bag.
Mm, it's so long, ooh!
This garment
is very form-fitting,
tight to the body,
latex and vinyl.
Ooh, bitch, I'm hot.
RuPaul: Honey, she put
the "ho" in "hocus-pocus."
[all laugh]
Michelle: Oh, there it is.
RuPaul: Now you see her,
now you don't.
Utica, Doggie Bag.
Michelle: What a dog.
Utica: I am a beautiful
French poodle,
and I am just wiggling my nose.
I am panting,
I am marking my territory.
Please curb your dog.
She's rocking
these poodle poufs,
but she's got a couple fleas.
And I am just hungry
to show the judges
who this scratchy
little bitch is.
Carson: Rumor has it
she has a huge schnoodle.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Coming up...
Carson:
All she sees is dollar signs.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Ladies and gentlemen,
Ms. Patti Lapel.
Michelle: You are so bad!
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
RuPaul: Welcome back
to the Bag Ball.
Category is Miss Moneybags.
Up first, Denali.
Carson: Fingernailed it.
Denali: I am serving you
a Cruella de Vil-inspired,
editor-in-chief
of a fashion company.
And she has got
this big custom bag,
and this bitch-ass long nail
that is holding her cigarette.
Nicole: She's smokin'!
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Joey Jay.
I spy with my working eye...
[all laugh]
Joey: I'm giving you
Annie Lennox
meets El Driver fromKill Bill.
Signature Joey Jay hair,
and, bitch,
you can't come for me
because I see you even
though I only got one eye.
Carson:
Oh, let me get her number.
Uh, 01000110111.
Oh, that must be in Sweden!
[all laugh]
RuPaul: LaLa Ri.
Michelle: Ladies
and gentlemen, Mrs. Clean.
[all laugh]
Lala: I love a female that
is not afraid to be bald.
So I went for, like,
this Black bitch from Africa.
Like, bitch,
she makes sure you on time.
You in your area.
Bitch, she look over at you.
That's not right. Boom.
Nicole: Sex in the City,
Bald in the Jungle.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Elliott With 2 Ts.
Carson: Representing
the accounting firm
of Bottoms and Bottoms.
Elliott: I have chosen
this super-structured,
over-the-top blazer
with matching pencil skirt.
I feel like Rose Nylund
at 26 years old.
She is the CEO
of a lending library,
just ready to read everyone.
Carson: Al and I built Coach.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Tamisha Iman.
Michelle: Green means money.
Tamisha: So I'm walking
down the runway,
I'm representing straight ATL,
the glamorous aspect of Atlanta.
We got the nice, big purse,
the hair's on fleek.
I have on my feathers,
because
we have to have a peacock.
That means you're rich.
She's one ol' classy,
sassy lady.
Carson: Oh, yes, we lepre-can.
RuPaul: Symone.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Miss Patti Lapel.
Michelle: Oh, you are so bad!
Symone: I am serving you
futuristic businesswoman lady.
I decided to wear this
pink reflective material.
Big ol' collar.
VeryFifth Element, darling.
Carson: I "kneed" this look.
Michelle: Listen, those pants
would have come in handy for me
many years ago.
RuPaul: Olivia Lux.
Nicole: She's cape-tivating.
Olivia: Can anybody
say "coffee break?"
I'm showing the judges
that although
I'm a powerhouse executive,
I can still be cute
with a little cape
and show them a little ooh-ooh.
Michelle:
Okay, guys, suit or boots?
[all laugh]
Gottmik. Oh, my Gottmik.
Gottmik: I'm serving you
boss bitch boss.
I'm a Generation Z CEO, girl.
I have a fully Swarovski
pinstriped suit
with one bra side out.
This is what you're gonna see
when you walk into my meeting
at my company.
Nicole: Ahh, that's
what I aspire to be:
Black and dripping in diamonds.
Yes! Wow.
Michelle: And if she thinks
I ain't gonna jump her
in the parking lot for
that suit, she is wrong.
RuPaul: Rosé. She means
business, big business.
Rosé: Baby,
I'm giving you eighties down.
From the triangular hair
to the red lip,
and we've got this beautiful
Balmain-inspired silhouette.
This look is a direct nod
to the movieBig Business,
one of my favorite
Bette Midler roles,
and I'm feeling
completely expensive.
Michelle: Bette on it.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Tinta Burnter.
Carson: Sparkle, Tina, sparkle!
Tina: I'm long
in the tooth today, honey,
because I am serving
houndstooth Miranda Beastly.
My houndstooth is stoned to a T,
and you best believe
I own 100% of this company.
RuPaul: Is this
the houndstooth fairy?
Nicole: Houndstooth?
More like hounds-cute.
RuPaul: Kandy Muse. Bank rolls?
Kandy: Bam, bitch, I'm a CE-Ho.
She used to work the corners,
but now she owns the corners.
My hairpiece
and my little blunt in my hand
are made outta money, bitch.
Carson: All she sees
is dollar signs.
[all laugh]
Let's get down to business.
You know, fucking.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Attica? Utica?
Carson: Look at them knockers!
Utica: This outfit
is inspired by Carol Burnett
and the musicalChicago.
So I'm giving you this
executive black, fitted suit,
all custom jewelry that I made,
and I'm 24-karat gold
from my head to my feet.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Clearly, her company
has fringe benefits.
Yes, complete with a 401-hey.
♪ Bring back my girls ♪
Final category is
Gag Us With Your Bagus.
100% bag drag.
Up first, Denali.
Michelle:
Hey there, sugar skull.
Denali: I am serving you
a fashionable twist on
a traditional Mexican garment.
I have used probably 10
of these floral print purses.
I'm living
for this trellis of flowers
that frames
my Dia de los Muertos face.
I love that I get to celebrate
my Mexican heritage.
I am so orgullosa de este...
vestido.
Carson: I'm dead,
D-E-Day of the Dead-dead.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Joey Jay.
Michelle: Tuile of fortune.
Carson: Pinwheel of fortune.
Joey: I'm giving you Madonna
meets Lady Gaga
meets Minnie Mouse.
I have created this look
out of black and white
polka dot canvas bags,
black net bags,
and some black sequin bags.
I've got my high pony.
I'm feeling sexy,
and I think it's adorable.
Michelle:
Oh, whoa, you betta don't!
[all laugh]
RuPaul: LaLa Ri.
Carson: She got this at Sacks.
[all laugh]
Lala: Bitch, I'm serving you
pink and purple
rock star realness.
I've added the purse on my head
because I want them
to focus on, like, the head,
and they kind of look past
the construction
of the actual outfit.
And it gives me, like,
this whole Grace Jones vibe.
Like, bitch, I am working it.
Michelle: She's
what they call a bag lady.
♪ Bring back my girls ♪
RuPaul: Elliott With 2 Ts.
Michelle: Pink cow stunning.
Elliott: You cannot even clock
that this was a beanbag chair.
It is so well made.
I look like I ain't got
no time for nobody.
I am having drinks
with the girls
on the Las Vegas Strip,
and, honey, I look sickening.
Carson: I'm really very moo-ved.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Tamisha Iman.
Nicole: It's like
Rosie the Robot, but slutty.
Tamisha:
Walking down the runway,
I'm feeling confident
in what I created.
It has a nice silhouette.
I'm catching the glints
with these shoulders.
They are sparkling.
My skirt is sparkling
under the lights.
I know I'm looking good,
you know I'm looking good,
everybody know
I'm looking good. [laughs]
Carson: That is $500 worth
of dime-baggies up in here.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Symone.
Michelle: Ahoy!
Symone: It's a sunny day
in California,
and, bitch,
I'm going to the beach.
I have this red and white
two piece ensemble.
A little miniskirt
showing almost too much.
She's trying
to find a man, honey.
She sees these bitches
at the beach,
and she's like, oh, no,
all these cute boys is for me.
Michelle:
Touch this melanin, honey.
Touch all of this melanin!
RuPaul: Beach, please!
♪ Bring back my girls ♪
RuPaul: Olivia Lux.
Nicole: Those are the tiniest
handcuffs I've ever seen.
Olivia: I decided
to use holographic bags
all on my shoulders,
coming all the way down
to my wrists.
I'm giving you that
gladiator Athena goddess
that just stepped foot on Earth
and is ready to serve it
for the children.
Michelle: Take that, Chromatica!
RuPaul: Gottmik.
Michelle:
She is a strapping young queen!
Gottmik: I'm giving you
very Joan Jett, veryMatrix.
Everything is this silver-black,
futuristic fantasy moment.
I have straps from a backpack
on one shoulder,
and then I sewed together
all of these
drawstring bags down my leg,
so it looks like this weird,
one-legged chap situation.
And I'm living.
Carson: Oh, it's a punk
Joyce DeWitt!
RuPaul: Rosé.
Carson: Takes a lotta balls
to wear a look like this.
Rosé: I've created
this futuristic
femmebot fatale look.
I look like an alien goddess
warrior from another planet,
and I've come to Earth
to wear purses as couture.
And if I'm a super-shero
from the future,
my superpower is dizziness,
because, baby, we are
spinning out of control.
Nicole: Bye-bye, blue balls,
hello, silver balls.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Tina Burner.
Michelle: All right,
that's it, you're suspended.
[all laugh]
Tina: Bitch, I have taken
a mother fucking beanbag
and made a fucking dress.
I got some suspenders on.
Of course my signature
colors, red and yellow.
I know you wanna sit
on this beanbag.
Aow!
RuPaul: It's Rhonda McDonald!
[all laugh]
Over one billion served.
Kandy Muse.
Michelle: Ooh, what does
she have in her Trapper-Keeper?
Carson: Mm, trapper keep-her.
[all laugh]
Kandy: I'm a naughty
schoolgirl, bitch.
I've chosen to go with bookbags
and cut them up
and make it into a skirt,
and make a really cute bra.
It is bright, it's colorful,
it's first day of school
realness.
Bitch, fight me,
and I'll take your lunch money.
Michelle: Meet me
at the flagpole at 3:00.
Carson: Crrrrck.
RuPaul: Syracuse,
Schenectady, Utica.
Ooh.
RuPaul: What's your
sleep number, Michelle?
Michelle: Nine. I like it hard.
[all laugh]
Utica: I am so campy.
I am walking down the runway
as a sleeping bag couture
and serving
this ethereal starlet.
I got these puffy sleeves,
a fitted waist.
I see the judges' eyes light up,
and they are loving
this garment.
Michelle: Kumbayahhh.
Nicole: Good night, Sun.
Good night, Moon.
Good night, Drag Queen!
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Coming up...
Your mixed bag look, stunning.
This is frightening,
and I'm entertained.
It was more like
a campy nod versus drag.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
Welcome, queens.
Based on your 36 Bag Ball looks,
I've made some decisions.
When I call your name,
please step forward.
Denali.
Elliott With 2 Ts.
Symone.
Olivia Lux.
Tina Burner.
Kandy Muse.
Ladies, you are safe.
You may leave the stage.
Ladies, you represent the tops
and the bottoms of the week.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques,
starting with Joey Jay.
I do wanna compliment you,
first and foremost.
You incorporated the Joey Jay
signature natural hair,
which I wasn't mad at.
But it was fun to see you
in different hairdos.
With that said,
here on the runway
I can tell by looking at this
you're not the sewer.
Maybe more of a gluer?
- [tongue pop] You know it.
- That sound right?
So the construction
is not the best,
but I've definitely seen worse.
Your first look, which was,
I guess, Poison Ivy...
- Was that the idea?
- IV bag.
Right, but didn't you have
poison ivy,
and the IV bag is an IV?
- Yes, yes.
- Okay. So it was poison ivy?
No, it was just ivy,
it wasn't poison ivy.
- Get it? IV bag.
- No, I know.
I just thought
that was the joke,
that it was, like, poison IV.
I was going for IV bag.
Okay, we gotta let it go.
Yeah, I'm gonna stop now.
I'm overthinking.
I liked the touch of floral.
I wish it was poison IV
and had more of a story.
I thought it was poison IV bag.
I thought it was, like,
two puns in one.
You know, like a two-for-one?
So next time someone goes,
"Ooh, was it a two-for-one?"
Just say yes.
You know, just lie.
Yes!
Up next, LaLa Ri.
Your Mixed Bag look,
I wish maybe
you'd used the bones
to create more of a pattern,
just to give us
a little bit more
than that haphazard
bones thrown on.
- Okay.
- Your Moneybags look,
with that great
multicolored cheetah print,
that was really fun.
And it allowed us
to really see that clutch.
It's called "featuring
the merchandise," I believe.
This look,
stunning, all of this.
We get down to the dress.
Yeah, it's some bags that
were glued onto a bodysuit.
- Yeah, that's not gonna work.
- Yeah.
How come you didn't cut up
them bags or do something?
Well, originally
I was making this
into, like, a dress
with just the bags.
- Mm-hmm.
- And then I ran out of bags,
so I started gluing it
onto the corset.
But why not cut it
or do something
so they're not just
literal bags glued to you?
- Yeah.
- Okay?
So if something doesn't work,
you've gotta have a plan B.
Up next, Tamisha Iman.
Yes, ma'am.
Your old bag of bones
I could relate to.
I hope that that's me,
you know, yeah, in the future.
- It is.
- Hey, not now! Calm down!
But with that said,
I think you focused
more on the character
than more about the drag
in that.
And then your Moneybags look,
it was just, like,
a nice business lady.
I was like, oh, okay,
she gonna fire somebody today.
It was too much like real life,
and I missed
the theatricalness of it.
This look,
it's texture for days.
I love that you used
oversized sequins,
and you used
the silk jewelry bags.
But sometimes
when you get these challenges
to make something
out of a bunch of stuff,
you think more is more.
I think
if you got rid of the cuffs
and you got rid of
or downsized that choker,
just want this lightened up.
And one thing I do wanna say
is that your makeup
sometimes comes across
a little not blended enough.
So I'm gonna recommend to you
that you talk to
some of the makeup queens
and get a little info.
But you are a joy,
and I appreciate
what you did tonight.
Thank you very much.
Up next, Gottmik.
You should change your name
to Gottaste,
because you have
a really good taste level
that transcended
all three of the looks.
The body bag that was
that autopsy moment,
it was gruesome,
but kind of fashionable
all at the same time.
It was like you were
a literal dead person,
cut open, walking at me.
I was like, this is frightening,
and I'm entertained.
Your Moneybags look,
like, I can't even breathe.
That is a moment.
Thank you.
It is remarkable.
And all the details that
went with it, unbelievable.
And then this look, it's edited,
I love the silhouette,
it's edgy and cool and like
a modern Joan Jett rocker thing.
Yes!
Gottmik actually went
to fashion school.
- Oh, well, there you go.
- I did.
- So do you know how to sew-sew?
- I do.
That gets me even more excited
to see what
you are gonna bring me,
because now that I know you
went to fashion school,
she's gonna challenge you
a little bit more.
Maybe I didn't go, then.
[all laugh]
Rosé.
I'm gonna start with your nod
to your Scottish heritage.
I didn't realize
you were from Scotland.
Yep, I was born in Greenock,
which is a wee town
near Glasgow.
That look kilt it.
[laughs]
The silhouette was perfect,
the tailoring was perfect,
the details were perfect.
Your Moneybags moment
was a nod to the great
Bette Midler.
Bette Midler in Big Business.
And I thought it was
the simplest out of yours,
and it was more like a campy nod
tribute versus, like, drag.
And then this
I think is stunning.
Did you cut the bags in half,
the ones that are on the skirt?
Yeah, I cut them in half
and then I half-sewed
and half-glued it
all back together.
It had movement, as well,
so when you did those turns,
those bags kind of
flew out into the air
like an amusement park ride.
That's a great drag look,
when it's fun and it has
that sense of whimsy
and it makes us smile,
but it's still chic.
- Thank you.
- Next up, Utica.
Hello!
One thing I like
to pride myself on
is say when I'm wr...
Wrong.
[all laugh]
Doesn't come easily.
But I think in the beginning
I pegged you
as, oh, she's
the weird, quirky queen.
She's gonna just do
weird shit just to do it.
But you have continuously
upped the fashion,
and I think tonight
was no exception.
Starting with your Mixed Bag,
it was just all really chic.
And then you gave us that great
variety in your Moneybags look.
I loved the giant,
oversized earring detail.
It was just really
well executed.
And then you came out in this,
and my mind was kind of blown.
Sleeping bags are not
an easy medium to work with,
and you've made it
look flattering.
The cowl neck with the zipper,
it's just all so enticing.
Thank you.
Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
While you untuck
in the werkroom,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
Okay, just between
us squirrel friends,
I think we've seen
one of the best looks
in Drag Raceherstory
and one of the worst looks.
[all laugh]
Let's start with Joey Jay.
The first look, the IV bag,
Joey didn't even realize
the poison IV was the joke.
And then the second look,
I thought was just, like,
okay, it's a blazer,
some leggings,
we got some pumps.
But what else?
It was like Chico's formal,
you know?
Yes, yes. And the third look,
I thought it was fun.
Did I think it was,
you know, mind-blowing?
No, but I appreciated
that there was hair.
[all laugh]
LaLa Ri.
The Moneybags look
was one of my favorites.
Her attitude and her radiance
and how she presents
was so lovely to watch.
Now, this look tonight, y'all,
absolutely no.
No. That face, beautiful!
That lip, gorgeous!
That outfit, burn it.
[all laugh]
Tamisha Iman.
Tamisha has that
kind of presence,
and she's got the experience,
and it showed in her acting
when she came out
and did her "that old bag."
She was really selling it,
but it wasn't, like, a great
razzle-dazzle drag moment.
Her Moneybags
was my least favorite.
For a girl
who can sew her butt off,
it looked kinda off-the-rack.
Her final look, to me,
kind of says who she is.
The way she did the bodice
and the breast part
was not easily done.
I just think she overdid it,
that's all.
- Yes.
- Gottmik.
She started out with her
dead-on-arrival autopsy look,
which I loved so much
that I was begging for more.
The second look, stunning.
My God.
I mean, you wanna talk
about texture?
I could stare at that all night,
it was so beautiful.
She really got that challenge.
We want opulence with Moneybags.
I don't need Mildred Pierce,
I need today's
Alexis Carrington Colby Blake
Dexter Dexter Carrington
Blake Dexter Colby.
[all laugh] That what I need.
And then she came out here
in this deconstructed,
one-legged outfit, and I lived.
It was so punk rock, really,
but yet so chic and fashion.
Like, I could see this
on a runway.
All right, Rosé.
That first Scottish look
was so well done.
It had a sense of humor,
it was crafted beautifully,
it was on-brand.
And then the second look,
I missed the tongue-in-cheek
and the fun.
Maybe the hair was big,
I don't know.
Just go bigger with it.
Absolutely agree with that.
Tonight in the final look,
I really enjoyed this.
I thought it was fun.
There were different shades
of metallic in the ball skirt.
She knows how to edit,
she didn't have anything
that she didn't need,
but she had everything
that she needed.
Utica.
She came out with
her first doggie bag look.
It was so chic, it was so
French, it was so fashion.
That second look,
with the short,
Thoroughly Modern Millie
bob in brown...
Thoroughly Modern
Billy-Bob Brown!
[all laugh]
And that look with
the sleeping bags.
My goodness!
This girl is intuitive
about her fashion.
That I would see
on any runway anywhere,
and people
would go crazy for it.
My only critique is on
the first two presentations,
you know, she camps it up a bit,
and I think
it kind of takes away
from how fabulous
those outfits were.
But, boy, you cannot take away
from the craftsmanship there.
And I'm like, "You made this
in the same time
that LaLa
glued bags to herself?"
[all laugh]
That's incredible!
Silence! I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Utica Queen. Gottmik.
Tonight, you each served
three iconic looks,
but one of you truly gagged us
with your bagus.
Gottmik, con-drag-ulations.
You are the winner
of this week's challenge.
Oh, my God!
You've won a cash tip of $5,000.
Thank you!
I won the ball challenge, bitch!
I'm done.
Utica, outstanding work
this week.
You all may join
the other girls.
Rosé, great Scot.
You kilt it again this week.
- You are safe.
- Thank you, Ru.
LaLa Ri, your final look
was epic,
as in epic fail.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
Joey Jay, we wanted to see more.
Tamisha Iman,
we wanted to see less.
Joey Jay, I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
Tamisha, you are safe.
Thank you.
I know how LaLa lip syncs,
and I know she's about
to let me have it.
But I'm a gay-ass bitch.
I'm Joey Jay.
Like, bitch,
I'm not going home today.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come... [thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing] for your life!
I may be the loser by my look,
but one thing
I'm not the loser by
is me as an entertainer
when I need to entertain.
Bitch, this is the moment
that I'm about to give you
the LaLa Ri experience.
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
[music plays]
- Yeah!
- Yes, bitch!
♪ First things first,
I'm the realest ♪
♪ Drop this and let
the whole world feel it ♪
♪ And I'm still
in the murder business ♪
♪ I can hold you down ♪
♪ Like I'm givin' lessons
in physics ♪
♪ You should want
a bad bitch like this ♪
♪ Drop it low and pick it up
just like this ♪
♪ Cup of Ace, cup of Goose,
cup of Cris ♪
♪ High heels, somethin' worth
a half a ticket on my wrist ♪
♪ On my wrist.
Takin' all the liquor ♪
♪ Straight, never chase that ♪
♪ Rooftop,
like we bringin' '88 back ♪
♪ Bring the hooks in,
where the bass at ♪
♪ Champagne spillin',
you should taste that ♪
♪ I said, baby, I do this ♪
♪ I thought that you knew this ♪
♪ Can't stand no haters
and honest, the truth is ♪
♪ And my flow,
they speak it, depart it ♪
♪ Swagger on super,
I can't shop at no department ♪
♪ Better get my money on time,
if they not money, decline ♪
♪ I just can't worry
'bout no haters ♪
♪ Gotta stay on my grind ♪
♪ Now tell me who that,
who that? ♪
♪ That do that, do that? ♪
♪ Put that paper over all ♪
♪ I thought you knew that,
knew that ♪
♪ I be that I-G-G-Y,
put my name in bold ♪
♪ I been working,
I'm up in here ♪
♪ With some change to throw ♪
♪ I'm so fancy ♪
♪ You already know ♪
♪ I'm in the fast lane ♪
♪ From L.A. to Tokyo ♪
♪ I'm so fancy ♪
♪ Can't you taste this gold? ♪
♪ Remember my name,
'bout to blow ♪
[cheering]
♪ Still stunting,
how you love that? ♪
♪ Got the whole world
asking how I does that ♪
♪ Just the way
you like it, huh ♪
♪ You're so good, he's just
wishing he could bite it, huh ♪
♪ Never turn down money ♪
♪ Slaying these hoes,
gold trigger on the gun, like ♪
♪ I'm so fancy ♪
♪ Can't you taste this gold? ♪
♪ Remember my name ♪
♪ 'Bout to blow ♪
♪ Who that, who that, I-G-G-Y ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
[cheers and applause]
Ladies, I've made my decision.
LaLa Ri, shantay you stay.
[applause]
Thank you.
You better step
your pussy up, girl.
I will. I promise you.
You may join the other girls.
Joey Jay, you've only
just begun to slay.
Now sashay away.
Mwah.
[applause]
♪ I'm a gay-ass bitch,
I'm Joey Jay ♪
♪ I belong here, bitch,
I came to slay ♪
[cheering]
I am disappointed,
but I have no regrets.
And bitch, I look so good,
so... till next time.
Con-drag-ulations, ladies.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an "amen" up in here?
- Amen!
All right,
now let the music play!
♪ I'm a winner ♪
♪ I'm a winner, baby ♪
RuPaul: Next time
onRuPaul's Drag Race...
You'll be making a dancing
documentary about disco, baby.
One, two, three.
Pas de bourree, pas de bourree.
Aah!
What the hell?
Your performance
was out of this world.
You killed that shit.
What the fuck is going on here?
Don't look my way,
I won't look your way.
Don't speak to me,
I won't speak to you.
I don't need you
to tell me that.
I'm a grown-ass woman.
For everyone else that has
something to say about me...
♪ I'm a winner
♪ I'm a winner, baby ♪
♪ I'm a winner ♪
♪ Losers, weepers ♪
♪ I'm a winner, baby ♪
♪ Finders, keepers ♪
♪ Losers, weepers ♪
♪ I'm a winner, baby ♪
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org