- Previously on
"RuPaul's Drag Race"...
You're going to form
your own New Wave bands.
- I think our costumes
should be cardboard cutout
geometric shapes.
- Yeah, no.
-  I just want you to be
hot and saucy!
- [laughs]
- [spits]
-  Rectangle girls
of the world
-  I'm every girl,
in a circle I run
- In terms of the outfits
in your group,
were you in charge of that?
- It was a group challenge.
- Well, Chi Chi's
shaking her head.
- The thing
Thorgy had on her head.
That's what I wanted to wear.
- I'm not gonna
be in a cardboard box.
- Robbie Turnter.
Condragulations.
You are the winner
of this week's challenge.
- Yes!
- Chi Chi DeVayne.
Shantay, you stay.
Naysha Lopez.
Sashay, away.
- Ugh.
- Ooh, Chi Chi.
- Oh, Lord.
- How do you feel, Chi Chi?
- Tonight there was a lot
of drama on the runway.
I ain't gonna be
in no bottom again.
- I apologize, Derrick.
If I'm feelin' some kind of way,
I completely shut down.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I have to change that.
I mean, it's just me being
a bitch. I'm sorry.
- Yeah,
it was you being a bitch.
Well, this is my second week
in the bottom three.
I am so happy to still be here.
- I was in shock
that it was not you lip-syncing.
It was Naysha.
- But Chris and Debbie
thought I stood out.
Chris was like, "I think
you could impersonate Debbie.
And we'll take you out on tour."
- They may have been on drugs.
I want a drug test.
- Yeah,
I didn't hear you get that.
But--
- I did get told
that my performance
was phenomenal.
Which you didn't get told.
- All right.
- Derrick, I think
you just missed the point,
but it's not a big deal.
- Okay.
Well, I don't know
if there was a point.
It's just Bob talking
is your point all the time.
- But you'll do, like,
side shady comments,
and it's funny,
but when I do side shady
comments, it's like, over.
- No. No, but what you--
- Anyone else see this?
Am I on Lonely Island?
Am I on Staten Island or am I
living in Manhattan right now?
- You're right.
- Thank you.
- [laughs]
- I don't see that I do that.
- I can't wait
till you do it again.
It'll be, like, five minutes.
- Lord have mercy.
- The two of you, honey.
That is a pot boiling.
- Derrick's, like,
"I ain't never
make jokes about anyone ever."
- Hey, Bob.
If I want to do
ratchet drag next week,
can you give me any tips?
- Ooh hoo hoo!
- If you want to do, like,
memorable drag next week,
I can give you some tips.
- [laughs]
- So all I need to do
is not wear a wig
and I'll be told by
the judges that I'm pretty.
- Babe.
- Didn't I remind you guys?
I said, "In about five minutes,
she'd make a shady comment
out of nowhere"?
- And I did.
- What I said wasn't meant
to hurt your feelings.
You're trying to be spiteful.
You see the difference?
- Your intentions
weren't to hurt me?
- No, they weren't to hurt.
If I wanted to hurt you,
you'd be cryin'
right now, bitch.
- I will never cry
over you at all.
- Don't give me a challenge.
- I work on the strip with
really big drag personalities.
So if you think
you're gonna come for me,
I am not that innocent.
[car engine starts]
-  RuPaul Drag Race
- The winner
of "RuPaul's Drag Race"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia
Beverly Hills cosmetics
and a cash prize
of $100,000.
With extra special
guest supermodels
Chanel Iman
and Gigi Hadid!
-  RuPaul Drag Race
-  May the best woman
Best woman win
[pastoral music]
[rooster crows]
- Where they chicken wings?
- [screams]
- You know what I love
about this process?
I'm becoming, like,
a morning person.
I'm up at, like, 6:00,
and I'm like, "It's 6:00!"
- Bob, you're, like,
an all day person.
- Yeah.
- You're like,
"It's mornin', evenin',
and night!
Yeah!
Yeah!"
- Whoo!
- I'm boisterous.
I'm excited to be here.
I'm on my favorite
fucking TV show.
And that bothers some people.
Sorry, girl.
[siren blaring]
- Whoo, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
Carol Channing, Brittany G.
- Whoo!
- On a game show
with a bunch of queens.
Judge Judy, Maggie too...
- Yes!
- Little Richard, we love you.
Drag queens with an aptitude
for thinking fast
and being crude.
Don't just stand there.
Let's get to it!
Make me laugh.
There's nothing to it.
Bang, bang, bang, bang.
[laughter]
Hello, hello, hello.
[cheers and applause]
- Wow.
- Ladies.
For this week's maxi challenge,
we're going to break
out of the studio
as we drive
along the Hollywood freeway
looking for fresh roadkill.
Then, back in the workroom,
you'll need to transform
the furry little pelts
into evening gowns
that scream
"#CritterCouture."
Oh, hell,
who am I kiddin'?
It's time to play
the Snatch Game.
[cheers and applause]
- [laughing]
#SnatchGame.
Now, you know how it works.
Impersonate a celebrity,
fill in the blanks,
and stake your claim
as a front-runner
in this competition.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
[applause]
- Who you doin', baby?
- I was gonna do Nancy Grace.
- Which is brilliant by the way.
- Yeah, I think it's funny.
- Because she's so, so funny.
- Over the top.
- Oh, she's the craziest.
- Right.
- And just have outrage
at every--everything.
- Every corner.
I'm impersonating
Nancy Grace, herself,
because she seems
like a major bitch,
and I can relate to that.
- Robbie,
what are you thinkin' about?
- I'm doing Diana Vreeland.
- Who?
- She was the first
editor in chief
of "Vogue" in the '60s.
- Oh.
Do you think
that's a hair obscure?
- No.
Not at all.
I have been practicing
Diana Vreeland for months.
Jinkx Monsoon and BenDeLaCreme,
my Seattle sister wives,
won Snatch Game each year
that they were on.
So there's a lot
of pressure on me to be great.
- What character
are you doing?
- Well, I was going
to do Whoopi Goldberg.
"The Color Purple" is, like,
one of my favorite movies.
And it's so quotable.
Everyone knows
"The Color Purple."
- Yeah.
- I've been working on it
since I found out I was gonna
be on the show.
And I cannot wait to be able
to prove that I am a performer.
I'm not just a runway queen.
- Who are you doing?
- I'm torn
between Whoopi Goldberg,
Uzo Aduba,
who is an actress on, um,
"Orange Is The New Black"...
- Oh, yeah.
- And my last choice
is probably my favorite,
but I look the least like her,
is Carol Channing.
- Why would you do--well.
- I know some folks
are gonna question
why is a 6'2" black man
doing Carol Channing, but it's
because I feel a connection
with Carol Channing.
I really do.
- See, isn't this not--
Miss Celie?
- [laughs]
- You really do look like
Miss Celie.
- I sure is ugly.
- I want to show you how much
I look like Whoopi Goldberg.
- So Bob basically has,
like, ten characters
that he could possibly do.
All the sudden, he's got
the "Sister Act" outfit on.
He is, like, really giving
that Whoopi look.
- I think that if you hit a man,
a man has the right
to knock you out.
You don't want
to get hit by a man,
don't go around hittin' people.
That's all I'm sayin'.
- This is gonna
be the Whoopi Game
instead of the Snatch Game.
- I'm realizing,
"Oh, shit.
I might be out
of my league here."
So I'm gonna have to go
with my plan B backup.
- Bob is so excited
for Snatch Game,
- [laughs]
- Today's challenge--
Ding! Ding! Ding!
Is gonna be Snatch Game.
It's a celebrity impersonation,
so you have
to make people laugh.
So I'm gonna be busier
than a one-legged cat
in a sandbox tryin'
to win this challenge.
- Hey, celebrities.
all: Hey!
- Are you ready
to snatch my attention?
[all cheer]
Hi, Chi Chi.
- Mama Ru.
- [laughs]
Who are you doing?
- I'm doin' Eartha Kitt.
- Uh-huh.
How are you gonna make
Eartha funny?
- Um, I know
that she played Catwoman
and I have two cats at home.
I'm just gonna play off--
- Well, that--there it is!
You've got two cats at home.
To play Snatch Game,
you've got to stay in character,
and you've got to make me laugh.
- Yeah.
- All right. See you out there.
- All right.
- Thank you.
Hi, Kim Chi.
Have you decided on what
character you're gonna portray?
- Um, there's two characters
I'm debating between.
First one is...Pearl.
Is there something on my face?
- [laughs]
- I started doing drag
with Pearl,
who was on season 7,
so I know her quirks
really well.
- Right. Right.
And who's your
other character?
- The other one
is kind of obscure.
- Uh-huh.
- Kimmy Jong-un, maybe.
- Kimmy?
- Kimmy, yeah.
Kimmy Jong-un is a huge risk,
but if I turn
the North Korean dictator
into a drag version of him,
it would be a chance
for me to show
another side of Kim Chi
that's a little fucked up.
- Huh.
That's interesting.
Listen, whatever works for you.
Just so long as
you make me laugh.
- Kimmy Jong-what?
A made-up character,
my friend.
I really hope that
lands her in the bottom.
-  Hey, Derrick
-  Hey, Ru
- Are you gonna do Brittney?
- It's an obvious choice.
But this is my chance
to show everyone
that I'm more than
just a Brittney impersonator.
- Uh-huh.
- And so
I think I'm gonna go
with Laura Bell Bundy's
character.
- Yes,
she's the country singer
Broadway star.
- Right.
And she made up
all these characters,
and Shocantelle
is my favorite one.
- Uh-huh.
- She is a black girl
trapped in a white girl's body.
- Ah.
Can I see a little bit
of your Laura Bell Bundy
character?
- Hello, RuPaul.
I am here.
My Shocantelle you
that I do have a penis.
- You know, sometimes
the most obvious thing
is the thing to do.
You just have to decide
where you want to go.
Stakes are high.
There's $100,000 on the line.
- Yeah, that's true.
- All right, Derrick.
- Thank you, Ru.
- Bye.
- Oh, Lord.
- Thorgy Thor.
- That's me.
- Wait a minute, let me see.
I'm getting, uh,
Charles Manson.
- No.
- No?
- Uh, I'm doing Michael Jackson.
- How are you gonna make
Michael Jackson funny?
- His little quirks.
His little movements
that I have down.
- Yeah.
Who's your biggest
competition here?
- You know, I'm gonna say Bob.
You know, what you're asking us
to do in this season,
Bob is really excelling at,
which is pissing me off.
- Well, let me tell you this,
Thorgy.
And this might help you.
You second-guess
and you take it into your head.
- Constantly.
- This is an opportunity
for you to feel confident
going with your gut
and not overthinking things.
- Yeah.
- All right, Thorgy.
I'll see you out there.
- Okay.
- All right, ladies.
Gather round.
Tomorrow on the runway,
the category is
"Night of 100 Madonnas."
[all cheer]
- Madonna has so many
iconic looks.
I can't wait to see
what everybody comes up with.
It's gonna be amazing.
- So express yourself,
'cause it's a celebration.
[all cheer]
So don't fuck it up.
- Holiday.
- Bye.
- Bye, Ru.
[drum roll, triumphant music]
- Welcome to Snatch Game!
Let's meet
our supermodel contestants.
"Vogue" cover girl Chanel Iman.
- Hey.
[laughs]
- And "Sports Illustrated"
bombshell Gigi Hadid.
- Hi, Ru.
- Hi, darling.
- I'm so excited.
- Are you ready
to meet our stars?
- We are.
- Yes.
- First up, the king of pop,
Michael Jackson.
Was Billie Jean
really your lover?
- I love everyone.
[scatting]
- The king of pop is here.
- [giggles]
- Next, we have the sister
of the supreme leader
of North Korea, Kimmy Jong-un.
- Anyoung haseyo.
- [laughs]
Oh, my goodness.
I just know my emails
are gonna get hacked
after this show airs.
You know what I mean?
[laughs]
Next up, television host
and former prosecutor,
Nancy Grace is here.
Hello, Nancy.
- You know,
I'm worried about
the children, RuPaul.
There's reefer smokers
influencing them every day.
- All right.
All right.
Up next, legendary "Vogue"
fashion editor,
Diana Vreeland.
- RuPaul!
- What's in this season, Diana?
- How the hell should I know?
- Up next, reality superstar,
Tiffany "New York" Pollard.
- New York is in
the mutha-fuckin' house.
- [laughs]
Up next,
Eartha Kitt is here.
- How are you?
- You're not wearing
any panties, are you?
- Who wears panties?
What are those?
- All right, up next,
Britney Jean Spears is here.
- I don't wear panties either.
- You don't
wear panties either?
- Especially when I get
out of cars.
[laughter]
- [laughs]
[exciting game show music]
- Welcome back to Snatch Game.
Here's how the game works.
I ask a question,
and you give an answer
that you think will match
our supermodel contestants.
- [giggles]
- First question.
Gigi Hadid.
There's a new dating app
for drag queens.
When you join,
the first question they ask
is, "How big is your blank?"
Let's go to Gigi Hadid.
- How big is your wig?
- I love that!
Let's go to our superstars
and find out
if you got any matches.
- Okay.
- Let's start with Kimmy Jong-un
from North Korea.
The first question
they ask is, "How big is your"?
- I wrote down
weapons of ass destruction.
- Weapons of ass destruction.
Not a match.
[laughing] I--yeah.
Well, thank you,
the unbreakable Kimmy Jong-un.
Ms. Eartha Kitt.
- Well, I'm sorry, Gigi...
[laughter]
But I said,
"Big furry balls."
- How big is your big
furry balls?
- Honey, get your mind
out of the gutter.
- Of course.
[laughing]
- [purring]
- Prosecutor Nancy Grace.
- Well, as everybody knows,
not only do I do newscasting,
but I also was on another show
where I danced.
So I said, "How big
are your bunions?"
- What do you do for bunions?
- Well, I was told
you can get 'em shaved off.
That's what they do.
I'm about to get that done.
- All right.
Sorry, Gigi.
Not a match.
Let's move on to
Tiffany "New York" Pollard.
- How big is your clock?
- Because drag queens
love a big-ass clock, right?
[feeble laughter]
- Ru seems to be throwing Naomi
every bone she can find.
- Do you like a big clock,
yourself?
- But this dog won't catch.
- Chanel Iman.
It's your turn now, darling.
The big bad wolf
is a drag queen.
Instead of huffing,
and puffing,
and blowing,
she blanks the house down.
- Shakes?
- She gonna shake
the house down.
Shake that ass.
- Mm.
- All right, well,
let's go to our celebrities
and find out
if you've got a match.
Let's start
with Latoya's brother,
Michael Jackson.
- I just said,
"Takes a long nap
in a bed
with everyone they know."
- Michael, that's crazy.
- Thank you.
[laughter]
- Mm-hmm.
- Let's move on
down to Diana Vreeland.
- I used to work
for "Vogue" magazine.
But I heard that now
"Vogue" means a dance.
So I think they vogue
the house down.
- Girl.
This performance is poo.
And you're from the same town
as Jinkx and Dela?
Ooh, girl.
Them girls is gonna--
I was about to say
they gonna hang you,
but I ain't gonna say that.
[laughs]
- Eartha Kitt.
Instead of huffing, puffing
and blowing,
she blanks the house down.
- She licks the house.
- Ooh.
Licks the house down.
- And speaking of lick,
it's time for my bath.
- What?
Oh, you--
[laughs]
- [giggles]
[laughter]
- Ha, ha.
That's what cats do.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Eartha Kitt
didn't do that, Chi Chi.
- Let's move on down
to Britney Jean.
- She reads the house down.
- That's not a match,
unfortunately, Chanel Iman.
But has Eartha Kitt
got your tongue?
- I've had that tongue before.
- You have?
- Good girls gone bad.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
- You should do
that one more time.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I would be very
popular in prison.
[laughter]
- All right.
Crazy Eyes.
- Because you pretty,
I just wrote a poem...
- Yeah.
- To Iman.
A-Once a queen named Iman
remind me of the Sun.
Instead of her
supermodel life,
She can be...
my wife.
[laughter]
- Unfortunately, Chanel,
that is not a match.
Next question.
Let's go to Gigi Hadid.
Lady Bunny has an unusual way
of celebrating gay pride.
Instead of the rainbow flag,
she hangs her blank
out the window.
- Her tucking panties.
- Let's go to the king
of pop and hear
if you have a match.
- Oh, Ru.
It's not a match,
but I said, "She waves
her blanket."
Say "Hi."
- Oh, hi, Blanket.
- Hi, Blanket.
Hi, hi. Bye-bye.
- Oh, please be careful.
You don't want Blanket to fall.
No.
- Oh, thank you.
- Yes.
- [scatting]
- Moving on down
to Tiffany "New York" Pollard.
- When I think of Pride,
I think of...my hair.
So I said $800 weave?
- That's an $800 weave?
- Well, of course.
Blended.
- Yes.
- Naomi's "New York"?
- I'm sorry, Gigi.
You didn't get
a match this time.
Maybe next time.
Well, look who's here.
- I'm sorry
that I'm late.
But, uh, Uzo Abu-boo
left the stage
and she asked me
if I would fill in.
- Ladies and Gentlemen,
Carol Channing.
- Oh, thank you.
[laughter]
- All right.
Chanel Iman.
Sally the Supermodel
is so lactose intolerant,
when the photographer
says, "cheese," she blanks.
- Sneezes.
- She sneezes!
Let's go down to Nancy Grace.
- She sends out an Amber Alert.
- Nancy Grace is terrible.
- It's important
to keep the children
safe from the boozers
and the users
and the reefer smokers.
- It's lifeless.
It's basically Acid Betty
turned into Boring Betty.
- Let's move on down
to Britney Spears,
the princess of pop.
- She, "Oops.
I did it again."
- Ahh.
- [giggles]
- Do you mean
between me down there?
- She had diarrhea.
[laughter]
- All right,
let's move on to Diana Vreeland.
- I've worked with Sally
for so long.
She pops a pill, RuPaul.
She pops a pill.
- There is so much talk
about drugs.
I have-haven't taken
anything but Lipitor
for the past ten years.
You don't really
get a buzz off of that.
- Now, is there an anal option?
- I might happen to have a Fleet
or two in my home.
- A Fleet enema.
Now you're talkin'
my language.
- If you stay ready,
you ain't got to get ready.
By the way, Eartha,
I didn't know
that was you down there.
- It's me, darling.
- From here,
I couldn't tell if you were
Della Reese or Luther Vandross.
I couldn't see.
These aren't even
my good glasses.
But back to
the matter at hand.
I just wrote "corn".
- That's always a good answer.
- You know, there's no dairy.
And it comes out the way
you put it in, RuPaul.
- Well, listen.
On that note, I am sorry, folks,
but we are well out of time.
It was a really
close game,
- [laughs]
[upbeat music]
- What?
I can't believe she--
[laughter]
- Always the first.
- It's elimination day,
and it is the
Night of the 100 Madonnas.
And as I'm pulling out
my kimono,
I see Thorgy's also
pulling out a red kimono.
Great minds think alike?
- In New York, it's funny.
It's like we're always put
in these boxes of, like,
what people's expectations
of who we are as, you know,
drag artists?
- Yes.
- Now, even people
are putting Brooklyn in a box.
- Brooklyn doesn't accept me.
I think there's a lot
of queens at home
who do not interact with me.
It sucks that none of them
ask me to be a part
of their community.
So I don't fit in anywhere.
There are certain definitions
of "drag."
You know, and there's,
like, "I'm put in it 'cause
I'm the 'look queen.'"
I've had fights
with those people
where they're like, "Oh,
you're not a drag queen.
You just do looks."
- Yes. Mm-hmm.
- It hurts me, actually,
that I'm a lone soldier.
And I think
that's that huge wall
that I put in between me
and myself and everybody else.
I think this show's
a great platform, though,
because it kind of shows
that we do something more
than just stand around
and serve booze.
- Yup.
- You know, or sit around
and be a bitch.
- Yeah.
- You know,
I do all these shows.
I make all these things.
But I'm also a musician.
What I really want to do is,
like, do a grand,
like, event,
like, "Thorgy
and the Thorchestra."
- Fabulous.
- Like, a 40-piece orchestra,
and I want to conduct in drag.
I am a professional violinist,
violist, cellist.
You know, I've played
at Carnegie Hall many times.
I feel like I'm
the perfect medium
to kind of appeal to, like,
the younger generation
and make Classical music cool.
It's a throwback to, like,
events where, like,
you dressed up just to get
on the red carpet.
- I love that.
- Do you have any siblings, Bob?
- I have two brothers, actually.
- Uh-huh.
- How many do you have?
- I have eight brothers
and three sisters.
- Whoa.
- That is crazy.
- You said you were adopted?
- Yeah.
- Did they have a talk where
they were, like, "You know--"
Where they went, like, one day,
like, "Well, just so you know."
- Well,
it's--like it's very obvious
that I'm adopted.
These are my parents.
So growing up
with white parents.
- A rainbow family.
- Like, this is my mom.
- She's gorgeous.
- Yeah, she's, like,
the best mom ever.
I'm literally the only gay one
in my family.
And I have
a Christian background,
and I've heard stories of kids
being shunned from the family
and all that.
And my mom has done nothing
but make me feel accepted.
And, she's just
an amazing woman.
I love my mom.
Growing up, I literally had,
like, the best parents
and best childhood.
- Did you ever feel a--a need
to just study up on black stuff?
- Kind of.
It wasn't a weird thing
until I got to high school,
middle school.
People were throwing out
all these, like,
black references.
And I was, like, "Wait.
What does that mean?"
Did you grow up with,
like, black culture
was, like, second-hand?
- I grew up
in an all-black family.
I went to all-black high school,
all-black elementary school
and a majority
black middle school.
- Like, I get called "Oreo,"
like, all the time.
- It's obnoxious.
- Or, like, "Oh,
he's kind of cute
for a black guy."
- Oh, don't even get me started
on being cute for a black guy.
It's kind
of a--it's really obnoxious.
- Wait, I think you're kind
of cute for a black guy, Naomi.
- Thank you, Kimberly Chi.
- Kind of, though.
[laughter]
["Cover Girl"
by RuPaul playing]
- [laughs]
Cover Girl,
put the bass in your walk
Head to toe,
let your whole body talk
And, what?
- Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
The world's biggest Madonna fan,
Michelle Visage.
- You must be my lucky star.
[laughter]
- A guy who's game for anything,
Carson Kressley.
Now, who would you do
in the Snatch Game?
- I would impersonate, um,
like, maybe a man.
Like, Michelle Visage.
[laughter]
- The gorgeous Gigi Hadid.
Now, is it more fun to hang out
with models or drag queens?
- Well, I've never had
this much fun at a runway show,
so, drag queens, of course.
[laughter]
- And the stunning Chanel Iman.
Did you have a good time
yesterday?
- Yes.
It was everything.
- [laughs]
This week, our queens
channeled showbiz greats,
as they went
for Snatch Game gold.
And tonight, my girls
are ready to take a bow,
because bitch!
They're Madonna.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
-  The realness
Thorgy Thor.
- Crouching Tiger,
Hidden Drag Queen.
- Nothing really matters.
- No, sure doesn't.
- As I'm walking down
the runway, I'm giving you,
like, angular,
interesting artistic movements,
and I'm feeling it.
- Undercover geisha.
- Oh, kimono,
she better don't.
- Up next, Kim Chi.
- Oh.
- Two in a row.
- I have a gorgeous
vintage wedding kimono.
But I wish I wasn't wearing
the same thing as Thorgy.
- She's servin'
that walk, Michelle.
- She is.
- W-O-K.
- Yeah.
Derrick Barry.
Nothing really matters.
The remix.
- Yes.
- I'm walking down
in the most original kimono.
It's hand-painted,
and I feel like
this is a standout piece.
- Is that sidewalk talk?
- Jean Paul Gaultier.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Naomi Smalls.
- Oh, again.
- Yeah, these girls
are really hung up on kimonos.
- I didn't think
anybody else
was going to choose
kimono Madonna.
I'm trying to own this
even though three other girls
are in the exact same look.
- Kung fu fightin'.
- This is, like,
the Victoria's
Secret section of Madonna.
- I like that material, girl.
[laughter]
- Acid Betty.
- She's keepin' her baby.
- It may have a few holes
in it, but--
[laughter]
- My Madonna look today
is from "Bedtime Stories,"
where she's pregnant,
giving birth to doves.
This outfit
represents who I am,
because obviously
I'm the only one
creative enough to think of it.
- I think she just
flipped us the bird.
- Bye, bye, birdie.
- Robbie Turnter.
- She's in a league of her own.
- There's no crying
in baseball, Robbie!
- I feel so cute.
I've got my cute little dress.
It's all hand-painted
with my little patches.
- I wonder if she's a pitcher
or a catcher.
- Me too.
- Chi Chi DeVayne.
You're gonna poke somebody's
eyes out with those things.
- If you're lucky.
- When you think of Madonna,
you think of the cone bra.
Bitch, I look good.
- Oh, yeah.
It's--she's totally
expressing herself.
I think she likes
a little hanky-panky.
Bob The Drag Queen.
- Oh!
- Not to be confused
with Bob the camp counselor.
- I love.
- My favorite Madonna look
- [laughs]
- Welcome, ladies.
When I call your name,
please step forward
and strike a pose.
- [whispers indistinctly]
- Kim Chi.
Chi Chi DeVayne.
You're both safe.
- Thank you.
- You may leave the stage.
Oh, the power of good-bye.
- [laughs]
- Ladies, it's time
for the judges' critiques.
- Tonight
on the runway,
I don't know
if you guys had some kind of
symbiotic message
to each other,
but there's a lot of kimonos
which is very interesting.
Thorgy, you did your take on it.
You kept it in geisha,
but still Thorgy's in there.
- The Michael Jackson
was so good.
I loved all of it.
- You kept character
better than anyone.
- It was everything for me.
- Up next, Acid Betty.
- I was not expecting
to see "Bedtime Stories"
and the whole
bird-fly-out thing.
So kudos to that.
- Thank you.
- I think your make-up
is okay tonight.
It's nothing spectacular.
But where I was really let down,
was in the Snatch Game, Betty.
- It didn't look like her.
It was like the wig
and the make-up,
you were like
a white Chaka Khan.
- I didn't get
any Nancy Grace from it.
It felt like
you were just being you.
It was just a fail
all the way around.
- I wasn't sure how to turn
such a serious woman funny.
- I needed like a nasal,
angry southern voice.
And then she leans in,
and she wants to talk
to you on the TV
like she's in your living room.
[laughter]
- I wish I had you as a coach.
- Okay.
- All right.
Up next, Robbie Turnter.
- I really enjoyed your catwalk
because it was really fun
and playful.
- I was really excited
about Diana.
And I--I think that most people
may not know who that is.
So I think that
how iconic she was,
and the voice and everything,
you kind of have to shove
that in people's faces
for them to get it.
- You could have gone
so much bigger with her.
- Punk took my voice away.
My voice kept cracking,
and I was going in and out
during Diana Vreeland.
- Well,
we could hear you perfectly.
It's just, we weren't impressed
with what was being said.
Up next, Naomi Smalls.
- It's becoming quite
predictable
for Naomi to come out
in basically, lingerie.
This is where we go, "Oh, maybe
I should switch it up now."
- In Snatch Game,
I got lost with the boobs.
I think if you would have just
stuffed it to the max,
it would of made the character
a lot more obvious to me.
- That was your moment
to go O-T-P.
- I was very underwhelmed
with my performance.
It was not coming out,
and I'm, like,
so embarrassed about it.
- All right.
Thank you, Naomi.
Up next, Derrick Barry.
- So we did Britney, huh?
I am so grateful.
- Oh, God.
- You done good, girl.
- Me and Gigi really,
really loved your
Britney performance yesterday.
- You kept character
the whole time.
You just were Britney.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you, Derrick.
Bob The Drag Queen.
- Tonight, on the runway.
Love it.
- I love your Madonna look too.
And I know you're
a huge Madonna fan.
And, like, one of
your biggest thing you said,
was when Madonna sent you,
like, a cease and desist?
- Yes!
- [laughs]
- Best moment of my life.
- The padding.
It's so good,
I wouldn't have known.
- You are serving "womana."
- This old luscious body.
- The Snatch Game.
Uzo Aduba, amazing.
- You were so good.
- Then, we get a little
Carol Channing.
You gave us extra,
which was wonderful.
- I do want to caution you,
however.
Sometimes you borderline
on showboating.
Just keep that in
the back of your mind.
- Mm-hmm.
- All right, ladies.
Well, I think
we've heard enough.
While you untuck backstage,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right.
Now, just between us
material squirrels.
- [laughs]
- What do you think?
Thorgy Thor.
- Her Michael Jackson,
I thought was divine.
- She was really good
at making fun of things
that are a little taboo.
- She stayed in character
the entire time.
I really felt
like Michael was there.
- Acid Betty.
- Her runway was very creative.
- But her Nancy Grace
was more like Nancy Disgrace.
- Ooh, child.
- How does a drag queen
do Nancy Grace
and she doesn't even
have the wig right?
- You need a little
helmet-y blonde.
And then you need a few
little Nancy Grace-isms.
And none of that happened.
It was just like,
she didn't even know
who Nancy Grace was.
- Robbie Turnter.
- The "League of Their Own" look
stood out from the rest.
I would give it a B plus.
- We love Diana Vreeland.
- We do, indeed.
Everything was wrong about it.
Why didn't she go
for the blown-back hair?
- With the--
with the bump at the top.
- Yes!
- The worst part
of the whole thing tonight
with Robbie, was the--
[coughs feebly]
[whispers]
"I have no voice."
- Uh-huh.
- All of a sudden,
you don't have a voice anymore?
And I think she needs
to get out of her head
and get into my car.
- Okay.
All right, Billy Ocean.
Naomi Smalls
did Tiffany Pollard.
New York.
- She didn't do New York.
- She did not do New York.
- She wasn't New York.
She wasn't Connecticut.
She wasn't New Jersey.
She wasn't Long Island.
I don't know what she was.
- But, Naomi's was my favorite
of the kimonos.
She made me want to wear it,
but I don't know
if it really screamed "Madonna."
- Derrick Barry.
- The Britney blew me away.
I was so excited for every time
that she was going
to answer a question.
- The runway thing,
I always find her a bit
timid on the runway.
- When you're on the catwalk,
you've got to just
give it all you got.
- You know, I once asked Iman
what is on her mind
on the runway.
And she looked at me dead
in the eyes and said, "Africa."
- That's what I do
when I go to bars.
- Oh, really?
- Yes. Think about Africa.
- Oh-kerr!
- Oh--
[trills, clicks tongue]
- Bob The Drag Queen.
- She flipped the script.
- [laughs]
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Thorgy Thor.
Your Michael Jackson
was off the wall.
And your Madonna look
was something to remember.
Bob The Drag Queen.
I's was crazy
about your Snatch Game.
And on the runway,
you are one unapologetic bitch.
Bob The Drag Queen,
condragulations,
you are the winner
of this week's challenge.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
[applause]
- You've won a collection
of handbags and wallets
from Lux De Ville
valued at $7,000.
- Wow.
[all "oohing"]
- [laughs]
Wow.
Whoo!
I took a risk, and it paid off.
- Bob and Thorgy,
you may join the other girls.
Derrick Barry.
You are safe.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
- Acid Betty,
your runway was
an immaculate conception.
But your Nancy Grace left us
asking,
"Who's that girl?"
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- I totally agree
with Snatch Game.
It sucked.
But I think Snatch Game sucks.
- Robbie Turner,
your runway was a hit.
But your Snatch Game
was a swing and a miss.
Naomi Smalls,
your runway look was borderline.
But your impersonation
of "New York"
bordered on "New Jersey."
Naomi Smalls.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
Robbie Turner,
you are safe.
- Thank you.
- Two queens stand before me.
As always, I've consulted
with the judges.
But quite frankly,
I don't give a
fuck what they say.
Because the final decision
is mine to make.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come
for you to lip-synch
for your life!
[echoes]
Life!
- I'm not about to go home
to Acid Betty.
I'm gonna bring it,
and I'm gonna do everything
I can to send this bitch home.
- Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
["Causing a Commotion" playing]
-  I've got the moves, baby
You got the motion
If we got together
We'd be causing a commotion
Someday you'll see
my point of view
- I'm pregnant with birds
coming out of my belly,
and now I have to lip-synch
for my life?
I'm ready to make TV history.
-  Work for you
You've got to
make the compromise
And maybe
Then we can keep
our love alive
And when it falls,
we won't let it die
It doesn't matter
if you win or lose
It's how you play the game
So get into the groove
- All you hear is music.
You have no idea what's
happening around you.
And in that moment, you will do
whatever it takes to stay.
-  Commotion
I hope you find
What you're looking for
Is it mine?
Walk through that door
We're wasting time
Make up your mind
And get into the groove
I got the moves, baby
You got the motion
If we got together
We'd be causing a commotion
Causing a commotion
- Yeah!
[cheers and applause]
- Ladies.
I've made my decision.
Naomi Smalls,
shantay, you stay.
- Oh.
- Acid Betty.
You've taken us
on one wild trip.
Thanks for the high.
- Thank you for the opportunity.
It's been amazing.
And I'm so happy to be
a part of royalty now.
- Now, sashay away.
- I love you guys.
Acid Betty out!
I'm so happy that I came here.
I would not change this
for anything.
Legends are born
in "RuPaul's Drag Race".
And now I'm officially a legend.
Bitches beware.
'Cause Acid Betty is now
being released to the world.
And it's gonna be trouble
from here on out.
- My seven rays of light.