- Previously on
"RuPaul's Drag Race"...
This is the 100th episode
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
all: Yes!
- Whoo!
- Oh, my God.
- So I've arranged a photo shoot
with some extra
special guest stars.
[laughing]
Pose the house down.
- You remind me of a dog trying
to get comfortable on the couch.
- Oh, my God.
- Each of you will be assigned
a legendary design challenge
from a past season.
[fabric rips]
- [gasps]
My fucking
panties just ripped.
Shit.
- Acid Betty.
- Every inch was kind
of covered with a thought.
To me that's what drag is about.
- Naysha Lopez.
- I just don't think
it looks good.
- I don't really sew.
- Kim Chi.
- You were giving me, like,
this Cowardly Lion
ferociousness.
- I like that you kept
your areolas bald.
The breasts are the windows
to the soul for sure.
- Laila McQueen.
- I felt like the bottom half
was just a cop-out.
- Do you think
that your missteps
would warrant you in the bottom?
- I don't think that
I am the least put together.
- Who do you think
is the least put together?
- Naomi.
Her look is very plain.
- Do you agree with that, Naomi?
- No.
- Kim Chi, condragulations.
You're the winner
of this week's challenge.
- Yeah, girl.
- Laila McQueen,
shantay, you stay.
Naysha Lopez, sashay away.
- Girl.
- Whoo.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Aww.
- The first message
in lipstick on a mirror.
Holy fuck.
Too real.
- "It was a pleasure
meeting you all.
Play the cards you are..."
both: "Dealt
and turn da party."
- Aww.
- Cutie.
- I'm sad to see her go.
She had such a nice butt.
- I'm gonna miss my sister
a lot, so te amo, mamita.
For me it's shocking
that Naysha
left this competition
too sooner
because I know
she can offer a lot more.
- I got to say,
when you hear the words
"lip-synch for your life"
in person,
it's not fucking funny.
- It sucked.
Hearing the judges' critiques,
I definitely need to do more
to stand out.
- Wipe her away, girl.
- Shit's getting real.
Back at home I'm more of the,
like, edgier girl,
but, like, seeing people
like Thorgy, Acid Betty,
and Kim Chi,
it's like, "Okay,
"I am no longer the big fish
in a small pond.
Bitch, you need to, like,
step it up."
- So, Laila,
were you gagged
that I was not
in the bottom two?
- I had to say something.
To be honest,
I do not think
that a lot of the girls
really deserved to be safe.
Naomi's boat
looked like shit.
Cynthia's outfit
was a knockoff pink version
of Detox's from her season,
and Miss Derrick Barry--
girl, the first episode,
a bikini, really?
It was so hard to read.
Between you, me, her,
and Naysha, I was like,
"I honestly have no idea
who they're gonna pick."
I don't blame Laila
for being salty
about being in the bottom two.
I think she's feeling like
she's really just blending in.
Everyone wants to meet the star,
not the entourage,
and right now
Laila's just giving entourage.
- Oh.
- ¶ RuPaul's Drag Race ¶
- The winner
of "RuPaul's Drag Race"
receives a one year supply
of Anastasia
Beverly Hills cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100,000.
With extra special
guest judges
Jamal Sims,
Lucian Piane,
and "Pitch Perfect"'s
Ester Dean.
- ¶ RuPaul's Drag Race ¶
- ¶ May the best woman,
best woman win ¶
[upbeat music]
- Good luck.
- Good morning.
- Walk into the room
purse first. Clack.
- We've all survived
the first elimination.
The race has finally begun.
- Bye, Naysha.
- There goes the prettiest one.
- She was beautiful.
Emphasis on "was."
Who's the next prettiest?
- I know Britney
wants to think she is.
- Why can't I know I am?
all: Ooh!
- Girl.
She done already had her.
[siren wails]
- Ooh, girl,
she done already done
had herses.
Hey, bitches.
all: Hey.
- True or falsetto:
America's next drag superstar
needs to strike a chord
in the key of,
"Gee, your drag
sounds terrific."
Otherwise,
you're gonna fall flat,
and I ain't just preaching
to the choir, okurr?
- Yes, work.
- Whoo.
- Hello, hello, hello.
[cheering]
- Yay!
- Whoo!
- Now, ladies,
who likes to dance?
[cheering]
- Good, because for
today's mini challenge
we're having
a Latin style dance off.
- Yes.
- Escándalo.
I want to see you swing
those hips to a song
by AB Soto featuring me,
"Cha Cha Bitch."
Yes.
Hola, Pit Crew.
all: Whoo!
- Delicioso.
- The Pit Crew
is delivering clothes
provided by Out of the Closet
Thrift Store,
benefiting the AIDS Healthcare
Foundation since 1990.
- Oh, awesome.
- So grab your cha-cha heels,
get into quick drag,
and meet me on the dance floor.
Go.
- Go.
- Anyone need a mother
of the bride outfit?
- I love it.
- Someone should be doing J. Lo
and just ass out.
- Actually, Spanish women
don't shave their legs, right,
so my hairy legs are good?
- Back home in Brooklyn,
Thorgy is well-known
for her alternative
kind of style,
and it's a hairy style,
to say the least.
- You know what?
I don't think I need to--
I don't want to wear tights.
- All right, kids,
time's up.
Señoritas, look who's here
to help me judge
the "Cha Cha Bitch" fight.
Say hello to AB Soto.
all: Whoo!
- Oh, my God.
- So, AB, any words
of advice for my chicas?
- Yes, give me reina,
give me perra,
and work your cha cha, bitch.
- [laughs] Acid Betty,
you're first.
Ready, set,
cha cha, bitch.
[laughing]
Ain't no party
like a cha cha party
'cause a cha cha party
goes ah!
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
- Ow!
- ¶ Five, six,
cha cha, bitch ¶
- Derrick Barry.
- ¶ Cinco, seis ¶
both: ¶ Cha cha, bitch ¶
Yes, honey,
we are serving taco Tuesday.
¶ Ella morena ¶
¶ In the club
and we're gonna slay her ¶
- Cynthia Lee Fontaine.
- ¶ They wanna know,
¿oye quién es ella? ¶
¶ ¿Qué es lo que
quiere la nena? ¶
- The cha-cha heels
are alive.
- ¶ Now dance,
no twerking, bitch ¶
¶ Shake my ass,
move my hips ¶
- Whoo!
Bob The Drag Queen.
¶ ¶
- Whoo!
Yes, ma'am.
- ¶ Cha cha, bitch ¶
- Dax ExclamantionPoint.
- ¶ Uno, tres, cinco, seis ¶
- Naomi Smalls.
[laughs]
- ¶ Five, six,
cha cha, bitch ¶
- Laila McQueen.
- ¶ Five, six,
cha cha, bitch ¶
- Señorita Robbie Turner.
¶ ¶
Chi Chi DeVayne.
- ¶ Cha cha cha,
cha cha cha ¶
¶ Cha cha cha,
cha cha cha, cha cha cha ¶
[cheering]
¶ Cha cha cha,
cha cha cha, cha cha cha ¶
- Take that, Donald Trump.
Kim Chi.
¶ Cha cha cha, cha cha cha,
cha cha cha, bitch ¶
cha cha cha ¶
[record scratches]
¶ Cha cha cha, cha cha cha,
cha cha cha, bitch ¶
- This is sad.
Kim Chi has two left feet
and vertigo.
- Work!
- Thorgy Thor.
¶ ¶
[laughs]
- Cha cha, bitch.
¶ ¶
- [laughing]
[cheering]
- Oh, my goodness.
I'ma call immigration on y'all.
Ladies, we'll be posting
all of your best "Cha Cha Bitch"
moves at LogoTV.com,
and I just got to say,
Thorgy Thor,
special shout-out for serving
Frida Kahlo realness.
- Oh, thank you.
- Now, ladies, two of you were
the baddest bitches of all.
The winners are...
Cynthia Lee Fontaine...
[cheering]
And Chi Chi DeVayne.
Let's give a big "Drag Race"
thank you to AB Soto.
all: Whoo!
- Now, cha cha, bitch.
Ladies, I'm glad
you're all warmed up
because this week's
maxi challenge
is an all dancing,
all lip-synching extravaganza.
all: Whoo!
- Choreography?
Mm-mm.
- You'll be competing
in two teams
in the dragappella movie
"Bitch Perfect."
[cheering]
- #BitchPerfect, okay?
Plus you'll be meeting
with a choreographer
who's worked with Miley,
Madonna, and J. Lo, honey.
The red hot Jamal Sims.
- Whoo!
- Cynthia and Chi Chi,
you won the mini challenge,
so you are team captains.
Cynthia, your group
is the Lady Bitches,
the sweethearts of dragapella
from the prestigious
Lace Front Institute
of Technology, darling.
[laughter]
Chi Chi, your group
is Shady Bitches.
Y'all the bad girls
from the Lake Titicaca Academy
of Braids, Weaves,
and Waffles.
[laughter]
All right, ladies,
it's time to pick teams.
Cynthia, who will you
choose first?
- Bob The Drag Queen.
- All right, all right.
- Chi Chi, you're next.
- Acid Betty.
- It don't get
shadier than this.
- Derrick Barry.
- Oh, thank God
I did not get picked last.
- Thorgy Thor.
- Whoo!
Ay-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi-yow.
- Laila.
[laughter]
- Let's go with
Dax ExclamationPoint.
- Yay, my turn.
- Robbie.
- That means that Kim Chi
and Naomi Smalls are left.
- Sorry, Kim, but I'm gonna
have to go with Naomi.
- Which of course means that
Kim Chi goes to Cynthia's team.
- Wah.
It's okay.
I wouldn't want me either.
- Ladies, this week
you've got to use
your charisma,
uniqueness, nerve,
and talent
to chorally gratify
me and the judges.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[cheering]
- Oh, my God.
Kim Chi's a horrible dancer.
She's so bad.
How is she gonna get
through this dance challenge?
- So, girls, like,
we're gonna, like,
take one, pass it down.
The pressure of being
a team captain,
it--it can be a lot,
but I've done choreography
for the girls back at home.
I got this.
- I think we should
get some choreography together.
- Let's just worry about that
when in time comes.
Don't--don't confuse yourself.
We need to know
where you come in first.
- I think after this
we should
put something
together just in case.
- Don't get scared.
- I'm not scared.
I'm just trying to be prepared.
- I know, but--
- I'm not gonna be unprepared
because of you, boo.
- I can sense that Acid
definitely wants
to be the group leader,
but it ain't happening.
We need to learn
where we come in first.
- Fine, but we got to
start doing something.
We can't just sit here
sitting here learning words.
- I've known Betty for,
like, ten years,
and sometimes because Betty
is so artistic,
she gets away with
being a fucking asshole.
- Let's go from the beginning.
"Oh, really,
is that all you got?
What about this?"
- Is that what
you're gonna be doing?
- "Lake, Lake,
Titi, Titi, Titi."
Yeah.
- No, you're gonna be out there.
- But the rest--
- Whatever.
- Well, we should probably
set it instead of "whatever."
Let's get beyond "whatever."
- Okay.
- Acid Betty is an asshole,
and she knows it,
and she loves it,
and that's why she doesn't
work in New York.
She's so demanding
and mean to everyone
that nobody wants
to work with her.
You're gonna be shamed.
You're gonna be put down,
so, Chi Chi, good luck.
- Coming up...
Cynthia Lee.
- Hi, RuPaul.
- What's the name
of your group?
- My name
of my group is--
- You got to look at a paper
to get the name of your group?
- Ay-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi.
- Now, Chi Chi,
you're the leader.
How are you navigating
all these strong personalities?
- I'm finding them
a little bit difficult.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- [laughs]
- Formations, formations.
- One, two, three, four.
- I like that roll back
and sit in the hip.
- Yeah.
- That's cool.
This week's maxi challenge is
an a cappella lip-sync battle.
Oh, my gosh,
we have to lip-synch.
We have to dance.
Basically we're putting out
"Bitch Perfect."
- Here we go, and pat,
pat, pat-pat-pat.
Let me see y'all do it.
- Boom, boom.
- Bam, bam, bam, bam.
Uh-uh, y'all look like
flailing fishes.
- Well, "pat, pat,
pat-pat-pat,
"pat, pat, pat-pat-pat"
was the original rhythm.
- No, ma'am.
It's pat, pat, pat-pat-pat,
pat, pat, pat-pat-pat.
- Switch it
to something simpler.
- That's so simple too.
I can't even get any simpler.
I picked my team based
off the mini challenge,
but girl,
these girls cannot dance.
Boom, boom.
- Wait, we're now--
we're robot-ing.
- Okay, simple.
One, two, three, four,
turn and down, down.
- It look crazy.
- I'm just trying to fucking
get your visual in my head
so I can have it.
- Do it, bitch, do it.
- Three, four, five, six, seven.
- That's it.
- One, two, three, four, five.
- No, five, six, seven,
eight is just a turn.
Don't move on five, six,
seven, eight at all.
- We should change it if
you can't get it.
What the eff?
It's simple.
One, two, three, four, turn.
- One, two,
three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
- Is that--
- Got it.
The hands weren't the same,
but fuck it.
We got to move on.
You ready?
¶ One shot, one shot
of adrenaline, adrenaline ¶
- I don't know.
- We're doing it.
It's happening.
- All right, girl.
Can you just give me a shot,
and I'll flip out?
- I'll do the second one.
- And I'll punch you
in the face--boom!
- See, you trying to get
out of the choreography.
Bitch, you trying to do comedy.
- I can do all of it.
If we're standing there,
"One shot,"
five beats of silence,
it's boring.
- I don't want you to do
that punch thing.
I just want you to, like--
- Okay.
Chi Chi does not get funny,
and I'm, like, a comedy queen,
so I'm like,
"Okay, you know what?
I'm gonna do it anyway.
I don't care, bitch,
it'd be funny."
- All right,
so shall we move on
and do it again,
or do you want to stand here?
- We'll get it.
- Oh, my God.
These bitches getting
on my nerves.
They getting on my nerves now.
- All right, Lady Bitches,
are you ready?
- Kim, I feel like you're
the one who is kind of,
like, nerdy and not cool.
- Yeah.
Regina George.
- I'm the ringleader.
- I think you should be,
like, her kid sister.
- You do exactly
whatever she does,
just not as good
as she does it.
- Aw, Laila's my impersonator.
That's cute.
- Yeah.
- My biggest concern
is that I'm gonna
fade into the background
comparatively
to all the other girls,
so I'm not sure
about playing the,
like, little sister, like,
wannabe Derrick Barry,
'cause I probably wouldn't be
the best Britney impersonator.
- Look at this
giant fucking heel.
- Yeah.
- Those are so cute.
- Bitch, I hope y'all can dance
in them high-ass heels.
You need something
this size, hon.
- That's like a--four inches.
- No, ma'am.
- Have you ever, guys,
been in proper shows before
where you have to learn
choreography and stuff?
- When I was a kid, yes.
Like, for years.
- Just--oh,
when you were younger.
So you don't really
know how to, like,
just focus
and get it done?
- Yeah, I do.
- 'Cause we're
talking about shoes.
I would love to,
like, save the time
and figure out
what we're doing.
This is how
the group's gonna down.
"So what'd you guys do?"
"Well, we spent time talking
about how comfortable
these shoes were."
- We're not going down.
- No.
- My worry with this group
is that I might be the only
one that's gonna give it
and the other girls are just
gonna take me down with them.
Chi Chi needs to step up
and get us together.
So we all know
our lip syncs somewhat?
Like, the words?
- Ish.
- Mm-hmm.
- I think that's gonna be
the most important part
so when we meet the
choreographer
we can kind of just take
in what he's saying.
You're, like,
looking at me like
I'm Charlie Brown's teacher.
Wah, wah, wah, wah,
wah, wah, wah.
Wah, wah, wah,
wah, wah, wah, wah.
You're done?
- No, I'm not done.
Definitely not done.
I just want to be good.
My biggest fear
in this challenge
is these girls flopping
and me having
to take the fall
for my whole team.
- Hey, kitty girls.
- Hey, Ru.
all: Hi!
- How are my
little treble makers?
- We're working it out.
- Yeah.
- Cynthia Lee.
- Hi, RuPaul.
- What's the name of your group?
- My name
of my group is--
- You've got to look at a paper
to get the name of your group?
Lady Bitches.
- Yes, ma'am.
- So what--
did you have a strategy
in choosing these ladies?
- Actually, yes,
'cause I got dancers.
I got the comedians one,
the actors, makeup artists.
- Now, Kim Chi,
this is a lip-sync challenge.
Are you a lip-sync artist?
- I think I am,
but my biggest problem
is sometimes when I lip-synch
my lisp comes through.
- I'm not mad at a lisp.
- Yeah.
- In fact,
I'm partial to a lisp.
My empire was built on a lisp.
- Really.
- Absolutely.
Are you familiar with
the movie "Pitch Perfect?"
- I've never heard of it
or even know what it's about.
I was probably in Korea
at the time.
- Well, it just came out, uh,
six months ago.
[laughter]
- Oh, my God.
Ay-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi.
- So now, Laila,
why do you think you wound up
in the bottom two?
- Well,
the photo with Mathu
was definitely
less than amazing.
- Right, because, you know,
you were scrunched over.
You weren't shining through.
How are you gonna shine through
in this challenge?
- I ain't gonna
be squatting down
and sitting in the back.
I'm gonna come forward
and be present.
- Well, you know,
a lot of girls say that.
There's more strategy
to it than that.
You realize that?
- Yes, ma'am.
I get it.
I need to bring myself up
to the level
of the other girls
so I can be like,
"I'm here too."
It's not just them.
I am here.
- Listen, I am
so excited for this,
and we're gonna see
the real crème de la crème
rise to the top, all right?
- Oh, she's coming back?
- She's coming back.
All right, get to work.
- Thank you.
- All right.
- Thanks, lady.
- Whoo.
- Well, all right, now.
- Hey.
- Hi, Ru.
- Are y'all the Shady Bitches?
- Yes, we are.
- Are there any shady bitches
in this group?
Oh, okay, well,
there you have it.
Now, Chi Chi,
you from Louisiana.
- Louisiana, baby.
- You know, both my parents
are from Louisiana.
- Yes, I enjoy being
a country queen.
- Yeah.
- I mean, who doesn't like
an old smoked turkey neck, baby?
[laughter]
- Now, Chi Chi,
you're the leader.
How are you navigating all
of these strong personalities?
- I'm finding them
a little bit difficult.
- Really?
Are you for real?
- I'm for real.
I've never had to deal
with such big personalities,
and back home I'm the star,
so to get this many
stars in one room?
It's just, like, girl.
- Okay, well, is anybody
afraid of choreography?
- No.
She didn't like my comedic
take of a punch in the face.
- No, ma'am.
- I'm always been,
like, putting in
my little comedic
chime in there,
but you're shutting it down,
so I'm probably
gonna do it anyway
regardless of
what Chi Chi says.
- I prefer the whole thing
to be choreographed.
I feel safer,
and I think
I'm having a hard time
getting her to actually
put down the steps.
- Maybe you should be
more of a tyrant.
- I cannot be a tyrant.
That's not in my blood.
I think I'll give that part
to Acid Betty.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- Are you a tyrant,
Acid Betty?
- No, I haven't showed
that side yet.
- Girl.
- She's the leader,
so I'm letting her
kind of make decisions.
- All right,
get back to work,
and knock 'em dead.
All right. Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Let's get this work done.
- All right, ladies,
gather round.
Now, if at any time
during this competition
you feel the need
to get something
off your chesticles--
yes, take advantage
of the Shade Tree.
- Uh-oh.
- Oh.
- Think of it as a diary room
where you can say whatever
you want in total privacy.
all: Ooh.
- So good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
All right?
all: All right.
- Coming up...
- Give me one shot.
- Uh, uh.
- They can't do it.
- Oh, she's a diva.
both: And three, four.
- Whoops.
- Kim Chi is the worst dancer
in "Drag Race" history.
We're fucked.
- [laughs]
- Hey, hey, hey,
Team Lady Bitches.
- We're ladies,
and we're bitches.
- My team are setting up
to met Jamal.
I'm so excited about that.
He's a sexy--mmm--
chocolate flavor.
[laughs]
[record scratches]
Did my teeths look yellow?
No.
- Let me something
y'all put together.
- We have, like,
a pose that we do,
which is, like,
a one, two, look pose.
¶ Who do you think you are? ¶
¶ We're all born naked
and the rest is drag ¶
We like to incorporate
our little move.
- Uh-huh,
it's--I--I see it.
- Jamal's
pretty much like,
"Oh, well, that's cute,
but no."
- You guys are Lady Bitches,
and so I really want
to present you guys
dancing very up,
very, you know,
trained and very precise
and classic.
So let's start
from the top, yeah?
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight.
One, two, three,
four, five, six.
Let me see you do it.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
- Kim Chi
is the worst dancer...
- Whoops.
- In "Drag Race" history.
both:
One, two, three, four.
- We're not doing crazy stuff.
We're not pirouetting
and back flipping.
Step, touch,
and not only that,
it's the first move.
We're fucked.
- One, two, three,
four, five, six.
All right,
something's going on here.
- Yeah, I'm, like,
losing it with the arms.
I'm trying to--
- Yeah.
Don't think about the arms.
Let's get the feet first.
- Okay, right first or--
- Right first.
- It's profoundly difficult
to try and do all these steps
but then also I have to think,
"I need to stand out
as a character."
- Let me have you two
do it by yourselves.
- Don't be--one, two.
- Okay, can we--
can we start over.
I'm so sorry.
All right.
- Don't be--
both:
Jealous of my boogie.
- Three, four, five.
Okay, listen.
One, two, three, four.
All right, and right now
you guys are doing
three, four, five, six,
so on one, two.
- One, two, three, four, five.
What?
It's like I'm learning English
all over again.
- Don't be afraid.
Right now you're
looking like this.
Let it go, all right?
Here we go.
Five, six, seven.
Don't be--
- ¶ Jealous of my boogie ¶
¶ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ¶
- Whoa.
- Uh-oh.
- Are you all right,
sweetie?
- Kim Chi falls,
and just my heart
drops out of my cuckoo.
Oh, my God.
- Kim Chi,
are you sure you want
to keep doing it in heels?
- 100%.
- Okay.
- She need to nail this
because if she falls tomorrow
in front of the judges live,
we are completely done.
- Shady Bitches in the house.
all: Hey.
- So we're working with
the fabulous Jamal Sims.
I'm ready for him to just
give us some structure
to this dance routine
that I've come up with.
- Show me what you got.
- Well, what about this?
Tit, tit,
ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah,
Titi, Titicaca.
Seven, eight.
Ay.
all: Ay!
- Ay.
all: What!
all: Oh!
- Ay.
all: Bitch.
all: La-la, la, la-la.
- All right, guys.
So you guys have
a lot of good ideas,
and I think we could kind of
clean 'em up and make 'em...
- Together.
- Cohesive.
"Cohesive" is the word.
- I'm so happy that we have
a little bit of choreography
like I suggested--
Chi Chi,
because now we're with Jamal,
and he's actually
using our choreography.
- I want to see
"Give me one shot."
- ¶ Give me one shot ¶
- Okay.
- ¶ One shot ¶
- Okay, all right.
- ¶ Of adrenaline ¶
- All right, we're gonna--
you might want to
be careful with that.
- Yeah, that's what
I said right away.
I was like,
"Why are we shooting drugs?"
I don't know.
- Give me one shot,
and then from here,
grab each other's arms
so--yeah, lock in
underneath--
- Underneath.
Underneath.
- There you go.
- Oh, sorry.
- Five, six, seven.
all: ¶ Give me one shot,
one shot ¶
- Oh.
- What the hell?
- Can we scooch down
a little teeny bit?
Like, can we get a little bit
more space for us?
Thank you.
- One more time.
all: ¶ Give me one shot,
one shot ¶
- Oh, one more time.
- Sorry.
- Yeah.
all: ¶ Give me one shot,
one shot ¶
- ¶ Of adrenaline ¶
- Ah!
- Ahh! Boom.
- I really like this moment.
- Yeah.
Thank God.
Jamal loved
my adrenaline thing.
He thought it was funny,
and he kept it,
and I was like,
"Eat it."
- I want to see this
individually.
¶ Give me one shot,
one shot ¶
¶ Uh, uh, of adrenaline ¶
There you go.
Next.
- ¶ One shot ¶
- Click, click,
- ¶ Of a sexy, sexy,
sexy adrenaline ¶
- All right.
¶ Give me one shot, one shot,
uh, uh, of adrenaline ¶
All right.
Here we go.
¶ Give me one shot,
one shot ¶
Uh, uh.
- Look--I keep--
sorry, one more time.
Sorry, sorry.
The look, I forgot.
- Let it go.
Just shake it off,
shake it off.
- I'm thinking too much.
- We'll come back to you.
Your turn.
Five, six, seven.
¶ Give me--
shot, one shot ¶
click, clack--
¶ Of adrenaline ¶
¶ Uh-huh, adrenaline ¶
Ah!
- Oh, she's a diva.
- It's about commitment.
Sweat flying, hair dripping,
whatever, it doesn't matter.
As long as you commit,
you're in it, okay?
How you feeling?
- I mean, I'm shaky on it,
but I got to
go through it a few times
and I'll get it.
Like, that's how I work.
Like, I don't pick up
choreography super quick.
Like, if I think while
I'm dancing, I can't do it.
I get really in here,
and it just becomes
all fucked up, so...
- Dax's attitude was
really off-putting to me
just because it didn't feel like
she really wanted to do it.
I think there's a lot
of insecurity there
when it comes
to the choreography.
You have to push yourself
on this one,
'cause we don't have
a lot of time.
- Totally.
It means a lot
for me to be here,
and I don't want to have
to go back to Savannah
and find some shitty day job
picking up dog shit
or, you know, just doing random
sporadic shows in dive bars.
Like, I want to take
over the world,
and I want to do it now,
and I want to do it with drag,
so I will make it work.
- I'm a little nervous,
I'm not gonna lie.
We didn't get
all the way through, so...
- So rehearsal is over,
and the Lady Bitches are
in a little bit of trouble.
Kim Chi seems a little too
in her head to pull this off,
and nobody's expecting her
to be the best
dancer in the room,
but she's thinking that,
and that's
what's messing her up.
- I remember the choreography,
but my only problem is hitting,
like, the points, like,
at the right time, so.
- We can help you with that.
- One thing we can't do
is teach you
that rhythm in a day.
- Yeah.
- But you can, like,
just live in your character,
and like,
if you're offbeat,
just be like--what happened?
- 'Cause then you're funny.
- We're all, like,
rallying around.
We're like, "Kim Chi,
you can do this,"
but Kim Chi is being really,
like, down on herself.
- I just really wish, like,
I could hit the beats.
- They said last week
that they love
that you're a nerd.
You'll be fine.
- I am so nervous
about tomorrow.
I really don't want
to let my group down.
Everyone has been
super, super helpful
guiding me through all of this.
I'm not ready to go home yet.
I have so many looks and ideas
that I want to showcase.
Man.
I'm just gonna try my best
and do what I always do.
- Uh, uh-uh, uh.
Uh, uh-uh, and stop.
You all okay?
You guys hot?
- Yes, very.
- That means we're
putting in work.
- Yeah, that'd be great.
- Yeah, do you have
any paper towels?
- Y'all need to focus.
- What?
- Y'all need to focus
on what y'all doing.
- I think I'm doing
a good job, you know.
- Yeah, do a good job
or you're gonna have to
lip-synch against me.
- Why do you think you're
gonna be in the bottom?
- 'Cause I'm the team captain.
They're gonna say,
"The team captain
"should have had everybody
at her's--at her level."
- Yes, but I'll be
the first person
to be like, "Mm,
she did a fucking
good job as captain."
- 'Cause she gonna
throw me under the bus.
- Fuck yeah,
I'll be honest as fuck.
She was--
- What'd I do?
- You were like, "At least
I can lip-synch for myself.
I know I was gonna be all that."
That's what you did.
- But then I
pulled it back together.
- She pulled
the team together, yeah.
- You can say
that if they ask me.
- Exactly.
- Betty is being
so negative,
and, like, counterproductive,
and I'm like, "Oh, my God.
This is so stupid."
- It is what it is.
Just hope you're not
lip-synching
against me, darling.
I don't have time
to coddle this girl.
We're both on this
competition together.
When that bus comes by,
I'm gonna throw her first.
I told her that too.
- Coming up...
- I'm still learning how to be
comfortable in my own skin.
I'm still a virgin.
- What?
- [laughs]
[upbeat music]
- Oh.
- Shady Bitches.
- Ooh, we're gonna kill
the Shady Ladies.
- Oh, my goodness.
- Time to get styling.
Today's elimination day.
This the first time we're
performing for the judges.
I'm very nervous.
How did your group's
rehearsal go?
- It went well.
I was nervous
as fuck at first,
but I have to understand
that everybody's not a dancer,
and everybody's not gonna
catch on as fast as me,
so I can't be
frustrated about it.
You know what I mean?
- Oh, yeah.
This challenge--when I first
got it, I'm like, "Oh, my God.
This is, like,
my biggest nightmare."
- Everybody's not
a born dancer.
- Yeah.
Growing up,
I was definitely an outsider.
The weird, fat art kid
who had a strong lisp
and a strong accent,
and that's why
I just really never learned
how to dance
and never learned how to,
like, feel the music.
I used to be 350 pounds.
- 350?
- Jesus.
- Yeah.
Until about 3 1/2 years ago.
both: Wow.
- Obviously, like, I'm not
as fat as I was before,
but the fat kid is,
like, still in me.
- Oh, yes.
- Yeah, no,
it never goes away, girl.
Come on, proof.
This is me fat.
- Oh, queen.
- Oh, my God.
- Girl, you look
completely different.
- I was chubby too.
I was always aware it,
like, when I was kid, like,
'cause other kids
made it very apparent like,
"Mm, reminding you.
Not only are you super gay,
but you're also chubby."
When I was an overweight kid,
being ridiculed
and made fun of,
I wanted to have that poise
and that confidence
and that power,
and now finally with drag
I can do that.
- That's how it was.
Like, when you're fat,
people just, like,
just don't treat you like--
- Like a person?
- Yeah.
Like taking public transit,
people never sit next to you.
- Really, you notice
things like that?
- All the time.
Because of those experiences,
I'm still learning
how to be confident in myself
and how to be comfortable
in my own skin,
but just like all the other
things I'm doing here,
I want to commit to it
and become better.
- Did people start hitting on
you when you lost the weight?
- I'm still a virgin, so no.
- What?
- I was totally coming onto you
when I met you that one time.
- Maybe people
are hitting on you
and you literally
have no clue.
Is that a possibility?
- Not really; I don't know.
- Yes, yes.
- I think so.
Acid said she was
hitting on you and you--
- I was, hard too.
- I just thought
you were being friendly.
- I'm gagging.
- Hopefully someone
sees the beauty in me
one of these days.
- I don't think Kim Chi knows
what she looks like.
She's still a virgin
because she's not aware
that she's, like,
a good-looking 6'4" man.
You got to own that.
- So, Cynthia.
- Uh-huh?
- What was it
like in Puerto Rico?
- Oh, amazing.
- They got a lot of gangs
in Puerto Rico too.
- Yes.
- When I was
younger, girl,
I wanted to be in a gang.
Girl, I had a gun,
a .38 Special.
- What?
- Yes, God.
I was a little gangbanger.
Girl, I've seen people shot.
- Oh, my God.
- I've smelled, like,
the smell of brains.
- Chi Chi, that is insane.
- Girl, to see my mom
break down and cry?
That was it.
Plus my daddy beat the hell
out of me for having a gun.
- Good parenting.
- Yeah.
- I can't even imagine.
- When I tell you
I come from the streets,
I'm not kidding.
People don't make it
where I come from.
- Were you doing
all of that
with gangs and everything
'cause you were trying
to hide the fact
that you were gay?
- Yeah,
'cause I was afraid
of what my mom,
my brother, you know,
everybody would think of me.
When I look back,
I can kind of see
why I was acting out.
It was because
I wasn't being me.
When I finally came out,
it was a turning point
in my life.
I could have been dead.
I could have been locked up,
but I'm here with you girls.
I feel blessed,
bitch, to be here.
- And you're a role model,
an example
for the future generations.
So, so proud of you, baby.
- Baby, I overcame it.
- All right.
- Okay.
Can I get an amen?
all: Amen.
- [speaking Spanish]
- What?
- What does that mean?
- "If you can't love yourself,
how the hell you can
love somebody else?"
I will never read
another queen on TV again.
- I know, bitch,
no, ma'am.
- Who does she think she is?
Blahbedy-blah-blah-blah.
Hasn't she ever heard
of a lace front?
Blippity, bloppity, bloopity.
If I was on
"RuPaul's Drag Race,"
I tell you what I would do.
- Ain't that
the truth, right?
- I would do this,
and I'd never do that.
Cut, too, girl.
[upbeat music]
["Cover Girl" by RuPaul plays]
¶ ¶
- [laughs]
- ¶ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ¶
¶ Head to toe ¶
¶ Let your whole body talk ¶
¶ And what? ¶
Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
My duet partner Michelle Visage.
Don't you look eloguent?
- [laughs]
and the writer and the arranger
of "Bitch Perfect,"
Lucian Piane,
is here.
- Hey, Ru.
- Our dean of dance,
Jamal Sims.
Were my girls ladies or shady?
- It was a bit of both.
[laughs]
- Just the way I like 'em,
and multi-talented
singer, songwriter,
and actress,
Miss Ester Dean.
Girl, you co-wrote "Firework,"
"Super Bass," "S&M."
When you gonna
write a song for us to do?
- I'm gonna write it right now.
[laughter]
- This week we challenged
our queens to be bitch perfect
in a dragappella
lip-sync extravaganza.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
Coming up...
- ¶ We're all fly,
fly, fly, fly ¶
[glass shatters]
- Oh, my God!
- [laughs]
- Once a year, two rival
dragappella groups
meet in the
BoobsForQueens warehouse.
- Calling all
the basic pitches.
- The Lady Bitches
from the Lace Front Institute
of Technology...
- Well, look who's here
for an off-key kiki.
- Have a sing off
with the Shady Bitches
from the Lake Titicaca Academy
of Braids, Weaves, and Waffles.
- I thought I smelled
out of tuna fishes.
- Oh, hell no.
- The rules are simple.
Keep it cute or sashay away.
- Category is RuPaul.
- Bitches better beware.
all: ¶ Ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ¶
- ¶ Five, six, seven ¶
- ¶ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ¶
¶ Jealous of my boogie ¶
¶ Jealous of my boogie,
jealous of my boogie ¶
- ¶ Hey, DJ, love the way
I lose my inhibitions ¶
¶ When you spin ¶
¶ And I don't care
if people stare ¶
¶ I'd rather boogie
than try to fit in ¶
- ¶ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ¶
¶ Jealous of my boogie ¶
¶ You can say
that you are not ¶
¶ But I always
see you looking ¶
¶ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ¶
- ¶ Jealous of my boogie ¶
- ¶ Don't be ¶
- ¶ You can say
that you are not ¶
¶ But I always
see you looking ¶
- ¶ Don't be so jealous
of my boogie ¶
- Oh, really?
Is that all you got?
What about this?
all: ¶ Lake, Lake,
Titi, Titicaca ¶
¶ Titi, Titi, Lake, Lake ¶
¶ Titi, Titicaca, Titi, Titi ¶
¶ Geronimo, Geronimo ¶
¶ They're falling
like they're dominos ¶
¶ Sight beat the world
and we shall see ¶
¶ Ay, ay ay, ay,
ay, ay, ay, ay ¶
¶ La-la-la, la-la ¶
- ¶ Geronimo, Geronimo ¶
¶ These girls
are falling dominoes ¶
¶ They, they call me dynamo,
but I be yelling vámanos ¶
- ¶ So you 'bout
to undergo Daenerys ¶
¶ In "A Game of Thrones" ¶
¶ No, I'm not no common ho ¶
¶ Slip sliding
down a rabbit hole, what? ¶
- ¶ And they be slain ¶
¶ I slay these bitches,
double Dutch ¶
- ¶ And they be slain ¶
¶ I slay these bitches,
so what's up? ¶
- Yeah, so what's up?
What else you got?
- We'll show you what's up.
- ¶ All of the glamour
and all of the fame ¶
¶ People are gonna
remember your name ¶
¶ Now and forever,
your dreams coming true ¶
- ¶ Dreams coming true ¶
- ¶ They're gonna love it
whatever you do ¶
all: ¶ Gonna love you ¶
- ¶ As you are ¶
- ¶ You're a superstar ¶
all: ¶ Gonna love you ¶
- ¶ As you are ¶
- ¶ You're a... ¶
all: ¶ Superstar ¶
- ¶ And do the ones
I love know ¶
¶ That you're the reason
why I dare to live my life ¶
¶ I dare to liberate my mind ¶
¶ You're running
through my veins ¶
¶ Make me come alive ¶
all: ¶ Mmm, da-da-da-da ¶
¶ Give me one shot,
one shot of adrenaline ¶
- ¶ Oh-oh ¶
- ¶ Adrenaline ¶
- ¶ Oh ¶
- ¶ One shot, one shot ¶
¶ Of adrenaline ¶
- [beat boxing]
all: ¶ Can I get,
can I get it to go? ¶
¶ Can I get,
- Oh, yeah?
Well, listen to our beats.
- [beat boxing]
- ¶ If I dream everything
I want to be ¶
¶ If I dream
all the possibilities ¶
- ¶ Pick myself up,
turn the world on its head ¶
¶ Don't forget what ¶
¶ Don't forget
what my mama said ¶
- ¶ Who, who do you
think you are? ¶
¶ I'm telling the truth now ¶
¶ We're all born naked
and the rest is drag ¶
all: ¶ Scamming money,
don't make no money ¶
¶ But freaky money
do get the money ¶
¶ 'Cause freaky money,
¶ 'Cause freaky, freaky,
money, money, money ¶
¶ Money, money, money, money ¶
all: ¶ Money, money,
money, money ¶
¶ Money, money, money, money,
money, money, money, money ¶
- ¶ Money, money,
money, m-money ¶
¶ M-money--money, money,
money, money, money, money ¶
- Yo, yo, why are we all
battling each other?
Aren't we all
just mens in wigs?
- ¶ Can I get an amen? ¶
all: ¶ Ooh ¶
¶ If you can't love yourself ¶
¶ How in the hell you gonna
love somebody else? ¶
- ¶ Everybody wants her ¶
¶ Ms. Sexy in the city ¶
¶ She's on the prowl ¶
¶ She rock this town ¶
- ¶ Who's that girl?
¶ A fly ferocious lady ¶
¶ Get up and dance,
Get up, get up and... ¶
all: ¶ Sashay, shantay,
panther on the runway ¶
- ¶ Do it, do it, ohh ¶
¶ All these girls say ¶
together: ¶ Girls say, girls
say, girls say, girls say ¶
¶ Girls say, girls say ¶
girls say, girls say ¶
- ¶ This is the main event,
are you ready? ¶
¶ Just let the music
dance into your soul ¶
- ¶ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ¶
¶ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ¶
¶ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ¶
- ¶ She's so wild, so animal ¶
[glass shatters]
¶ She's gonna work
that sexy body so sexual ¶
¶ She's like
a female phenomenon ¶
- ¶ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ¶
¶ Cover girl ¶
- ¶ Fly, fly, fly, fly,
fly, fly, fly ¶
¶ Uh-oh,
now sissy that walk ¶
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, my God!
- Coming up...
- You're a complete standout.
- Fantastic.
- You cannot dance.
- [laughs]
[dance music]
- Category is
movie premiere realness.
¶ The realness ¶
Cynthia Lee Fontaine.
Yes, the ALMA Awards.
Hola, como estas.
- I love my runway look.
My hair is very Latina.
It's like Roselyn Sánchez
and Sofía Vergara have a baby,
and it's Cynthia.
- You know who else it is?
- It's...
both: Valerie Harper.
- That's who it is.
- Yes. Adiós.
Bob The Drag Queen.
As opposed to
Bob The Chiropractor.
all: Yes.
- Afro she better don't.
- I'm wearing this black gown.
It's completely see-through.
I have great legs;
I got 'em on eBay.
I like to do looks that are,
like, very natural black woman,
so I'm wearing my hair
slicked straight back
with a nice afro
in the back.
I just want to look elegant,
and I think I'm pulling it off.
- What's she gonna
do with all that?
[laughter]
- Ooh, "Good Times."
- Derrick Barry.
¶ Hey, Derrick ¶
- [laughs]
- Ann-Margrock.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm giving you
Vegas red carpet.
I want it to be
a little revealing,
and I love this big hair.
I wanted a big pompadour.
The curtains definitely
don't match the carpet.
- Would she be a ginger?
- She's a ginger, yes.
- Oh, okay.
- She's got an AMBER Alert.
- Yes.
- Whoo.
- Laila McQueen.
- I want to be seen in green.
both: Yes.
- This is a very
atypical look from Laila.
I am trying to be
a classy broad this evening.
I am rocking these iridescent
purple and green sequins.
I'm trying to show the judges
that I can be glamorous.
I'm not always
just a nasty slut
with smeared black lipstick.
- Oh, and then
there's that too.
- All right.
- Wooden.
[laughter]
Laila McQueen,
pretty in green.
Robbie Turner.
- Yes, Marilyn.
- Her glamour-puss is on fire.
- Yes, it is.
- I chose a Vera Wang
wedding gown
that was hand dyed
strawberry red,
and it is to die for.
I know some bitch is gonna
want to buy it off of me,
but you know what?
I sleep in this;
this is my pajamas.
- She's here to accept her Oscar
for lifetime achievement.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Jayne Meadows.
[laughter]
- She's been red.
- Several times.
[laughter]
Kim Chi.
Hollywood glamour.
- Why don't you come up
and see my sometime?
- Slow motion with it.
- Uh-huh.
That's right.
Sneak all of this in right here.
- Mm-hmm.
- I chose this delicate-looking
flower fantasy.
It's ethereal,
serene, avant-garde,
and there is a very
innocent quality to this look.
I just want to feel
like I'm a nymph
who lives on
a cherry blossom tree
that just came down
to the ground to party
with all the earthlings.
- Bam.
- Oh.
- Oh, yes.
- She's like Anna Mae West.
Gorgeous.
- We'll take a journey
through her poppy field.
- Chi Chi DeVayne.
- She is your dream girl.
- Oh, stop.
- Shine, Dina, shine.
- I'm stomping it down.
Walking around puddles
on the girls.
For those who don't know
what that is,
it's making
a figure eight on stage.
Just serving up
this beautiful red dress.
Oh, I'm gonna serve
these bitches up.
- She got dreams of her own.
- Yes.
- That's the Louisiana glamour.
Down in the bayou.
"RuPaul's Drag Race"
Fashion Week
presents Naomi Smalls.
- Come on, baby.
- Ooh, yes.
- I know that the judges
are admiring me
from every angle.
The hair is right.
The legs are right.
The shoes are right.
The face is right.
Everything's right.
I just made
the best dressed list.
- Serving legs,
necks, arms, thighs.
Cover girl.
Acid Betty.
Oh, architecture.
She is giving 1970s
Pat Cleveland on the runway.
- Yes.
- You know what, Ru?
- Huh?
- She don't fool me.
I see right through her.
[laughter]
- I've chosen to wear
this skin color gown
and, of course, my fierce
Philip Treacy wannabe hat.
This outfit is couture
made just for me,
and no other bitch
will have one.
- Is that a new telephone?
- Bluetooth.
- This is the 5G network.
[laughter]
- Dax ExclamationPoint.
- Southern belle.
- Come on, Lonette McKee.
"Cotton Club."
- Can I borrow a cup of flour?
- She's all out.
[laughter]
- Tonight on the runway
I'm serving
lady sings
the green and gold blues.
I'm not a gown girl,
but I really want to show
that I have clothes
that can touch the floor,
and I want to show them
a different silhouette
than I normally would wear.
- Yes, bang, bang
into the room.
Thorgy Thor.
- She doing the neutron dance.
- Oh, yeah.
- Thorgy Minnelli.
- Whoo, it's disco, bitch.
I decided to not wear
what everyone else is wearing,
which was a boring gown.
I'm wearing my big
Donna Summer hair
and my sequin jumpsuit
that I made from scratch.
I'm comfy,
and I'm feeling it.
- "Xanadu."
- I want to dance
with your somebody.
- She's the drag daughter
of a "Solid Gold" dancer.
Welcome, ladies.
Now, this week
you performed in teams,
but tonight you'll be
judged as individuals.
Harshly.
When I call your name,
please step forward.
Laila McQueen.
Thorgy Thor.
Kim Chi.
Acid Betty.
Dax ExclamationPoint.
Chi Chi DeVayne.
Ladies,
you represent the tops
and the bottoms
of the week,
and the rest of you bitches
in the background...
are safe.
You may leave the stage.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
Coming up...
- The one thing
I'm concerned about
with you
is when you'll fall,
you'll fall hard.
- [laughs]
Ladies,
you represent the tops
and the bottoms of the week.
Now it's time for
the judges' critiques.
First up,
Laila McQueen.
- Hello, Laila,
I think the dress is pretty.
The problem is,
you're lost in it.
The hair is flat and long.
Everything's being pulled down.
You can see none of you.
- And as far as
the performance goes,
I feel like I wasn't getting
much of the comedy,
especially with the big
personalities around you.
- Up next, Kim Chi.
- I can tell
that you cannot dance,
but on the positive side
of that, you chose a character
to cover up
that you can't dance,
and it worked.
- I don't mind
that you can't dance
because this look
is, like, fantastic.
Yeah, I just want to smell you.
- Mmm.
- I do get concerned
about your walk.
I'm not sure anymore
that it's a choice.
It's very stiff, darling.
Give yourself over to it.
Allow yourself to have fun
on this runway.
- How do you say
"sissy that walk" in Korean?
- [speaking Korean]
- Pow, pow.
- Yes, yes, yes.
- [speaking Korean]
Up next, Louisiana glamour.
Bayou country.
Chi Chi DeVayne.
- Hey, y'all.
- [laughs]
- It's funny 'cause
we shot "Pitch Perfect"
in Baton Rouge,
so you make me feel really good
by hearing your voice.
- Your performance today,
you turned it completely out.
- That got them ass clap.
You know, they'd be
throwing some dollars
at your ass real fast.
- You definitely are
my new trap queen.
- So tonight,
I think you look--
for lack of a better term,
sort of basic.
Look around.
This is a crew that came
to play this season.
- But she looks amazing.
I love the red dress.
- "Dreamgirls"
is one of my favorite musicals,
so right now you're giving me
Sheryl Lee Ralph realness.
- I don't really have anything
negative to say about you.
- Thank you.
[laughter]
- Next up, Acid Betty.
- What I really loved
about what you did is,
you were really a team player.
You were concerned
about everybody else,
and I appreciate stuff like that
because it lets
me know you care.
- So I love the headpiece.
I love the body art.
I'm not getting the train.
- I just like looking
at you right now.
- I like looking
- Ha-ha!
- Do you need this?
- You can't see
this right now,
but he's got a fistful
of Jergens lotion.
[laughter]
- The one thing I'm
concerned about with you is,
you're setting the bar so high.
I'll be waiting to see
if you can keep raising it
'cause when you'll fall,
you'll fall hard.
- Is that a challenge,
Michelle?
- It's always a challenge when
I throw it out there, darling.
- Next up,
Dax ExclamationPoint.
- I love your face.
I love the hair.
Something about the bottom
of the dress is not done.
- One thing I did notice
from last week.
I have an issue
with your padding.
It almost gives you
a quadru-butt.
Just look at it.
- The performance,
I really wanted you
to get that hood,
like, uh, you know,
and it--and it still never came,
and in rehearsals
you were saying,
"Oh, yeah, I'll do it when
I figure out these steps."
- I am not a classically
trained dancer in the least,
and like, I was also trying
to kind of create a character
while also thinking too much
about other stuff, and like--
- You just got to go.
Whether you do it wrong
or whatever, commit.
- All right,
Thorgy Thor.
- As far as
the dance portion,
you're one of the people
I didn't have to worry about.
- What I love about
the jumpsuit is,
it's smart because
you said, "You know what?
"At a movie premiere,
everybody else
"is gonna do
some glamorous gown.
I'm gonna do something
that's representative of me,"
But you wear your eyes so black
that I'm losing your eyeballs,
so blend it out.
- I'll take that challenge, yes.
- Thank you, ladies.
Now, while you
untuck backstage,
the judges
and I will deliberate.
Now, just between us altos,
what do you think?
Laila McQueen.
- She stood out to me because
she was the most improved.
I would have never thought
she could last through
the whole performance.
- But I didn't really
remember what she had done.
- The only thing
I remember about her
is the mole
underneath her eye,
so I don't think that's good.
- You know what this is?
This season has
very strong personalities.
She's out of her league.
- I know she has a fire in her,
but she gonna have
to step her pussy up.
- Oh.
- Kim Chi.
- Talk about somebody who's
the polar opposite of Laila.
You can't stop
looking at Kim Chi.
- When I see her on the runway,
I was blown away,
but it's so weird to me
that she can't walk in heels.
- It could become a trend.
New York Fashion Week,
a sasquatch, a Godzilla.
You better Kim Chi
that walk, girl.
- Yes.
- But my fear for Kim Chi
is that she is a look.
Because she's had such success
with who she is visually,
she hasn't had
to deliver a performance.
She just had to be really cute
and kind of nerdy and anime-y,
but I think there's
a personality in there.
I just want her to unleash it
and let us have it.
- Chi Chi DeVayne.
- Tonight on the stage,
did she play it safe?
Yes.
- I loved her outfit.
It just seemed
very classic and beautiful,
and as far
as the performance goes,
she really slayed
the other girls.
- I mean, really.
- Yes.
- She was doing
her neck ghetto style
upside down while twerking
and not missing a word.
Honey, I was ready to make
the Louisiana Purchase
one more time.
[laughter]
Acid Betty.
- Energy-wise,
a complete standout.
I particularly loved
her runway look
with that weird
fiber optic spiderweb.
- Yes.
- Everything I love about drag.
- Look, it wasn't perfect.
There was weirdness at the back
that looked like draperies
being dry-cleaned.
- I would have liked
if that dress just
did the see-through thing
all the way down
because it made
her bottom heavy,
and the color's ugly.
Sorry.
- Sorry 'bout it.
Dax ExclamationPoint.
- Tonight on the runway,
it just was all wrong for me.
The flower did not go
with the dress.
The colors were dull,
and in the performance
you literally forgot
that Dax was there.
- In "Pitch Perfect,"
I know what it felt like
to not be a classical dancer.
It just takes courage
to get past it.
She don't want to fight for it.
It's like she's the girl
in the girl group
with the Beyoncé in it.
Beyoncé only stands out
because she really wants it.
- She's the Farrah.
- LaTavia.
- I don't want
to call no names.
- Thorgy Thor.
- She nailed the performance.
She came out in that catsuit.
It was 180 degrees different
from the performance
personality.
- Just hated the shoes.
- Uh-huh.
- They look like ugly shoes.
- Well, no,
my issue is her makeup.
Two times in a row
it's a--two black eyes.
- So, Michelle,
what you're saying is that
Thorgy is in an abusive
relationship with her makeup.
- Yes.
- Silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
- [laughs]
- Welcome back, ladies.
Based on your
"Bitch Perfect" performance
and your movie
premiere eleganza,
I've made some decisions.
Thorgy Thor, you're safe.
- Thank you.
- Chi Chi DeVayne,
not only did
you turn it out,
girl,
you turned it upside down.
Condragulations, you are the
winner of this week's challenge.
- Wow.
- For real?
- Really, Ru?
Chi Chi sucked as a leader.
- I won a challenge.
I'm definitely on the radar.
Y'all girls better look out.
- You've won
a four-night getaway
to an all gay
bed and breakfast
in beautiful New England
courtesy of MyGayGetaway.com.
- So I get to go overseas?
- No, New England is here
in the United States.
- Oh, okay.
[laughter]
- Chi Chi,
you may cross the seas
and join the other girls.
- Whoo!
- Acid Betty,
you're safe.
- Thank you.
- Dax ExclamationPoint,
the lack of commitment
to your performance
forces me to put a question mark
after your name.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- I think there were girls
that did worse than me,
and I'm sad,
and I'm just pissed about it.
- Laila McQueen,
in your performance
you got lost
in the din and tonic.
Kim Chi, in your performance
you put your left foot forward.
Both of them.
Laila McQueen,
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are
up for elimination.
Kim Chi,
you are safe,
and you may join
the other girls.
Two queens stand before me.
Prior to tonight
you were asked
to prepare
a lip-sync performance
of "I Will Survive"
by Gloria Gaynor.
Ladies, this is your
last chance to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
[thunder rumbles]
For you to lip-synch
for your life.
[echoes]
- I don't really do disco.
It's just not my genre,
but I'm pretty confident
I can definitely beat,
uh, Laila.
Sorry, I forgot her name
for a second.
- I feel the song
that we're doing
has such strong emotion
tied with it,
and Dax is kind of lackluster,
and the song is not lackluster,
so I'm like,
"You got this."
- All right, here we go.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
["I Will Survive" playing]
¶ ¶
- ¶ At first I was afraid ¶
¶ I was petrified ¶
¶ Kept thinking I could never
live without by my side ¶
¶ But I spent so many nights ¶
¶ Thinking
how you did me wrong ¶
¶ And I grew strong ¶
¶ And I learned
how to get along ¶
¶ And so you're back
from outer space ¶
¶ I just walked in
to find you here ¶
¶ With that sad look
upon your face ¶
¶ I should have changed
that stupid lock ¶
¶ I should have made
you leave your key ¶
¶ If I'd have known
for just one second ¶
¶ You'd be back
to bother me ¶
¶ Go on, now go ¶
¶ Walk out the door ¶
¶ Just turn around now ¶
¶ 'Cause you're not
welcome anymore ¶
¶ Weren't you the one who tried
to hurt me with good-bye? ¶
¶ Did you think I'd crumble? ¶
¶ Did you think
I'd lay down and die? ¶
¶ Oh, no, not I ¶
¶ I will survive ¶
¶ Oh, as long as I know ¶
¶ How to love
I know I'll stay alive ¶
¶ I've got all my life
to live ¶
¶ I've got all my love to give,
and I'll survive ¶
¶ I will survive ¶
¶ Oh ¶
¶ ¶
¶ Go on now go,
walk out the door ¶
¶ Just turn around now ¶
¶ 'Cause you're not
welcome anymore ¶
¶ Weren't you the one who tried
to break me with good-bye? ¶
¶ Did you think I'd crumble? ¶
¶ Did you think I'd
lay down and die? ¶
¶ Oh, no, not I ¶
¶ I will survive ¶
¶ Oh, as long as I know ¶
¶ How to love,
I know I'll stay alive ¶
¶ I've got
all my life to live ¶
¶ I've got all my love to give,
and I'll survive ¶
¶ I will survive ¶
[applause]
- Ladies,
I've made my decision.
Dax ExclamationPoint,
Laila McQueen...
Neither one of you
survived that lip sync.
I must ask you both
to sashay away.
- Wait, second time
in history of "RuPaul."
Two eliminated!
- Thank you, ladies.
You may leave the stage.
- Both of us?
- We're glad
we made it here,
but it sucks to go home
second, third.
- That's about
accurate, yeah.
I know I gave it.
I didn't half-ass it.
I just wish
it hadn't gone this way.
I look forward
to a nap and vodka.
Lots of vodka.
- Michelle,
may I borrow your phone?
[phone dialing]
[sighs]
Hi, it's RuPaul.
- Who the fuck
is RuPaul talking to?
- Listen, I had to eliminate
two queens today.
How soon can you get here?
- Fuck.
Someone's coming back.