It's a new year
and a new season
with all new surprises.
Girl!
From the hood to Hollywood.
I'm Kandy Muse,
and I'm a Dominican doll
from New York City. Meow.
My drag style is kind of like
if you took a sex doll
and threw her in the Bronx,
that is literally me.
My most impressive drag talent
is my mouth.
I'm a good lip syncer.
I'm a loud-ass bitch.
You know, everyone
can be a drag queen,
but not everyone's
gonna be a star.
I'm a star.
First one!
Oh, my God, bitch, Season 13.
Most people might recognize me
from the former Haus of Aja.
And when we dismembered
and broke up,
I was definitely a loudmouth,
and I would say things about Aja
that maybe
I should have kept to myself.
But I also think that
she was a little jealous of me.
Come on, Miss Anastasia
Beverly Hills.
I want a sponsorship,
thank you very much.
She used to always be, like,
"Well, you're not famous,
so tone it down."
But now I'm here.
Well, no, I'm here.
That's so shady.
First one. Seems correct.
I'm here to prove that I am more
than just Kandy Muse
from the Haus of Aja.
I can stand as an entertainer
by my damn self.
I look fucking stunning.
Being the first bitch
to walk in the competition
after waiting years
to get on Drag Race
is such a fucking dream.
I am so excited to be here.
Come on, now!
And now, any bitch
that walks in after me,
second place.
- Ooh.
- Filler queen.
"Filler queen?"
My name is Joey Jay,
and I'm the dumbest bitch
you'll ever meet.
She's wacky, she's crazy,
she's an adrenaline rush.
I can perform the house down,
boots back, bareback.
To be here, it is
a dream come true, so...
I lost my train of thought.
- Aah!
- Oh, what up, bitch?
Come on, Season 13. Good, girl.
- Hi, baby! Mwah, mwah.
- Hi, babe. Kandy.
Joey. Oh, my God,
I'm molting, girl.
Miss Thing is wearing
a chicken-feather coat.
Chicken feathers.
There are feathers
all over the floor.
Bawk bawk bawk bawk bawk.
Come on, chicken feathers.
Chicken feathers are
the least expensive feathers
that there are in the planet.
Girl, not even a marabou coat?
So wait. You do drag
full-time in your city?
No, I don't. I work
for a software company.
This is just
my little nighttime gig.
Oh, okay. Werk.
How many shows a week do you do?
- Just one.
- Just one?
Y'all think I'm a basic bitch.
You're not wrong.
I can't eat spicy foods,
I like Vanessa Carlton.
But don't underestimate
us Vanessa Carltons.
Really, bitch, I'm gonna
be in that top four.
Filler queen.
Plot twist.
This is my third time
auditioning.
Oh, this is my fourth.
Word.
Ooh, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
Girl, what?
What?
There's only two of us?
- Aah!
- What is going on here?
Welcome, my queens.
What? You weren't expecting
to see me so soon?
No, ma'am.
Well, I hope you like surprises,
because I've got a big one,
and it's right around
the corner.
Racers, please report
to the main stage.
Ooh.
Like, now.
Girl.
God. I am so confused right now,
and I have no idea
what's about to go down.
Girl, I am poofed and gagged.
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
And what?
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race,
and we are serving Season 13
with some serious safety, honey.
Michelle Visage, what do you
think of the new judges' panel?
Baby, I feel like
I'm the head teller
at RuPaul's Savings and Loan.
Wanna make a deposit?
The hilarious Ross Mathews.
Now, what do you think?
You know what, I love it,
and I even brought
my own squeegee.
Hi! Oh, Carson, hi!
Michelle!
And style superstar
Carson Kressley.
Are you ready to read some lips?
Which ones?
Both sets.
Tonight we're doing things
just a little differently.
For the first time
in Drag Race herstory,
we're kicking off the season
with six
lip syncs for your lives.
Now, some will shantay
and some will sashay away.
Wow.
Ooh, child,
you ain't ready for this.
Racers, start your engines,
and may the best drag queen win.
What the fuck is going on?
Yo, I just walked into Drag Race
and now I'm standing
on the main stage
and I don't know
what is about the happen.
I can't even look at RuPaul
in the eyes,
because I'm getting so nervous.
I'm already feeling scared
as fuck and insecure,
but I signed up for this.
Get it together.
Welcome, ladies.
Surprised to see me?
You've made it to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race,
and so soon.
We'd like to take this moment
to get to know you
a little bit better.
Judges, say hello to Kandy Muse.
- Hi, Kandy.
- Hello.
- I would love to know
what makes this
a signature Kandy Muse look.
It's sexy, it's slutty,
it's denim,
it's from Brooklyn,
it's New York.
I heard you're a member
of the Haus of Aja?
That's the former
Haus of Aja, but yes.
Well, what house now?
The dollhouse, with my drag sis
Dahlia Sin from Season 12.
Part of the broccoli bunch.
She is a broc-ally.
International
House of Pancakes here.
Judges, say hello to Joey Jay.
Tell us about your look, Joey.
Well, I like chicken,
I like to cluck, I like a butt,
so I decided to dress up
as all three.
Cluck, cluck.
What inspired you to do drag?
Self-expression,
and cluckin' and buckin'.
Thank you, Joey.
Thank you.
Ladies, your charisma,
uniqueness, nerve, and talent
got you here.
Now let's see
what you can do with it.
Two queens stand before me.
Prior to tonight,
you were asked to prepare
a lip sync performance
of Call Me Maybe
by Carly Rae Jepsen.
In a moment, I'll ask
one of you to shantay
and one of you to sashay away.
Bitch, excuse me?
We just walked into
the competition,
and now we have to
lip sync for our lives?
One of us is about to go home.
It ain't gonna be me.
Ladies, this is your
first chance to impress me
and save yourself from...
getting the porkchop.
The time has come...
for you to lip sync...
for your life.
Even though I'm shook
as fuck on the inside,
I'm a lip sync assassin. Eat it.
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
♪ I threw a wish in the well ♪
♪ Don't ask me,
I'll never tell ♪
♪ I looked to you as it fell ♪
♪ And now you're in my way ♪
♪ I trade my soul for a wish ♪
♪ Pennies and dimes for a kiss ♪
♪ I wasn't looking for this ♪
♪ But now you're in my way ♪
♪ Your stare was holding ♪
♪ Ripped jeans,
skin was showin' ♪
♪ Hot night, wind was blowin' ♪
♪ Where you think
you're going, baby? ♪
♪ Hey, I just met you
and this is crazy ♪
♪ But here's my number,
so call me maybe ♪
♪ It's hard to look
right at you, baby ♪
♪ But here's my number,
so call me maybe ♪
♪ Hey, I just met you
and this is crazy ♪
♪ But here's my number... ♪
Well, Miss Ru, I just met you,
and this is crazy.
♪ And all the other boys... ♪
Whatever this bitch
next to me is doing,
girl, I can give two fucks,
because this stage is mine.
Take out your dollars, bitch.
♪ Before you came into my life,
I missed you so bad ♪
♪ I missed you so bad ♪
♪ I missed you so, so bad ♪
♪ Bad, bad, bad ♪
♪ It's hard to look
right at you, baby ♪
♪ But here's my number,
so call me maybe ♪
♪ Hey, I just met you
and this is crazy ♪
♪ But here's my number,
so call me maybe ♪
♪ Before you came into my life,
I missed you so bad ♪
♪ I missed you so bad ♪
♪ I missed you so, so bad ♪
♪ Before you came into my life,
I missed you so bad ♪
♪ And you should know that ♪
♪ So call me maybe ♪
Ladies, I've made my decision.
This is a one-in-a-lifetime
opportunity.
I'm not going home
before I even start.
Fuck.
The winner of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
and a cash prize of $100,000.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Kandy Muse, shantay you stay.
Thank you so much.
RuPaul just called my name,
and I tried to stay real calm
and bow down.
Thank you so much.
But, bitch, I'm inside,
I'm like, ooh, bitch,
I won the motherfucking
lip sync! Ha-ha-ha!
Joey Jay, I'm sorry, my dear,
but that means
you're getting the porkchop.
You are and will always be
Drag Race royalty.
Now sashay away.
Mwah. Thank you so much.
I'm really sad
to leave the competition.
I worked so hard to get here,
just to go home early.
I don't wanna go home, girl.
Let's see who's next.
Let me break the ice.
I'm Denali, and I am
Chicago's ice queen.
So I am icy, spicy,
and a little bit dicey.
Okay.
First one in.
Winners come in first.
I do drag.
I'm a professional ice skater.
I am drag's gold-medal bitch.
And I might not have made it to
the Olympics in figure skating,
but I did make it
to the Olympics in drag.
I am competitive,
and I'm here to win that crown.
Oh, what you say, what you say?
LaLa Ri is here to slay.
I am the sensational,
dynamic LaLa Ri.
She's ratchet, she's sexy,
she gives you a little glamour.
LaLa Ri is like
a Olive Garden pasta
with, like, Popeye's
chicken tenders on the side
for the razzle-dazzle.
Most of all,
she's entertaining, girl.
- Hi!
Oh, my God, nice to meet you.
I'm Denali.
LaLa Ri.
Girl. Not gonna lie.
I was expecting
a little bit more.
Your entrance look
is a basic bodysuit, a blazer,
and this kind of like flat wig.
Okay, cute.
We're the first two in, bitch.
I know. First two in,
last two out.
Ooh, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
But...
Bitch.
Wait. What's going on?
What... what alarm?
One plus one equals two,
but if you carry the three,
minus the four,
bitch, that don't add up.
What is really the tea?
Hello, dolls.
The competition
has started without you,
so get your sassy selves
to the main stage.
We're waiting!
Uh, okay.
Holy shit, this is crazy.
There's two of us.
Why would we be going
to the main stage already?
I am feeling just gagged.
I'm sorry, floors.
Welcome, ladies.
I'm so glad you could join us.
You know, people come and go
so fast around here.
We'd like to take this moment
to get to know you
a little bit better.
Let's start with Denali.
Hey, Denali.
Hey, Michelle.
So tell me about this look.
Well, I'm a professional
figure skater outside of drag,
so I love to mold
the two worlds.
Just when I thought the show
couldn't get any gayer,
now we have figure skating?
But I have a serious question
for you, okay?
Are you more of a Tonya Harding
or a Nancy Kerrigan?
I'm definitely more of a Tonya,
if you know what I mean.
I know what you mean.
Why?
Next up, LaLa Ri.
Hey, LaLa Ri.
- Hey, girl.
- You know, I always love
when a queen comes out
missing her trousers.
But she got her jacket on.
So tell us about what
does this look say to you.
Yes, LaLa Ri is very sexy,
but a little classy,
so this represents
the class and the sex.
And the ass.
- Of course.
- There you go.
LaLa, I wanted to ask you,
do you think you could beat
Denali in a lip sync?
Of course I think I can
beat Denali in a lip sync.
I mean, she's a lovely girl
and all, but bring it.
Well, we will see about that.
We're doing things a little
differently this season.
Two queens stand before me.
Lip sync?
I absolutely
am a lip sync assassin,
but not in ice skates.
Ladies, this is your
first chance to impress me
and save yourself
from getting the porkchop.
The time has come...
to lip sync...
for your life.
I'm an entertainer
first and foremost,
so Miss LaLa Ri
is about to give you hell,
about to bring you fire.
She'll give you everything
you need, plus more.
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
♪ Boys call you sexy ♪
♪ What's up, sexy? ♪
♪ And you don't care
what they say ♪
♪ See, every time
you turn around ♪
♪ They screaming your name ♪
♪ Dark child ♪
♪ Now I've got a confession... ♪
Boom, I automatically
just hit my performance mode.
I'm thinking, okay, bitch,
it's time for you to shine.
♪ But I ain't complaining ♪
♪ We all wanna be famous ♪
♪ So go ahead
and say what you wanna say ♪
I was not expecting to lip sync.
This is not a lip sync outfit,
but Imma make it work.
♪ When I grow up,
I wanna be famous ♪
I decided to do
a cartwheel. Okay.
Nobody got a haircut.
♪ I wanna be have groupies ♪
♪ When I grow up, be on TV ♪
♪ People know me,
be on magazines ♪
♪ When I grow up,
fresh and clean ♪
♪ Number one chick
when I step out on the scene ♪
♪ Be careful what you wish for ♪
♪ 'Cause you just might get it ♪
♪ Hey! You just might get it ♪
♪ I see them staring at me ♪
♪ Ooh, I'm a trendsetter ♪
♪ Yes, this is true
'cause what I do ♪
♪ No one can do it better ♪
♪ You can talk about me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm a hot topic ♪
♪ I see you watching me,
watching me ♪
♪ And I know you want it, oh ♪
♪ When I grow up ♪
♪ I wanna be famous,
I wanna be a star ♪
♪ I wanna be in movies ♪
♪ When I grow up,
I wanna see the world ♪
♪ Drive nice cars,
I wanna have groupies ♪
♪ When I grow up,
fresh and clean ♪
♪ Number one chick
when I step out on the scene ♪
♪ Be careful what you wish for ♪
♪ 'Cause you just might get it ♪
♪ Hey! You just might get it ♪
♪ Hey ♪
Whoo!
Ladies, I've made my decision.
I didn't come here
to go home early.
I'm just gonna pray on it.
Throw it up and bring it down.
Ladies, I've made my decision.
LaLa Ri, shantay you stay.
Aroo? I'm, like, do I say
thank you or what?
Okay, girl.
Well, shantay I stay,
thank you, girl.
Denali, I'm sorry, my dear,
but you're getting the porkchop.
Now sashay away.
Feeling icy, feeling spicy.
I'm unbelievably devastated.
I'm just kind of,
like, oh, my God,
I'm going home without
showing anything on Drag Race.
What the fuck is up on here?
- I'm Denali.
- I'm Joey.
- Nice to meet you.
- A pleasure.
I'm, like, I don't understand.
Was I not the only one
eliminated?
Oh, no, look it.
They're all the first girl outs.
I see on the wall
the porkchop loading dock,
and all of these pictures
of first-eliminated queens
from Drag Race.
Oh, no.
Porkchop herself, Shangela,
Miss Vanjie, Dahlia Sin.
There's some sort of trickery.
I don't know what's going on.
I feel like something's
gonna jump out of a box.
So here we are,
trying to figure out
what the fuck
has just happened to us.
Are we being sent home?
Am I about to de-drag
at the airport?
Can I call my mom?
Don't let the smooth taste
fool you, baby.
My name is Symone,
I am 25 years old,
and I am the ebony enchantress.
Queen number one, all right.
Let's do it.
My drag is very real woman,
very female illusional.
This is gonna be my spot,
front and center, honey.
I love strong women
who've been through things,
and if you Black,
that's even better.
I'm here, bitch!
Symone is the confidence,
the essence.
She is a goddess,
she's everything.
Holler at me.
I know you know me.
Tamisha is here.
I am Tamisha Iman,
one of the baddest in the art
form of female impersonation.
I am sassy, I am lovable,
but at the same time,
I can be W-I-T-C-H if need be.
- Hi.
- Hi, how are you?
Nice to meet you. I'm Tamisha.
It's lovely to meet you, too.
I'm Symone.
- It's nice to meet you, Symone.
- Thank you.
I love the power shoulder.
Thank you, I'm into fashion.
There we go. Pageant gal?
- Of course.
Yes. Of course.
And the matriarch
of the Iman family.
Word!
I'm the mother of the dynasty.
- Come on, dynasty.
- Yeah, it's a dynasty.
Miss Tamisha is very...
Now, no shade, no shade.
Like a mother figure.
But also, like, you know
that she is here
to play and slay.
Ooh, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
What the hell?
Maybe they hit
the button too soon.
Just two of us?
We ain't even done nothin' yet.
We just walked in.
Well, hello, my queens.
I wanna see both of you
on the main stage.
Hit it!
What the hell?
Come to the floor?
You supposed
to come in the room.
We don't supposed
to come to the floor.
Welcome, queens.
Surprised to see me?
Now it's time
to make a positive first
impression on the judges...
starting with Symone.
So I see you've got little mini
Polaroids as your dress.
Oh, yes.
Are they pictures of you?
Each one of them
are pictures of me,
a little couple faces,
a couple of shoes,
a couple of asses pictures, too.
So does that tell me
that you love yourself?
Yes, I do love myself.
- Good.
- I love my drag persona.
- Great.
- It saved my life.
Where did you grow up?
I grew up in Conway, Arkansas.
I dated a guy
from Pine Bluff, Arkansas.
Oh!
Is he your grandfather?
I think so.
I knew he said something
about a cross-dresser.
So we might be related.
All right, Tamisha Iman.
I see that you have found
what I have lost.
- Oh!
- Yep.
I did get 'em.
Yeah, you sure did.
You got 'em, girl.
How long have you
been doing drag?
30 years.
What?
- Yeah, 30 years.
- Wow.
Do you think
your vast experience
is going to be helpful
or be a hindrance
in the competition?
Well, I'm not as great
as I used to be,
but I'm still
as good as I should be.
I'm recently
getting over cancer.
Because you were cast
on Season 12.
Yes. On that Friday,
I got the call to say,
"Hey, you made it!"
On that Sunday, I got
the call from my doctor
stating that I had
stage three colon cancer,
and they had to start
immediately radiation and chemo.
So it devastated me.
You know, I got so bad
to where I couldn't walk.
The cancer and the radiation
took such a control over me.
And knowing that
I could possibly fight
to get back here just
one more time, I fought it.
So within a year, I'm...
I'm a conqueror,
and I'm so thankful
that you gave me this chance.
So I'm blessed.
Whatever happens, I'm blessed.
- All right.
- God is good.
Thank you, Tamisha.
Ladies, I have
just one more thing to say.
Oh.
Two queens stand before me.
H-h-h-huh?
Ladies, this
is your first chance
to impress me and save yourself
from getting... the porkchop.
The time has come...
for you to lip sync...
for your life.
I ain't been here five minutes
and y'all doing all this.
This is crazy.
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
Whoo!
♪ You might think I'm crazy,
but I'm serious ♪
♪ It's better you know now ♪
♪ What I thought was happiness
was only part-time bliss ♪
♪ You can take a bow ♪
♪ It was all just one big night
out on the town ♪
♪ Riding in your limousine ♪
♪ We turned right
and I say wrong ♪
♪ Which brings us to a stop ♪
♪ As the light is changing ♪
♪ Oh, my meter's running,
so I got to go now ♪
♪ It's the pleasure principle ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ It's the principle
of pleasure ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ It's the pleasure principle ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I know... ♪
Tamisha is giving you
Janet Jackson concert vibes.
Arms, movements,
da, da, da, da, da.
I was, like, oh, no, ma'am.
♪ You know... ♪
This is my stage,
I can't let her have it.
This is not her Janet Jackson
moment, it's mine.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, hey, yeah ♪
♪ It's the pleasure principle,
principle ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ You might say
that I'm no good for you ♪
♪ I wouldn't trust your looks,
baby, if I could ♪
♪ Love me ♪
♪ Love me, yeah ♪
♪ Pleasure principle ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
Ladies, I've made my decision.
The thing about
watching the show,
you think you know
until you get here,
and now you don't know nothing.
Let me take a deep breath,
because I don't know
what's about to happen.
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Symone, shantay you stay.
Aah!
Sorry.
In the seven minutes
that we are here,
I have literally walked
through the werkroom,
went to the main stage,
and won a lip sync.
What is going on, America?
Whew.
Tamisha Iman,
I'm sorry, my dear,
but that means you're
getting the porkchop.
Now sashay away.
Thank you. I'm always
gonna be a Ru girl.
Thank you. Mwah!
Wow.
I'm totally destroyed, because
this is my second chance,
and it's over that fast.
Just that fast,
in the blink of a eye.
- Hey, cutie.
- Well, well, well.
I'm Denali. Nice to meet you.
Joey Jay.
Nice to meet you, Joey.
I'm Tamisha.
I'm still in shock and awe.
They're excited.
"Hey, girl, how are you?"
I'm like, "Why are we here?"
We're here in a room
full of first eliminees.
Oh, are we?
Our picture is gonna
go there for next season.
No, I don't feel like
it's the end, exactly.
It felt like the end to me.
I got eliminated on that stage,
and it hurt like...
Yeah, but you know
it's not RuPaul's Drag Race
without a twist.
Bitch, I don't know
what you feeling,
but at the end of the day,
the lady said go home.
The bags are packed,
we all in this room.
They just letting us
come together
so it'll be one van
to take us all to the airport.
You're very hopeful,
and I get it, but, you know...
I'm holding on because I am not
accepting elimination just yet.
This ain't no twist.
The twist is
we twisting to the door.
The lady said go home.
Time to crash the system.
I'm Gottmik,
and I'm ready to kill it.
My drag is inspired by fashion
and designers
like McQueen, Galliano.
Picasso's paintings
inspire me a lot.
I love putting shapes on my face
where they probably
shouldn't be.
She's just a campy, spooky,
clown artistry thing, I guess.
Not the first person here.
I cannot.
I'm so excited to be here
on RuPaul's Drag Race.
Thank you. Hold the applause.
I think I'll bring a different
angle to this competition.
I am a transgender man,
so born a girl,
transitioned to a guy,
dress like a girl for money.
Very that.
But, I'm so psy...
No one saw that.
I am an extravagant
celebrity makeup artist.
I'm gonna have, like,
a buffalo bump on my hair.
I've painted Cindy Crawford,
Heidi Klum, Paris Hilton.
And so the biggest
misconception about me
is that I'm just
a makeup artist.
I'm so much more, and I cannot
wait to show these bitches.
Ah-choo!
She's sickening.
I am Utica Queen,
and I am from Utica, Minnesota.
See what I did there?
I'm the queen of the unexpected.
I am the wacky, inflatable,
waving-arms tube queen.
I'm always dishing a hot dish of
ridiculousness to an audience.
I'm so excited to spread smiles
to all the wonderful people
in the world.
Hello!
Hi, I'm Gottmik.
Nice to meet you.
A pleasure, Utica.
- Go ahead, you look gorg!
- God, your paint.
Good morning, hello,
and good night.
Hi, how are you?
This is crazy!
So what type of drag is she?
What does she do?
So I'm really kooky.
Uh-huh.
It's kind of like if your
best friend's a supermodel.
Like, she walks into the room,
but then she trips
and falls on her face
and eats her own booger.
Uh, that's me.
Oh, no.
Ooh, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
The alarms are going off,
the lighting is changing.
Oh, my God, I love
this lighting, though.
It's matching my outfit,
so I'm living for that.
Welcome, queens.
Meet me on the main stage,
because I wanna see you sweat.
I'm already sweating.
Aah! What's happening?
Welcome to the main stage.
- Whoo!
- Thank you!
Thank you for having us.
Now, listen, we just wanna
get to know you a little better.
So starting with Gottmik,
we're gonna talk to the judges.
Hey, Gottmik.
Hey, Ross. How are you?
How would you describe
your drag?
I like everything to be
kind of Pierrot inspired,
clown, black and white,
but with, like, a vibrant,
campy touch to it.
We can obviously see that
you are great with makeup,
and you've got
a great fashion sense.
Thank you.
Would you describe yourself
as a lip sync assassin?
I'm not a lip sync assassin,
but I can lip sync
the house down for sure.
Okay.
Thank you, Gottmik.
Thank you.
- Up next, Utica.
- Hi.
I wanna know how this outfit
describes who Utica is,
and why is there a strawberry
on your head?
So the strawberry,
I used to be allergic
to strawberries growing up,
and it's kind of a testament
to me getting through it.
So... That's so crazy.
- It's so dumb. Whoo-oo.
- I love it. Okay, go on.
And, yeah, I would say my style
is if you took this pattern
and that pattern
and this pattern and this
pattern and put it in a jar,
and then shook it all up
and then there you go,
but with a touch of polish.
Just a touch.
Are you a little nervous?
Feel it in my nuggets.
- You feel what?
- I feel it in my nuggets.
Oh, okay. We all love nuggets.
Ladies, I have a question.
How well do you perform
under pressure?
Actually, you know what?
Don't answer that.
I think we're about to find out.
Two queens stand before me.
What? Right off the bat?
Ladies, this is your
first chance to impress me
and save yourself
from getting the porkchop.
The time has come...
for you to lip sync...
for...
your...
...life. Hah!
I'm cracking my knuckles
right now.
But, like, getting ready,
like, focused.
No one is sending me home
on the first episode.
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
♪ Saturday,
steppin' into the club ♪
♪ There'll be someone
wanna tell DJ turn it up ♪
♪ I feel the energy all around ♪
♪ And my body can't stop
moving to the sound ♪
♪ But I can tell
that you're watching me ♪
♪ And you're probably gonna
write what you didn't see ♪
♪ Well, I just need
a little space to breathe ♪
♪ Can you please
respect my privacy? ♪
♪ I'm tired of rumors starting ♪
♪ I'm sick of being followed ♪
♪ I'm tired of people lying ♪
♪ Sayin' what they want
about me ♪
♪ Why can't they
back up off me? ♪
♪ Why can't they let me live? ♪
♪ I'm gonna do it my way ♪
♪ Take this
for just what it is ♪
♪ Here we are
back up in the club ♪
♪ People taking pictures ♪
♪ Don't you think
they get enough? ♪
♪ I just wanna be
all over the floor ♪
♪ And throw my hands
up in the air ♪
♪ To the beat like, what? ♪
♪ I've gotta say, respectfully ♪
♪ I would like it if you
take the cameras off of me ♪
♪ 'Cause I just want
a little room to breathe ♪
♪ Can you please
respect my privacy? ♪
♪ I'm tired of rumors, rumors ♪
♪ Followed, followed, followed ♪
♪ Followed, followed,
followed, followed ♪
♪ But they follow me ♪
♪ Why can't they...
They... they... they... they ♪
♪ Let me live? ♪
♪ Take this
for just what it is ♪
♪ I'm tired of rumors starting ♪
♪ I'm sick of being followed ♪
♪ I'm tired of people lying ♪
♪ Sayin' what they want
about me ♪
♪ Why can't they
back up off me? ♪
♪ Why can't they let me live? ♪
♪ I'm gonna do it my way ♪
♪ Take this
for just what it is ♪
Whoo!
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Oh, what's gonna happen next?
This is crazy!
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Gottmik, shantay you stay.
Oh, my God, thank you.
I fucking just won a lip sync
on RuPaul's Drag Race.
Hello!
Utica, I'm sorry, my dear,
but that means
you're getting the porkchop.
Now sashay away.
Thank you very much
for this opportunity.
Oh! No!
It can't end this soon.
I'll get you for this, RuPaul!
Hey!
Oh, my God,
I am the first one here.
I could have gone
to the dentist.
My name is Rosé, and I reside
at the busy intersection
of Wit Avenue
and Fashion Boulevard.
Rosé is a comedy queen,
kind of like if Robin Williams
and Jim Carrey had a child.
What a horrible daughter for
the two of them to procreate.
Got a little stage
going on here.
I'm not gonna step on that.
It might collapse.
I had breakfast today.
I'm a singer and a dancer.
I was on The Voice
and America's Got Talent.
I'm very competitive.
I don't like to lose.
But I usually win.
I should, uh, probably
wipe off this tooth,
since no one's gonna see it.
I'm basically doing shtick
for an empty house,
which is not something Rosé's
used to, I'm proud to say.
Lux be a lady tonight.
I'm Olivia Lux, and I like
to light up a room
whenever I walk into a space.
I consider Olivia Lux
as that diva,
but that, like,
really nice diva,
like Diana Ross
and the Supremes.
Oh, my God!
- You look so good.
- Mwah, mwah.
You look amazing.
It's so good to see you.
You, too, baby.
I think the last time
I saw you in drag
was literally Lady Liberty.
Yeah, where I was a contestant
and you were hosting it.
I look up to Rosé so much.
She's, like,
New York City drag royalty.
And now we're in America's
biggest drag pageant together.
Like, whaaa.
At that time,
I had been doing drag
for, like, what, six months?
Wait, how long
have you been doing drag?
Like, a year and a half.
A year and a half? Okay, girl.
I'm a little surprised to see
Olivia here, to be honest,
because I would expect Olivia
to take just a little bit longer
to be really ripe enough.
But her smile is stunning,
and I can't wait to knock
her teeth out one by one.
Ooh, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
Welcome, ladies. What?
Were you expecting more?
Good, because so am I.
Meet me on the main stage.
Ha!
Pronto!
Okay, the main stage.
- Let's go!
Oh, it is about to start, honey.
Welcome, ladies.
Breathe deep and take in
the charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent
of the queens
that came before you.
The smell of hairspray
and desperation.
Now, the judges wanna get to
know you a little bit better,
starting with Rosé.
What does this outfit
tell us about you, Rosé?
RuPaul always says that
if you wanna make money,
you should wear a suit.
And I never understood that,
so I wore this instead.
I think I recognize you
from New York.
Are you part
of the girl group with Jan?
Yes, I am. Stephanie's Child.
Are you planning on lasting
a little longer than Jan?
I am absolutely planning
on lasting longer than Jan.
- Ooh.
- Okay.
Up next, Olivia Lux.
Hi.
I would love to know what this
outfit says about Olivia Lux.
Well, I do love
a good Showgirl moment,
and I thought
I'd go with something
that reminded me
of a theater curtain.
And a large purse for all
those things you have in it.
Exactly.
I like to carry
my extra eyelashes in this.
If I were to go see
an Olivia Lux show,
how would it be different
than any other drag queen show?
I really like to incorporate
live drag elements,
so you may see me sit down at
the piano for a bit, you know.
Well, I love a big organ.
Ladies, we're doing things a
little differently this season.
It's all come down to this.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your
first chance to impress me
and save yourself
from getting the porkchop.
The time has come...
for you to lip sync...
for your life.
For our life?
On day one?
And against Rosé?
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
♪ Well, I had me a boy,
turned him into a man ♪
♪ I showed him all the things
that he didn't understand ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ And then I let him go ♪
♪ Now there's one in California
who's been cursing my name ♪
♪ 'Cause I found me
a better lover in the UK ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Until I made my getaway ♪
♪ One, two, three,
they gonna run back to me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm the best baby
that they never gotta keep ♪
♪ One, two, three,
they gonna run back to me ♪
♪ They always wanna come,
but they never wanna leave ♪
♪ Ex's and the oh, oh, oh's,
they haunt me ♪
♪ Like gho-oh-osts,
they want me ♪
♪ To make 'em, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ They won't let go ♪
♪ My ex's and the oh, oh, oh's,
they haunt me ♪
♪ Like gho-oh-osts,
they want me ♪
♪ To make 'em, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ They won't let go... ♪
It sounds so cliché
and band camp
to say that I am one
with the music,
but, honey,
I am one with the music.
I'm an incredible lip syncer.
I'm gonna show the judges
that I've got a few tricks
up my sleeve
and I'm the bitch to watch.
♪ But they never wanna leave ♪
♪ My ex's ♪
♪ And the oh, oh, oh's,
they haunt me ♪
♪ Like gho-oh-osts,
they want me ♪
♪ To make 'em, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ They won't let go ♪
♪ Ex's and the oh, oh, oh's,
they haunt me ♪
♪ Like gho-oh-osts,
they want me ♪
♪ To make 'em, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ They won't let go ♪
♪ Ex's and oh's ♪
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Olivia Lux, shantay you stay.
Aah! I can't believe it!
Thank you.
I'm shocked!
Rosé, I'm sorry, my dear,
but that means
you're getting the porkchop.
What? Wait, what?
Now sashay away.
Thank you.
Oh, wait, I'm so confused.
Me, too.
I just got here.
I haven't done anything.
I haven't even
opened my suitcase.
Am I supposed to, like,
leave with a zinger?
I'm not sure what's going on,
but bye, I think.
Didn't your parents ever teach
you not to play with fire?
Now let's turn it
and burn it, bitches!
I'm Tina Burner,
and I'm New York's premiere
costume comedy queen.
I have been a staple in
the drag community for 10 years.
I am just large and in charge.
I'm The Muppets
Take Manhattan, okay?
I have a reputation of being,
like, loud and outspoken.
I got a lot to say,
and I will not be silent.
The fireworks show is on... ooh...
Oh, clean brushes. Thank God.
I am literally gonna
light this place up.
Ah, fire. Oh, my gosh,
did I just do, like, Showgirls?
I did!
Whoo!
The Mackie doll
is finally out of her box.
I'm Kahmora Hall,
and I'm Chicago's
premiere Mackie Barbie doll.
Kahmora Hall is always living
that rich, white woman fantasy.
She is just dripping in luxury.
You can smell the privilege
off of her.
And my drag is all about
the glitz and glam.
Shine and sparkle
never go out of style.
- Hey!
- Hi!
Oh, my God, Miss Big Red,
how are you?
Mwah, mwah!
- Kahmora Hall.
- Kahmora Hall?
Kah-mora, okay?
Not Kim-mora, Kah-mora.
- Get it right.
- Kahmora Hall, got it.
That's right.
- Tina Burner.
- Oh, I know you, girl.
I know who Tina Burner is.
She is a local legend,
and even though she's
the only one there right now,
I just know that
she's one to watch out for.
So who are you wearing?
I'm giving you
a firefighter, honey.
I'm just giving you the
whole Tina Burner experience
from head to toe.
I see.
You look like
a sexy hot dog right now.
Kahmora is shady, bitch.
I'm, like, yes,
you can be on Team Burner.
Oh!
♪ I'm the queen
you want to see ♪
♪ Elliott with 2 Ts, okay? ♪
♪ Uh, uh, uh, uh-uh-uh-uh ♪
Okay? Get into it.
White girls can't dance, huh?
My name is Elliott with 2 Ts,
and I'm the most famous
drag queen
you ain't never heard of.
My drag is very much
a housewife with a secret.
I've been doing drag
since I was 15 years old,
dancing, acting, singing.
I didn't practice my autograph
since I was a baby for nothing.
She looks fun.
Sis.
She got a windbreaker on
and some pants,
and I'm just, like, sis,
do you just go
power walking with my mom?
- Hi!
- Hello, hello.
Hi. I'm Kahmora.
I'm Elliott with 2 Ts.
- Hi, Elliott with 2 Ts.
- Hello.
All I can think about is ET.
Elliott...
And I was, like, ooh, girl.
She needs to phone home
and get a new outfit
for the werkroom entrance, girl.
I've seen you before.
You were at a drag brunch
in Las Vegas.
I sure was.
That's where I'm from.
Is this look very Vegas
or something?
I'm just curious
what your inspiration was.
Here we go with the shade.
That is not shade!
Here you go. Watch out for her.
Ooh, girl.
Is this really happening
right now?
My queens, main stage, now.
Get to the main stage.
Is that what they said?
I don't understand.
What's going on?
Trying to raise my eyebrows,
but they don't raise right now.
All that pumping.
Wait, let me get my purse!
Are they moving?
Welcome, ladies.
Surprised to see me?
Say hello to the judges.
- Hello, judges.
- Hi!
They're dying to get to know
a little bit more
about each of you.
Starting with Tina Burner.
Little bit of a New York legend
here with you.
I'm glad to see you here.
That just means I'm old.
Well, join the club, sweetheart.
You've got your whole
fire department thing going on.
Does this speak to us
and tell us who you are?
I'm, like, a campy,
comedy, sassy queen.
So, like, Tina Burner,
turn it and burn it,
burning down the house.
And so, we're here
to put that fire out
with my large hose.
Yeah.
Sss.
Is it true that
you were in a boy band
when you were 19 years old?
Yes, I was in a boy band.
After three years,
I had to say Bye, Bye, Bye.
You guys are no longer N'Sync?
No. No. We're more like the
Back Door Boys now, you know?
Well, that's
a fascinating back story.
We got a lotta back
going on today.
Back to you, Ru.
- Up next, Elliott.
- Hi.
You look like
a member of Exposé.
Okay.
Yes, I love that outfit.
Thank you.
What does it say about you?
I love an eighties throwback,
I love a good structured moment.
I grew up as a dancer,
so the big dancing
female divas of the eighties
really speak to me.
What kind of dancing
did you grow up doing?
Well, not to
Brooke Lynn Hytes myself,
but I was a ballet dancer
my whole life,
and I worked on cruise ships
for a while as a dancer.
And what was your favorite
port of call?
My favorite was Cozumel.
You like to party, don't you?
A little bit. Just a little bit.
Last but not least,
Kahmora Hall.
You know, I just watched
Beyond the Valley of the Dolls
last night
again for the eightieth time,
and your hair is serving
Beyond the Valley of the Dolls.
That was definitely
the inspiration.
You look stunning.
Thank you so much.
I really love this look
that you have on.
Who's the designer?
It's an original Bob Mackie.
I bought it
from an auction house,
and I just had to have it.
What?
They had it reconstructed
to fit my body,
because I'm sample size.
- That is insane.
- Wow.
I love it.
Kahmora Hall, any relation
to our queen Jaida Essence Hall?
Jaida Essence Hall
is my big sister.
The House of Hall.
We're known for great shoulders
and great clavicles.
Yes. That's always good to know.
Well, those are some
very big shoes to fill.
She got some big feet, so, yeah.
Exactly.
Thank you, Kahmora.
Thank you.
Ladies, show of hands.
Who likes surprises?
- Me!
- Love 'em!
Oh, goodie.
Three queens stand before me.
What?
Ladies, this is your
first chance to impress me
and save yourself
from getting the porkchop.
The time has come...
for you to lip sync...
..for your life.
Nobody puts Burner
in the corner, okay?
Because I'll tell you what.
I didn't come all this way
to watch these bitches beat me.
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
♪ Hey, sista, go, sista,
soul sista, flow, sista ♪
♪ He met Marmalade
down in old Moulin Rouge ♪
♪ Struttin' her stuff
on the street ♪
♪ She said, hello, hey, Joe,
you wanna give it a go, oh ♪
♪ Gitchie, gitchie,
ya-ya, da-da ♪
♪ Da, da, da ♪
♪ Gitchie, gitchie, ya-ya here ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Mocha chocolata, ya-ya... ♪
Thank God Bob Mackie
works for all occasions.
I'm feeling confident
and beautiful.
I'm killing it.
♪ We come through with the
money and the garter belts ♪
♪ Let him know we 'bout that
cake straight out the gate ♪
♪ We independent women,
some mistake us for whores ♪
♪ I'm sayin' why spend mine
when I can spend yours? ♪
♪ Disagree? Well, that's you,
and I'm sorry ♪
♪ Imma keep playing
these cats out like Atari ♪
♪ Wear high-heel shoes,
get love from the dudes ♪
♪ Four badass chicks
from the Moulin Rouge ♪
♪ What? Creole lady Marmalade ♪
♪ One more time, come on ♪
♪ Marmalade ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey, oh ♪
♪ Touch of her skin,
feeling silky smooth ♪
♪ Hey! Color
of café au lait... ♪
I'm a Clydesdale
in this battle right now.
I'm not no little
My Little Pony.
It is time to bury these girls.
- ♪ More ♪ - ♪ More ♪
♪ Gitchie, gitchie,
ya-ya, da-da ♪
♪ Gitchie, gitchie, ya-ya here ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, yeah ♪
♪ Mocha chocolate, ya-ya ♪
♪ Creole lady Marmalade ♪
♪ Ooh, yes ♪
Great.
Ladies, I've made my decision.
This is not what day one
is supposed to be.
I'm just trying not to throw up.
Ladies, I've made my decision.
I would give up masturbating
for a year
just to hear, "Tina Burner,
shantay you stay."
Tina Burner, shantay you stay.
Thank you so much.
Damn, I just won!
And the choices I made
I will deal with.
That means Kahmora Hall
and Elliott,
I'm sorry, my dears,
but you are both
getting the porkchop.
Porkchop?
I don't like pork chops.
- Hey, ladies.
- Hi!
- Hello!
Okay, what is going on?
Hi, hi, hi.
I'm seeing
all these other girls.
I see Denali, my Chicago sister.
I'm normally the queen
that knows all the twists
and the gags and the goops.
But this is throwing me
for a loop.
So you all just both lip synced.
- We just lip synced.
- Yeah.
Oh, my God.
- Porkchop.
- Yeah.
Welcome to all the people
who went home first.
They can't send us home.
They can kind of do
whatever they want.
No!
I object.
We're trying to figure out
what's going on.
This is what we've been
talking about this whole time
is is this the real tea?
Here we all are
in the porkchop lounge,
who famously went home first.
So is that what's gonna happen
to all of us?
I'm not okay with that.
I wonder what the winners
are doing right now?
We won our first challenge,
essentially.
I know!
Clearly Team Talent.
Oh, shit.
- Oh!
- Aah!
Yes!
- Diva!
- Winner's circle!
Child, everyone in New York City
knows Tina auditions every year,
and God bless her heart.
She is ancient.
I love her to death,
but she needed to get on
before she died.
- Hi, mama!
- Hi!
New York is in the house!
Oh, goodness.
Okay, we've got a New York girl
that is a comedy queen
and a campy queen.
You always gotta watch out
for those girls, honey,
because they may not
be gorg in the face,
but that don't mean shit.
Competition register locked.
So I'm guessing you won
your lip sync as well?
I did. Did you?
Mm, well, we're sitting
right here, bitch.
We're all the winner's circle,
all right.
- All right!
- Winner's circle!
I lip synced
against a New York sister.
Oh.
Rosé.
Rosé's here?
Oh, here we go.
Olivia beat Rosé in a lip sync?
Miss Olivia Lux, who's been
doing drag for 10 seconds?
So I'm thinking
Rosé's beside herself.
Because, like, Rosé is, like,
a little more
of a seasoned queen.
She got, you know,
America's Got Talent.
She is... "I was on The Voice,"
you know, "I can sing."
Well, I guess
you couldn't lip sync.
Wait, so are
the other girls gone?
Do you think they're still here?
- They have to be.
- It's not us.
- I have no idea.
But what I do know
is that we here.
Aah!
We're stunning, we're winners,
and, baby,
may the best woman win.
Come on, Season 13!
Yes!
Did you guys lip sync
against each other?
It was us
and then one other queen.
Who were you against?
Tina Burner.
Oh, fuck.
She's here!
Tina's from New York.
So are you from New York, too?
I'm from New York.
And Tina won
against you beauties.
That fucking bitch.
Me and Tina work
in the same circles.
I like Tina.
I don't think Tina likes me.
What in the heck do you think
is about to happen next?
We're gonna de-drag
at the airport...
Our picture's
gonna be on the wall
with the rest of the girls.
Attention, queens
in the porkchop loading dock.
Oh, that's us.
The departure van
will be arriving soon.
On behalf of the judges,
we want to wish you
safe travels,
wherever your final
destination may be.
Okay, so everything
I just said, forget it.
I guess we're going home
instead.
Mm, girl, I told you.
The lady said... go home.
The lady said go home.
For me, this is really,
really emotional,
because this means
the world to me.
Like, this is my dream.
And, like, not getting
to show the world anything
of what kind
of drag queen you are,
it's just the period
on a really shitty day.
- Uh, Ru?
- Yes?
You do realize
you just eliminated
half of the cast, right?
Oh.
Oh, okay, hold up.
Attention, queens
in the porkchop loading dock.
All is not lost.
You all have a chance
to return to the competition.
First, you must give one
of your fellow queens the chop.
What kind of All Stars
bullshit is this?
This is just bonkers.
We don't know each other!
You all have a chance
to return to the competition,
but first, you must give one
of your fellow queens the chop.
And remember, no matter
what happens next,
please enjoy a complimentary
copy of my album,
You're a Winner, Baby.
Let the voting begin.
Wait, for real-real?
I don't know.
But I'm the only Black girl,
so don't vote me off.
Oh, my God.
Girl, we're gagged.
We just met, and now
we have to send one of us home.
I thought
I was already eliminated.
Well, guess what, filler queen?
You might be eliminated again.
Next time
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
You need to perform
a show-stopping version
of my song Condragulations.
♪ Condragulations,
you're number one ♪
You're somebody that
I could not take my eye off of.
Racers, more twists and turns
are just around the corner.
What the fuck?
I don't wanna vote anyone off.
I don't know any of you yet.
We've literally just met.
We have to vote someone off.
This is a competition.
This is what we signed up for.
Shit's about to go down.
♪ I'm a winner ♪
♪ I'm a winner, baby ♪
♪ Losers, weepers ♪
♪ Finders, keepers ♪
♪ I'm a winner, baby ♪
♪ Losers, weepers ♪
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org