[RuPaul] Tens, t-t-tens...
tens across the board!
Oh, like a Phoenix from
the ashes, Eureka is back!
I'm Eureka,
and I am so, so excited!
Oh! I'm so excited
to be back for real.
I just like want to die!
Oh, God! Mwah!
Missed you, workroom.
I was originally on Season 9,
and I injured myself.
So I had to go have
immediate surgery.
Thank you all so much.
I love you.
I didn't get
to really bring my all.
So now I got something to prove,
and I'm here
to fucking slay.
Let me practice.
Hey, girl, how are you?
Oh, my God,
your makeup looks amazing.
Yeah. I'm lying.
Well, guys,
Texas is back in the house.
My name is Asia O'Hara,
and I am the superstar
of Dallas, Texas.
- Oh, yes!
- Cock-a-doodle-doo!
- You look great!
- Can I sit by you?
You look so-- [laughs]
I'm here to sabotage
already, bitch.
My God! I'm known
for doing pageants,
but I'm also
a versatile performer.
Every queen
should be able to pull
a couple different tricks
out of the bag.
- Hi, Asia. Oh, I know you.
- Yes.
- Asia O'Hara.
Wow, okay.
I've heard
of the pageant O'Haras.
Asia is a legend.
This bitch
is gonna be competition.
Girl, you need to come down
to Texas where all this is.
- Texas loves my fat ass.
- Yes.
'Cause I'll be coming in
all extra shit.
- Yeah, Texas likes that stuff.
- [laughs]
Okay, it's time for dinner!
Is that a grapefruit
on her head?
I'm Miz Cracker.
I'm thin, I'm white,
and I'm very salty,
and that's what makes me
a cracker.
As a performer, I'm wild.
Barbie on bath salts.
Come for the face,
stay for the crazy.
Nice to meet you.
What's your name?
My name is Miz Cracker.
Just like the snack
and the racial slur.
Miz Cracker.
This ho
gonna need a nickname.
So where you from?
I am Harlem's Jewish princess.
Harlem? Where's that?
That is in Manhattan,
New York, girl.
Is that a state?
New York. [laughs]
Can you feel the shade?
What the--
I'm Yuhua Hamasaki.
I'm blonde, ambitious
and I'm fucking fierce.
Hi, gay people!
- Hi!
- What the hell!
We know each other.
We're from New York.
My drag style is glamorous.
Fake lashes, makeup done,
and I have all my teeth.
- Asia?
- Hi.
And I thought I'm Asia.
[laughs]
Asia, Asian.
Where are you from?
I'm originally from China.
I moved here when I was seven.
I thought you were Japanese.
No, I'm Chinese, girl.
Hamasaki?
Well, you're not
a real woman either.
[all laugh]
I'm Blair St. Clair.
Just got here this morning.
I hope she gives us Broadway.
Maybe 7th Avenue.
My name is Blair St. Clair,
and I am the Broadway Diva
Extraordinaire.
Blair is a small-town girl.
Just got off the bus looking
for fame any way she can.
Well, hey, girls!
- Hi.
- Where you from?
- Indianapolis.
Yes. I'm the first Indi Queen
ever to be on the show.
That's so exciting.
Like, I get to be the first
person ever in history, ever,
to represent
my whole entire state.
[Yuhua] What type of drag
do you then?
I sing, I dance and I act.
I love tapdancing.
Broadway baby, huh?
- Oh, Broadway.
- ♪ Broadway ♪
[laughs]
Oh, don't mind me.
I'm just here to sweep up
the competition, girl.
I am Monét X Change,
and you better get
your currency in check,
bitch.
Oh, my God!
What the fuck!
You shady fucking bitch!
- I can't believe it!
- Cracker! Aah!
Monét is a very fun,
effervescent personality
and charming.
If there's any single men
out there, I'm very charming.
What kind of drag do you do?
I'm eclectic, I'm eccentric.
- Versatile?
- Versatile.
- Good. I like that.
- Ohh...
Eureka, you're not versatile.
[laughs]
I could surprise you, bitch.
[Yuhua] How about
break your knee again?
[all laugh]
I'm gonna have to watch out
for that bitch over there!
Well, I auditioned
for Pit Crew,
but this is gonna be
way more fun.
That's a man, Maury!
I'm Kameron Michaels,
and I'm the Muscle Queen
from Nashville, Tennessee.
- Hi, gorgeous!
- Hi.
Outside of drag, I am
a tatted muscle dude at the gym,
and then I tuck it back,
throw on some pads,
and walk out looking fishy
as fuck.
I'm a little bit of grunge
and a little bit of glamour.
[contestant]
So where you from, Kameron?
I'm from Nashville.
- That's cool!
- Yeah, southern queen.
- Tennessee, yeah!
- Yes, honey!
You are so gorgeous as a guy.
- Oh, thank you.
- And as a girl--
How do you know what
she looks like as a guy?
I follow her so hard
on Instagram.
What else do you so hard?
[all laugh]
Guess who finally decided
to crash the party?
Hey!
- Is that Mayhem?
- That is Mayhem Miller, girl.
I'm Mayhem Miller and I'm
the queen of the party.
My drag family has all
the fucking best girls
that used to be
on RuPaul's Drag Race.
Morgan McMichaels,
Delta Work, Detox,
and I'm the best one
out of all of them.
[laughs]
- I am gagging!
- Why?
Ms. Mayhem Miller.
Finally, girl!
Finally. I know, huh?
I auditioned year
after year after year,
and it took me forever
to get here.
I'm here.
I ain't going nowhere.
I need a bitch to fucking
move out the way
so I can get my money.
What is drag like
in California?
Like this.
No, just kidding.
It's not that good.
[all laugh]
Ooh.
Hope you're ready for your
all-carb, high-calorie diet.
Yes, ass.
I'm Kalorie Karbdashian
Williams,
and I am sass, class,
and a whole lot of ass.
[chuckles]
Oh, yeah!
[cheering]
Kalorie is pretty much
the twerk queen.
She can shake her ass
like full-on like booty shaking.
So where are you from?
I'm from Albuquerque,
New Mexico.
- Oh, New Mexico.
- New Mexico!
Yes, New Mexico.
[laughs]
So what's the drag
in New Mexico?
What drag?
[all laugh]
Cat-kitty-cat-cat-cat.
Cat-kitty-cat-cat-cow.
Bringing you the heart
of Season 10, honey.
Monique Heart, the Face.
Well, there's gonna be flavor
this year. I can't wait.
[all laugh]
My name is Monique Heart.
She's the Razzle Dazzle Queen.
A little sprinkle over here,
a little glitter over there.
Honey, yeah!
She gonna give you
the ooh-ah-ah sensation, honey.
[cheering]
Oh, yeah!
[laughs]
Oh, my God. Come on!
Girl, she's fabulous!
First of all, I can tell
you are a dancing queen.
Dance queen, hair queen,
hairography.
All of that good jazz.
You give me a category,
watch me play.
All right!
Well, she's gonna gag you,
honey.
She is "I'm a production!"
- Hi, I'm Blair.
- Blair, Monique.
- Hi, and then...
- Cracker.
[all laugh]
Look at her face!
- I did the same thing.
- Okay.
Honey, these southern queens,
they're like, Cracker?
They are not feeling
that shit, girl.
Miz Cracker loves that name
because it causes a stir.
Every time she says Cracker,
I'm like, girl?
Girl, yes.
Never loved ya.
Aah!
My name is Dusty Ray Bottoms.
I'm from the best city on earth,
New York City.
Dusty Ray Bottoms is dark,
glamorous and trashy.
She's also dyslexic.
[cheering]
Hi, girls!
- Come on, le queen.
- Aah!
Well, you guys
all know each other.
We all know each other.
Girl, there's like 100
people here from New York City.
New York City's drag scene
is some of the most
competitive drag there is.
What kind of drag do you do?
- I'm like a punk girl.
- Really?
I do a lot of rock queen,
Janis Joplin,
but I also do obscure
musical theater.
- Girl, I'm a drama queen, too.
- Yes.
- Come on, Broadway queen.
- Best friends.
Oh! Harpo, who this woman?
I'm just here to fight!
- Ooh!
- Uh-oh.
Ooh, she mad, y'all.
The Vixen is magical,
exciting and unpredictable.
[contestant]
I bet she's a Taurus.
When I'm onstage, I'm
giving you earth, wind and fire.
Hey!
[cheering]
[Eureka]
What kind of drag do you do?
Mostly political art,
a lot of protest performances,
such as that.
I definitely am very influential
in the Chicago drag scene.
I'm very vocal and sometimes
that rubs people the wrong way,
but I keep it real.
Y'all know Chicago
is full of it.
You know, we got some of
the best queens in the country,
so I'm gonna represent.
Tens, tens,
tens across the board!
I'm Vanessa Vanjie Mateo.
Gitchie's cookin', baby.
Vanessa's known
for dottin' and boppin'.
Hi-ee!
Like a hooker
on Rodeo Drive.
So she's kind of ghetto,
but still, you know, eloquent.
You have a big
like drag family?
Yes, guys! I'm like
a Mateo drag daughter.
Oh, a Mateo.
I don't remember her.
[all laugh]
Did she just shade her mama?
Oh, oh, she did!
Oh, she just shade.
- From across the table.
- Shady palm tree.
[all laugh]
Alexis Mateo is Drag Race
royalty from Season 3.
Now I'm gonna finish
what she started. Bam!
What type of drag do you do?
Vanjie, Vanjie.
I've done pageants,
but it's not like mine.
Have you won pageants?
[Monét]
These girls are so shady.
Have you won, though?
So does that mean
I'm a pageant queen, then?
Have you won one?
I've won all of them
I competed in.
But didn't you also say
like there's no drag there?
[all laugh]
Bonjour!
[cheering]
My name's Aquaria,
and I am a superstar.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Five New York girls!
Aquaria is the name
on everyone's lips
in New York City.
I've been told
that every girl in the room
knows exactly who this bitch is.
Oh, my God!
And, uh, they should.
Aquaria, Aquaria, Aquaria!
Cracker, your twin is here.
It's battle
between the twins, y'all.
Who? Who's the twins?
Cracker and Aquaria.
I can't. I quit.
This Cracker-Aquaria drama
has gone on for eons
in the New York City drag scene.
People call Aquaria Cracker.
People call Cracker Aquaria.
It is always like the hugest,
biggest elephant in the room.
Cracker and Aquaria
in the same competition?
It's about to go down.
Trust and believe me.
[Eureka] Well, you're coming in
very popular already.
I know that.
Are you excited?
I know there's a lot
to live up to,
so hopefully
I meet the measure.
I'm here to prove to people
that I actually do have the
chops that I say that I have,
and I'm ready to turn it.
Just throw a crown on it.
Aah!
[alarm]
Ooh, girl.
She done already
done had hers.
[Eureka]
That is hauntingly familiar.
[contestant]
Aah! This is really happening!
Hey, queens.
[cheers and applause]
I don't wanna Jinkx you,
but Monsoon you'll
BeBe sharing the spotlight
with queens that would Raja
you were dead.
You need to go above
and Bianca.
For the crown you must vie,
or let the other queens
steal your thunder.
So don't settle for a Bob.
The drag queen
with the biggest hair
is closest to, yes, God!
And if at first
you don't succeed,
Tyra, Tyra again.
So will you be America's
next drag superstar
or the first to Sasha away?
[cheering]
Hello, hello, hello!
[cheers and applause]
Bitch, when RuPaul walked
into the room, I was gagged.
If I said,
The Loch Ness Monster,
you hear a lot about it,
but you never see it.
So when you see it,
bitch, you done!
Welcome, ladies!
[cheers and applause]
You're here!
Do you believe it's been
a decade of Drag Race?
Do you like what we did
with the workroom?
[cheers and applause]
May these rejuvenated
sugar walls
inspire your charisma,
uniqueness, nerve and talent.
Now this season,
our mission is simple.
To take over
the mother-tucking world!
Yes!
[cheering]
#DragRace.
Let's start with
a mini challenge
that's been a decade
in the making.
And, ladies, I expect
tens, tens, tens
across the board!
Hey!
You might think that I'm less
nervous 'cause I've been here,
but you're wrong.
I'm scared to fucking death!
Because if I don't fight through
every single day,
they're not gonna let me last.
All right, ladies, let's go.
[RuPaul] The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100,000!
With extra special guest judge
Christina Aguilera!
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
[RuPaul] Eureka O'Hara.
[Eureka] It's time to do
the first mini challenge,
and I see
all these former queens,
and immediately my butthole
has sucked up the crotch
of my fucking leotard.
Notice any familiar faces?
- A couple.
- I've invited back
some of my favorite queens
from the past decade
to help me judge this challenge.
To win,
you must slay the runway.
Do whatever it takes
to stand out
from this legendary crowd.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Assume the position!
I'm looking at all
these faces of my peers.
Clearly they're judging
the shit outta me.
This is a lot of pressure
on the first day.
Season 10 ain't playing, baby!
Eureka, let's have a ball.
♪ Guess who's back
in the house? ♪
♪ Heels click-clackin' about ♪
♪ Fine French feminine,
style to eleven... ♪
You already had one season
to practice.
Better work that
knee replacement, bitch!
[RuPaul] Watch that leg, girl!
- [all laugh]
I'm just trying to give 'em
big-girl sexy,
even though
I'm terrified to death.
- Ooh!
- Oh!
For somebody to come back,
she knows the gig,
and I wanted more energy
and more excitement!
[RuPaul] Mayhem Miller!
[Mayhem] This is what
I've been waiting for.
And I'm really at home.
This is all my sisters.
Delta, Raven, Morgan, Detox.
I know every single one
of these hos.
Mayhem Miller is my best
friend in the entire world,
and she is killing it.
Oh!
Mayhem did a cartwheel
in a gown.
I couldn't do a cartwheel if
four people operated my limbs.
[RuPaul] Miz Cracker!
Represent New York, bitch!
Jazz crouching!
Cracker's whacked,
but this cracker is whacker!
This is a gag.
That is my drag daughter,
Miz Cracker
from the legendary
House of the Drag Queens.
She is crazy, but it does
run in the family.
That's my baby!
I want to show people
the Cracker brand.
- Do it, bitch!
- Stupid.
♪ Can you feel my love? ♪
[RuPaul] Asia O'Hara!
- Jazz broken legs!
Work that fringe!
Yes, like a carwash, bitch!
I am working this fringe
because I'm from Texas,
and we wear fringe on our
sleeves when we mean business.
I'm a fierce queen.
Yes.
Asia is giving me
Mary J. Blige, honey.
Yes for the cowboy fringe.
[RuPaul]
Kalorie Karbdashian Williams!
I'm stomping down that runway
giving them hip,
giving them ass.
I'm into it. I love carbs.
I love bread!
Drag has definitely helped me
love my curvaceous body,
because through drag,
I've been able to realize
that you can be a big girl
and still be beautiful.
Drop dead!
Kalorie Karbdashian, oh, oh.
I see the fishnets.
They're ripped.
[RuPaul] Monique Heart!
No shade,
no T from these girls.
They're living for me,
because they're going,
get it, girl!
Twirl, sidewalk, sidewalk.
Ooh, ah, ooh, ah,
ooh, ah-ah.
Yes, honey,
shake those golden girls.
Monique
is a great entertainer.
I thought the silhouette of the
outfit looked super gorgeous,
and it looked like
there was a hem everywhere.
I'm impressed.
[RuPaul] The Vixen!
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but I think she might be
from Chicago.
When I'm onstage,
I am going to move the real.
My skirt is coming apart,
but I don't care.
As long as they know
that I came to party.
This is RuPaul's Drag Race,
Season 10, girl.
Hot glue that shit!
[RuPaul] Dusty Ray Bottoms!
But that ain't
none of my business!
I'm killing this challenge.
I'm not giving you death drops,
splits, dance moves.
I'm giving you something
you didn't expect.
These frowns
are turning upside down.
Except for Tempest.
She doesn't smile too much.
Could someone please
wake me up when Dusty's gone?
Oh, yes, honey,
she's Scary Bradshaw.
Yuhua Hamasaki.
You a ho.
It's a U-Ho. That's the girl
that works for the company
that moves people
from houses, no?
When people see me
for the first time,
they're like who is this
glamorous man in a dress?
But I'm actually
a very silly person.
I'm not scared
to act like a frikkin' fool.
Yuhua Hamasaki is giving me
Asian Bianca del Rio,
and I'm rooting
for my Asian sister.
Yuhua better work!
[RuPaul] Vanessa Vanjie Mateo!
[Vanessa]
From the House of Mateo!
I see these girls
and I was excited.
Because I said, oh,
I'm about to show the movement
that the Vanjie is.
Ooh, yes.
Vanjie was because I wanted
to be called Vanjie like ghetto.
But Alexis couldn't even
pronounce Vanjie.
She said it wouldn't be Vanjie
because of our accent.
So we took the Vanjie and Mateo,
because I'm part
of the Mateo Empire.
♪ You wear it--
you wear it well ♪
♪ Connect the dots ♪
[RuPaul] Kameron Michaels!
Ms. Kameron Michaels,
I love some freshly got
fuck in there,
and she knew how to toss it.
I say, bitch,
she's coming from a gig.
[Kameron] Some of the queens
are giving me judgy looks,
and some are living for me
and saying, yes, girl, twirl!
Flip that hair!
So I'm getting
mixed reactions, I think.
[RuPaul] Monét X Change!
Ooh, Monét changes everything!
Monét X Change, she looks
like a million bucks.
Her body looks great.
She's giving you high energy.
She is earning it!
I am channeling
my inner Paris Is Burning.
I'm just gonna feel my oats.
And I dip
like three times in a row.
Boom! Boom! Boom!
[all laugh]
Monét X Change
is not here to play.
[RuPaul] Blair St. Clair!
Oh, my gosh!
I just can't believe
this is happening right now.
Put your hands in the air
like Blair St. Clair!
She is like
a super slutty Ginger
from Gilligan's Island.
Yes, Blair.
[RuPaul] Aquaria!
I really love Aquaria.
I thinks she's super original.
I've been following her
since she was like 14.
I think she's gonna shine
and be like
one of the top ones for me.
Oh! Category is sickening!
I am so excited. I am falling
head over heels for these girls.
Whoo!
Literally, I've nearly fell
on Jinkx Monsoon.
Roxxxy Andrews just jumped out
of her seat at a gay bar
and is clapping 'cause
you just slapped Jinkx.
I didn't mind being slapped
across the face.
I was happy for the air time.
[laughs]
Why y'all gagging so?
I bring it to you every ball!
[cheering]
Oh!
- Yes!
- Whoo!
I'm about to put the D
back in D Drag, girl.
We about to do this.
All right, y'all.
Time for us to get outta drag.
These girls went from ladies
to hard men.
I said, "What the--
Bitch,
are we on "Big Brother?"
Blair out of drag, she goes
from a beautiful lady in drag
to a fucking boy scout.
I thought she was
one of the producers
like Saundra something.
That's a real story.
I don't recognize you at all.
Which one are you?
Mayhem. Mayhem?
She says, which one are you?
- Vixen.
- Damn.
Monique.
Which one are you, girl?
Dang, we all skin.
We all don't look alike.
Oh, girl,
Monique is over there.
Who the fuck are you, then?
- Asia!
Asia. Asia.
She is all confused
by the black people
getting out of drag.
She done went down the whole
line of chocolate girls.
Yes.
Ladies, I have to say
I was really, really, really
trying to stop the booger,
but everyone looks
fucking fierce.
Y'all are cute.
If you can't spot
the booger...
[laughs]
Oh, my God!
What?
I have a new crush.
[laughs]
With a K.
Miss Kameron
is looking so juicy.
Standing there looking all fine
and tattooed from neck to navel.
I wanna know
where that trail go.
What is all that?
Why nobody say there was
actual trade up in here?
She's smuggling ham
and shit.
Kameron is definitely
the trade of Season 10.
And I mean rough trade,
the kind of trade that'll
throw you on the wall
and you be like,
oh, I think I'm into it.
Yeah, but for sure, he's it.
Hey, kitty girls!
[cheers and applause]
Whoo, butch queens.
First time out of drag.
- Yeah.
Ladies, now, on the runway,
y'all snatched our attention.
But one of you
scored a perfect 10.
Monét X Change,
you're the winner
of this season's
first mini challenge.
You've won a $2,000 gift card
from Fierce Queen Heels.
[applause]
Yes, bitch! I won the first
mini challenge of Season 10!
I'm here to let these girls know
don't fuck
with New York City.
Yeah, we won last season,
and we gonna win again.
[chuckles]
Now, ladies, to kick off
a new decade of drag,
we're going back to our roots,
as in back
to the very first challenge
from the very first episode
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
We call it Drag on a Dime.
[cheering]
Oh, pit crew?
- Ooh!
Oh, yes!
Wait a minute! Is that it?
There's gotta be more!
Oh, my God!
Now that's what I'm talking
about right there.
For this week's maxi challenge,
you need to create
million-dollar looks
using a bunch of junk
from the 99 Cent Store.
Now, you can use your own hair,
heels and undergarments,
but everything else
that meets the eye
should be bargain-bin beautiful.
I don't do drag on a dime,
so this is about to go left,
right, up, down, side to side.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
Our first challenge
is based on
the first challenge
in Drag Race herstory, girl.
We have to make things
from the 99 Cent Store.
It's chaos, madness,
confusion,
and everybody's running
like hell and high water.
Look at all these
Barbie dolls.
I'm grabbing the flowers
and the tulle,
and I'm making me
a princess look.
And I'm gonna make sure
none of these hos
is doing the same look as me.
- What you need?
- That doggie.
I see this little stuffed dog,
and I immediately got
inspiration from this puppy.
I wanna go very Valley Girl
or Sweet 16,
someone that would carry
a dog in a purse.
Excuse me.
Don't come for my shit, girl.
[Monét] Get outta here.
- Oh, honey, shit.
- Ladies...
You're acting like men.
I'm gonna look like
a charcuterie plate.
Got carrots and celery
and things.
I don't like to spend
a lot of money on drag,
so dollar-store challenge
is right up my alley.
I feel like if I spend $5.00
on a dress
and I make $100 in that dress,
that's a good investment.
All I'm missing
is the hot wings.
What material does she have?
Looking at what I have,
I realize that
it adds up to nothing.
But I'm gonna Cinderella
this pumpkin into a carriage.
- Monique?
- Yes?
[Miz Cracker] Do I have
anything that you want
in exchange for your blue hat?
In order to make my look,
I beg and barter.
- Here you go.
- Oh, my God, you're amazing.
Look at y'all sharing
and whatnot.
I end up with three straw hats
and a shower curtain.
Not even a partridge
in a pear tree.
Do you make
a lot of your outfits?
I really like making things
from the stuff
that I find in the street.
Like in a literal street?
In the actual street.
When we were growing up,
I was really, really poor,
so we had to improvise.
My mother is an artist
who learned to make
fabulous things on a dime.
So my mother taught me to comb
the streets for garbage I liked
and to make it into something
fascinating by sunset.
There's something
really rewarding
about the challenge
of like looking at something
like on the street,
and being like, okay,
what could this be
in another life?
And I love that.
I think I've reneged
on the Barbie dolls.
If anyone want
the Barbie dolls...
Here, babe,
'cause I don't think
I'm gonna have enough
of the flowers.
[Monét] My first idea is to do
this doll-constructed thing.
But I realized that there aren't
enough to cover my big-ass body.
And I know that I can create
this really like Gaga
couture-esque look with sponges.
I'm either gonna be couture
or cou-torn.
I don't think nobody wants
to look like the cleaning crew.
I came here to get
the Drag Race check,
not the cleaning crew's check.
[Monét] Girl, wait.
So what is your plan?
Is this like some
like aluminum foil fantasy?
I have a vision.
I'm inspired by this sun shade
to make like
a Judy Jetson dress.
Oh, word.
Come on, Judy Jetson.
I'm very crafty.
I can craft
a look the house down.
[contestant] Look.
Somebody's doing something, too.
It look mighty similar!
Ooh!
Well...
Get into those cookies.
Cool.
Nuts.
[Yuhua] So I have
these two ideas.
I was thinking of like a leotard
with ping-pong balls
all over it.
Or use this
and make a dress out of it
and glue the caution tape
all over it.
Which one do you think
is better?
I think I like
the caution tape look better.
If you can find a way to
make it like really like chic.
I am feeling the pressure
because I'm known
for being a seamstress.
I've made a lot of costumes
for the girls in New York City,
and I can't go on the runway
looking like a fucking mess.
I can totally hear
a show reading
about Gaga, caution tape.
We've seen it before.
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
- So should I skip it?
We're just trying
to caution you about it.
People think that Yuhua
is a designer.
No. She's a seamstress.
She can use a sewing machine,
but that a designer
does not make, okay?
I hate this
fucking challenge, girl.
[laughs]
What you doing over here?
How you feel about this?
Now you coming
to my station.
Well, because you got pink too
and pretty stuff,
so I need to get
some like inspiration.
So now you coming to see.
Mama, this is the epitome
of winging it.
I'm gonna do a headpiece with
the Barbies and kook 'em out.
I'm gonna take the tulle
and make a little...
Like a little bolero-ey
kind of thing? Okay.
You know, to come out serving
a little bit of crank.
Are you nervous about it?
I'm nervous about mine.
I'm nervous on how these
judges might feel about it.
I need to slay and get
these girls to recognize
I ain't trying to be pork chop.
I might be fish fillet.
Ooh, wait a minute, Jesus.
Fuck!
It is the end of the day.
We are running out of time.
- [whining]
- Is she burning herself?
Everyone is going crazy
a little bit.
Oh...
No one wants to be
the first girl to go home.
[Mayhem] You only get one chance
to make a first impression,
and for somebody,
this is going to be
their only chance
to make an impression.
Fuck!
[Kalorie] Day two!
Hey, y'all!
[Eureka] It's elimination day.
It's the first runway
of the season.
Stakes are high,
hearts are pounding,
buttholes are clinched.
Whew!
How do you feel, girl,
about this outfit?
They wanted
a million-dollar dress,
so I'm giving them
a million-dollar dress.
Oh, it's all money.
Just rich fish.
I went literal. Yeah.
You know, if Kim Kardashian
just had a bunch of extra money
and she just wanted to get
rid of it, she'd make a dress.
Kalorie is very confident
about her look.
She is like,
I am the color of $100,000.
Hopefully, they live for it.
I'm living for it.
[Aquaria] Whose look do you
think are not--are like--
Bottom three,
I would say Vixen probably.
It doesn't look finished.
It looks poorly executed.
But she is very crafty.
That's like
her drag style, so...
Listen, there's a difference
between crafty and crunchy.
[all laugh]
Monique, how's this
house of cards?
Oh, bitch.
From head to toe,
I am serving the 99 Cent Store.
I'm gonna do a whole
Queen of Hearts thing.
I made hair out of the plastic
No Trespassing signs.
She's looking opulent.
Are you worried
about going home today?
Oh, I'm not going home. Trust.
Look around the room, I really
feel like I'm gonna win this.
Bitch, if I don't win it,
I'm pushing whoever does.
So, Eureka, last season
you ended up falling
and hurting yourself?
- Oh, my knee?
- Yeah.
It was a lot, you know.
It was hard, of course.
The surgery was a lot tougher
than I ever imagined.
- I didn't even--
- You had to have surgery?
I had to have surgery, yeah.
I tore my ACL in my knee
completely.
- Oh, no.
- Yeah.
I didn't even know if I
would be able to dance again.
Like...
oh, I'm gonna get emotional.
How was like the recovery
process for you?
It was horrible. [sobs]
Oh, baby.
It was terrifying.
You know what I mean?
Even though Ru invited me back,
once I found out more
information about my injury,
I thought there was a chance
I wasn't gonna be able
to come back.
The doctor was like,
oh, it could take
up to two years to be back.
And I just every day,
I like did my physical therapy
and stretched my knee and stuff.
It was like six months in,
and the premier show
for this show
was the first time that
I danced again since surgery.
It was just amazing
to dance again.
It's why I do this, you know.
- Well, look at you now, girl!
- I know.
You back!
You're in Season 10!
I'm here!
Sorry. I didn't mean to--
And you still kicking and
splitting and twirling, girl.
This is my second chance,
and you barely get those
in life.
So if I fuck it up,
it might be my last chance.
How do you feel?
Of course like I'm nervous.
The world's been waiting
on you to be here.
And that's why I'm like,
oh, my God.
I don't wanna let no one down.
Like I'm--
You won't, though.
It's tough.
It's really tough...
I know. It is tough.
To have that pressure on you.
We're all here
with the same goal.
I definitely feel like
I have a lot to live up to
because of the drag family
I come from.
I come from the best.
Let's paint.
Which one are you doing?
I think I'm gonna do
like my 1930s one
if I can find it.
Cute. That is so smart.
What made you decide to put them
all in the scrapbook?
Because I know that when
I'm second-guessing everything,
I just wanna be able
to look at something
that I know
that I've done before.
These are makeup ideas,
what I have done in the past.
So that I remember
who I have been
when I can't remember
who I'm going to be.
I don't think there's
gonna be any problem
with me standing out.
Dusty, so what look are we
serving the children tonight?
I might be doing
my signature makeup tonight
and putting the dots on my face.
It's funny, because
I didn't mean to do it at first.
I was trying to figure out
my eyebrows.
Someone told me I could map
them out by making dots,
and they were like,
put the first dot here,
the second dot there.
So that's what I started doing.
And I looked at it and
I was like, that's really cool.
And I just kept doing
variations of it
and it stuck
and it looks good on me,
so I kept it.
Cracker's doing those
downturn eyebrows.
Any time we do this look,
it cracks me up.
'Cause you think
I'm really upset.
And like doing a whole show,
it cracks.
So and then you're like...
- Hmm.
- [laughs]
So I feel kind of confident
with my look, but...
We're both doing like
the same brows now, too?
- I noticed.
- Girl.
Cracker and Aquaria
are doing the same face.
[gasps]
I just saw!
Like not the same,
but the same.
Why is she
so obsessed with you?
I cannot believe
we're doing the same makeup.
That's the gag.
Gag to the gag
to the gag, gag, gag.
Is this like a frequent thing?
[laughs]
It's a common moment.
Miz Cracker seems to take
a lot of inspiration
from my makeup looks.
I think that can be
a little annoying sometimes.
I am in it to win it,
and I did not come here
to make friends, bitch.
Oh, we gonna talk about this!
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
She's back, back, back again!
Michelle Visage!
It's our 10th anniversary,
darling.
And they said
it wouldn't last.
No, they said that about
your girl group Seduction.
[all laugh]
Style superstar
Carson Kressley!
What's in fashion this season?
Oh, gosh, Ru. All the kids
are wearing sponges,
pool noodles and piñatas.
I love it.
I'll take one in every color.
Done!
And the hilarious
Ross Mathews.
A decade of drag.
Can you believe it?
You know, I've been watching
since kindergarten, Ru.
- [laughs]
- Lies. Pathological liar.
This week,
we challenged our queens
to make million-dollar looks
out of 99 Cent Store junk
in the classic challenge,
Drag on a Dime.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[RuPaul] Up first, Aquaria.
Larry had a little lamb.
[Carson] Was that
a staff infection?
[Aquaria] It's my first time
on the runway,
and I am overwhelmed
with confidence.
My look is very Little Ho Peep
meets New York Fashion Week.
Call me Mother...Goose.
[Carso] So sheepish
about everything.
[RuPaul] Yeah, well, that's
because she's on the lamb.
[all laugh]
[Michelle] Oh, Mary.
[RuPaul] Asia O'Hara.
I'm sorry, ma'am, but that
is not 15 items or less.
[all laugh]
[Asia] I'm giving you
very Katy Perry,
cutesy, little girl fantasy.
My drag is all about creativity
and fun and magic.
[Michelle] Oh!
[Carson] Oh.
[RuPaul] Yes, girl,
she's going back to Party City.
Ross] Where she belongs.
- [all laugh]
Kalorie Karbdashian Williams
Bonina Brown Zeta Jones.
[RuPaul]
Dolla make you wanna holla.
[Michelle] Yes.
[Kalorie I'm just trying to give
very expensive, rich,
white woman.
I'm feeling like Kris Jenner
at the Met gala
giving you Mama's realness.
I'm feeling fabulous.
[Michelle]
The buck stops here.
[all laugh]
[Ross] Cash me outside.
How about that?
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Well, I declare,
Blair St. Clair.
[Ross] Category is
things you find in my windshield
in Palm Springs.
[all laugh]
[Blair] This look to me is
Vivienne Westwood-inspired
Paris runway. I feel
very high-fashion and edgy.
I came here to slay.
[Ross] She's a vision!
No, I'm sorry. A visor.
[RuPaul] Are you advising her?
[Carson] I wouldn't advise it.
[RuPaul] Now she's off
to call her spiritual advisor.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Dusty Ray Bottoms!
Tin! Tins across the board!
[Dusty] I am serving
Space Odyssey clown realness.
And I've got my cute little dots
all over my face.
And, listen,
I'm Dusty Ray Bottoms,
so I've got to show
a little bottom.
[RuPaul]
Oh, and there's the bottom.
Kameron Michaels!
The grass is always greener
between me down there.
[Kameron]
This outfit is very me,
because I like to play on
the opposite end of the spectrum
and be very feminine,
since I'm a little more
masculine out of drag.
[Ross]
I think I see her tulips.
[Michelle]
Look at all that AstroTurf!
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Monét X Change!
[Ross] Cleanup on Season 10.
[laughs]
[Monét]
My look is very conceptual,
and it feels like a whole story
with the dirt in my eyes.
And I have ping-pong balls
to make little soap suds,
and I have blue earrings
to signify the water.
I'm literally cleaning the floor
with my garment
as I'm walking down the runway.
And it's fucking fierce.
[Carson] Oh, God,
she's so self-absorbent.
[RuPaul] Yeah.
[Michelle] That is Brillo-iant!
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] The Vixen!
[Carson] She really used
her noodle on this one.
[Michelle] She has!
[The Vixen]
My look is kind of Carnival.
It's definitely art,
but it's still fun.
It's everything
that I hope that I am.
[Michelle] Hope floats.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Mother,
may I Mayhem Miller?
[Michelle] Ooh, I wonder if
that dress has three-ply lining.
[RuPaul] Hmm.
[Carson] Well, for safety,
she double-bagged it.
[Michelle] Yes!
[Mayhem] She's giving
garbage pail goddess.
It's lovely, it's fierce,
it's dark,
it's mysterious,
it's mayhem.
[RuPaul] And if the glove
don't fit...
[Michelle] You must acquit!
[RuPaul] No.
Make an outfit out of it.
[Michelle]
All right, all right!
[RuPaul]
Eureka! I found it!
[Michelle]
Do not comfort her!
[all laugh]
[Eureka] The light hits my face
and I feel like I'm at home.
Giving 'em Sweet 16 Valley Girl
with my puppy dog.
Honey, I'm giving 'em
every bit of sass and class.
My Drag on a Dime is bitchin'!
I'm letting them know
Eureka is back.
[RuPaul] Bye, sugar tits!
Monique Heart!
[Michelle]
Somebody call my dealer quick!
[RuPaul] Now, Michelle, would
you call this a poker face?
[Michelle] Yes, I would,
and I would also poke her face.
[laughs]
Monique] I'm serving
Queen of Hearts, Queen of Cards,
Queen of Structure,
Queen of...
Bitch, is that hair
made out of plastic?
It is.
#Stunning.
[Ross] She's giving me
a straight flush.
[Michelle] Yes.
[RuPaul] Vanessa Vanjie Mateo.
From the Mateo Dynasty. Bam!
[Ross] Flower power bottom.
[Carson] You can lead
a whore to culture.
[all laugh]
[Vanessa] Forget fashion week.
This runway
is the one that matters.
Eat it up, eat it up!
These cookies is coming down
the runway, baby.
Giving these doll fantasies,
baby.
A little wink-wink, nudge-nudge,
and headed for the door.
Let's go.
[RuPaul]
Flowers in the attic.
[Michelle] And in the basement.
[RuPaul] Mm-hmm.
- [all laugh]
[Carson] And on the back porch.
[RuPaul] Mm-hmm.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Yuhua Hamasaki!
You a ho.
[Michelle] Ankh, ankh!
[Ru laughs]
[Carson]
I didn't get it.
It's an ankh on her head!
[Carson] Oh, that's an ankh?
- [all laugh]
[Yuhua] I'm embodying
a futuristic woman
because in the future,
there's not many supplies left.
And as I turn, all those
caution tapes just turn with me.
I feel beautiful.
This is Law and Order,
SV-Yuhua.
[Carson] Well, I think this look
is criminal. Ankh, ankh!
[Michelle]
Thank you! I tried!
[RuPaul] Miz Cracker!
Mr. Cheez-It!
Oh, she looks so sad.
[Miz Cracker]
Today, I'm serving sad widow.
My body language
is silent film drama.
I'm telling you everything
without saying a word.
It's not the outfit that will
sell the runway, it's me.
[RuPaul] Miz Cracker,
she's putting on the Ritz.
[all laugh]
Welcome, ladies.
That runway
was worth every penny.
Now when I call your name,
please step forward.
Kameron Michaels,
Aquaria,
Asia O'Hara,
Eureka,
Monét X Change,
Monique Heart,
The Vixen.
You are all safe.
What? Safe?
Bitch, I was stunning!
#Bitter.
You may step your pussy up.
And step
to the back of the stage.
Ladies, you represent the tops
and the bottoms of the week.
Now, before the judging begins,
I have an announcement to make.
There's one more queen
I'd like to add
to this competition.
- What?
- Shut up.
We have enough! We already
got Eureka from last season!
Oh, my God!
Y'all are killing me!
A queen we all know and love.
Please welcome back
to the main stage...
Farrah Moan.
[Kalorie] Farrah? Really?
They have to bring back
another Season 9 girl?
[Monique]
I'm like wait a minute.
Farrah Moan got some work done.
[cheers and applause]
Yes!
Aah!
Stop the press! Xtina
is in the building, baby!
- Oh, my God!
- Whoo!
Farrah Moan, you look
beautiful in every single way.
Thank you, Ru.
Farrah, tell me.
Why do you deserve to return
to the competition?
Oh, Ru, I only have
one thing to say.
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh...yeah ♪
[cheers and applause]
My queens, say hello
to the one and only
Christina Aguilera!
[cheers and applause]
I want to like run onstage
and like grab her and touch her,
but I know security
will probably check me,
so that's why
I didn't make that move.
Christina, you may join
the other judges.
Come on over, baby.
All right.
Not only do I live for
Christina Aguilera,
but I ♪ live ♪
for Christina Aguilera!
I'm gonna tell you one thing
about Season 10.
When you think you know
what the fuck is going on,
you don't know nothin'!
Ladies, Christina watched
your runway presentations
from backstage.
And now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
First up,
Kalorie Karbdashian Williams.
- Hi.
I loved your confidence
coming out here,
and you do such a sweetness
about you, and I loved that.
[Michelle] But I'm gonna
go out on a limb here
and say that I'm thinking
designing may not be
your strong suit.
I mean, I might be biased,
but I feel like
a million bucks, so...
A design challenge look needs
to have presence on the runway.
I would have loved
to have seen earrings
made out of dollar bills
in origami shapes.
I would have loved to see
like maybe a big green wig.
I wanted more impact.
This is a dress
that's been done a few times.
In fact, Raja did
a version of it, Manila,
and Acid Betty did one, too.
And that's a lot
to live up to.
But this just falls short
for me.
Up next, Blair St. Clair,
I declare!
You look really young.
Me, too.
That's funny.
Tell another one.
[all laugh]
I love this look
because of all the textures.
It's very artful,
and I really appreciate that.
It's not easy to make a visor
look like a skirt.
I think the only thing
that throws me off
is maybe the visor in the back.
I have to disagree
with Michelle.
I love the reflective collar
because it's really
shooting some nice light
right under my chins.
[all laugh]
Is it okay to say that
the 99 Cent Store can be chic?
Like you made it look very cool
and futuristic.
I'm intrigued by you.
I think you have
something special.
Thank you.
Up next, I want to talk about
my favorite subject, bottoms.
Dusty Ray Bottoms.
I think this is really fun
because it's got
a very 1960s mod feeling.
It's a little bit like
Jo Anne Worley and the Tin Man
had a baby.
Yeah.
You chose to put a cone
on your head for a hat.
It almost turned it witchy
when it was really fashiony
on the bottom.
I also want you to talk me
through the dots on your face.
That's my signature makeup.
That's what I do.
You just wanted to do your
first look as your signature?
Absolutely.
We're gonna see this
all the time?
Not all the time.
I can do a lot of things.
Okay. Looking forward
to a dot-free face, Dusty.
Mayhem Miller.
[coughs]
Sorry. I was gagging.
That's never happened before.
[all laugh]
But I'm gagging over your look.
I love the way you created
that shoulder detail
and how you used the trash bags
to kind of almost make it
look like quilted leather.
Even using the latex gloves
as a chic cocktail glove
is fantastic.
You can serve a cocktail
and check a hernia
all at the same time.
[all laugh]
The creativity
is off the charts with this.
This is a fantastic way
to come out of the gate.
Somebody's who's auditioned
as many times as you have,
you're here
and you did what you came to do.
[sniffles]
How you feeling?
I'm just...
I'm overwhelmed.
Because I was so nervous.
I've waited so long for this.
[sobs]
Sometimes the universe
knows better, Mayhem.
The universe was waiting
for you to be here at Season 10.
This is your time,
and this is a great start
to this season for you.
Thank you.
Up next, Vanessa Vanjie Mateo
of the Mateo Dynasty. Bam!
So do you have
a background in design?
I wouldn't say
I'm Project Runway ready,
but I got my patterns
in my clutch.
[all laugh]
You have a lot of flavor,
uh-huh.
All kinds of flavors.
Yeah, and I like
fell in love with you
the minute you started talking.
I agree.
As soon as you talk,
it like brings everything about
you to a whole different level.
I love the quirkiness
and the campiness
of the dolls on your boobs,
coming out of your waist.
They're just like, hey, girl.
But here's the story.
I'm looking at you
and I see round almost.
It's about definition.
You wanna see
the lines in the outfits.
So it's literally
a head and legs,
and the rest is flowers.
You guys put so much time
and effort
into making undergarments and
bodies that give an illusion,
and then you're slamming
everything on it
and covering it up.
So think about that before
you step out onto the runway.
Yuhua Hamasaki.
I really like this look.
You've taken two disparate ideas
where you did
a very couture shape,
but you used
a very campy material.
The caution tape,
was it something
we've never seen before?
Absolutely not.
But it was cute, and I think
you...Yuhua pulled it off.
[all laugh]
So do you know that you have
an ankh on your head?
I don't even know
what an ankh is.
An ankh is an Egyptian symbol,
I believe, of peace.
Oh, I thought you meant
by like car, onk, onk.
That was the joke.
[all laugh]
I thought you had personality
when you came out.
Obviously, all I saw was an ankh
that you had no idea
you had on your head.
Michelle, you're never
gonna make ankh happen.
- [all laugh]
- Onk, onk!
Up next, Miz Cracker.
Yes, Miz Cracker,
if you're nasty.
And I'm disgusting.
[all laugh]
Sassy cracker, too.
Where'd you get that name?
I used to be Brianna Cracker,
like "brie on a cracker."
Oh, my gosh.
But then
it was too complicated.
And a little cheesy.
Yeah. I thought it would be
simpler to be just Miz Cracker.
And I live in Harlem,
so people call me by name
all the time.
[all laugh]
Okay, let's talk
about this look.
This is not an easy shape to do,
this kind of 1940s
peplum jacket.
So kudos on the way
you've constructed it.
So what materials did you use?
Shower curtains
and broad-brimmed hats.
I think that you constructed
a masterpiece here,
and you painted your face
to go along with that.
But I think
what really sold it
was the presentation
on the runway
when you came out
and you were looking lost.
I saw myself
as this sort of tragic figure
that goes with the outfit.
What was the tragedy,
a fisting accident?
There are no accidents
in fisting.
[all laugh]
To know that you created this
from the 99 Cent Store,
I'm super blown away.
Awesome job.
Thank you, Christina Aguilera.
Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
While you untuck backstage,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right, so just between
us squirrel-friends,
what do you think?
Kalorie Karbdashian Williams.
I think she has
a beautiful smile,
but I think that dress
was hideous.
Everything just came out
ill-fitting,
and when she turned around,
the back
was kind of falling apart.
What I really didn't like
was the black showing
in the back of her.
This was essentially
a fashion challenge.
You have to wow us visually,
and it just looked, for me,
like she ran out of time.
You can't show up and show us
something we've seen before,
and not even show it as good
as it was done the first time
or the second time
or the third time.
This is Season 10.
You've gotta be different,
you've gotta be unique,
and you've gotta wow us.
Blair St. Clair.
[Christina] She was hands down
one of my top favorites.
I really, really
liked her a lot.
[Carson] And I love
that she's giving us
Vivienne Westwood Judy Jetson
looks made out of a sun visor.
And she also is gorgeous.
She's like our little ingénue.
I've got tucking panties
older than her.
[all laugh]
Tonight what she did
with the sun visors
is not easy to do.
There's a regalness about her
which I love,
and I just cannot wait
to see more from Blair.
[RuPaul] Dusty Ray Bottoms.
[Michelle] I actually really
liked the construction
she did with these visors.
From back to front,
it all went together.
And then she lost me
by putting a cone on her head
covered in tin foil.
It took me out of fashion
and into costuming,
and I didn't want to see that.
I wanted to remain
in the fashion sphere.
I would have loved for her
to connect the dots, per se.
I thought it was moderate
plaque psoriasis.
[all laugh]
There's a pill for that.
At least it was interesting.
At least it was something
I hadn't really seen before.
Now, if she does that
every week,
of course
we're gonna read her for that.
But I want to see
what she's gonna do next week.
Mayhem Miller.
I loved just the boldness
and the fearlessness.
She knew
what she was here to do,
and she executed it flawlessly.
I love
when a queen's time comes
right when the stars align,
and it's happening
for Mayhem.
But now she set herself up.
Can she deliver
at that level every week?
Vanessa Vanjie Mateo.
She's in your face,
and I love that.
What I didn't love
was everything else.
She's wearing like flowers
that are all pastels,
and she has sparkly rhinestones
and Barbie dolls.
And then she's like...
[deep voice]
Yeah, I caught a bitch. Like--
I love that dichotomy.
We've seen these queens
who we love
who don't necessarily
have the taste level yet
evolve and mature.
I just hope she's around
to get there.
Yuhua Hamasaki.
She did have beautiful
movement with the dress.
It was kind of predictable
in the sense
that we've seen it, you know,
a few times before.
But I think what I fell in love
with this girl about
was her personality.
She seems to really know
who she is
or at least thinks she does.
But will she have the talent
to back it up?
If she doesn't,
things are gonna get ankh-ward.
[laughs]
Shut up, Ross!
Miz Cracker.
I love how she constructed
the look.
I thought it was kind of
a complicated look to build.
She's very interesting.
She's very cerebral.
Whenever she started speaking,
she was so articulate
about everything she had to say.
She's the Serena Williams
of one-liners.
Every time you threw
something out, she hit back.
She is a weirdo,
and that's
what I love about her.
And she's funny.
- And smart.
Okay.
Michelle want a cracker?
Yes, please,
and my goal is to--
[clap clap]
Silence!
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Miz Cracker.
You're safe.
Blair St. Clair.
Mayhem Miller.
Mo glove, mo love.
Con-drag-ulations.
You're the winner
of this week's challenge.
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
You've won
a luxury Hawaiian getaway
to the Hale Mohalu
Guesthouse and Retreat.
Thank you.
I won the first challenge
of RuPaul's Drag Race
Season 10.
It is amazing.
Yuhua Hamasaki.
You are safe.
Thank you, Mama Ru.
Dusty Ray.
Your topper just might
land you in the bottom.
Kalorie Karbdashian Williams.
You're dripping in dollars,
but you didn't make it rain.
Vanessa Vanjie Mateo.
You're a doll,
but your body was overpowered
by a field of flowers.
Dusty Ray Bottoms.
You're safe.
Thank you.
You may join the other girls.
Kalorie, Vanessa,
I'm sorry, my dears,
but you are up for elimination.
Two queens stand before me.
Prior to tonight,
you were asked
to prepare
a lip-sync performance
of "Ain't No Other Man"
by Christina Aguilera.
Ladies,
this is your last chance
to impress me, save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip-sync...
[echoing] for your life!
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
♪ Yeah ♪
D-d-do your thang, honey!
♪ I could feel it
from the start ♪
♪ Couldn't stand to be apart ♪
♪ Something 'bout ya
caught my eye ♪
♪ Something moved me
deep inside ♪
♪ I don't know what ya did,
boy, but you had it ♪
♪ And I've been hooked
ever since ♪
♪ Told my mother, my brother ♪
♪ My sister and my friends ♪
♪ Told the others, my lovers ♪
♪ Both past and present tense ♪
♪ That every time I see you ♪
♪ Everything
starts making sense ♪
D-d-do your thang, honey!
♪ Ain't no other man ♪
♪ Can stand up next to you ♪
♪ Ain't no other man... ♪
[Vanessa] I'm a big
Christine Aguilera fan,
so I said,
bitch, go ham and cheese,
dish it up, and you better
give it buffet style.
♪ Ain't no other man,
it's true ♪
♪ Ain't no other man but you ♪
Break it down now.
♪ Ain't no other ♪
♪ Ain't, ain't
no other, other ♪
♪ Ain't no other ♪
♪ Ain't, ain't
no other lover ♪
♪ Ain't no other man
but you, oh ♪
♪ You are there
when I'm a mess ♪
♪ Talk me down
from every ledge... ♪
I swear to you, Vanessa,
you better watch it, girl.
'Cause I'm coming.
I'm gonna give you a fight.
♪ You're the only one
who's ever passed every test ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
[Monique] She pulled out
that money, and I had my life.
Make it rain!
♪ Does what you do ♪
♪ You're the kind of guy ♪
♪ You got soul,
you got class ♪
♪ You got style,
you're bad ass ♪
♪ Don't you know ♪
♪ Ain't no other man,
it's true ♪
♪ Ain't no other man but you ♪
[cheers and applause]
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Kalorie. Shante, you stay.
[sobs]
You may join the other girls.
Vanessa Vanjie Mateo.
You've done your house proud,
and I have just one thing
to say.
Bam!
Now sashay away.
[cheers and applause]
Miss Vanjie. Miss Vanjie.
Miss Vanjie.
- Bye, girl.
- Bye, sister.
[cheers and applause]
Walk the runway!
To go home first
is the worst.
I wish I could have
been here longer.
[sobs]
I feel like I've let Alexa down.
I hope I didn't disappoint her.
Con-drag-ulations, ladies.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen in here?
- Amen!
Can I get an amen, Christina?
♪ Amen ♪
[cheering]
All right!
Now let the music play!
Whoo!
♪ To-to-to to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Ain't gonna take me away ♪
♪ To-to-to to the moon ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ Hey, kitty girl ♪
♪ It's your world ♪
♪ When you walk the street,
steppin' to the beat ♪
♪ Hey, kitty girl ♪
♪ Get your twirl ♪
♪ In the disco heat ♪
♪ You're the
boogie-body-rockin' queen ♪
♪ Hey, kitty kitty ♪
♪ Hey, here, kitty kitty ♪
♪ Hey, kitty kitty girl ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh ♪