- Previously
- On "RuPaul's Drag Race..."
You need to create
your own Drag Con panels.
[cheers and applause]
- I am trying to focus
- On that T.
[all laugh]
- I'm a wig-aholic.
- You wouldn't know
by looking at you.
- Oh.
- Hairlines are what
can look really masculine
- or go really femuline...
- Feminine. Femuline.
- Eureka.
- You are setting the tone.
You did such a great job.
- I said that. Vixen.
- It was just in Yiddish
- A mishegas.
- We were very confident,
and they're like, fine,
we don't need a moderator.
- Actually, you would have
benefited from a moderator.
That was the real issue.
Eureka, you are the winner
of this week's challenge.
[applause]
- The Vixen, shantay, you stay.
Blair St. Clair, I do declare.
Sashay away.
- Sisters.
Vixen, you're here!
- That is not fun at all.
"Let me be your star."
- I'm gonna miss Blair so much.
- She's been one of the most
- Genuine sweet people
I've ever met.
- I am more than happy
to live another day,
- but I'm scared,
- Because I'm giving my drag,
and it feels like the judges
just don't get me.
- Congratulations on your win.
- Oh, yeah. Okay.
- Oh, yeah.
- Well, this win
is for my twin sister,
- because the video tonight
- In "Untucked" reminded me, yeah,
she's the strength
that I wish that I had, so...
- Let's just get the elephant
out of the room.
I know you were shocked.
- Absolutely.
- You was gagged.
- I was really trying
to like make peace
with, okay, you could go home
right now.
And I started thinking about all
the queens that look up to me,
like, I see myself in her.
- Y'all think
- I don't hold back now,
- y'all should...
- Y'all in trouble, 'cause...
- But one thing's for sure.
You care about these people
that you're a role model to.
Keep that in your mind
during this competition.
You have a level
of intelligence
and a level of love and passion
- that doesn't always have
- To be the bite from the bear.
You can show that love
and be, you know, the...
- Well, thank you so much
- For bringing that up.
Even the bear is a part
of why people look up to me,
- because
- That is being 100% honest.
- I've seen The Vixen use
- Her anger for fire and for fuel,
but you've got to know
when to leave it alone
and when to use it
for the greater good.
- I'm okay being safe,
but I'm at that middle road
where I go, bitch,
I know I'm stunning,
I know I'm talented,
- and I feel like it's the clothes
- That I have with me
that are not putting me forward.
My issue coming in is money.
My look probably
wasn't the strongest.
Was it probably
the most creative?
- Yeah, maybe, with
- The materials that I had
- in making a costume
- Literally in 30 minutes.
- Thank God
we're addressing this problem,
I don't have a lot
of fucking money,
but you know what?
I make things work.
And to see Monique literally
as we're walking up the stairs
to the runway,
she is gluing on sequins.
I love her to death, but you
just have to step your pussy up
a little bit more than that.
- You have been safe or better
- on outfits that
- You made in 30 minutes.
So that must mean that you have
something really big going on
- to make up
- For this hemless outfit.
Take it as a compliment.
- America, I may sew
at the last minute,
but my shit is right.
This mug is always right.
The hair always matches.
- And the bitch's personality
- Is right.
But you know what?
Bitch, if I am safe
all the way up
and then I win the damn crown...
I'll take my check.
[laughs]
- The winner
- Of "RuPaul's Drag Race"
receives a one-year supply
- of Anastasia Beverly Hills
- Cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100,000.
With extra special
guest judges Audra McDonald
and Kate Upton.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman ♪
- ♪ Best woman win ♪
- ♪ Cookie monster ♪
- Whoo!
- It is a randy day
in the workroom,
and I'm ready to hopefully
win a challenge this week.
- 'Cause I feel that
- The gods are on my side,
- and I'm ready to take over,
- Darling.
[alarm]
- Whoo, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
Hey, queens.
- Hey.
- It's not about who you know.
It's about who you do.
And I'm not talking about
that thing with Carrot Top.
That was a long time ago.
- I was young,
- And he needed the money.
[all laugh]
Hello, hello, hello.
[cheers and applause]
- Yeah.
- Ladies,
as the department of education
continues to make
deep budget cuts,
we are doubling down
to our commitment
to teach the children
how to read.
[cheers and applause]
- The library
- Is officially open.
- Yes.
- [cheers and applause]
Because reading is what?
All: Fundamental.
- That's right.
- First up, Kameron Michaels.
- Whoo, come on, Kameron.
- Here you are, darling.
- [clears throat]
Eureka, we found it.
Girl, how could we miss it?
[all laugh]
Miss Monet X Change.
Ru, just an exchange?
I would have asked
for a full refund.
[all laugh]
- The Villain.
- I mean, The Vixen.
[all laugh]
I really think it's so fierce
that back in Chicago
- you have that show
- Called "Black Girl Magic."
- Now can you show me a
- Magic trick and just disappear?
[all laugh]
- Monique Heart,
- You've got a heart of gold,
- the voice of an angel,
- And a hairline
that looks like it's been
fucked with a weedwhacker.
[all laugh]
- Oh, my God.
- The Vixen,
- You told us from day one
you are here to fight.
Sweetheart, why don't you
fight some of those wigs
with some soap and water?
[all laugh]
Aquaria, God's gift to makeup.
So sorry God didn't bless you
with the gift of a personality.
[all laugh]
- Kameron Michaels, I don't
really have a read for you.
Please, just fuck me.
[all laugh]
Please, just fuck me!
- Aquaria,
- I love you confidence.
You're always telling yourself
how you're beautiful,
how you're talented,
how you're gonna win.
You're also a pathological liar.
[all laugh]
The Vixen, do you have
a housekeeper, girl?
Your kitchen is a mess.
[all laugh]
Thank you all so much.
- I can't wait to hear your reads
- About me being fat.
[all laugh]
- You won't have to wait long.
- [laughs]
- Eureka O'Hara, I know
you've probably seen "Dumbo"
like a thousand times.
But it doesn't matter
how big you paint these wings.
You are staying
on the ground, bitch.
[all laugh]
- Aquaria,
- People don't appreciate
- how much money
- You have to spend on makeup
when you're covering two faces.
- Ooh.
- [laughs]
- Kameron Michaels, I think
I speak for all the girls here
when I say we're really
gonna miss you next week.
- Ooh!
- Eureka O'Hara,
- Stop relying on that body fat.
[all laugh]
- Miss The Vixen, though
your tumbles are stunning,
your hair gives me tumbleweed.
[all laugh]
- Monet X Change, girl,
- You know better to be black
using hotel lotion.
[all laugh]
- Asia O'Hara,
- You are the Amazon queen.
You get your tights from Amazon,
- you get some of your outfits
- From Amazon,
and apparently
they sell teeth, too.
[all laugh]
And Miz Cracker.
- You coin yourself
- As thin, white, and salty,
but you're forgetting bitter.
Bitter that you are
a near titty queen
- that had to fuck Bob the
- Drag Queen to get to the top.
[all laugh]
- [laughs]
- And that's shade.
- All right, ladies.
- The library
- Is officially closed.
[applause]
The winner of today's
mini challenge is...
Eureka.
[cheers and applause]
Con-drag-ulations.
You've won a $2,000 gift card
from l.a. Eyeworks.
- Don't be jealous
- Of all this weight, honey.
- 'Cause y'all
- Are waiting to win some.
- Waiting for you to go home.
- All right, ladies.
- Time to show me
- How far you can stretch
- your charisma, uniqueness,
- Nerve, and talent.
- Because for this week's
- Maxi challenge,
we're playing the Snatch Game.
[cheers and applause]
- I am so glad and proud
- To have made it to Snatch Game.
This is a mile marker.
Everybody wants to be here.
- Pick a celebrity
to impersonate,
and make me laugh my blank off.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[cheers and applause]
- Hello, RuPaul.
My name is Maya Angelou.
- Oh, my God, this week
- Is the Snatch Game.
- It is the greatest show
- I've ever seen.
- It's almost like Christmas
- For drag queens.
- What do you have planned?
- I'm going to be Chyna,
- The wrestler.
- What is Chyna's voice like?
- It's very, like, high pitched,
like up here.
[laughs]
- You sound like a ho-man.
- So you're definitely
doing Miss Blue Ivy?
- Yeah. And like
- who's more Black Girl Magic
- Than Blue Ivy?
- Just off her
- Facial expressions alone,
- I have this whole personality
- Of what I think she is.
- The thing about Blue
- Is we don't know how she talks.
But I get a kick
out of all the memes.
Her face is always telling you
that she is not
in the mood for it,
and I relate to that.
- Hey, kitty girls.
We've got company.
[cheers and applause]
- Yeah!
- Bianca del Rio is here
to lead us all
in a peaceful group mediation.
- Baloney.
I'm here to say everything
hateful that RuPaul won't.
[all laugh]
- Oh, my God,
- It was Bianca del Rio.
Her Judge Judy is legendary.
Probably one of the best Snatch
Games in Drag Race history.
It's just really cool
to have Bianca here
to give us some solid advice.
- Well, hello, Eureka.
- Hello. How are you?
- Meet Bianca del Rio.
- Hi, Bianca.
- There's a lot of stuff here.
- Yeah.
- I see a little doggy
- Over there.
- Right. This is Devine,
and this is Honey Boo Boo.
- Have you done
- Either of those before?
- As far as Devine, I actually
- Find a lot of inspiration
from her character for Eureka
the character herself.
- Because she wasn't afraid
- To be ridiculous.
I'm not afraid to be silly
and ridiculous, either.
- That's important.
- Can I hear a little bit
of your impersonation?
- Filth. Filth is my life.
- I am Devine.
- Condone cannibalism.
Kill everyone.
- Blood.
- I love the taste of it.
Hot, freshly killed blood.
- Okay, now do Devine.
[all laugh]
- That was Devine.
- If you have to tell us,
- It wasn't convincing.
- Yeah. Okay.
- Honey Boo Boo is really funny.
I mean, that show alone,
- I always say,
- It's on the Learning Channel,
and it just shows you
what you don't wanna be.
- [laughs]
- But it is quite amusing.
I mean, the child is hysterical.
- Yeah.
- I don't know
- If she realizes she's funny
- or if it's just the inbreeding,
- But it's really amusing.
- I'm just a little torn.
- You've seen
- How Snatch Game works.
You've got to go
for what you know
and go for the jugular.
I can't wait
to see you out there.
- Make me laugh.
- I will do my best.
- Okay.
- Trust me.
- See you later.
Well, hello, Monique Heart.
- Hello, Mama Ru.
- Meet Bianca.
- Hi.
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
So I thought I wanted
to do Maxine Waters.
- I mean, she's very much
- Against Trump
and getting him out of office.
- And she's right,
which makes it good.
- Boom.
But I auditioned
with Cookie Lyon.
- From the TV show "Empire."
- So I don't know.
- I mean,
- I don't watch "Empire,"
so I'm unfamiliar with
the character of Cookie.
But Maxine just seems like
the obvious choice in my world.
- I think her only strong point
- Was "reclaiming my time."
- Are you not familiar
with her other slogans?
- She has a few that I know.
- Not that many.
Now I'm drawing a blank
- because I'm feeling
- The pressure right now.
- That's the game.
- So if I asked you a question,
can you answer me back
as Maxine Waters?
- Yes.
- Madam Congresswoman,
- what is on the lunch menu
- For today?
- On the lunch menu today, Ru,
we're having greens, beans,
tomatoes, yams, collard greens,
you name it and I'll have it.
- No?
- Oh.
- I was thrown off
by the soft-spoken.
- Well, she has this really
kind of Clair Huxtable voice
where she hits these highs
and lows when she talks.
- That ain't funny.
Make it funny, bitch.
- You've got to sell it.
- Uh...
- All right. I'm gonna
ask you another question,
Madam Congresswoman.
Could you be friends with Trump?
- I surely couldn't be friends
- with Donald Trump's
- Little orange Cheeto ass.
- [laughs]
That's what I'm talking about.
- Sell it.
- Trust your gut.
- Mother Ru
- Gets me right together.
- It's reclaiming my time,
- Reclaiming my time.
Maxine Waters it is.
Time to give it to the children.
- Hey, Asia.
- Hey.
- Meet Bianca del Rio.
- Hi.
- Very nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- So what are you thinking?
- My first choice
is Whitney Houston.
- Oh, I love Whitney Houston.
- So do I.
- Have you done Whitney
- In your act?
- I do it in my shows
- All the time.
- And when you do it
- In your act,
does it also involve
powdered sugar?
- It has in the past.
- I see, which we're probably
- Going to stay away from.
- It's not gonna work.
- I don't feel like
- I can make Whitney funny
without the whole drug thing.
- Now, you have
a strong Texas accent.
Have you thought of doing
a famous Texas person?
- Beyoncé.
It has been done,
but I can do her voice
- and I know what's funny
- And what's not funny about her.
- So I'm gonna ask you
- A question.
- So, Beyoncé, when's
- The next album coming out?
- Well, Ru, my team and I have
been working on some things,
and when we know, you'll know.
- That was not funny at all.
- [all laugh]
- Oh, you're killing me.
- Well, either she tells you now
- Or you find out later.
- So Beyoncé. Any others?
- Maybe one of the ex-members
- Of Destiny's Child.
That would be funny.
- Um, that's all.
- But we knew
- This was coming up.
- I mean, Snatch Game is kind of
- Like a Drag Race staple.
- [sighs]
I am upside down
hanging from my toenails now.
I still do not know
what the hell I'm about to do
for Snatch Game.
- All right, so you've got
your work cut out for you.
- Absolutely.
Oh, Jesus, be with me.
- Well, hello, Miz Cracker.
- Hello, Ru.
- Now, I see
- You have a pussy bow
- on your fabulous fit form
- Over there.
- Yes, I do.
- The blouse.
And I see black hair.
- Would it be Edith Head?
- No, I'm looking
for Dorothy Parker.
- Oh.
- She is an icon of comedy
- And the one-liner,
- which is where I live
- In my comedy.
- Now, many people at home
won't know who that is.
- Yeah, and what solves it
is that she makes everything
dark, everything funny,
everything turns into an insult.
- Sounds like me.
- [laughs]
- I didn't want to...
- I was trying not to look at you
when I said that.
- Most people
- Try not to look at me.
- [laughs]
- She wasn't ever really gross.
- It was just taking a nice thing
- That someone said to her
and bending it backwards
and jabbing them with it.
- Well, it is quite
a challenge, though,
because it's the kind of humor
that your receivers
have to think about.
It's not like, oh, ha-ha-ha.
So therein lies the challenge.
- But I wanna go
- With something that I love
that feels like
it is absolutely me.
- Because last week,
- Even though I was playing,
I came off as mean
to other people.
- It's not easy.
This is really challenging.
- But you've got to make it
- Entertaining.
- Right.
- I mean, that's the main thing.
- All right, Miz Cracker.
- Make me laugh.
- Thank you, guys.
- Aquaria.
- Hi, RuPaul.
- Hi.
- Bianca del Rio.
- It's so nice to see you.
- It's nice to see you.
- Now I see a gorgeous
little dress with a necklace.
There's a Tiffany box.
- I'm getting with the Tiffany
box, Melania Trump.
- Yep.
- All right.
Do you consider yourself funny?
- You know, I don't
consider myself funny,
but I think my humor
- comes from a very
- Confused place in my brain.
- [laughs]
- I don't get my words right.
- I don't form sentences
- Very well.
- Well, it works
for our president.
- Yeah.
- [laughs]
- So I'm trying to play that up
with Melania.
- Yeah, I feel like words
- Get tripped up
because you're thinking about
- how you might be perceived
- By other people.
- I mean, in such
a tight competition,
- you have to be mindful
- Of your words,
- especially being popular online
- And stuff like that.
- Well, the thing is,
- When you watch "Drag Race,"
the realest people are really
the ones you gravitate to.
- When you take a Latrice,
- Everybody's like, I love her.
Adore is another one.
It's those people that are
really their true selves.
- But you just need
- To trust your instincts.
- Mm-hmm.
- I think that's most important.
- Yeah, I mean,
I really can't form a sentence
most of the time.
- That's all right.
You're consistent.
- Hey.
- That's important.
- I definitely know
that my strengths lie
in my look turning.
But this is a great opportunity
- to show that not only
- Am I great at being myself,
but I can also do
a stupid silly job
- of being
- Another great celebrity.
Catch that?
- All right, listen up, ladies.
Make a splash,
and don't fuck it up.
- Yes, Mrs. Charles.
- Let's go have a drink.
- Let's do it.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- What'd you end up deciding on?
- I guess I'm doing Beyoncé.
- Beyoncé?
- I decided to do Beyoncé
because although it's not
something I brought with me,
- it's something
- That I can pull together.
- And The Vixen
- Is doing Blue Ivy Carter,
so if I'm stuck, there's
another person on the panel
I know I can have banter with
and play off of.
- Gotcha.
- Beyoncé has been crucified
on the Snatch Game twice before,
and Asia is gonna try
to resurrect her
for the third time?
All right, girl.
- I'll wait to play off of you
until you've like really
established your character.
- I'm nervous.
Facts are facts.
Beyoncé really doesn't have
personality that we get to see.
- Blue Ivy, just like her mother,
- Has no personality
as of yet.
So...
we gonna pray.
- Welcome to Snatch Game.
Let's meet our contestants.
She's a Tony, Grammy,
and Emmy award winner.
Audra McDonald,
welcome to the show.
- Thank you.
- I'm so excited to be here.
- Who knows, maybe you'll even
- Get an Oscar for this.
- Fingers are crossed.
- And she's graced the cover
of "Sports Illustrated's"
swimsuit issue three times.
It's Kate Upton.
- Hi. I'm so excited
- To be here.
- Oh, we're excited to have you.
Are you ready to meet our stars?
- Yes.
- Okay, here we go.
- Washington DC's HBIC,
Congresswoman Maxine Waters.
- Hello, Ru.
- May I call you Auntie Maxine?
- You surely can.
- You've got your
"impeach Trump" there.
- Impeach Trump.
He has to go.
The Cheeto has to go.
Say it with me.
- Okay. All right.
Up next.
[bell dings]
Professional wrestler
and bodybuilder Chyna.
Hey, Chyna.
- Hi, Ru.
- Wow, you're looking good.
- Do you have
- Any workout tips for me?
- Eating all the beef, Ru.
- [laughs]
All right. Literary icon,
the original shady lady
Dorothy Parker is here.
- Hello, Ru.
- I love spending an evening
making jokes with smart
and beautiful people,
so you can imagine
how disappointed I am.
[all laugh]
- Up next,
- She woke up like this.
It is Beyoncé.
- What's your name?
- I'm RuPaul.
- Who-Paul?
- Uh-huh. RuPaul.
- Well, I'm glad
to be here with you.
- All right, moving right along.
- Author, actress,
- And a national treasure,
Maya Angelou.
- Hello, RuPaul.
Do you know why
the caged bird sings?
- I've always wanted to know.
Why does the caged bird sing?
- Because Mariah Carey
- Lost the key.
[all laugh]
- Oh, the shade coming from
Miss Maya Angelou this evening.
- All right, the First Lady
- Of the United States of America,
Melania Trump is here.
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Now, RuPaul,
- I did bring you a gift.
- Oh. Oh, is this from
where I think it's from?
- Trinity's.
I love Trinity's.
Let's see what we got here.
Oh, this is lovely.
- I hope it fits.
- Thank you so much.
All right, up next,
Destiny's Grandchild, Blue Ivy
is here with us this evening.
Hi, Blue Ivy.
- Hi.
- You look lovely.
- Is that from
- The House of Dereon?
- This is couture.
- No, it's not.
That's OshKosh B'gosh.
- You're so tall.
- Yes, I am.
- Okay, shut up now, girl.
Shut up now. Hush now, hear?
- Uh-oh. Mama has spoken.
Up next, another gorgeous child.
Mama June's pride and joy
Honey Boo Boo is here.
- Oh, my God, hi.
I'm Alana. I'm six.
And I'm a beauty queen.
- Yes, you are a beauty queen.
- Have you competed
- In any pageants lately?
- Well, the last pageant
- I competed in
- was Miss Trailer Park 2015,
- And I won.
- Oh, good for you.
- I won.
- Oh, you are a winner,
- Honey Boo Boo.
- I am always a wiener.
- [all laugh]
- I'm sitting on the lucky side
of the room.
I have a grown woman
and an overgrown woman.
- Oh, how lucky
for Dorothy Parker.
All right, now, here we go.
Kate, did you hear about the new
Smart Phone for drag queens?
Instead of face recognition,
it recognizes your blank.
Looks like Beyoncé is writing.
- This is the first time
- Beyoncé's ever written
- For herself.
- Watch it, Toots.
- All right, Kate Upton.
- Charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent.
- Oh, that's a great answer.
- Let's see if you matched
- Any of the stars.
Maya Angelou, Maya Angelou,
new Smart... are you asleep?
- No, sorry.
- I was resting my eyes.
- I see. Okay.
Did you hear about the new
Smart Phone for drag queens?
Instead of face recognition,
it recognizes your...
- Well, RuPaul,
- I've written 17 books, 19 plays,
13 autobiographies
and two Hallmark cards.
- And it recognizes
- You're a phenomenal woman.
- Yes.
- Almost. Let's move on down
to Honey Boo Boo in the house.
We're looking for charisma,
uniqueness, nerve and talent.
- What did you write down,
- Darling?
- I really don't know
- How to write,
so just I just drew pictures.
My mama said if I don't know
what to do, just start drawing.
So I put like a star,
because I'm a star.
And I put my baby puppy,
- because that's
- A puppy right there.
- Let's go on over
to Auntie Maxine.
Did you hear about the new
Smart Phone for drag queens?
Instead of face recognition,
it recognizes your...
- Tuck touch.
- That's a very smart idea.
I think you should patent that,
- and maybe
- Bring it up in Congress.
- I'll bring it up in Congress,
- and then I'll bring it up
- At Drug Can.
- At where where?
- Drag Con.
- Poor woman
- Can barely speak English.
What a disgusting...
- Aren't you dead?
- Like dust, still I rise.
- [all laugh]
- What's a tuck?
- Ask your mama.
- Mom, mama, mama.
- What's my name?
What's my name?
- Your highness?
- Continue.
- Reclaiming my time.
- Please tell your granny
to shut her mouth.
- Reclaiming my time.
- See, let me
- Let you know something.
- Oh, oh, it's starting
- Already up in here.
- Stop looking at me like that.
You're making me nervous.
- Beyoncé, you seem
- A little hostile today.
- You have to be on guard
- With these bitches,
claiming that I didn't write
my music and stuff.
- Mama, you said a bad word.
- Shut your mouth.
- I did not know Beyoncé
was that kind of mother.
- Somebody needs to call CPS
- For her girl,
because that is not cute.
- All right, this next one's
for Audra McDonald.
Martha Stewart is a really
bad influence on Snoop Dogg.
Now when he makes brownies,
he puts blank in them.
- He puts parsley, sage,
- Rosemary, and thyme.
- "Scarborough Fair."
It's a really good song.
Sounds like some awful brownies.
- Yes.
- Okay, let's go on down
- to the First Lady
- Of the United States of America.
[mispronouncing]
Me-lane-ia Trump.
- Melania.
- Melania, Melania. Sorry.
- It's all right, Barack.
- No worries.
[all laugh]
- I went with
- Russian hooker urine.
- It has a funny smell,
but it just the right kick.
- That's an unusual answer.
What made you think of that?
- I don't know.
- My husband does the same thing,
- so I figured that the Snoop Dogg
- Would probably love it.
[all laugh]
- All right, Chyna.
- Yes, look at those guns.
- My goodness.
We're looking for parsley,
sage, rosemary, and thyme.
Did we have a match?
- [deep voice]
- I said testosterone.
[all laugh]
- I ate a whole pan.
- Yeah.
- Got my estrogen levels
- A little low, so...
- Oh. Okay.
Not a bad idea to put
testosterone in your brownies.
- My husband
- Could use some as well.
[all laugh]
- Okay, Blue Ivy.
- My mama don't make brownies.
- My mama don't cook.
- She's rich.
But when she gives me lunch
money, she calls it royalties.
- Royalties.
- Unfortunately, not a match.
- I wanna go home.
- Everybody's old and poor...
- And fat.
- Your mama.
[all laugh]
- Vixen has made
a daring choice.
I knew it could go either way,
- and right now
- I see it going only south.
- How cunning is this fox
- After all?
- All right, let's move on down
- To Maya Angelou.
- Well, RuPaul, before
I answer the question,
these women seem very hostile,
- and I wrote a soliloquy
- To inform them.
- Oh, I'd love to hear it.
We have nothing but time here.
- If these hos
try to come for me,
I surely will cut thee.
- I will not hesitate
- To put thou in a ditch,
because Maya Angelou
ain't no punk bitch.
- [all laugh]
- Oh, it rhymes, it rhymes.
- All right, but did you write
- An answer to this?
- I would put my underwire
- In a brownie,
because I don't have
any support here.
- Oh, underwire.
Unfortunately, Audra,
it's not a match.
- It's still not a match,
- But it's good.
- All right, our next question
is for Kate,
and it is our Gaily Double.
It's a video question.
- Hi, everyone.
I'm Alex Trebek,
and I'm putting together a
brand new version of "Jeopardy!"
just for drag queens.
- Instead of answering
- In the form of a question,
- the queens must now respond
- With a blank.
- Well, thank you, Alex.
That's a great question.
All right, Kate Upton.
- Instead of answering
- In the form of a question,
the queens answer with a blank.
- With a death drop.
- That is a great answer.
I would watch that show.
Let's see what Congresswoman
Maxine Waters...
Now, what district are you in?
- The 43rd.
- Is that Compton?
- [laughs]
- Actually I think it is.
It's probably Inglewood
or something like that.
- It surely is.
We... I'm the 12th...
one of the 12 women
that are in the Black Caucus.
We're really involved
in the black community,
trying to raise us up.
- Okay. All right.
- So we're looking for death drop,
- All right?
What do you have,
Congresswoman?
- I have Honey Boo Boo
eating President Cheeto.
- Okay, Honey Boo Boo eating
President Cheeto.
All right, I'm afraid that's
not a match, Congresswoman.
Let's move on down
to Honey Boo Boo.
Maybe she's got the match.
- Well, again, I just
kind of drew pictures.
- But whenever
- I really don't know,
and I'm in a sticky situation,
- I just draw a smiley face
- On my belly, and I talk with it.
I'm Honey Boo Boo, y'all.
- That sounds like a match.
- That's a death drop
in its own way.
- It's a match.
- I won? I win? I win?
- No, she gets a point.
- Oh, you're welcome.
- All right.
Here's our fourth and final
question for Audra McDonald.
Lady Bunny's therapist
said she was going crazy.
- She said,
- I want a second opinion.
- He said, okay,
- You're also a blank.
- You're also
- A thousand years old.
- [laughs]
- The truth hurts.
All right, let's move on down
to Dorothy Parker.
What did Lady Bunny's therapist
also say?
- Well, I want to say
very quickly, Audra,
I hear you have
a swimsuit issue?
- No, darling.
That's Kate.
- I have one, as well.
It's that no one
wants to see me in one.
- Now the answer to your question,
- I believe,
- is something that me
- And Lady Bunny have in common.
She's an antique.
- That's a match.
- Yes.
- All right, let's go on down
- to our First Lady,
- Melania Trump.
What say you?
- I think this Snatch Game
- Was a bit rigged.
- Oh, was it?
You think?
- I haven't won any points.
- You haven't won any...
- That's because you didn't
have to suck to get any.
- All right.
Now, you still have
a chance, darling.
I said, Lady Bunny
is a wonderful entertainer,
a humble queen,
and she keeps the show going
and is a handsome
and smart gentleman.
[all laugh]
- Close?
- So close, but not a match,
- I'm afraid.
- Any hole is a goal.
- What did you say?
[all laugh]
- My mother used to tell me that
- When I was little.
- Clearly it worked.
- All right,
- Let's go down to Chyna.
Lady Bunny's therapist
said, okay, you're also a...
- Well, I think we have
two things in common.
- A right answer, and another
- Old whore right here.
- An old whore.
- I think that's probably a match.
It is a match.
- No wonder why my husband's
- complaining about Chyna
- All the time.
[all laugh]
- Let's move on down
- To Beyoncé Knowles-Carter.
- Boo Boo, do me a favor.
- Close your ears for a second.
I said that she is a woman
whose husband cheated on her
- and she wrote
- An entire album about it.
And y'all thought she was joking
- and then I still made a whole
- Bunch of money off of it,
so it don't even matter.
It's a match.
Continue.
- Mother!
- I told you to close your ears.
- Oh, okay.
- I knew that was about you.
- Okay. All right. Right.
Unfortunately not a match. No.
Let's move on down
to Honey Boo Boo.
Maybe she's got the match.
- I drew a picture of a bunny.
- Oh, you did, didn't you?
- I'm such an artist.
- RuPaul, that's exactly why
I fight for the arts
in school education.
- Yes, it's very important.
- I'm home schooled.
[all laugh]
- Wow. What a game.
But the winner is...
me, because I get to go home
and watch Judge Judy.
- Baloney.
- Here she is.
- Why wait until 4 P.M., Ru?
- I'm here.
- Well, that's our show.
Remember, "uh" is not an answer.
By-ee.
- Reclaiming my time.
[cheers and applause]
- Yeah!
- Get in there.
- Sitting on a zero.
- Yeah!
- Today's elimination day,
and everyone is snatched
after Snatch Game, honey.
There are no edges in sight.
♪ noonehasedges.
- It doesn't matter
who did well and who did not.
It was traumatic.
- I know.
- Wish Melania would have
- Bantered with me,
because I gave her
plenty of opportunity.
- Ooh.
- It's not my job
to make your Snatch Game good.
- Ooh.
- I'm just fucking with you.
You opened the door.
- Snatch Game has turned
- People upside down.
- Half of us
- Have not been to sleep.
Kameron is very quiet,
even more quiet than usual,
if you can imagine that.
- The stakes of what we're
- About to present to the judges
- are really high
- Because it may come down
to what we wear on the runway.
- Psst. Mama.
Ma. Mama.
- We're no longer related after
the catastrophe of yesterday.
- That's not nice.
How you think we did?
- Terrible.
- As a family?
- Yes.
- I would love to get
a positive critique.
I don't know how that feels.
- That's not going to happen.
- It's kind of random how we
both did, like, the little kids.
- Yeah.
- And we both get ready
beside each other.
- Honestly, Eureka, I don't know
how you're gonna take this,
- but I feel like
- You stepped on a lot of people,
and like, kind of took
their moment from them.
Do you hear me?
- Yeah, I hear you.
- I don't think you can blame me
- For that because...
- I'm not blaming you...
- I was just trying to chime in
- Like we're supposed to.
You know what I mean?
- But I think there's a level
of professionalism
- where you know
- When to hold back.
- Vixen is just pissed
- that Eureka did a good job
- In Snatch Game,
- and that she didn't shine
- As bright as her.
Eureka was very funny.
She was doing what she had to do
to let her presence be known.
I feel like if anything
Asia was the one
like pouncing on everyone
throughout the whole thing.
- Does anyone feel like they did
something political yesterday
- that, you know,
- Might come back at them?
- Maxine Waters is the auntie
that says whatever she wants
and can get away with it.
- So you.
- So, well, yeah.
- Do you do like
a lot of political numbers?
- I really don't.
- I do
- A lot of political numbers.
I feel like it's really
important to do them.
- I agree.
- Especially, you know,
- As drag queens,
- I feel like
- That's our call to duty.
- Yeah, to get
- The queer agenda out there.
- Exactly. All the shit
- Going down, girl.
- 'Cause in Denim and Diamonds,
I really thought about
doing homage to RuPaul,
and doing that confederate flag.
- Yeah.
- Oh, that would have been cute.
- But tensions were really,
really high in Kansas City,
and I just didn't want to
come back and just get shot.
I have really not done
a lot of political work
- because I live
- In a former slave state.
Where I work, African-Americans
were not even allow to walk on
until the late sixties,
early seventies.
So I'm very aware
of what's going on,
however, I have to kind of
make sure that I educate you,
- but make sure
- That my bills are paid.
- I do a lot
- Of political performances.
- Oh, yeah,
- You did say that.
- I wouldn't say
- That mine were humorous.
- Sometimes I just like to
- Throw it in white people's faces
that you know what you did.
- That's Vixen.
- I like carry like
- A giant crucifix on stage
covered in like racial slurs.
And then I'll like beat it
until it's like broken.
- There's two ways I could see
white people reacting to that.
Either A, completely silent,
or B, like, applauding
as hard as they can
to like get rid of
their white guilt.
- Which one is the one
- That you get?
- Exactly. I usually get
the white guilt applause.
They're like, yes!
- I think that's probably
- Why I don't
because I hate dealing
with the white guilt.
Like white fragility
really bugs me.
- But you can make
- Some cute coin off of it
if you play it right.
A lot of people say drag should
only be an escape from reality.
- But drag can also help us
- Face reality
and deal with it.
What set me off and like
really took me on that path
was after the Pride parade,
this bartender was posting that
Southside trash ruined Pride,
- which basically means
- That black people ruined Pride.
- And so I just became
- Another queen
and just started speaking up.
And then I was like, let me
figure out who the underdogs are
and how I can help.
- It is hard being
- A black person in America.
It is hard being a black
gay person in America.
It is impossible being a black
gay drag queen in America.
And so I spend so much time
keeping my mouth shut
to get ahead
- that when I feel attacked,
- It all comes out.
- Vixen just
- Seems to be the girl
that has always had to defend
herself and defend her drag.
- It's like a dog
- You get from the shelter
that has been bitten
and beat and abused.
- And it's cool
- While you feeding it,
- but will bite you
- If you look at it crazy.
- It's quiet time.
- I hate quiet time.
- We know.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul laughs]
- ♪ Cover girl,
- Put the bass in your walk ♪
- ♪ Head to toe,
- Let your whole body talk ♪
[applause]
- Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
- Michelle Visage,
- You look snatched for the gods.
- Like Goldie Hawn
and Amy Schumer "Snatched?"
- You're obsessed
with that movie.
- It's my favorite focus
- Ever on a camera.
- [laughs]
Style superstar
Carson Kressley.
- Now, is there a celebrity
- You get mistaken for?
- Oh, yeah.
- Ruth Bader Ginsburg.
- But only
- When I wear all black.
[all laugh]
- And Cover Girl Kate Upton.
- Hi. I'm so excited
- To be here.
- We are so excited to have you.
And the gorgeous Audra McDonald.
- Now tell me.
- Did your six Tony awards
prepare you for the Snatch Game?
- Honey, not even a meditation
in a Zen garden with Buddha
would have prepared me
for the Snatch Game,
let me tell you.
- This week,
- We challenged our queens
- to serve their best
- Celebrity impersonations.
And tonight on the runway,
- as a salute
- To the divine Miss M,
category is Mermaid Fantasy.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
- ♪ I want you to remember me ♪
♪ Snap shot ♪
- First up, Monique Heart.
From Maxine Waters
to salty waters.
[all laugh]
- Not to be koi, mother darling,
but I am serving fishy fish
realness, honey.
- You know, getting rolled around
- By the Pit Crew
is not a bad gig.
I could get used to this,
but Jesus, I don't want nothing
to happen to my legs, girl.
I need to walk.
- Yes, honey, work that omega-3.
[all laugh]
- She got a fatty acid.
- Miz Cracker.
- Call her saltine now.
- I'm serving Barbie
fresh out of the box.
Happy to be there,
confused about why.
I'm giving you a little crown,
and beautiful plastic titties.
- What do you call them? Tits.
[all laugh]
- Those thingamabobs?
- Yes. I got 20s.
- Aquaria.
- This look brought to you
- By the Exxon Valdez.
- Black gold, Texas tea.
- I'm giving you
head-to-toe custom
- dripping in water
- And oil slick everything.
I have blue tears coming
directly out of my eyes.
I can't see anything
except for cyan.
- I'm giving
- The most lethargic mermaid,
but in the most editorial way.
- She's fin-ished.
[all laugh]
- Asia O'Hara.
- Ooh, from the Chernobyl Reef.
- Yes. Never go swimming
- In Love Canal.
[all laugh]
- No.
- I don't believe mermaids
in real life are pretty.
They're half woman, half fish.
So my mermaid look
- is inspired by lionfish
- Meets mermaid
meets a sea cucumber.
- Having fish and tits
- For dinner.
- Oh, yes.
I think Jason's making
the tartar sauce now.
[all laugh]
- Here's The Vixen.
- Well, it's obvious
she has clam-mydia.
[all laugh]
- My mermaid look is heavy metal
- And reflective.
I am spray painted.
I am sequins.
I am every girlie thing
that I would usually avoid.
But I just wanted
to feel full fantasy.
- She's looking
- For her friend Annette.
[all laugh]
- Monet X Change.
- Battlestar Gill-actica.
[all laugh]
- Tuna Turner.
- I'm giving you a beat up,
tattered warrior mermaid,
because I'm here to fight
these bitches to the top.
- Monet is a strong, powerful
- Warrior mermaid fish.
- You wanna talk about
the deadliest snatch?
- [all laugh]
- Stop polluting our oceans.
- Eureka.
- I think we're gonna need
- A bigger boat.
[all laugh]
- I'm giving you
the biggest, baddest,
most evil mermaid of them all.
I think everyone expects me
to be this colorful rainbow
Disney princess mermaid.
No, bitch.
- I am Ursula's cousin
- Twice removed,
- drooling blood
- Where I just ate my food.
- Don't forget to floss.
- Yeah.
- Kameron Michaels.
- Oh, it's one of
the Reef Housewives.
[all laugh]
- My mermaid is a little vain.
She's interested in herself
and nobody else.
I'm way too grand
to look for Nemo,
- because I'm only worried
- About myself.
She looks fishy
and she knows it.
- Touch this fin.
Touch all this fin.
[all laugh]
- Welcome, ladies.
- Based on your Snatch Game
- Performances,
and your splashy
main stage presentations,
I've made some decisions.
When I call your name,
please flap your tail.
Miz Cracker.
Kameron Michaels.
You are safe.
You may leave the stage.
- Well, actually you can't.
Oh, Pit Crew.
[all laugh]
Miss Vanjie.
- Miss Vanjie.
[all laugh]
Miss Vanjie.
- The way she was moving
- Backwards when she was doing it.
- It was just like, Miss Vanjie.
[all laugh]
- Girls.
- Woman named Miss Vanjie.
[all laugh]
- Ladies, you represent the tops
- And bottoms of the week.
- Ladies, it's time
- For the judges' critiques,
starting with Aquaria.
- I love this whole oil spill
- Chic mermaid.
I love the latex
dripping from the bodice,
- how the tail
- Is kind of tattered.
- it's so Italian "Vogue,"
- And I love the hair.
I'm obsessed with it.
- Thank you so much.
- You chose Melania.
- Yeah, I mean, Melania Trump
- is just as cold and aloof
- As I am,
- so I figured
- It would be a nice way
to use my weakness
to my advantage.
- I think you killed it.
- You gave us
- So many great references
- with the help in the box,
- And the Michelle Obama placard.
That was genius.
- For me, it was the subtle
things that you did.
- And when the focus
- Wasn't necessarily on you,
I kept going back to you anyway.
And I had to keep
reminding myself
- that's not really Melania Trump.
- [laughs]
- So I was just very impressed
- With everything you did,
- both the Snatch Game
- And tonight.
- Thank you.
- Up next, Monique Heart.
- ♪ Hi ♪
- I was really excited
for Maxine Waters,
but you didn't really
dig into who she was.
You had set bits,
but you weren't able
to carry that throughout it.
- And the kiss of death
in the Snatch Game
is not being present.
- I tried, but as soon
as anyone bantered,
it just became a cluster fuck.
- Which happens a lot,
which is another talent
of knowing when to interject
and when not to.
- Okay.
- And tonight on the runway,
I don't understand
what's happening.
I've got a look from here up,
and I've got a look
from here down.
The top up is kind of like
a bridal store thing for me.
- And this multicolored
- Glittery look,
- under the lights,
- It can just look a little cheap.
- This really sucks, because
I feel like week after week,
no matter what I do,
it's never what you want.
- This is a competition.
It's tough.
It ain't easy.
- No, ma'am.
- That's why
- Only the strong survive.
- Boom.
- Up next, Asia O'Hara.
- I'm dumbfounded
as to why we're wearing a mask
for a mermaid fantasy.
- Grasping at straws,
because I didn't feel
like when I got here,
I didn't feel like
this was enough.
- I kind of loved it,
because I've never thought
of a mermaid like that before.
I think the art is amazing,
and the outfit is fabulous.
- With the Snatch Game,
- I thought you looked beautiful,
- but I wished
- There had been more joy.
- Yeah.
- When did Beyoncé get so mean?
- Okay, shut up, now, girl.
- Shut up now.
- She's good old southern charm.
- Was there a reason
- Why you played her so mad?
- I didn't feel like the
- Sweet route was very comedic.
- When we did the walkthrough,
one of the clues I dropped
was the ex-members
of Destiny's Child.
- And then
- You could have been angry
- about why's Beyoncé
- Getting all the attention?
- But Beyoncé
- Don't need a reason
- because
- She's queen of the world.
In hindsight, do you get it now?
- Yes. Can we do it again?
[all laugh]
- Up next, The Vixen.
- The mermaid fantasy,
I want that wig.
- The neck up
- Is absolute perfection.
- But no one wants
- The breasts in the armpit.
- That's why we all wear them...
- A little bra.
- They're very far apart.
It takes the illusion away.
- I can see what you look like
- Out of drag.
- Oh.
- So, Blue Ivy,
- The outfit was adorable.
- I loved that
- She had the big old fro.
- But sorry, girl,
there was not much there.
- It needs to be more
- Than just a few moments.
There was not really
anywhere you could go
if you weren't going
completely over the top
like Honey Boo Boo.
- Being next to someone
who was being such a brat,
my mind went to like images
of Blue next to North West,
- and North West
- Is having a having a fit,
and Blue's like,
that's not how we behave.
- But it still wasn't funny.
- Up next, Monet X Change.
- This outfit is really cool.
It feels like Wonder Woman
meets the Little Mermaid.
- So, a shark... what... help me.
- Well, I am a warrior mermaid,
- fighting sharks
- And sea monsters and shit.
- I got more of like
- A littering political storyline.
- Oh, that, too.
- I meant to say that one.
- Sure. And want to talk
about doing your homework.
We had just had somebody do
Maya Angelou on "All Stars 3,"
- and this is how
- It should have been done.
- Thank you.
- All of the moments that
- You had as Maya were fantastic.
When you fell asleep,
and then to have the typical
black family response,
I was just resting my eyes.
[all laugh]
- Brilliant choice,
brilliant execution.
Monet is on a roll.
Keep it going.
- Thank you.
- Up next, Eureka.
- I love this Ursula
finds her inner leather mama.
My goodness.
I wanna look like that when
I go home to my husband tonight.
[all laugh]
- Alana was amazing.
- Oh, thank God.
- You just completely
- Embodied her.
You never broke character.
- You were very smart
to play a character
that you could really
rely on your strengths.
- And you were freaking funny.
You made Ru laugh.
You made the other people laugh.
- And it was really, really
- Well done.
- Thank you so much.
That means the world to me.
- All right, so, ladies,
I have one final question.
Who deserves to go home tonight?
And why?
Starting with Eureka.
- Oh, gosh.
Honestly, maybe Asia O'Hara,
because she's my biggest
competition, to be honest.
- Monet X Change.
- Taking into account
- Snatch Game
- and tonight's assignment
- Mermaid Eleganza,
I would have to say The Vixen.
- Vixen.
- I have never seen such
- A level of unprofessionalism
as I have watching Eureka,
- and it baffles me
- That you guys enjoy her so much.
- It has really
- Been very difficult
- working in an environment
- With her
because she takes
all the air out of the room.
She's always the one
who has to get the last word.
- In my defense,
I tell everyone all the time
I'm sorry that I'm loud
and I'm sorry I'm too much.
- But you don't try
to stop being loud
or try to stop being too much.
You're like, I'm sorry, but
this is who I am, deal with it.
- It's also a strength of mine
- when it comes to
- The confidence and acting.
- But what I've seen from Eureka
is I'm the one who's getting
all the attention in the room,
which to me is very childish,
- which I guess is why
- The characters that she's played
has worked for her,
because she's a child.
- I'm sorry
- That she feels that way,
but I will say one more thing.
- Again getting
the last word in.
- I'm sorry,
but I can't let her sit there...
- Again.
- And literally
verbally attack me.
Yes, I do talk too much
and I'm expressive and...
- But everyone
- Doesn't have to accept it.
- But I'm also extremely kind
and I'm full of love
- because I know that sometimes
- I am a lot to deal with.
But I can't change that.
- You can try.
- And I try to be
- Understanding of people...
- You weren't attacked.
- You're a grown man.
- But I can't help it
verbally attacking me
in front of people that I want
to have respect for my art,
- when I really have tried
- Everything I can
to be as kind as I can to Vixen.
- And that's all I'll say.
- I'm sorry.
- All right, thank you, ladies.
All right, Asia.
- Because I'm an adult,
- and although I've grown
- To love her and she's my sister,
I think The Vixen
has the most room for growth.
- Monique.
- I love her so much,
but I would say The Vixen,
basing it totally
on the challenge.
She had the weakest character
out of them all,
and she has kind of
just plateaued.
- And what say you, Aquaria?
- The Vixen with the way
- she's interpreted
- Some of the challenges.
- All right. Well, thank you,
- Ladies, for being honest.
I think we've heard enough.
While you untuck backstage,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
Just between us
squirrel friends,
- what do you think?
- Aquaria.
- The mermaid fantasy
was my favorite of the night.
It was cool.
It was edgy.
It told a story.
- Her Melania was a really
brilliant character study.
- Not only was it political,
it was also funny.
And it actually kind of
made me dig Melania.
- Mm-hmm.
- Which is hard to do.
Monique Heart.
- "Reclaiming my time"
does not Maxine Waters make.
There were so many things
that she left out,
and the most important
was the comedy.
- She read
- Maxine Waters' Wiki page,
and had the top 10 facts.
- I think she read
the first couple lines.
- Exactly.
- Up on your phone.
And the mermaid fantasy,
- it was way too disjointed
- For me.
- It was just a mess.
- I like Monique,
- But tonight on the runway,
she was just defensive
and mismatching.
- And the defensiveness,
- There's no place for that here.
- No.
- This is a competition,
and you have to hear
what the judges have to say.
Asia O'Hara,
our Beyoncé, oh, boy.
- Every time somebody tries
Beyoncé for the Snatch Game,
they fail.
- Beyoncé is not known for
- An over-the-top personality.
- And then the mermaid fantasy.
There's was such
pageant-y glamour.
I wanted to see that carry
through in the hair and makeup.
- I disagree with you guys.
- Sometimes pure beauty
gets to be a little bit boring.
I enjoyed the fact
that it was such a contrast.
- The Vixen.
Tonight was the prettiest
I think she's ever looked.
- But the body wasn't there.
- And I've got to admit,
I wasn't a big fan of her
interpretation of Blue Ivy.
- She didn't go far enough
- With it.
- She could have had
a Polish accent.
- She could have
rapped everything.
- I got 99 dolls, but...
- But my mommy won.
- [all laugh]
- And it was interesting to hear
- that there's
- An abrasiveness about her.
- Her sisters done threw her
under the Greyhound,
and there's a reason for it.
- Yeah. Monet X Change.
- Snatch Game,
- My edges are gone.
- She snatched them all
- Right away.
- She had every note
of Maya Angelou down.
Ru, may I read you a poem?
[all laugh]
- And tonight on the runway,
- even though
- It wasn't my favorite,
it told me a story.
Now, my story was 100% wrong.
[all laugh]
- I just didn't get it.
- It wasn't my thing.
- But I think her Snatch Game
- Moment was so great
that no matter what,
she's a winner tonight.
- Eureka.
- I think Eureka sucks...
- characters into her
- And then lives as them.
- She was able
- To get her jokes in,
but not in an annoying way.
- She did really well with
bantering with the other girls.
- My favorite thing
was the brilliant idea
of answering all the questions
with pictures.
[all laugh]
- Then drawing on herself
- At the end.
I loved it so much.
- But tonight on the runway,
it was just kind of basic.
- I didn't think
- She needed the blood at all.
- I just thought
she did everything right.
Character, makeup, all of it.
That's someone who is obviously
detail oriented in everything.
She's very impressive.
- Let's hear what Alex
- Has to say.
And Alex, please answer
in the form of a question.
- What is chunky, yet funky?
- All right, for
the Latrice Royale reference.
- [laughs]
- He's a fan of the show.
- I know.
- You can tell.
- All right, silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back my gills.
[all laugh]
- Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Aquaria, from the Snatch Game
to the runway,
this week we bought
what you were selling
hook, line, and sinker.
Con-drag-ulations. You are the
winner of this week's challenge.
- [applause]
- Whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo.
- You've won a six-night stay
- at the Grove Hotel
- And Ice Palace on Fire Island.
- Whoo! I've finally won
- My second challenge.
And Snatch Game to add.
- Eureka, Monet X Change...
You are both safe.
- Thank you.
- The Vixen,
playing Beyoncé's child
was not your destiny.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you
are up for elimination.
Asia O'Hara,
- your snatch
- Was not the catch of the day.
- Monique Heart,
- Your Auntie Maxine
hit some rough waters.
Asia O'Hara...
You're safe.
- Monique, I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
- America, if I could cuss
in this competition right now
and just scream the capital F.
America, y'all say it
for me right now.
- One, two, three.
- Thank you.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
- The time has come...
- [thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing] for your life.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
[music plays]
- ♪ I had a dream,
or was it real? ♪
♪ We crossed the line
and it was on ♪
♪ We crossed the line,
it was on this time ♪
♪ I've been denying how I feel ♪
♪ You've been denying
what you want ♪
♪ You want from me,
talk to me, baby ♪
♪ I want some satisfaction,
take me to the stars ♪
♪ Just say, oh-oh-oh ♪
- ♪ I wanna cut through
- The clouds, break the ceiling ♪
♪ I wanna dance on the roof,
you and me alone ♪
♪ I wanna cut to the feeling,
oh, yeah ♪
- ♪ Cancel your reservations,
- No more hesitations ♪
♪ This is on ♪
♪ Can't make it stop ♪
♪ Give me all you got ♪
- She don't know the words!
- ♪ Take me all the way ♪
♪ Take me, take me,
take me all the way ♪
- ♪ I wanna cut through
- The clouds, break the ceiling ♪
♪ I wanna dance on the roof,
you and me alone ♪
♪ I wanna cut to the feeling,
oh, yeah ♪
♪ I wanna play where you play
with the angels ♪
- ♪ I wanna wake up with you
- All in tangles ♪
♪ I wanna cut to the feeling,
oh, yeah ♪
♪ I wanna cut to the feeling ♪
♪ Cut to the feeling ♪
[applause]
- Whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo.
- Ladies, I've made my decision.
The Vixen...
shantay, you stay.
[applause]
- If there's one thing
I learned from you, Ru,
- it's unless
- They paying your bills,
pay them bitches no mind.
Thank you.
- Monique, it breaks my heart
to say sashay away.
- I appreciate you
- For giving me this opportunity.
- I'm sorry I let you down,
- And I love you all.
Thank you.
- Now sashay away.
- Bye, girls.
- Bye. We love you.
- The heart may leave right now,
- But it's not gone.
It's still beating full of love.
[applause]
- Love you.
- America,
- I didn't know my words,
and I have to own that.
- You may clock my lip sync,
- America,
- and you may clock,
- Oh, the bitch is horrible.
- What the hell is she doing?
- Da-da-da.
- But you cannot say
- That the bitch didn't try.
I got my Ru-ward.
I made America know my name,
a little girl from Kansas City
that no one knew.
And that's a fact,
and facts are facts.
- Con-drag-ulations, my queens.
- And remember,
- If you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
- Amen.
- All right,
- Now let the music play.
- ♪ To-to-to to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To-to-to to the moon ♪
- Next time
- On "RuPaul's Drag Race..."
It's time to pay tribute
to the one and only Cher.
[cheers and applause]
- Hey.
- Oh.
- Girl, I'm Disco Cher.
- American Horror Story,
- Cher Edition.
- You set the bar
very, very high.
- [imitating Cher]
That's called show biz, kid.
- I actually left, had a whole
Grindr hookup, and came back.
- Hey, babes.
[cheers and applause]