- Tonight, from the Ace Theater
in downtown Los Angeles,
it's "RuPaul's Drag Race
Season 10 Reunited."
All the queens
have gathered to catch up.
- Vanjie.
- Vanjie
is a multipurpose thing.
- It's like gay "aloha" now.
It's like "hello," "goodbye,"
and "thank you."
[all laugh]
- Watch unseen moments.
- You are so hot.
- Wow. I changed my mind.
Your panel was great.
[all laugh]
- And break it down.
- When you gonna find out
when to shut
the fuck up sometime?
- You made a mistake, fine.
Not next time, bitch.
- Honey, things
are about to get real.
- It feels like you don't care.
That's what it is.
- You said yourself
that you were attacking me.
- No, I never said "attack,"
darling.
- There's a camera.
That's what happened.
- There is a camera,
and I never said "attack."
- So it is my fault?
- It's a reunion
unlike any other.
- Nobody wanted
to fucking help her.
- Look at me, look at me,
goddamn it.
I come from the same goddamn
place she comes from.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ Gentlemen,
start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman win ♪
- ♪ Gentlemen,
start your engines ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman
- The winner
of "RuPaul's Drag Race"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
and a cash prize of $100.000.
- ♪ "RuPaul's Drag Race" ♪
- ♪ May the best woman ♪
- ♪ Best woman win ♪
- Welcome to "RuPaul's
Drag Race Reunited."
Now, if you think you know
everything about Season 10,
child, you got
another thing coming.
Ladies, are you ready
to spill the T,
the whole T,
and nothing but the T?
- Yeah.
- [laughs]
Now, "Drag Race"
trends on social media
across these United States
and around the world.
#DragRace.
But one Season 10 queen
was a true viral sensation.
Take a look.
Sashay away.
- Miss Vanjie.
Miss Vanjie.
- Bye, girl.
- Work, sister!
- Miss Vanjie.
- [stifles laugh]
- Vanjie.
- Vanjie?
- Vanjie!
- Miss Vanjie.
- [laughs] Don't you
start with me, Michelle.
Vanjie.
- [laughs]
- Vanjie.
- Miss Vanjie.
- [laughs]
- Yes, mama!
- Miss Vanjie.
- [laughs]
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, my goodness.
Now, Vanjie, what were you
thinking when you were exiting?
What was going on in your head?
- Truth be told, girl,
in my head
I was not gonna go home,
so I did not prepare
no message to leave.
- Okay. Had you ever used
"Vanjie" before
to exit or to say hello or--
- Right. Well, "Vanjie"
is a multipurpose thing.
You could use it for whatever.
- It's like gay "aloha" now.
It's like "hello," "goodbye,"
and "thank you."
- People even sent me videos
of them intercoursing,
and it said,
"I'm getting Vanjied."
- "Intercoursing?"
Is that what you said?
- Intercoursing on Instagram.
- Intercoursing?
- Yeah. So now I've been scared
to open up my DMs.
But they sent me one that says,
"I'm getting Vanjied."
[all laugh]
- So where has this taken you?
Have you traveled the world?
Have you made lots of money?
- Well, originally I was like,
well, I need to get
all my bookings quick.
- Wait, get the bookings quick
because you thought
you would be forgotten?
- Right, because
I got sent home first.
So I was like, girl,
this is my little 15.
So take your 15
and act like it's, you know,
you was there the whole time.
So when the promos
and everything came out,
I said, "Yeah, I'm in the show.
Do you want to book me?"
Like I didn't--you know,
there was no ifs, ands, or buts.
I said, "I'll be there."
- Right.
So where were you
when you realized this thing
had really blown up?
- I was in Denver, Colorado
with Dusty.
We were doing a booking.
- The audience just
started going "Vanjie!"
The cookies they threw at her
on the stage.
- Yeah!
- Chips Ahoy.
- Yeah, I was ducking
and dodging the cookies.
But I felt the love
even though I felt like they
might be trying to attack me.
But it was--
I knew it was all with love.
- I heard you met Lil' Kim.
- Yeah.
Lil' Kim came up to me
and said,
"Miss, Vanjie, Miss Vanjie,
I know who you are."
I know my face hit the ground.
I'm trying to come out
with a single with her,
'cause if we come out
with one,
it's gonna be a shutdown.
And they don't even want us
to do a video together
'cause that--
we really gonna be--
I'm gonna go viral again
for the wrong reasons.
- Yes!
- Now, Kalorie,
Kalorie, you were standing
right next to her
when this whole sensation
started.
You claim responsibility for
the whole Vanjie phenomenon.
- Oh, honey, I own 20%
of this company, okay?
- I see. So had you
not sent her home,
the Vanjie thing
would have never happened.
- Exactly. Exactly.
- Right. Thank you, Kalorie.
- I love Vanjie.
It was heartbreaking
to send her,
but I couldn't be more happy
for her success.
- Yeah. Well, Vanjie,
you have given everyone
around the world
so much to be excited about,
and I have
a very special message
to your drag mother,
Alexis Mateo.
Bam!
- Nice, girl.
[cheers and applause]
- Next week at the grand finale,
a lip sync smackdown will
determine who wins the crown,
but all season long,
our queens delivered
some of the most epic lip syncs
in "Drag Race" herstory.
Let's start with Monet X Change
and Dusty Ray Bottoms.
- ♪ Sexy and hotter,
let's shut it down ♪
- Come on.
- ♪ Pound the alarm ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my goodness.
Dusty, what was going through
your mind at that time?
- Going into this lip sync
knowing that Nicki Minaj
is something that
is in Monet's wheelhouse
that she does maybe seven,
eight times a week,
was very intimidating.
I mean, I do, like,
weird musical theater
and punk rock
and classic rock music.
So I stood up all night
memorizing that rap,
and you know what?
I gave it everything
I had that day.
- Now, Monet, your fake
death drop was legendary.
Did you know you were
gonna do that fake out?
- I did not, I did not.
- It was just in the moment.
I was like,
who knows what Dusty--
Dusty might do
some crazy ass shit
and send my raggedy ass home.
And I'd have to roll my three
broken suitcases across LAX,
so I was like, I need
to really turn it out
and do something crazy
to make RuPaul laugh.
- Uh-huh. Yeah.
Up next, Monique
versus The Vixen
when they cut to the feeling.
- Really?
Didn't we watch this already?
- ♪ I can't make it stop ♪
♪ Give me all you got ♪
- She don't know the words.
- ♪ I wanna cut to the feeling ♪
- Girl, why didn't you know
your words?
- 'Cause I stayed up
working on that damn costume.
- On that costume right there.
- That costume.
- Was the outfit worth not--
- Clearly it was not.
- So in that moment, what
was going through your head?
- The hardest thing on
"Drag Race" is how you go home.
- Right.
- To get to this competition
and then to eff up
the very thing that you do,
how you pay your bills,
and I tried to do a cartwheel,
and then it was like,
oh, don't kick her,
so let's pull those legs in.
- Yeah, but your wig
fell off, too.
- That--hey.
- Have you had a wig fall off
in a performance before?
- Multiple times.
- Multiple times?
- But it doesn't bother you?
- To be perfectly honest,
America--camera man, zoom in.
- This bitch is forever
editing and directing
this motherfucking show.
- Did you keep going?
America saw me, I kept going.
Was the song over? No.
[all laugh]
- Next, Eureka
versus Kameron Michaels,
which ended
in a rare double save.
- ♪ Never knew I had
such a lesson to learn ♪
♪ I'm feeling good
from my head to my shoes ♪
♪ Know where I'm going
and I know what to do ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, my goodness.
- Ladies, that is what you call
a lip sync for your life,
and that is why
no one is going home tonight.
Oh, my goodness.
Eureka, what was that moment
like for you?
- The moment when you gagged
the fudge outta me?
- Uh-huh.
- That was scary as hell.
In that moment,
I was like, girl,
I gotta show the judges that
I'm not gonna fuck up again,
and I can't and had
to get out of my head
and just be like, you can do it.
- So you got a new attitude
after that?
- Baby, I had a whole new
motherfucking attitude
after that.
- Aquaria, you were upset
that there was a double save
because you felt that bitches
need to be peeling off
to make more room
for your ascendance.
- Well, I definitely--
[all laugh]
As far as I know
like there's never been
like two double saves
in a season before,
so I'm like, well, crap,
what if, you know,
this was a week I thought I was
going to do poorly potentially.
What if next week is the week
that I actually do poorly,
and, you know, it's me against
someone's who's turning it out
just a little bit more than me
and now Aquaria's time.
- We've already used
the double save. Yeah, yeah.
I want to talk about
another lip sync right now.
This one
is between nasty girls
Kameron Michaels
and Miz Cracker.
- Disgusting girls.
- Take a look.
- ♪ Dance, nasty girls, dance ♪
- ♪ Everybody ♪
♪ Uh, it's time to jam ♪
- Hey, bitch!
- ♪ Nasty girls,
dance, dance, dance ♪
- Kameron, was this a pivotal
moment for you, this lip sync?
- I think you could
see it on my face
that I was very surprised.
- 'Cause most girls
don't get past three.
- Most girls
do not get the third one,
and at the same time,
I'm a performer,
and that's what I do best,
and for me to give up,
it wouldn't be
who I am as a person.
- For people my age, we know
that song is a super sexy song,
and you chose to do it
as a super sexy song.
And you chose to do it
as a comedic song.
- Oh, absolutely.
- Do you regret doing that?
- No.
- Not at all?
- Because I have found
when I perform
that when I try to be sexy
and serious,
it looks even more ridiculous.
I am built like R2D2.
I just have--I'm like
a trash can on wheels.
My legs are this long.
If I tried to do what Kameron
did, I would've lost harder.
Do you know what I mean?
- Yeah. Well, you made it
to the top five.
- Dammit.
- Yes. Yes.
- Bottom 10, everybody.
I'm fine with that.
- Now, after the break,
we'll talk to The Vixen
about her most
confrontational moments.
Stay tuned.
Welcome back.
"Drag Race" is a microcosm
of what's going on
in the world today,
and when people
don't see eye to eye,
things can get real.
Now, The Vixen,
you said you came to fight,
and fight you did.
Let's take a look.
- Someone brought up the fact
that Cracker and my face
looked very similar today,
may have had some situations
like that in the past.
Like, it doesn't bother me,
it's not like--
- No, too vague.
So what happened was--
- Yes!
- Oh!
- She said--
- This is what happened.
- No. Excuse me,
this is what happened.
- I obvious--well,
I kind of felt like--
- Excuse me.
- No, this is what happened.
We all know that these two
heifers look alike.
You was bothered that she was
doing the same face as you.
You was mad. Be mad to her face.
- Vixen, shut the fuck up.
This is what had happened.
You interjected and you got
everything all fired up.
- So why did it take me speaking
up right now for you to say it?
- I guess you did need
your moment to pop off,
'cause you're not gonna
have too many more.
[all laugh]
- Ooh! Ooh!
I am over it.
This is none of The Vixen's
fucking business.
- You done ran across
the whole room, girl.
Scared. Sad.
- Do you regret bringing that
up, that whole confrontation?
- No, absolutely not.
In "Untucked,"
the girls had convinced me
to believe that Cracker
was this monster--
- Okay, don't say "the girls."
Don't say "the girls."
- Okay.
- That's too vague.
- Even better. Even better.
At the time, Monet and Aquaria
had convinced me
to believe that Cracker
had worked her way
into this competition--
- Monét convinced you
that Cracker
worked her way into what?
Please be clear,
because that was never
my point of view on that.
I was very vocal in saying
that I never felt
that Cracker faked her way
to "Drag Race,"
because I knew that Cracker
was a very successful queen
in New York City,
and Cracker is fucking fierce.
I want to make that very clear.
- So as it showed in television,
because it did air,
Monet and Aquaria said that this
has been going on for years.
So based on what Monet
and Aquaria said,
I felt that Cracker had faked
her way into the competition.
So when Aquaria wasn't
copping up to what she said,
I felt bad
because now I believed
all these bad things about her,
and now she's backing away
from the story.
- But why did you bring it up?
Were you trying to stir the pot
to sort of throw them
off their game?
- Not at all.
I kind of felt like, girl,
I need to tell you the truth.
- Mm-hmm. So, Aquaria,
why did you run away?
- I realized that I wouldn't be
able to say what I meant to say.
I was very overwhelmed,
and I didn't have the words
to describe that
I didn't mean to be vague
just to bullshit Miz Cracker.
This was something
that I didn't want to disrespect
Miz Cracker with to her face,
and I can understand--
- Only behind my back.
[laughs]
- No, no, no.
I think--I think--
I can see why--
- That is the truth.
- How casually I said it
behind her back.
- Facts are facts.
- How I wanted
to take care of it
in front of her face.
- Did you ultimately have that
conversation with Miz Cracker?
- We did at the end of the day
after we were done
getting out of drag.
Really quickly,
I was like, that was a lot.
Let's just move on.
You be
the best Cracker you can be,
I'll be the best Aquaria
I can be, and--
- Aquaria and I
are like real sisters
in that we resent each other.
[all laugh]
- I think what we agreed
was that was ugly.
And, you know, we didn't
go back and heal things
or sort things out
or Vixen our positions,
but--do you know
what I mean?
- Oh, is "Vixen"
an adjective like "Vanjie?"
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- Get the popcorn.
- Like, if somebody doesn't
give me everything in my order
when I open the bag, I'm like,
I'm about to go back
and Vixen this bitch,
do you know what I mean?
[all laugh]
So we didn't Vixen it out,
but we, you know,
we agreed that that--
we did not want this
to be a part of our story.
- Sure. Now, Aquaria
wasn't the only one
who poked the bear.
Let's take a look at this.
- Do y'all hear me?
- I'm getting tired
of hearing you talk, honestly.
Can I go smoke?
- If you need to go smoke,
just say that.
- Thanks.
I ain't even arguing.
I'm big as hell, and I want
to go smoke a cigarette,
and I'm gonna go smoke me
a cigarette.
I just feel like
you have more respect
for other people than me.
- I don't think it's fair
that you get to say that
and then walk away.
- I don't think it's fair
that you get to be respectful
to other people
more than you are me, and I've
been nothing but nice to you,
and even get ready
beside you, girl.
- When have I been mean to you?
- Girl, she can say or do
the exact same thing
that I say or do,
and you act like
she didn't shit.
- First of all,
I am not your mother.
- What the fuck
you talking about, bitch?
You ain't my mama.
- Because you acting like
I have to baby you.
- Oh, bye, sis.
- You're a grown ass man.
- Really, girl? Really, girl?
- I don't owe you
any more than anybody else.
- You just want someone
to fight with.
- I don't need
to fight with you.
You are picking this fight
right now.
This is my problem with you.
You and Aquaria
are in the same fucking boat.
- You're the same way.
- You are exactly the girl
that I did not like on Season 9.
- You don't know me, girl.
- And see the good in you.
But you know what?
You are another bitch
who doesn't know when
to let somebody else talk.
You think that your problems
are the only problems.
- Really? Okay.
- Bitch, get your shit
together. Fuck you.
- Somebody says
one negative thing
and you want to flip
the fuck out?
- Fuck you.
Clean the fuck out.
- Really? Really?
Can't fuck me, bitch.
- No, fuck that.
- I do like you as a person.
- Go have your cigarette,
bitch!
- No, I'm not going.
- Because it's done.
- Oh, my goodness.
Vixen, Eureka, what was it like
watching all that back?
Oh, now you silent?
Now you ain't
got nothing to say?
- Now that I've seen it
a hundred times,
it's a lot easier,
but seeing it at first,
it was very hard to watch.
- Why?
- Because honestly
in my whole life
I've never seen myself
that hurt or upset.
- Would other people
say the same thing about you?
- Yes. My boyfriend
of three years
said that that was
the most bothered in any way
that he's ever seen me.
- Really?
What about you?
- I was getting
a lot of tensions
from several people
up to that point,
but most specifically
The Vixen,
and I just didn't feel like
I was being allowed
to be a part of the group
with a couple of the girls.
And it was like
when I had opinions,
I would be cut off
and what I was saying
didn't seem like
it came across important,
and so I got a little defensive.
- That's a little defensive
for you?
- Oh, well, so I got
really motherfucking defensive.
- Yeah. Do you stand
by what you said?
- "Go have your cigarette?"
- You said a little bit more
than, "Go have your cigarette."
- Well, okay, so every time
there was a little awkward thing
that happened
between me and Eureka,
I tried to push it away, pay it.
So by that point, I had like
tried as hard as I can
to be non-confrontational.
So all the fives were
out the window and 10 was here.
And so I can't regret it,
because I know that I did
everything I could to avoid it.
- Do you stand by what you said?
- I--I--yes.
- All right. All right.
Do you stand by what you said?
- Not completely, no.
I don't stand by
the direction I went
about talking about it.
You know, maybe I could've been
like, "Girl, what's going on?"
You know, maybe instead of
being immediately defensive.
But as far as like
defending myself in the moment,
I stand beside
what I said in that case.
- But I don't think you should
say that it's defending yourself
because you weren't
defending yourself.
You said yourself
that you were attacking me.
So you poked at me until
you got me upset enough
to make you look like
the victim.
- No. My decision
was never to attack you.
- No, that's what happened.
- No, I never said "attack,"
darling.
- There's a camera.
That's what happened.
- There is a camera,
and I never said "attack."
- You said it from your mouth.
- No!
- You said "testing."
- This is exactly what I said.
"I just wanted to test her
because I tell that she
had something against me,"
blah blah blah blah blah.
- When you walked away from
the argument, you were smiling.
- It wasn't fair
that I did that to you.
- You were happy
that you got me.
- And it wasn't okay.
- And you did got me.
Listen, you got me.
- Do you feel differently now
than you did?
- About what?
- About your relationship
with Eureka.
- No. Because I sat at home
for months
believing that
I made that happen,
that it was my fault
that all of that happened.
And so I had to sit with that
and think that,
oh, I'm this monster.
It's gonna come out that
I'm like just this testy bitch
who can't keep it under control.
And then I find out that
she wanted me to go there.
She took me there on purpose.
Even before that, I knew
that I had issues
in my own mind with Eureka,
and I was trying every day
to make it--to keep it cool,
but you took it to
the worst possible level.
- Yeah, but that's
like saying, you know,
"Eat the cake, Anna Mae."
- Oh, so it's--
so it is my fault?
- You had a choice to react--
- Wait, how is this--how--
I don't get the "Eat the cake,
Anna Mae," thing at all.
- It's like saying,
"You made me do that."
- I think what Ru
is trying to say
is that you do not
have to accept the goad
when you are goaded.
- Yeah, but I think
the problem is
there's now five of us
talking to The Vixen
telling her why
you didn't have to do that.
- Yeah, everybody's tell me
how I should react,
but nobody's telling her
how to act.
- And, listen, you're not off
the hook either, Eureka.
Everybody has choices to take
the bait or to poke the bear.
- That's the truth.
- Yeah.
- And I'm doing my best not to.
- But you admit
that you have a problem
being able to not say anything?
If somebody says anything to
you, you're gonna respond to it.
- Yeah. It's honestly--
It really is something
I've tried to work on
as far as like the thinking
people all have to like me.
- It's not something
you have to work on,
it's just something
you just have to do.
- Yeah.
Can I say
what I wanted to say?
- What else do you want to say?
- We talked about it,
and I thought that we moved on,
and that's all I want
ultimately.
I did apologize for that because
I acted like a foolish bitch,
and I tried to come at you
because I was feeling sensitive,
and it wasn't cool that we ended
up in a heated, nasty argument.
But the next day
we talked about it.
You told me that
we were okay to move on,
and that's really what I want.
- There was a lie in there.
The next day--
I remember getting to the studio
the next day
and you pulling me to the side
and saying, "Girl, so how
do we wanna handle this?"
And that was the moment
that I knew
that everything
you had done was intentional
and that you were also
gonna produce how we fixed it,
and that is why
throughout the competition
I never trusted you again.
I never wanted
to deal with you again.
- But you came into
the competition
saying, "I came to fight."
And, you know,
it's not like you were--
- I came--okay,
so I came into the competition
saying that I came to fight.
Never once in this competition
did I start a fight.
- Wait, is that true?
It looked like you were
instigating things, and even--
- What did I instigate?
- Well, this thing between
Miz Cracker and Aquaria.
- It's not instigating
to tell someone the truth.
It's not instigating to tell--
- You can also not say anything.
- You could, but what's wrong
with telling someone the truth?
- Well, if you're
gonna tell the truth
and it's gonna create
tension in the room,
then that is creating a fight.
You also have a choice
to not say anything.
- Okay, so I came here
to thank my fans
for the love and support
that they gave me,
for all the wonderful people
who relate to me,
understand me and appreciate me.
And now that I've done that,
y'all can have a good night.
- Wait, wait, wait, Vixen, wait
Vixen, can I say something?
- No, I'm done. No.
- Okay. Well, Vixen...
- Welcome back to
"RuPaul's Drag Race Reunited."
Now, unfortunately, The Vixen
has decided to not rejoin us,
but before moving on,
does anyone have anything
they'd like to say
about this situation?
- I don't think
it was the best thing to do,
but I do think
her getting up and leaving
was her way of separating
herself from a situation
where either A, she was
gonna either have to fight
or leave the room.
- I disagree. I really do.
There's still a way
to have a conversation
without having
to do that, though.
- Agreed. Agreed.
But that's the--
- If she would just sit there
and just say, you know what?
Let me take a moment, breathe,
think about
what I'm about to say
so that I could get
my message across,
everyone at home
can understand her more.
- She walked out of the room
because she does not know
what else to do,
and it's our job as people
to try and help her
through a situation
that it's clear that
she's struggling through.
- Listen, as a community,
we do have responsibility
to each other,
but each of us,
we are all adults.
At one point you gotta say,
there is nothing else I can do.
And each of us have had
people in our lives
who you realize I can't do
anything for this person
unless they want
to meet me halfway.
- Valid. But I also feel like
earned authority is real.
- Accepting love is something
that's really important
just as much as giving love.
- But what
I don't understand is,
why do we just automatically
expect everybody
to understand that?
I don't agree with everything
that The Vixen says or does,
but I understand
where it comes from,
and I think...
The Vixen seems to me
like a person
that's crying out for help.
And it's like everybody else
is like, girl, that's on you.
You gotta figure it out,
and I just...
That's just unfortunate to me.
Like, I feel like
our sole purpose here
is to, you know, enrich
the lives of other people,
and even if I'm met
with controversy or whatnot,
I can do that every day
because 20 years down the road
we've got something, then
it's because, you know,
I was persistent in trying
to make your life better.
- Listen, I love the girl.
In fact, I invited her on
in the first place
because I felt her voice
needed to be heard.
But at one point,
and you've seen this
with your friends back home,
at one point sometimes
you gotta let people go
whether it's anger
or whatever the issue is,
because it's not
a two-way street.
It's one-sided.
And that's where we are.
It's a one-sided conversation.
She decided she's gonna get
the last word and walk out,
so there, it's done.
- It's just ridiculous.
It's just ridiculous.
Like it's ridiculous that our
thought process about people
is so self-centered that if
it's hard to help somebody,
well, just let them struggle.
We're not drag queens,
we're people,
and now we've got
one of our people outside.
Here were are filming
during Pride season,
and we let one of our sisters
walk out the fucking room
'cause nobody wants
to fucking help her.
And we're the first people--
we are the first people
to say that people
aren't treating us right.
- Do you think there's anything
we could have said to The Vixen
to make her stay?
- It's not about what we say,
it's about what we do.
- What could we have done?
- If I had of got up
and walked to that door
and said, "The Vixen,
we need you to stay."
But the fact that we, including
myself, let her walk out,
she--that door
closed behind her
and she said, yeah, I guess
I'm making the right choice.
- When Vixen decided to say,
"Thank you, but I'm leaving,"
do you believe that she had
already made up her mind?
Clearly you don't believe
she had already made up her mind
that this is it.
Because I believe
when she said that,
she was done
and there was nothing
anyone could do to stop her.
I mean, you've had
discussions with her.
In fact, we saw you have
a lovely discussion with her,
where we actually got to see
the sweetness in him,
and I saw the fear,
and I saw all of that,
and I understood
why that wall was put up,
because I have that wall,
you have it,
you have it, we all have it.
And it's coming
from a hurt place. It is.
But I can't teach her that.
I can teach her
through my own example.
- Of course you can.
- What, am I gonna go back
and follow her
and go say, "Come here,
let me tell you something."
- I mean, not at this moment.
- Can you explain to someone
who cannot be spoken to?
- No. I don't expect you
to do that, but--
- But look at me,
look at me, goddamn it.
I come from the same
goddamn place she comes from.
And here I am,
and you see me walking out?
No, I'm not walking out.
I fucking learn
how to act around people
and how to deal with shit.
I'm not fucking walking out
and saying,
"fuck all y'all," you know?
That's disrespectful
to each of you.
And I know you feel for her
because you see yourself in her,
'cause we all have
that same frustration.
Let me tell you something.
I have been
discriminated against
by white people for being black,
by black people for being gay,
by gay people for being too fem.
Did I let that stop me
from getting to this chair?
No. I had to separate
what I feel
or what my impression
of the situation is
to put my focus on the goal.
You can't just make excuses
for bad behavior
or for inconsiderate behavior.
I invited each of you back here
to my house, into my home,
and if I'm invited
to someone's home,
I'm not gonna disrespect
their home.
I'm not gonna just disrespect
the invitation.
You know, the world is hard.
It's hard to live
on this planet.
But we all have to learn
how to deal with it,
but you gotta ask
for help first.
Listen, at the end of the day,
we are all a drag family,
and as you can see here tonight,
it doesn't always come easy.
I want you take a look at this.
- My mom knocks on my door
and says,
"Your dad just found something
on your computer."
They lost it.
They took me to church.
They got me exorcised
because they thought
I was possessed by a gay demon.
- Really?
- I was so confused after
the whole thing went down
because was I straight now?
Like...
I had to go through therapy.
- Oh, my God.
- And I was on a track
to go to straight camp.
I was meeting
with these pastors,
and he was like,
"In a homosexual relationship,
you'll never find success,
you'll never find love."
[sobs]
And I stopped him and I went
upstairs and I packed my car.
I said,
"I can't do this anymore."
- Oh, my goodness.
You know, Dusty,
I watched this at home,
and I busted out crying
when I saw this.
And you went through this thing
that's so horrific.
If you don't mind,
would you tell us,
what is conversion therapy?
- Conversion therapy
is a cleanse and a confession.
You go through this process
where you have to literally list
every person you've had
a sexual experience with,
and it's literally just this
very humiliating process.
It was really rough,
and I just had to have a day
where I said, enough.
- How did you find the strength
to do that?
- I've gone through
some hardships as a kid,
and I've always told myself that
this moment is just for now.
What I'm experiencing right now
cannot last forever.
So I know
that there is a tomorrow,
and it will get better.
I found creative outlets
to immerse myself in
for distractions,
and the people who saw me shine
that needed to be there
for me became my tribe.
- And did that also mean
leaving your family behind?
- I had to, yeah.
- And do you speak with them?
- Since that day,
they've apologized.
We do not see eye to eye
on homosexuality still,
but we have moved on
past that day.
The things
that we don't talk about
is because we don't see
each other as equal humans.
- Is it enough for you
to just have your chosen family?
Is that--would that
be enough for you?
- You know, it...
I love my chosen family.
I'm so very lucky.
But...
It's just really hard
to have strangers come up to you
and say that I look up to you,
I'm so proud of you,
I'm cheering you on,
and then you don't have
those people
that you wish were there
the most
saying, we are proud of you.
We are wearing
the Dusty shirt.
We are posting you
on our social media.
We are there.
And I'm good.
My life is good.
It could just be better
that way, that's all.
- You are fabulous, girl.
- Thank you.
- Fricking fabulous.
- Come on to the Bottoms family.
- Well, thank you
so much, Dusty,
for your courage
to tell that story.
It's really helped
a lot of people.
Now, when we talk about queens
with deep spiritual connections,
we can't leave out
Monique Heart.
More with her when we return.
Welcome back to "RuPaul's
Drag Race Reunited."
Now, Dusty wasn't the only one
who struggled with faith
and family. Take a look.
- Being here and knowing
that my mother can potentially
watch this show,
and me being
my most authentic self
makes me very
like uncomfortable
because I'm like
she's gonna watch and like--
- Oh, yes.
- I am seriously--
like seriously fruity,
you know what I mean?
- Is there no feeling
of liberation in that at all?
- No, because I know my mother
and I have to deal with her,
and I'm trying to build
a relationship with her
at this point that
she knows that I do drag.
- Monique, how old are you?
- I'm 31.
- Wait, your family
doesn't know you do drag?
- No, she knows, but like
I'm grown and I don't--
like, my mom is my everything,
you know what I mean?
- I hear that.
- And I didn't talk to her
for like four years
because you can't
be black and gay.
Like, you just can't.
You just can't.
- Hello. Hello.
- You know what I mean?
And then when you have
such a strong--
I'm fifth generation
full-time ministry.
This is like heresy,
you know what I mean?
- Wow, that's deep.
So, Monique,
you can relate to Dusty.
- Yeah. The day that Dusty,
Blair, Eureka, and Asia
opened up
about their spirituality,
I really didn't 'cause,
like, I still kind of love
this one that we call God
and, you know,
go by the name of Jesus,
whatever.
But to hear again the BS
that you go through
just trying to become
your most authentic self,
thinking that if I just pray
it away or confess this name,
like, I'll finally be free,
but to be 100% honest,
it wasn't.
It really wasn't.
It really was not until
I put on a wig and a dress
and I grabbed that mic
and I saw this kid
sitting across from me,
and like we had this dance party
at Hamburger Mary's,
and he wanted to go up
and I said,
know that you are loved
and you are so worth it
and go twirl,
like go give it to 'em.
- Twirl, bitch.
- And I knew that in that moment
that, like, yo, black
gay youth come up to you,
because I wanted to be that boy,
but I couldn't be that boy.
So to be in a day and age
where they can,
that means so much.
Like, it was all worth it.
- It was all worth it.
All the pain,
it was all worth it.
Have you spoken
with your mother?
- I did, but she wasn't
like happy.
And so I felt very alone,
and to come back
to your room every night
and just you have friends, but
you just like God, I'm alone,
and there wasn't nobody
but me, Jesus,
and glitter and rhinestones.
That was it.
Like Psalms 110 says, he wraps
himself in a garment of light.
Dolce can't do that,
Versace can't do that.
Like the aah, he lives
for the ooh-ah-ah sensation.
So when you know that,
you're free, and I'm sorry.
- No, this is right.
This is it.
This is it right here.
Because what you're saying
is you,
through this journey
of a lot of pain,
you have found
what the true meaning is.
You just quoted the Bible.
You just interpret it
through your own path.
You've understood
what those words really mean,
and you're absolutely right.
- Amen.
- Dress yourself up
and go out there and celebrate.
And your ministry helped
this kid in Hamburger Mary's
come into the light,
walk into his own beauty,
into his own light.
But this is why this ministry
of drag is so powerful.
We can speak from so much pain
and so much heartache
and so much still frustration,
but we can walk that walk,
and you're doing it.
You are doing it.
We'll be right back.
- Welcome back to "RuPaul's
Drag Race Reunited."
Now, there's something
about the main stage
that makes queens
bare their souls.
It's like a truth serum.
But nobody was prepared
for the startling confession
of our dear Blair St. Clair.
Let's take a look.
- Um...
My first sexual experience,
I was raped at a college party,
and from that I have looked
to find pretty things.
It's something
I need to get over,
but I've tried
to turn positive the best I can.
[applause]
- So, Blair, in "Untucked,"
you share
that this was the first time
you had spoken about that.
What made you decide
to do it on this forum?
- You know...
sometimes your heart knows
when you're ready to talk
before your brain does.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I don't even think
my brain
was fully capable of what
I was doing at the moment.
- Yeah. When did you tell
your mother?
- I had a conversation
with my mother
a few weeks after I got home
from "Drag Race."
We sat down
and we talked about it,
and that was probably harder
than talking about it
to the world.
Telling the people
that you love the most
something traumatic about you
is really difficult,
and that's why
I've held it in for so long,
'cause I didn't even want
to admit it to myself.
- Yeah. And in all the years
before you revealed it
on television,
how had you been coping
with that pain?
- You know, everyone has
a different way of coping,
and everyone has a different
mechanism in what they do,
and whenever I found pain
and whenever I found hurt,
frustration, anger
or anything that was like
a negative emotion,
I would turn to alcohol,
and I would drink in excess.
It's something that
I didn't realize was a problem
until after coming home
from "Drag Race"
and recognizing that might be
something that I can't control
because I use to mask the pain.
Now I've been living
a sober life
since coming back
from "Drag Race."
[applause]
And I can tell you
that from what I've experienced
in my spiritual growth
is that I am a more humbled,
caring, thoughtful person,
and it has truly
changed my life.
- How have fans reacted?
- Fans have been incredible.
They've just been--
and so have my sisters.
You guys have just been
so wonderful,
and I think the best way
to describe it
is that I have gone through
something so painful,
so haunting and hurtful,
but it's only been received
back to me
in so much love
from everybody else,
and it's just been so amazing
for me to embrace that back.
- Thank you so much, Blair,
for being so brave,
and for inspiring
so many people.
Opening up is always hard,
especially when it comes
to family.
Let's take a look at this.
- In 2014, I won
a small pageant in Brooklyn.
The pageant was on Saturday.
I wake up Monday morning
with like 27 missed calls
from my mom.
I'm like what happened,
what is going on?
They sent an article
back to St. Lucia
with me in drag
on the cover of the newspaper,
the only newspaper
on the entire island.
She called me, she was like
what is going on?
Are you trans? Are you gay?
What is all this shit?
I'm like no.
I was just doing it
for a movie thing
and it got misconstrued.
It was the craziest thing
in my life, girl.
In retrospect,
I should have just said,
hey, I'm a drag queen,
but I like lied about it,
and there's a small sliver of me
that thinks that
they might reject me,
and that is why
I don't want to say it.
It's very scary.
- Now, you talked about
your Caribbean upbringing.
- Yeah.
- Tell me about that.
How did that affect you?
- Growing up in a small island
like St. Lucia,
there aren't lots of gay people.
You don't see gay people on TV.
You don't see gay people
at the store.
So when I moved back to America,
and I was thrust
into New York City
where going to school
on the 2 train,
I was seeing drag queens
coming off their shift from work
at 7:00 in the morning.
It is like--
it was a shock to me.
And me knowing that
there was a small part of me
that identified with that,
and it was like a very haunting
and daunting fear of mine
to realize that, hey, I'm gay,
but not just gay,
I'm like the highest form
of gay, I'm a drag queen.
- The highest form of gay.
[laughs]
- It was like the Megazord
of being gay.
I am a drag queen.
- [laughs]
Have they seen the show?
- I mean, she's still
very wary about it.
She won't say
that I'm on "Drag Race."
She's like, so that show you're
doing, how you doing on it?
Are you still on it?
And I'm like, yeah, Mom,
I'm still on it.
This was episode eight,
I was still doing well.
And I was like, yeah, Mom,
I'm still on there.
She's like, well, I hope
you go far, but she has not--
- Why do you think that is?
Why do you think
she is reluctant
to watching you on the show?
- I think just from
an afro-black perspective,
like being gay
and saying that you're
homosexual and all those things,
it's hard for black women
and black moms to reconcile with
because it is--
it often is demonized
because she's at church
every Sunday morning,
and like that is her devotion.
So seeing that her son
is amplifying all those fears
that she's been preached at
every Wednesday night
in Bible study
and every Thursday
at choir practice,
it's hard for her to--
- Amen.
- To accept that her son
is that thing
that she's been told to fear,
and is not--
- Yeah.
Because at some level
she'd have to deconstruct
her whole belief system
to accept what you're doing.
- Right.
- Is there still a part of you
inside that is--
that sort of demonizes
being a drag queen to yourself?
- Yeah. You know, I feel
old habits die hard.
I went to church every Sunday
morning and I was in choir,
and I still do sing
at a choir in drag.
Every Wednesday night
I'm in choir in full drag.
- Yes.
- Ooh, praise Him.
- It's a very loving place,
but the fact that my mom
still can't say
my son is a drag queen,
I think it is that part of me
that I know
that she is still probably
really wary
any airing of that fact.
- Yeah, yeah. All right.
One last question about that.
Does your whole family
wear a pussycat wig?
[all laugh]
- Ru, I come from
a very long lineage
of the pussycat wig ladies.
My grandmother,
my great-great-grandmother,
and my great-
great-great-grandfather, okay?
- Miss Hattie May X Change.
He was a drag queen girl,
and he had a pussycat wig.
- I love it.
Now, Yuhua, you have
an interesting relationship
with your parents,
is that correct?
- Yes. Yes.
I grew up in a very,
very conservative family.
I am original from China,
and in China we view drag queens
as someone who is mentally ill,
unstable, and crazy.
- Well, that's true.
That's true.
- So when I was growing up,
I used to be very, very,
very, very scared of drag
until I discovered
what drag was.
And I put a wig on.
I tried to play with all the
colors on the makeup palette,
and it made me so free,
and made me
so much more happier.
It gave me confidence
and determination,
and it saved me as a person.
- And did you do it in secret?
- I did it in secret.
I was 16 at the time.
- Where would you put
the clothes on?
- I would sneak out
and put the clothes on
in the basement of the apartment
that we lived in
near the garbage cans.
- Do your parents know
that you do drag now?
- They've seen pictures
when I was younger,
but they don't know
where I am with drag right now.
- Yeah.
Do you still see them?
- Yes, I still see them.
We don't talk about it.
I think it's very common
in Asian culture
that you don't talk
about stuff like that
where it's looked down upon,
it's shameful,
so it is best
that we don't talk about it.
Because if we talk about it,
then we would distance ourself
further away from it,
and I think a lot of Asians
out there
can relate to the same
situation as well.
- Do you ever see a day
where you tell them?
- I don't know.
I mean, till this day
they still ask me,
when are you gonna bring back
home a Chinese girlfriend?
But don't they know that
I am the girlfriend already?
[all laugh]
- Yuhua.
- After the break,
the queens read each other's
runway looks to filth.
Stay tuned.
Welcome back.
Now, we are only one week away
from crowning America's
next drag superstar
in an epic lip sync
smackdown for the crown.
But first, let's play a game
of what we call Toot or Boot.
- Ahh.
- Yes.
- If you love an outfit,
toot it,
and if you don't, boot it.
All right. First up,
Kameron's feather couture.
- Toot.
- That's a shoot, honey.
When Kameron came in,
I was like,
oh, this bitch
is going home tomorrow.
Like, she is done.
Episode 3, you came out in this,
I said, to quote
Monique Heart, "Okay!"
It was like everything.
- Okay!
- I was like,
oh, this is, like,
one of the best looks
of the season probably.
- She looked like she came
straight out of
a "Lord of the Rings" book.
- [laughs]
- Up next, we've got
Miz Cracker's silver foxy.
Toot or boot?
- Toot.
- I'm gonna say boot,
'cause this bitch
put on bigger lips
and just turned out to be
a fatter lipped version
of herself.
- And Michelle said
that she really believed
I would be that wrinkle free
at that age, so...
- All right.
So up next we've got
Monet's sponge dress.
- Boot.
- Really?
- [laughs]
- I'm gonna toot it because
when she was making it,
I was watching her and
I was like, this is a good idea,
and I was like, okay,
I'm feeling it,
and I still like it to this day.
- But her silhouette.
- It's just unshapely.
- But Monet,
tell me about the choice
to put the sponges on top
over the bottom part.
- I wanted to mimic
a loofah on a stick.
- Does the dress still exist?
- The dress still exists, Ru,
and actually,
I have a surprise for you.
- Uh-oh.
- A little birdie told me
that you liked it so much.
- Uh-huh.
- So I brought you--
I made one for you.
- Oh, my goodness.
I'm surprised
you still have them on there
because every week
you were dabbing yourself
with more of the sponges.
- Ru, can I get a toot or a boot
finally from you?
- You can get a toot.
- Yes!
- Absolutely.
For nerve, for nerve.
[all laugh]
It did take nerve.
[laughs]
Now, you bitches
were so extra this season,
it rubbed off on the judges.
Check out these
never-before-seen moments
from the judges' panel.
If you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen in here?
- Amen!
- Can I get an amen, Christina?
- Amen, Christina!
[all laugh]
- Now, Shania, have you worn
assless chaps before?
- Um, yes, I have.
- She's wearing them
right now actually.
- Oh.
- Let's go to Alex Trebek
and hear what he has to say
about Asia.
- No T, no shade,
but she was not serving
lemonade.
- Ooh!
- Ooh, all right, Alex,
for the Beyonce quote.
Alex is part of the beyhive.
- [laughs]
- Can I just say,
I know it's your husband,
you are so hot.
- Isn't he so hot?
- Oh, my God.
- I know, right?
- I'm--okay.
- Wow. I changed my mind.
Your panel was great,
really amazing,
and you really showed them up.
- I am in love with you, girl.
- That's very nice.
- I remember walking to school
right around "Spring Awakening"
when you were there,
and kids, like, sleeping outside
the theater for like days
to hopefully get a ticket, and
you would sometimes pop in there
and bring them
coffee and donuts.
- That was Jonathan Groff.
That wasn't me, but it's fine.
It's totally fine.
- I'm thinking
of "Book of Mormon."
"Book of Mormon," that was you.
- Look, we're gay and we're
white and we sing high.
I am on board for all of it.
- Courtney, have you ever used
a dating app?
- Yes.
- Are you single?
Because so is Carson.
- Yes, and we would make
a fantastic couple.
- Oh, my God, we could share
makeup and clothes.
- We put you together
for a reason.
- [laughs]
- So Alex, is there anything
more you'd like to say?
- Okay, that's it.
I've had it, officially.
- Okur.
[all laugh]
- Aah!
- All right, after the break,
more drama, mama.
Don't go anywhere.
Welcome back.
Now, after
the evil twin challenge,
I asked the queens
the classic question,
who should go home and why?
- North Korea.
- The person that I do not think
is a star in this lineup
is Miz Cracker or Miz Crumbs.
- How'd that make you feel,
Miz Cracker?
- Asia, you hurt my feelings.
I took that phrase
and I beat myself for months
till I couldn't get out of bed.
And the reason that that
happened for me, I think,
is because
I come from New York City,
and there is an infinite amount
of love in the world,
but there are so many bars
in New York City,
and I fought for a place
in all of them.
And all year before "Drag Race,"
people were like,
girl, are you ready
for Monet X Change
to be on "Drag Race?"
Girl, are you ready for Aquaria
I was always not a star.
I came here only to be a star,
to show people
that I was not less than.
That was something
I was already telling myself.
You opened it in me
that that's the story.
- Do you still stand
by saying that she's not a star?
- That was wrong, and it was
hurtful for me to say that,
and, you know, I would never
want to discredit anybody's work
or let somebody feel like,
you know, they're less than,
because, I mean,
you are more than.
You proved that by being here
and as far as you've made it
in the competition.
So I'm really sorry
from the bottom of my heart.
I knew as soon as the words
left my mouth
that that's not something
you say about somebody else
that's in the same, you know,
line of work as you.
- Right.
- Do you believe her?
- Do I believe her--
this apology?
Yes, I believe that.
What I will say is this time
you made a mistake. Fine.
Not next time, bitch.
- All right, let's move on.
Now, we are just one week away
from crowning America's
next drag superstar.
Now, ladies, I've been asking
a lot of questions,
but now I'd like
to give you the chance
to ask questions to each other.
It's the last call.
Now, if you have anything you
want to get off your chesticles,
now is the time.
Oh, okay.
- Okay, Mayhem.
- Mayhem.
- [laughs]
- Okay, so here's the thing.
This one's directed
to Asia and Aquaria.
Now, on "Untucked,"
you guys have both had
a discussion about me,
saying that my drag
didn't have a wow factor,
and at home watching that,
I was completely blown away,
because I was like,
wait a minute.
They never said anything to me
about that.
Every time we had
a design challenge,
like the first episode
that I won for my look,
everyone said, oh, my God,
wow, that was great.
And then
when it came to the ball,
my Martian look was sickening,
and you guys sat there
in "Untucked"
and said that about me,
and I was very hurt by that,
because I was like,
wait a minute, what?
I would have thought
that you guys
would have been like, girl,
what are you wearing? Like--
But I thought every time I hit
that runway I was put together.
I was like, okay,
fuck my drag all of a sudden.
- If I may, first,
I came into this competition
a very huge Mayhem fan,
because I think you're just
so freaking cool and so fierce.
And I think for me, you were
giving me fabulous drag,
but I didn't see you stand out
the way that I wish that
I could see you stand out,
and I think that's more
what I meant,
rather than, oh,
fuck your drag, you know?
So I'm very sorry
if I made you feel that way
watching especially.
- For me, prior to "Drag Race,"
you were always
the girl to beat.
And the first episode,
the design challenge,
I mean, I stood right there
with Eureka
and told you
how fabulous that was.
I did not not personally care
for your Martian looks,
but I wasn't just
gonna go over there
and say,
girl, I don't like that,
because you and I don't have
a friendship like that.
I'm not a judge, and, I mean,
I respect you enough as a person
to not like
rain on your parade
with my opinions that
a lot of times don't matter.
But there was never a time
where I said, you know,
oh, Mayhem, I love this,
and then went in "Untucked"
and said something different.
- Okay, that's a valid point.
Let's--anybody else want--
- Okay, I have one.
Kameron, you stunt queen,
strategizing the house down,
faces of many.
You on social media
have all of this mouth,
and I go--
now I understand strategy.
I just don't understand like
where's this girl
that claps back, pops off,
and then this one over here
was just very like,
I don't say anything,
I don't do--like who--
I'm just asking only
because it seems very like,
oh, she played
a completely different game
and we don't know you at all
or you're just completely
like fake.
- It wasn't really
even a strategy.
I was just intimidated
by you guys.
You guys were all--
I think all of you working
as professional drag queens.
I was not.
I was a hairdresser.
I stopped doing drag and
concentrated on my hair career,
and then I auditioned
for the show and I made it,
and then in that moment,
I realized, oh, shit.
What did I get myself into?
And so I had to come and compete
in a competition
where I didn't think
I would make it where I made it,
and that was why I was so quiet.
It wasn't a strategy, it was me
doubting myself the whole time.
But you come to my shows,
when you come and see me live,
I'm the same way
that I am on social media
as I am in person at my shows.
- You know,
it's very heartbreaking,
because when I see your
personality on social media,
that hurts my feelings,
because like I don't have
a relationship with you.
I don't know if many girls
have relationships with you,
but it's almost like
you don't want it at all,
and like press week, mama,
we were together in each other's
faces for a whole week.
I would walk into the room.
I literally
had to sit on your lap
and grab your face and say,
hi, Kameron, hello.
And then after that weekend,
I told myself I'm not
wasting any more energy--
- Why, because the response--
You wouldn't get a response
from Kameron?
- Listen, everyone here
will walk into the room
and say hello to each other.
Sis, how you been?
I can't even turn Kameron's head
when I walk into the room.
- Is that true, Kameron?
Why is that?
- I'm sure some girls
feel like that.
I don't have a close
relationship with everyone here,
but I--
when I walk into a room,
maybe I didn't do it
on the show,
but events
that we've done together,
I feel like I walk up
and say hello to you guys.
I feel like I say hi.
I feel like I say
that you look great.
- Sis, I love you,
but you will clear into a room
and just go...
And I--you will.
So it feels intentional.
It feels like you don't care,
that's what it is.
So it's not like you gotta be,
"Oh, Boo, woo, woo, woo."
No. Just, hey, fish,
keep it pushing, that's it.
- I have to disagree.
I feel like I comment
and tell you guys
that you look good.
Maybe I didn't do it--
- When we activate with you.
- Maybe I didn't do it
back then, but I do it now.
- But also I feel
actively on the show
you said to us often
that I'm not talking
because I don't want to say--
I don't want them
to put shady clips up of me.
But it's like, it you don't
have something shady to say,
then that's not gonna happen.
- See, that girl right here.
This girl, who's she?
That one right there?
You just said...
Who's she?
- Oh, did you just make a face?
- That's what I'm saying.
No, she just clicked.
Who--that's what I'm saying.
That's what I'm saying.
- She clicked out, not clicked.
- She just clicked over,
you know what I'm saying?
It's all in, like,
body language and everything,
you know what I'm saying?
And so I'm going like--
- She's here with us.
- You're here with us.
- To put a Band-Aid on that,
I'm not saying that you were
maliciously trying to ignore us.
It's just that when
we hear you say that,
oh, I'm not gonna
say nothing on camera
'cause I don't want
to say nothing shady,
that gives me pause,
like, okay, what does Kameron
really think about Monet?
What does Kameron
really think about Monique?
I think that's what
is the disconnect for me.
- I just think
you're so fabulous.
I just want you
to be my fucking friend.
- [laughs]
- Aw.
- Thank you, ladies, for getting
it all off your chests.
After the break, I'll ask
which of our Top Four
should take the crown,
so stick around.
Welcome back.
Now, ladies,
before you drag-uate
from "RuPaul's Drag Race,"
let's take one last trip
to the library.
- Ooh.
- All right, bitches,
the library is open.
Who wants to go first?
- Me!
- Okay.
- I went to public school, so I
might not be very good at this.
Vanessa Vanjie Mateo.
- What, bitch?
- How does it feel
to have a catch phrase
last longer on "Drag Race"
than you did?
- I'm glad
I have a catch phrase.
Who are you again?
Okay, bitch?
[all laugh]
- The bitch that sent you home.
The bitch that sent you home.
- Eureka, they say,
eureka, I found it, right?
But when you gonna find out
when to shut the fuck up
sometimes?
[all laugh]
- When you come put
that dick in my mouth.
- Aah!
[all laugh]
- You know, this season
we thought that The Vixen
and Eureka
was one of the biggest fights,
but no.
I enjoyed watching Yuhua
fight the English language
the entire season.
[all laugh]
- What kind of fish?
- Clearly she talking to Monet.
- What kind of fish is that?
[all laugh]
- Aquaria is smart!
- Eureka, I know you seem
to have gotten close
to Miss Kameron Michaels,
and that's really surprising
because no one gets close to her
without a $50 meet and greet.
- Ooh.
- And I know
maybe it's because of
Kameron's ego is so big
it makes you feel dainty.
And feeling dainty,
Miss Blair St. Clair,
I know you like to claim
you're a professional actress,
but being a decoy
on "To Catch a Predator"
is not a legit credit.
[all laugh]
And Michelle Visage,
never loved you.
[all laugh]
- Well, thank you, ladies.
The library for Season 10
is closed officially.
Aquaria, Asia O'Hara,
Eureka and Kameron Michaels,
in one week,
one of you will be crowned
America's next drag superstar
and win a year's supply
of Anastasia of Beverly Hills
cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100.000.
Next week, the Top Four
get to plead their cases,
but now I want to ask
the rest of our queens
who they think should be
America's next drag superstar.
Speak now
or forever hold your peace.
Mayhem.
- God, it's a hard choice
for me.
I really feel Aquaria
has shown how strong
of a competitor she is,
and I feel she has
the future of drag on her.
- Kalorie.
- Eureka.
I think it's time
for a big girl to win.
- Dusty.
- I would have to root
for my New York queen Aquaria.
She is someone who came in
and had the biggest
transformation as a person.
She's so kind,
she's so generous now.
I would even give her
Miss Congeniality
with the crown, really.
- Amen.
- Thank you, Dusty.
- Yuhua.
- I would have to pick Eureka.
She's fucking fierce.
- Monique.
- I said everybody
black and Aquaria,
so I want Asia O'Hara to win
because we need the example
of what she is as a person.
She's the queen I wanted to be,
and she's my queen.
- I love you.
- Miz Cracker.
- Came for me, came for me,
sent me home, Eureka.
Eureka, you win
by the process of elimination.
- [laughs]
- Blair?
- I think Asia O'Hara has such
an amazing voice behind her,
and I would love
to see her take that crown.
- Monet.
- I would have to pick
Asia O'Hara.
She's someone who did this
competition with her heart.
- Vanjie.
- I'm gonna pick Eureka,
'cause she is someone
who's been checking on me
all the time constantly.
She's a good sister to me,
and I think
you deserve it as well.
- I love you.
- All will be revealed
in one week
at the grand finale
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
Now I wanna hear from the fans.
This is your last chance
to let me know
who should be crowned
America's next drag superstar.
Are you #TeamAquaria,
#TeamAsia,
#TeamEureka,
or #TeamKameron.
Get posting on all your
social media and let me know.
Ladies, I want to thank
all of you
for sharing the love,
strength, and wisdom.
I may be the host of this show,
but you, all of you,
are my teachers.
Thank you.
I'll see everyone in one week
at the grand finale.
Now, if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
- Amen!
- Now let the music play.
[all singing]
♪ To-to-to to the moon ♪
- [laughs]
- ♪ To the moon ♪
- ♪ Come on
and take me away ♪
♪ To-to-to to the moon ♪