- ♪ Can you feel the love? ♪
- Live from the theater
at Ace Hotel
in downtown Los Angeles,
it's the grand finale
of "RuPaul's Drag Race
Season 10!"
[cheers and applause]
[alarm]
- Whoo, girl!
She done already
done had herses.
Howdy, racers.
[cheers and applause]
If you'd told me 10 years ago
that we'd be here tonight
celebrating a decade
of "Drag Race,"
I would have said, what
you talkin' 'bout, Willis?
Today, "RuPaul's Drag Race"
is a worldwide phenomenon,
and we owe it all
to the brave souls
who took one giant step
for dragkind
when they entered
the You Better Werk Room
for the very first time.
And now we get to thank
these drag pioneers.
Ladies and gentlemen,
here they are,
Season 1 queens
with Season 10 lighting.
All rise for the original cast
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ Give your all ♪
♪ So what if you fall? ♪
♪ Legends rise with attitude ♪
Victoria "Porkchop" Parker.
[cheers and applause]
Akashia.
Jade.
[cheers and applause]
Ongina.
Shannel.
[cheers and applause]
Rebecca Glasscock.
Nina Flowers.
[cheers and applause]
And our queen,
BeBe Zahara Benet.
- ♪ Legends rise with attitude ♪
♪ If you give your all ♪
♪ So what if you fall? ♪
♪ Legends rise with attitude ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Mother, we have one thing
to say.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
All: And may
the best woman win!
[cheers and applause]
- The winner
of "RuPaul's Drag Race"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100.000.
- ♪ May the best woman ♪
- ♪ Best woman win ♪
- Category is...
- Ladies and gentlemen,
the queens of "RuPaul's
Drag Race Season 10!"
- Start the music.
- She broke the internet,
Miss Vanessa Vanjie Mateo!
[cheers and applause]
[crowd chanting]
Vanjie, Vanjie, Vanjie!
- Miss Vanjie?
Miss Vanjie? Miss Vanjie?
Mwah!
[cheers and applause]
- She's got class, sass
and a whole lot of ass,
Kalorie Karbdashian Williams!
[cheers and applause]
Honk if you love her.
It's Yuhua Hamasaki!
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ That icy fire ♪
- Connect the dots,
it's Dusty Ray Bottoms!
- ♪ That icy fire ♪
- Start the music.
Start the music.
- She's here to start the party.
It's Mayhem Miller.
- ♪ Just wanna, oh, oh ♪
♪ Just wanna light you ♪
♪ Just wanna oh, oh ♪
♪ Just wanna light you up ♪
- I do declare,
it's Blair St. Clair!
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ Spotlight, spotlight ♪
♪ Ow, ow ♪
- She's the ooh-ah-ah sensation,
Monique Heart!
- ♪ That icy fire ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Serving Black Girl Magic,
it's The Vixen!
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ Oh, oh, you ♪
- Cha-ching!
Give it up
for Monet X Change!
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ You got the power ♪
♪ Hour after hour ♪
♪ I just wanna light you up ♪
- She's thin, white and salty.
She's Miz Cracker!
- ♪ Burning with desire ♪
♪ I just wanna light you up ♪
♪ You got the spotlight ♪
♪ Spotlight, spotlight ♪
♪ Baby, come on ♪
♪ Spotlight ♪
- And now our top four queens.
This is the dawning
of the age of Aquaria!
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ You got the spotlight ♪
♪ Hot, that icy fire ♪
♪ Burning with desire ♪
♪ I just wanna light you up ♪
- From Texas to the world,
it's Asia O'Hara!
- ♪ Baby, come on ♪
♪ Spotlight, spotlight ♪
[cheers and applause]
- We found her again.
It's Eureka!
- ♪ Just wanna light you ♪
♪ Just wanna light you up ♪
[cheers and applause]
♪ Spotlight, spotlight ♪
♪ Baby, come on ♪
- Behold the bodybuilder Barbie,
Kameron Michaels!
- ♪ Baby, come on ♪
♪ Spotlight, spotlight ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Give it up one more time
for the Queens of Season 10!
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ Charisma ♪
♪ Uniqueness ♪
♪ Nerve and talent ♪
- And now, ladies and gentlemen,
RuPaul!
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ Cha-ris-ris ♪
♪ Cha-- ♪
♪ Charisma ♪
♪ Uniqueness ♪
♪ Nerve and talent ♪
♪ Trust in the virtues ♪
♪ The rhythm within you ♪
♪ Let your body tell the truth ♪
♪ Let your body
tell the truth ♪
♪ Your body, your body ♪
♪ Your body,
body, body, body ♪
Give me that truth
one more time!
♪ Charisma ♪
♪ Uniqueness ♪
♪ Nerve and talent ♪
♪ Trust in the virtues ♪
♪ The rhythm within you ♪
♪ Let your body tell the truth ♪
[cheers and applause]
- To my Drag Race family
here tonight
and the millions of you
watching around the world,
welcome home, baby.
That's right.
Here in the House of RuPaul,
everybody is welcome.
There ain't no walls here
to divide us.
There's only love,
and now let's say it loud enough
so they could hear it
in Washington, D.C.
Everybody say love!
- Love!
- Everybody say love!
- Now drive that
down Pennsylvania Avenue!
Get your ass outta here!
[cheers and applause]
Tonight we are gathered
in this gorgeous theater
in downtown Los Angeles
to crown America's
next drag superstar.
But I couldn't do it alone.
Say hello to my Judge Judys,
Carson Kressley, Ross Mathews
and Michelle Visage.
[cheers and applause]
Now, how would you rate
this season's queens?
All: 10s! 10s!
10s across the board!
- Why y'all gagging?
She bring it to you every ball!
And, honey, it ain't over yet.
Aquaria, Asia O'Hara, Eureka
and Kameron Michaels,
you've made Mama Ru very proud.
Are you bitches ready
to lip sync for the crown?
[cheers and applause]
One by one, you'll battle.
And in the end, only one of you
will be crowned America's
Next Drag Superstar.
But before we get started,
I want to take a moment
to celebrate each of you.
First up, turning looks,
stunting pretty,
she's the bitch
from New York City.
Take a look.
- My name is Aquaria,
and I am a superstar.
I'm here to prove to people
that I actually do have the
chops that I say that I have.
I went with
Russia hooker urine.
[all laugh]
I can walk on this runway
in a diaper
and they would eat me up.
- Every week, you brought
amazing looks to the runway.
- It is an iconic
fashion moment.
- ♪ Turning looks,
stunting pretty ♪
♪ I'm the bitch
from New York City ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Hi, Aquaria.
- Hi, RuPaul. How are you?
- Now, you were never
in the bottom two.
- I'm not really into bottoming
as far as I know now.
But I am not necessarily
opposed to trying
or at least lip syncing.
- Yes, of course.
Well, now what's your strategy
for slaying
these lip syncs tonight?
- I've definitely learned
what the audiences like
and what the fans like from me,
which is for me to be me.
And I think I've tickled
your fancy
a couple of times on purpose,
by accident, either/or.
So I know how to impress you.
I know how to impress
the audience,
and I'm definitely here
to steal this show
and hopefully a check, so...
- Yeah. So now,
of all the top four,
who is the toughest queen
to take down tonight?
- Definitely,
the toughest to take down
seems to be Asia O'Hara.
She has been doing this for...
she has been doing drag
for nearly 46 years
or something like that
approximately.
And that's not age-ist.
That's just knowing that
she's proven herself
to be someone who is
fierce freaking competition.
- So, now, Aquaria, tell me.
Who are Gina and David
Palandrani?
- Not their government names.
- Are they from Philly?
- They are from Philly.
They are my beautiful mother
and father, so supportive.
- Whoo! Whoo-whoo!
- Now, I know
you have a restaurant.
Do you serve Philly cheesesteaks
at the restaurant?
- Well, where we live, you don't
call it a Philly cheesesteak.
- Oh, what do you call it?
- A cheesesteak.
- Oh.
[audience laughs]
- That's true.
- Mama Aquaria,
a little birdie told me
that you have a history
with one of our judges.
Actually, we have a photo
of your meeting
with one of our judges.
There you are.
- It's all coming back to me.
- What was the event
that you were at?
- Oh, "The Nutcracker."
- Was your Giovanni
in "The Nutcracker?"
- Yes, he was
The Nutcracker and--
- Oh! Giovanni
was The Nutcracker?
- Yes, he was,
and he had been cracking nuts
for a number of years.
[audience laughs]
- Aquaria, you should be
very proud that you have parents
who have supported you
from being The Nutcracker
to being a nut packer.
- [laughs]
- When we come back,
more with Aquaria.
- ♪ Hey, kitty girl ♪
♪ Get your twirl ♪
- Aah!
- ♪ In the disco heat ♪
♪ You're the boogie
body rockin' queen ♪
♪ Hey, kitty, kitty ♪
- Hey, RuPaul. I have to say
what an accomplishment,
and what "Drag Race's" influence
has been on our pop culture.
It's played such a role
in fostering a global message
of inclusion
and accepting individuals
for just being
their authentic selves.
And you and your show
have made that happen
in a way bigger
than anybody could imagine.
So congratulations to you all.
Thank you
for letting us all to see
that we're all
just humans in drag.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, my God.
Oprah! We love Oprah!
Oprah! [laughs]
Thank you, Oprah!
Okay, now we've got
some fan questions.
Let's go to the audience
and hear what they have to say.
First up is Jaymes Mansfield.
- Hi, Aquaria.
- Hey, shape shifter!
- Aquaria,
Ari from New York says,
I loved your Melania
in the Snatch Game.
How would you
make America great again?
Like truly great
and not just great for some?
- Facts are facts, America.
America's not great
for all right now.
And for me, I think
creating opportunity
for people to feel included,
whether it's within
our own community
or the country as a whole,
I think is very important.
As Melania Trump once said,
"Any hole is a goal."
[all laugh]
And I think that--
That cannot only apply
to something humorous,
but also creating opportunity
and filling that opportunity.
[cheers and applause]
Thank you.
- So what would it mean to you
to be crowned America's
next drag superstar?
- For me, I've been a fan
of this show since it started.
I remember catching Season 1.
Especially Nina Flowers, I was
like I don't know what it is,
but I see something
about me in her.
Let me be a fan of this
as long as I can.
And to go from that position
to literally
being in the Final Four
of probably the coolest season
of "Drag Race" ever.
[cheers and applause]
Facts are facts.
- And, finally, Aquaria,
I want to thank you
for giving me my new mantra.
Any hole is a goal.
Give it up for Aquaria,
everybody!
[cheers and applause]
Next, a queen
who's both motherly
and one bad ass mama.
Let's take a look.
- Texas is back in the house.
My name is Asia O'Hara.
I'm known for doing pageants,
but I'm also
a versatile performer.
With a "Baywatch" body, even
though she got a hurricane face.
[both laugh]
- Oh, my gosh!
Oh, I'm sorry.
- It's about to be
"Asia O'Hara's Drag Race."
I'm about to own
this whole building!
- You were one of the most
eye catching on the runway.
- You betcha!
♪ Her name
was etched in sorrow ♪
♪ But now
it's blasted in lights ♪
♪ She is stars and stripes
flying high ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Hi, Asia. How you doing?
- Good. How are you?
- So, Asia, who's rooting
for you tonight?
- Hopefully, the entire world,
but most importantly--
[cheers and applause]
But most importantly
my drag daughter Kiley
and my lovely boyfriend
Bret are here.
- So, Bret, how long
have you and Asia been together?
- A little over a year.
- So Mama Ru wants to know
what are your intentions
for my child here?
[all laugh]
[cheers and applause]
- We're going to get married.
- You are gonna get married?
[laughs]
Does he know about this?
- Well, he does now.
[all laugh]
- Now, Asia, we've got
some fan questions for you.
Let's see.
Oh, ladies and gentlemen,
it's Olympian Gus Kenworthy!
[cheers and applause]
You went to the Olympics!
- I did.
- Wow!
- It's like a straighter,
not as fun sporty version
of "Drag Race."
[both laugh]
Asia, Andre from Birmingham died
during your Buttrface
challenge,
and he wants to know have you
ever been catfished online.
- Oh, my God.
- Hoo!
- No!
[all laugh]
Yes, I have been catfished.
Unfortunately, people love
to catfish drag queens.
That is like a sport now.
- Really?
- And luckily
I didn't bite the bait,
but, yeah, I have been almost.
- Well, thank you, Gus.
- Thank you guys.
- Now, all season you were
lifting your fellow queens up.
What you gonna do
to tear these bitches down?
[cheers and applause]
- I'm not looking
at this experience
as an opportunity
to tear bitches down.
I'm looking at it
as an opportunity to show
that I'm the best person
for what you're trying to do.
- Ooh, bitch! [laughs]
- There we go!
- Asia, your parents passed away
several years ago.
And in case they're watching,
because, you know,
they get VH-1 in heaven,
what would you say to them?
- Oh.
- Asia, we love you!
- Thank you.
[cheers and applause]
I would say to my mom,
thank you for being
a symbol of excellence
for how people should help
other people down their roads.
And I would tell my father,
thank you for being
such a great example
of what type of man I should be.
Because it was through
dressing up like a woman
I learned how to be a man.
- All right.
[cheers and applause]
- Work! Work! Work!
- Last but not least,
I have talked to my lawyers
and I think I owe you an apology
for allegedly slapping you
this season.
- Yes.
- I would like to offer you
a chance to slap me.
[cheers and applause]
So go ahead, Asia.
Slap the one person
who brought you to "Drag Race."
[audience laughs]
The one person who stands
between you and $100.000.
I'm ready.
You can give it to me.
- Um, maybe I jumped the gun.
Maybe I should wait
and see how tonight plays out.
- Okay, sure.
[laughs]
Asia, all kidding aside,
thank you for reminding us
that kindness is cool.
Give it up for Asia O'Hara!
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ No, you ain't no lady ♪
♪ Oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ And you ain't
nobody's baby, baby ♪
- ♪ Charisma ♪
♪ Uniqueness ♪
- RuPaul, Michelle Visage,
this is to congratulate you
on your last 10 years.
It's brilliantly done,
and all I have to say is
shantay you stay.
And Finty
has to say to you...
- Good luck
and don't fuck it up.
- [laughs] Wow!
Welcome back to the grand finale
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
And thank you both.
You know, when I think about it,
the only queen Dame Judi Dench
hasn't played is me.
[audience laughs]
Now, once in a blue moon,
life gives you a second chance,
and this queen would be the
first to tell you all about it.
- Like a Phoenix from the ashes,
Eureka is back!
I got something to prove,
and I'm here
to fucking slay.
- Alana was amazing.
- Your mama. We do drag
to celebrate ourselves
in a political climate
where right now,
none of us feel like
we belong truly.
- The minute you said,
be yourself to free yourself,
I was just like...
- ♪ Watch me smile
and watch me slay ♪
♪ I'm living for my true self
every day ♪
♪ It's not about your color,
gender or size ♪
♪ But if we come together,
we can rise ♪
I'm the elephant queen!
What are you gonna be?
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, my goodness.
So tell me, Eureka,
what was it like watching
yourself this season?
- Honey, the camera definitely
adds 54 pounds.
- [laughs]
- You know.
- So tell me this.
Who are you looking forward
to lip syncing against tonight?
- I'm looking forward
to lip syncing against
all of them really
if it means I get the crown.
- Okay.
And what would you do
with $100.000?
- My mother raised me and my two
sisters as a single mother
and was put in debt
because of that,
also with her medical condition.
So what I would like to do is
I would like to actually
pay off all of those debts
and be able to give my family
a fresh start at life.
[cheers and applause]
- Well, hello, Mama Eureka
and Monique!
You're her twin sister?
- Yes.
- And who's
the more dominant twin?
- Obviously Eureka.
- [laughs]
- Honestly, being extra
is what makes her so wonderful.
- Yes.
- And you are gonna do it.
[cheers and applause]
- I love you, Mom.
- Thank you so much.
Okay, now time for
some fan questions.
Let's say hello
to Mariah Paris Bolenciaga!
[cheers and applause]
- All right, Miss Eureka,
us being two queens
from the south,
we know we love our snacks.
We love to savor, devour,
and then there's just some
to throw away.
That brings me to my question.
- [laughs]
Wait! Wait!
That was... [laughs]
That was the leadup
to the question?
[all laugh]
- So that brings me
to our question.
Shag, marry, kill
your top three fellow sisters.
- I would probably fuck Asia,
marry Kameron Michaels,
'cause she's quiet.
I talk a lot. I think
a match made in heaven.
- Uh-huh.
[all laugh]
- And I would kill Aquaria.
Why not?
[cheers and applause]
- And finally, Eureka,
your "Drag Race" experience
has been one wild ride.
What do you think it all means
sort of metaphysically speaking?
- I think it means
that we don't know the path
that we're designed,
and we have to follow that path
with our best foot forward
and as much positivity and joy
as you can.
What this path has done for me
is it has taught me
you have to care for the people
that love you the most
instead of worrying about
what society and what media
and what our peers
tells us we have to be.
We are so much more than that.
And we are family.
Treat each other like family.
- Thank you.
And remember, Eureka,
you're never too much.
You are everything.
- [laughs]
- Give it up for Eureka!
- Everything!
[cheers and applause]
- Next, a silent
but deadly queen
whose powerhouse lip syncs
took her all the way to the top.
Take a look.
- I'm Kameron Michaels,
and I'm the muscle queen
from Nashville, Tennessee.
Outside of drag, I am
a tatted muscle dude at the gym.
And then I tuck it back,
throw on some pads,
and walk out
looking fishy as fuck.
I like to think
I'm silent but deadly,
but maybe I need to be a
little more on the deadly side.
♪ Born in Cali,
mama named me Cherilyn ♪
- You set the bar
very, very high.
- I did not think
you could lip sync
the way that you lip sync,
bitch.
You can turn the party.
- ♪ I'm gay and proud,
might not be loud ♪
♪ But I found my sound ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Kameron Michaels!
Now, all season long,
you were underestimated,
and, bitch,
look at your ass now.
- I'm here!
- Yes!
[cheers and applause]
You lip synced four times.
Not many girls can pass three.
What's your secret
to the perfect lip sync?
- First and foremost,
we are entertainers.
And I think it's most important
to know your words.
- Mm-hmm. Yes.
Now, before "Cher, the Rusical,"
you failed to mention
that you actually do Cher
in your nightclub act.
- Did I not say that?
Did I keep that from everybody?
- You certainly did. Now,
does that make you a quiet queen
or a shady queen?
- That may have been
a little more shady.
- Yes. [laughs]
Now, Kameron, get ready,
because we have some
fan questions for you.
- Perfect.
- BeBe Zahara Benet!
- Hi, delta cutie.
- Hi, beautiful.
- Jesse from Seattle
wants to know
do you get laid more in drag
or out of drag?
We want to know, Kameron.
Tell us, bitch, tell us.
- You know what?
I don't have time!
I get four hours of sleep,
and I need all four hours.
I'm not giving that hour
or 30 minutes
or however long it takes
to anyone!
- So, Kameron, who's here
supporting you tonight?
- Here supporting me tonight
is one of my very best friends
for over a decade
who did about
three-fourths of the stuff
that you saw on the show.
And his name is Ryan.
- Hi, Ryan.
- Hi.
- And my amazing, lovely,
super supportive mother Vicky.
- Hello, Mother Michaels.
- Hi, Ru.
- When Kameron's in drag,
what family member
does Kameron look like?
- Me.
- Oh, okay.
Now, you guys share clothing?
- We do.
- And you have
the same shoe size?
- Yes, we do.
- How is that?
Girl, you must have
some big ass feet.
- I do, I do.
- Now, Kameron, our ratings this
season are higher than ever,
and thanks to you,
we've been attracting
a whole new demographic.
Take a look.
- Hello, Dane.
This is grandma.
I saw you on "Drag Race,"
and I am very, very shocked
at the talent
and what you have accomplished.
And I am so proud of you.
And I love you dearly,
and I always will.
- Oh, wow!
Gorgeous.
- My grandmother loves me.
I am her only grandchild.
She is the mother of my father
who's passed away.
Coming from a really religious
background and family,
I was very worried
what she would think of me
and how she would react
when she found out.
So to see that and know
that she still loves me
and supports me no matter what
is really amazing.
- See? I'm gonna say it again.
"RuPaul's Drag Race,"
still bringing families together
after all these years.
Ladies and gentlemen, give it up
for Kameron Michaels.
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ This is the main event ♪
♪ Are you ready? ♪
♪ Just let the music
dance into your soul ♪
♪ This is the main event ♪
♪ Are you ready? ♪
♪ Just let the music
dance into your soul ♪
- Welcome back to the grand
finale of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
Tonight we celebrate
10 wonderful years
of tears, triumphs
and tongue pops.
Unfortunately, due to a severe
case of wig water poisoning,
I can't remember any of it!
So with the help of super fan
Sally Jesse Raphael,
let's turn back time.
- The year was 2008.
Nine queens sashayed
into a little TV studio.
- It is my pleasure
to have you all here
at "RuPaul's Drag Race."
- Where they experienced
some very harsh lighting.
Little did they know
that they would be changing
herstory forever.
Soon change was in the air.
- All our equal, all are free.
- And we celebrated
the art of drag.
- These girls are given
production values.
- Okay.
- With sickening challenges.
- Baloney!
- That made us laugh...
- Get those nuts
away from my face.
- H-h-ham!
- Change.
- Gag...
- [gags]
- Oh!
- I'd like to keep it on,
please.
- I'm going home.
- What's going on here?
- And cry.
- I've been living with HIV for
the last two years of my life.
- My mother left my sister
and myself at a bus stop
when I was three.
- We are a family here.
- Always served
with a deep sense of love.
- [gasps] Uh!
- Soon the secret was out.
- Say hello
to Christina Aguilera.
- ♪ Oh ♪
- Mother Monster has arrived.
- Yes, Gaga!
[cheering]
- And "Drag Race" became
a national obsession...
- Okur?
- And an international
phenomenon.
- So they are supposed
to hire y'all hookers
to seduce the gays?
- Yeah.
- Growing up,
I never could have dreamed
that this day would come.
- In 2015, love won
and so did Violet Chachki.
- Congrats!
- Drag queens became superstars.
- Hello. This is what
makes me money.
This is what people hire to see.
- It even started
a whole new economy.
- Drag Con L.A. 2018!
[cheering]
- And, honey, we are
just getting started.
10 years later,
instead of focusing on
the things that divide us,
"RuPaul's Drag Race" celebrates
what brings us together.
- The night that Donald Trump
was elected president,
I watched five
back-to-back episodes
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
- Bob the Drag Queen
for president.
- I was basically watching
the version of America
that I wanted to live in
rather than watching the one
that was unfolding
in front of history.
- And the mission is as clear
as it was from day one.
- Everybody say love!
- Love!
- To take over
the mothertucking world...
- We will always be here,
and we have always been here.
- One death drop at a time.
[screams and cheers]
[cheers and applause]
- Now, before our Top Four
lip sync for the crown,
I have an extra special treat
for you all.
For the first time
in "Drag Race" herstory,
a mega mix that's
a decade in the making.
Please welcome to the stage
the queens of Season 1
versus the queens of Season 10
in a lip sync
eleganza extravaganza!
Hit it!
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ Cover Girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe
let your whole body talk ♪
♪ Cover Girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe
let your whole body talk ♪
- ♪ No, no, no, no ♪
♪ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ♪
♪ They say that you are not ♪
♪ But I always see you looking ♪
♪ Don't be jealous
of my boogie ♪
♪ They say that you are not ♪
♪ But I always see you
looking at me ♪
♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ Greatest of them all ♪
♪ Never gonna fall ♪
♪ You're a champion ♪
♪ Still standing tall ♪
♪ And you'll always be a hero ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh-oh ♪
♪ All the boys say ♪
♪ She's so wild, so animal ♪
♪ She's gonna work
that sexy body, so sexual ♪
♪ She's like
a female phenomenon ♪
♪ She's a GLAMAZON ♪
♪ Female phenomenon ♪
♪ A GLAMAZON, nah-nah-nah ♪
♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ The beginning ♪
♪ This is the beginning
of the rest of your life ♪
♪ This is the beginning ♪
♪ The beginning ♪
♪ This is the beginning
of the rest of your life ♪
♪ And if I fly
or if I fall ♪
♪ At least I can say
I gave it all ♪
♪ And if I fly
or if I fall ♪
♪ I'm on my way ♪
♪ Now sissy that walk ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Who do you think you are? ♪
♪ I'm telling the truth now ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Who do you think you are? ♪
♪ We're all born naked,
and the rest is drag ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
♪ My love is real ♪
♪ The realness ♪
♪ The-the realness ♪
♪ Catch it, touch it,
touch it, catch it ♪
♪ Flavor of this fever ♪
♪ The realness ♪
♪ The-the realness ♪
♪ Catch it, touch it,
touch it, catch it ♪
♪ Flavor of this fever ♪
♪ Ladies and gentlemen,
for your consideration ♪
♪ Bring it to the runway ♪
♪ Runway, run-run-r-r-r-runway ♪
♪ Bring it to the runway,
bring it to the runway ♪
♪ Bring it to, bring it to,
♪ Category is ♪
♪ I am American, American,
American ♪
the red, white and blue ♪
♪ American, American,
American ♪
♪ I am American, American,
just like you, too ♪
[cheers and applause]
♪ I am American, American,
American ♪
the red, white and blue ♪
♪ I am American, American,
American ♪
just like you, too ♪
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ This is the beginning
of the rest of your life ♪
- Welcome back to the grand
finale of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
Ladies and gentlemen,
the time has come.
Bring back my girls.
Give it up for our top four!
Aquaria!
- ♪ The realness ♪
- Asia O'Hara!
Eureka!
- ♪ The realness ♪
- Kameron Michaels!
Welcome back, ladies.
You've waited all season
for this moment.
But first, to explain
how this legendary lip sync
for the crown will go down,
here's our very own
Carson Kressley.
- Thank you, RuPaul.
Tonight's lip sync smackdown
is going to be bigger.
- Bigger!
- Louder.
- Louder!
- Queenier than ever.
- Queenier!
- Four sickening queens entered,
but only one will survive.
First, a spin of the wheel
determines which two tuck titans
will face off
in lip sync number one.
Then the remaining two glamazons
fight to the death
in lip sync number two!
Then those two finalists
will battle head-to-head,
camel toe-to-camel toe,
for the final lip sync
for the crown!
Ru, this is going to be epic!
Ooh! It was like someone else
was inside my body.
Anyway, back to you, Ru.
- [laughs]
Thank you, Carson.
- No, no, no.
Sit down, everybody.
Sit down. Sit down.
- Now, on this wheel are
the faces of our top four.
Wherever the wheel stops
will determine which queen
lip syncs first.
Ladies, are you ready?
- Yes.
- Yes, ma'am.
- All right, here we go.
I'm so glad I stretched.
[all laugh]
[cheers and applause]
All right, the wheel has spoken.
Kameron Michaels,
you will be competing
in tonight's first
lip sync for the crown.
And now it's your turn to pick
who you will lip sync against
in this first round.
Who do you choose?
- I didn't want to do this!
Um...
I think my choice
is going to be Asia O'Hara.
[cheers and applause]
- All right.
That means Aquaria, Eureka,
you two will face off
in tonight's second
lip sync coming up next.
You may leave the stage.
[cheers and applause]
Now, Asia,
it's your turn to choose.
Oh, pit crew?
[cheers and applause]
Each of these boxes
contains one of my favorite
Janet Jackson lip sync songs.
[cheers and applause]
Asia O'Hara,
are you ready to pick?
- Absolutely.
- Good.
Do you choose box number one
or box number two?
- Always number one.
- Jason, open your box.
"Nasty" by Janet Jackson!
Oh, bitch,
this is gonna be good.
Okay, ladies,
assume the position.
[cheers and applause]
Two queens stand behind me.
[audience laughs]
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing] for the crown.
[cheers and applause]
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
- Gimme a beat!
♪ Sittin' in the movie show ♪
♪ Thinkin' nasty thoughts, huh ♪
♪ Better be a gentlemen ♪
♪ Or you turn me off, huh ♪
♪ That's right,
a-let me tell it ♪
♪ Nasty ♪
♪ Nasty boys,
don't mean a thing, huh ♪
♪ Oh, you nasty boys ♪
♪ Nasty ♪
♪ Nasty boys,
don't ever change, huh ♪
♪ Oh, you nasty boys ♪
♪ I could learn to like this ♪
♪ Listen up ♪
♪ I'm not a prude ♪
♪ I just want some respect ♪
- ♪ That's right ♪
- ♪ So close the door
if you want me to respond ♪
- ♪ Ooh, ooh, yeah ♪
- ♪ 'Cause privacy
is my middle name ♪
♪ My last name is Control ♪
♪ No, my first name ain't baby ♪
♪ It's Janet ♪
♪ Miss Jackson if you're nasty ♪
♪ Nasty ♪
♪ Nasty boys,
don't mean a thing ♪
♪ Oh, you nasty boys ♪
♪ Nasty ♪
♪ Nasty boys,
don't ever change, huh ♪
♪ Oh, you nasty boys ♪
Hey!
♪ Who's that
thinkin' nasty thoughts? ♪
- ♪ Nasty boys ♪
- ♪ Who's that
in that nasty car? ♪
- ♪ Nasty boys ♪
- ♪ Who's that eating
that nasty food? ♪
- ♪ Nasty boys ♪
- ♪ Who's jamming
to my nasty groove? ♪
- ♪ Nasty boys ♪
- ♪ Ladies ♪
♪ Nasty boys ♪
♪ Don't mean a thing, huh ♪
♪ Oh, you nasty boys, huh ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Well, ladies,
I've made my decision.
The winner of tonight's
first lip sync,
the queen moving on
to the final lip sync
for the crown,
will be...
revealed
after this brief message.
[audience cheers and groans]
We'll be right back.
- ♪ To the moon ♪
- Welcome back to the grand
finale of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
Asia O'Hara, Kameron Michaels,
I've made my decision.
Kameron Michaels,
shantay you stay.
[cheers and applause]
Con-drag-ulations.
You are moving on
to the finals.
Now head on backstage
and get ready to lip sync
for the crown.
[cheers and applause]
Asia O'Hara, I'm sorry, my dear,
but this is not your time.
But I want to thank you
for making it
such a sickening season.
Now sashay away.
- ♪ I want you to remember me ♪
[cheers and applause]
♪ I want you to remember me ♪
♪ Being who I wanna be ♪
♪ Turn it on,
then you'll see ♪
♪ Snap shot ♪
- Welcome back to the stage
Aquaria and Eureka!
[cheers and applause]
Aquaria, Eureka, let's find out
which song
you'll be lip syncing to.
Oh, pit crew?
Well, hello, Sean.
- Hello.
- Let's see what you got
in your box.
"If" by Janet Jackson.
Thank you, Sean.
Aquaria, Eureka,
assume the position.
Two queens stand behind me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing] for the crown!
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
- ♪ Sittin' over here
starin' in your face ♪
♪ With lust in my eyes,
sure don't give a damn
♪ And ya don't know that
I've been dreamin' of ya ♪
♪ In my fantasies ♪
♪ Never once you looked at me ♪
♪ Don't even realize
that I'm wantin' you ♪
♪ To fulfill my needs ♪
♪ Think what you want,
let your mind free ♪
♪ Run free to a place
no one dares to ♪
♪ How many night I've laid
in bed excited over you ♪
♪ I've closed my eyes ♪
♪ And thought of us
a hundred different ways ♪
♪ I've gotten there
so many times ♪
♪ I wonder how 'bout you? ♪
♪ Day and night, night and day ♪
♪ All I've got to say is ♪
♪ If I was your girl ♪
♪ Oh, the things I'd do to you ♪
♪ I'd make you
call out my name ♪
♪ I'd ask who it belongs to ♪
♪ If I was your woman ♪
♪ The things I'd do to you ♪
♪ But I'm not, so I can't ♪
♪ Then I won't,
but if I was your girl ♪
♪ I've laid in bed
excited over you ♪
♪ One hundred different ways
I've thought ya ♪
♪ Many, many ♪
♪ All I got to say is ♪
♪ If I was your girl,
oh, the things I'd do to you ♪
♪ I'd make you
call out my name ♪
♪ I'd ask who it belongs to ♪
♪ If I was your woman ♪
♪ The things I'd do to you ♪
♪ But I'm not, so I can't ♪
♪ Then I won't ♪
♪ But if I was your girl ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Ladies,
I have made my decision.
Shantay you both stay.
[cheers and applause]
Con-drag-ulations.
You've both made it
to the finals.
[cheers and applause]
Now get outta here
and get ready for
the ultimate battle royale.
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ Hey, kitty girl ♪
- ♪ Charisma ♪
♪ Uniqueness ♪
- Welcome back.
All rise for the original
Miss Congeniality from Season 1,
Nina Flowers!
- ♪ Cha-cha, bitch ♪
[cheers and applause]
♪ Cha-cha, bitch ♪
♪ Five, six, cha-cha, bitch ♪
♪ Bien perra ♪
♪ Cha-cha-cha-cha-
cha-cha-cha-cha-cha ♪
- [laughs]
My original Cha-Cha bitch.
Nina, darling, how are you?
- I'm doing fantastic!
What about you? Look out!
[cheers and applause]
Yes!
- Now, Nina,
I have some breaking news.
The online election
to determine this year's
Miss Congeniality
was made null and void
due to outside interference.
[audience laughs]
But unlike those other
shady elections,
we're doing something about it.
[cheers and applause]
We decided to have
Season 10 queens vote
and decide which queen they want
to be Miss Congeniality.
- Work.
- Yes.
And here to announce
the results of that vote
from the Werq the World Tour,
last year's winner, Valentina.
[cheers and applause]
- Hello, Ru. Hello, everybody!
Buenas tardes from Berlin!
- Hi!
- Hi, Ru. I wanted to thank you
for changing my life.
[cheers and applause]
And I want to thank
my lovely fans
for voting me
your Miss Congeniality.
[cheers and applause]
And last but not least,
I would like to thank Aja
for naming me fan favorite.
[cheers and applause]
Oh-ho, but enough about me,
Valentina.
[cheering]
The winner
of Miss Congeniality is...
[drum roll]
Monet X Change!
[cheers and applause]
- Shut up!
Me?
No way!
Yes!
Thank you, Ru!
Mwah, mwah.
Yes!
Whoo! This is nice!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, I love this!
- Now, Monet, is there anything
you'd like to say?
- Soak it up, bitches!
[cheers and applause]
- Now as America's
next drag superstar,
this next queen
has dragged her charisma,
uniqueness, nerve and talent
around the globe.
And tonight, she's back
to crown a winner, baby.
All hail our reigning queen,
Sasha Velour!
- ♪ You wear it well ♪
♪ French tip, lipstick,
painted on ♪
♪ You wear it well ♪
♪ Value sure suits you-oo-oo ♪
♪ Work it for me ♪
♪ Work it for me, me ♪
♪ You wear it, you wear it,
you wear it well ♪
♪ Wig shop,
nonstop hair salon ♪
♪ You wear it well ♪
♪ Value, brand new,
ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Work it for me ♪
♪ Work it for me, me ♪
♪ You wear it, you wear it,
you wear it well ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Sasha Velour.
Last season
you won a lip sync battle
that could only be described
as a war of the roses!
What has this past year
been like for you?
- Absolutely out of this world
amazing.
In all seriousness,
I've been able to travel
and meet queer people
all around the world
inspired by this show
to keep fighting and thriving.
It's inspirational.
- I love that.
[cheers and applause]
Thank you, Sasha.
All right, children.
We are now just moments away
from a three-way lip sync
for the crown.
Don't go anywhere!
- ♪ Come on, let me see you
rock this town ♪
♪ With you all now ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Rock it, baby, rock it, baby ♪
♪ Hey, kitty girl,
it's your world ♪
♪ When you walk the street,
steppin' to the beat ♪
- Welcome back to the grand
finale of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
Ladies and gentlemen,
one of these three queens
will be named America's
next drag superstar.
I present to you Aquaria,
Eureka and Kameron Michaels!
- ♪ American, American,
American ♪
♪ I am American, American
just like you, too ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Ladies, every single thing
you've done in your entire life
has led you to this moment.
So take a deep breath,
and for the last time
this season,
assume the position.
[cheers and applause]
Three queens stand behind me.
Prior to tonight,
you were asked to prepare
a lip sync performance
of "Bang Bang" by Jessie J,
Ariana Grande and Nicki Minaj.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and prove to the world
that you are America's
next drag superstar.
The time has come to lip sync...
[echoing] for the crown!
[cheers and applause]
Let's go.
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
- ♪ She got a body
like an hour glass ♪
♪ But I can give it to you
all the time ♪
♪ She got a booty
like a Cadillac ♪
♪ But I can send you
into overdrive, oh ♪
♪ You've been waiting
for that ♪
♪ Step on up, swing your bat ♪
♪ See, anybody
could be bad to you ♪
♪ You need a good girl
to blow your mind, yeah ♪
♪ Bang, bang into the room,
I know ya want it ♪
♪ Bang, bang all over you,
I'll let ya have it ♪
♪ Wait a minute,
lemme take you there, ah ♪
♪ Wait a minute till ya--ah ♪
♪ She might've let you
hold her hand in school ♪
♪ But Imma show you
how to graduate ♪
♪ No, I don't need to hear you
talk the talk ♪
♪ Just come and show me
what your mama gave, oh, yeah ♪
♪ Okay, you've got
a very big shh ♪
♪ Mouth, but don't say a thing ♪
♪ See, anybody
could be good to you ♪
♪ You need a bad girl
to blow your mind ♪
♪ It's Myx Moscato,
it's frizz in a bottle ♪
♪ It's Nicki full throttle,
it's oh, oh ♪
♪ Swimming in the grotto,
we winning in the lotto ♪
♪ We dipping
in the pot of blue foam ♪
♪ Kitten so good,
it's drippin' on wood ♪
♪ Get a ride
in the engine that could go ♪
♪ Batman-Robin it,
bang, bang, cocking it ♪
♪ Queen Nicki dominant,
prominent ♪
♪ B to da A to da N
to da G to da, uh, baby ♪
to da G to da--hey ♪
♪ See, anybody
could be good to you ♪
♪ You need a bad girl
to blow your mind, your mind ♪
♪ Bang, bang into the room,
I know ya want it ♪
♪ Bang, bang all over you,
I'll let ya have it ♪
♪ Wait a minute,
lemme take you there, ah ♪
♪ Wait a minute till ya--ah ♪
♪ Bang, bang there goes
your heart, I know ya want it ♪
♪ Back, back seat of my car,
I'll let ya have it ♪
♪ Wait a minute,
lemme take you there, ah ♪
♪ Wait a minute till ya--ah ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Wow!
Ladies,
in addition to the title
of America's
next drag superstar,
the winner
of "RuPaul's Drag Race"
will receive a crown and scepter
provided by Fierce! Drag Jewels,
a year's supply of makeup
from Anastasia Beverly Hills,
and a cash prize
of $100.000.
Yes.
[cheers and applause]
Now the time has come
to crown our queen.
Ladies, I've made my decision.
The winner
of "RuPaul's Drag Race,"
America's
next drag superstar is...
Aquaria.
[cheers and applause]
Is there anything
you'd like to say?
- Sometimes in life, you're not
always given a second chance.
But if you do,
take advantage of it
and go out with a bang!
[cheers and applause]
- My Queen!
There's my queen!
- ♪ To-to-to-to to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
- And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
- Amen!
- All right.
Now let the music play!
- To the moon,
to the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To-to-to to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon,
to the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To-to-to to the moon ♪