[RuPaul] Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
You'll be performing
in Trump! The Rusical!
♪ Power to the pussy ♪
Ladies,
this is a teaching moment.
I can't believe what
I'm saying right now,
but listen to this.
[RuPaul] Scarlet Envy,
good job casting this week.
Mercedes Iman Diamond.
[Ross] You just sort
of disappeared.
[RuPaul] Ra'Jah O'Hara.
[Tiffany] I really didn't
see you punch it up.
[Ross] ♪ Silky Ganache ♪
You are the winner
of this weeks' challenge.
Ra'Jah O'Hara,
shantay, you stay.
Mercedes Iman Diamond,
sashay away.
Whew.
Oh, cyst.
Live to breathe another day.
[Yvie] Mercedes went home.
I'm a little heartbroken
to see her go,
because she is a sweetheart,
but she wasn't
a strong contender,
and I'm ready to thin the pack.
"It was so great
meeting you girls.
Love y'all. Mercedes."
-Aww.
-We love you, too, bitch.
[all] ♪ Ay-li-li-li-li-li-li ♪
♪ A-ya-ya-ya! ♪
[Ra'Jah] Going forward,
my strategy is just
to project positive energy,
because I always go to
the negative in any situation.
My God, give me a piece
of this couch. Ooh!
[Nina] Big silk, looks like
the milk is good.
Congratulations, mama.
-Yas.
-Congrats, girl.
-Well deserved, all right!
-Yeah.
[Scarlet] I feel
like we all shined,
and I got the validation
I needed
with Ru's comment to me about
like how well it was casted.
And I feel totally fine with it.
[Scarlet] Ru made it a point
to let me know I did a good job.
So, yes,
as the casting director,
I'm going to bask in the glory
that is that sunshine.
[Ariel] Girl, delusions.
Every time Scarlet speaks,
it's a giant eye roll.
It's not like she was giving us
the directions.
We all did the damn thing, and
it had nothing to do with her.
[Silky] I just wanted to send
all of you an invitation
to come we havin' a girls' trip.
But you have to leave
your man at home.
Okay, so what about
Brooke Lynn and Vangie?
[all laugh]
You know, I've been noticing
here lately, you know,
a lot of chemistry
between you and Brooke Lynn.
What exactly is going on?
Brooke Lynn's
a good friend of mine.
-A really good friend.
-[laughs]
We have a crush on each other.
Me and Vanjie have a crush
on each other,
and we'll see where it goes.
[giggles]
I think Vanjie's really cute,
and we're just getting
to know each other.
[Vanjie] It's real fresh,
out the womb.
You know,
I'm going with the flow.
If those kisses keep coming,
I'm gonna keep accepting.
Yes!
[cheering]
If you know what I'm saying.
Thank God I came back to that.
[all laugh]
This bitch
ain't fucking going home,
not when my jush is here.
[all laugh]
I'm grateful to be here
for another week.
I'm glad I didn't have
to fucking lip sync, girl.
But if I have to do that shit
every fucking week,
if that's how I have to fight
to stay here, I will do it.
Because I feel
the most comfortable
when I am on stage
living and getting my jush.
Yeah, girl, but when
are you going to apply that
to the challenges, because
that's what's going to keep you
out of the bottom.
Now, I will tell you this.
Don't try me right now.
That's not trying you, girl.
That's being honest.
No, but no, no, no, no, no.
That's the Tee, girl.
You better take
that tone back down.
[Yvie] She says
my least favorite thing
to ever hear on this show,
which is, well,
I'll lip sync every week
if that means I'm going
to get my way there.
And I'm just like, girl,
even if you pack every
other girl up this season,
do you really think Ru's
gonna put the crown on your head
if you're not delivering
in the challenges?
[Ra'Jah] Bitch. How dare you?
You, first and foremost
are not sickening at all.
You are literally
wearing trash.
I'm not gagging.
I mean, I'm gagging from like...
[sniffs] the smell.
It's like bitch do you bathe?
What I'm saying is
what I have to do
is silence all of these demons,
all of this extra
outside/inside noise,
and prove who I am by
continuing to be true to myself.
Ra'Jah's so full of shit.
Ra'Jah feels very attacked by
me
telling her to step her game up,
because it's the truth.
[Yvie] I just don't like it
if a bitch is not going to like
actually learn a lesson,
especially if you keep giving
the bullshit excuses
of like, oh, well, I'll try
harder next time, girl.
What happened to this time?
[Ra'Jah] Miss Yvie,
get over yourself.
At the end of the day,
you will catch
this motherfucking fade,
so keep it on mute.
'Cause, bitch,
I'm not from Denver.
I'm from fucking Dallas.
The Big D.
[RuPaul] The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100.000.
With extra special
guest judges
Cara Delevingne
and Elvira.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
[car tires screech]
Oh, another day.
-Girl.
-Yeah, eh-eh-eh-eh.
[Scarlet] The sun came up,
and so did I. I'm still here.
[Nina] I think we have
a couple name for you guys.
-Oh, yeah?
-Okay, what is it?
Branjie.
-Branjie.
Branjie. That's going to be
their new T-shirt
and their new merch
and the new hats.
So you're welcome.
What are the other couples--
My man left me,
but I'm working on another one.
[Brooke Lynn]
Who's your next man?
[all laugh]
[Vanjie]
Not in the eyes, I said.
[cheers and laughter]
[Vanjie] Oh, my God!
Big mama got to
give it to you, honey.
Hold on.
I don't know
if I'm ready for this.
[laughter]
I want to see tongue.
[screams and laughter]
[alarm]
Thank God.
[RuPaul] She done already
done had herses.
My tricks and treats,
whether you're a creature
from the black dragoon,
or a rocky horror show,
America's next drag superstar
needs to be unspookable.
Ooh.
Happy hallo-queens, boo.
[cheers and applause]
Hello, hello, hello.
[cheers]
Come on, green.
All right, be honest.
Who here played with dolls
as a kid?
All of us.
Good answer, because I'm
introducing a new RuPaul doll.
Available exclusively
at integritytoys.com.
[all laugh]
Yes!
So for today's Mini Challenge,
you need to transform yourself
into a living doll
that can be my doll's BFF.
Ready, set...
Oh, wait a minute.
Guess who I found
hiding behind the wig heads
in my dressing room?
Hello, hello, hello.
It's our very own backwoods
Barbie, Trixie Mattel.
[cheers and laughter]
[Shuga] Girl, Trixie is here.
She is the winner
of All Stars 3.
I love this queen.
-Hi, Trixie.
-Hi, RuPaul and RuPaul.
[all laugh]
What's the secret
to being a best friend?
Well, you wanna be nice
to everybody
because you never know when it's
gonna come down to a jury vote.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] All right, ladies,
you've got 20 minutes
to get all dolled up.
And I'll meet you
on the green screen.
Ready, set, go.
[Trixie] Some of that
is actually mine,
but I guess you can have it.
Get off my ass, you bitch.
[Brooke Lynn] It's like it's
a fucking sample sale
at Christian Louboutin
and everyone's
just like aah, aah.
[Trixie] I'm not hearing
any makeup brushes.
I should hear your skin
coming off your face.
[all laugh]
What's your name?
-I'm Scarlet.
-I already forgot.
[all laugh]
What are you doing?
I'm a penitentiary doll.
I actually killed a couple of
girls to be Ru's best friend.
Are you sure
you're not Michelle?
[all laugh]
So I have to ask.
What makes you think RuPaul's
best friend is a crash dummy?
[laughs]
Seeing all the people
she's crowned.
[all laugh]
So funny.
Welcome to
the Valley of the Dolls.
First up, Plastique Tiara.
[Trixie] Meet Plastique.
She's not just a supermodel,
she's also a manicurist.
If you give her
too much wig water,
she develops back rolls.
Back rolls?
Spring rolls?
[RuPaul laughs]
Meet Gloria Freebush,
RuPaul's feminist bestie.
When you pull her string,
her pussy grabs back.
[Trixie laughs]
Meet Laurena Maria Prudencia
Lisa de la Boom Badaboom.
Her friends call her Flaquita.
[Trixie] The hair
and that animal print
is vaguely familiar.
Have you been to Cameroon?
[RuPaul laughs]
[RuPaul] Meet Sticky
Finger Silky.
A lot of dolls drive
fancy pink sports cars,
but she drives
a doughnut truck.
Her box is stuffed
with all kinds
of fun-to-play-with
accessories,
like bootleg CDs and chips.
Dips not included.
Uranium Yvie.
Kids love to play with her
because they can shave
her periodic table
and watch the hair grow back.
[Trixie laughs]
[Trixie] Meet Awesome Ariel.
She's full of surprises.
When you pull her string,
she swallows.
Awesome Ariel
can't move her face,
but she can bend her neck,
her back,
from her pussy to her crack.
[RuPaul] Meet Stupid Scarlet.
She lives
in a state of judgment,
because she loves to hate.
[Trixie]
Cheap wig and a pink dress.
A woman after my own heart.
[RuPaul laughs]
[Trixie] Meet
Starr-Keisha Booty La'RaJah.
She might have smaller feet
than RuPaul,
but her badonkadonk
is enormous.
Her box is stuffed
with all kinds of
fun-to-play-with accessories,
like an extra-large cup
of drank.
[RuPaul laughs]
A lot of dolls drive
fancy pink sports cars,
but she drives a bus.
She's not just a doll,
she's a bad bitch.
Meet Bachelorette Brandy.
Her favorite hobbies
are cocktails,
peeing behind dumpsters,
and telling everyone
she's getting married.
I know that girl.
She's always a hit at parties,
because her hips
are double jointed.
Oh, Katya's here.
[RuPaul laughs]
[RuPaul] Meet Miss Vangie.
Trixie, I'm coming
for your gig, girl.
I do have a broken suitcase.
[RuPaul] Vanessa Mateo
is attending night school
at the University of Hookin'
to get her degree
in stripperology.
Whoo. Oh.
[laughs]
Did y'all get it?
[RuPaul laughs]
[RuPaul] She's not just a doll,
she's a Miss Vanjie.
[Trixie] Meet A'Keria.
Her friends call her
inmate 304.
When you pull her string,
she pulls a blade
from under her wig.
You know, in prison
she's armed and dangerous.
-Well, one-armed.
-One-armed and dangerous.
[RuPaul laughs]
[RuPaul] Nice work, dolls.
But one of you really
melted my plastic heart.
[all laugh]
The winner of today's
Mini Challenge is...
Ra'Jah O'Hara.
[cheers and applause]
Yes!
You've won
a $1.000 gift card
from Coolhaus Ice Cream.
-I'll take it.
-Ooh.
Trixie, thank you
for playing today.
Do you have any parting words
for my girls?
Winning isn't everything,
but it's super fucking awesome.
[all laugh]
-Byeee!
-Byeee.
The helicopters are circling.
I gotta go.
[all laugh]
Ladies, you know what
a drag queen calls Halloween?
What?
Amateur night.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] That's right.
It is time for you to show
the children how it's done.
For this week's Maxi Challenge,
baby, we are throwing us a ball.
[cheers and applause]
But not just
any old ball, darling.
We are throwing
a Monster Ball.
[cheering]
Now, you need to scare up
three lurks.
First lurk,
Trampy Trick or Treater.
You know, like, Naughty Nurse
or Dirty Doctor
or Sexy Soccer Mom.
[all laugh]
Second look, Witch, Please.
You know, like broomsticks,
bubbling cauldrons
and things of that nature.
And for your third lurk,
you need to design and create
a look that serves
both beauty and beast.
[all laugh]
Category is MILF Eleganza,
as in Monsters I'd
Like to Freak.
[cheers and applause]
Age!
For your MILF looks,
you can use these items here,
more materials
from the FandS Fabrics wall.
So good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
All right?
[all] All right.
[applause]
[Yvie] Our challenge today
is the Monster's Ball.
Because it's a ball, you have
to serve in three categories.
There's Trampy Trick
or Treater realness,
Witch Please!,
and Monster I'd Like to Freak.
What if I made the dress
out of this red pleather,
because I got enough
to make a whole--a full dress.
Right. What you wanna do?
I don't know.
I'm a devil.
What's a little devil wear,
honey?
Prada.
[all laugh]
And see, like, bitch,
I can cut this fur off
and put red on them.
That looks like werewolf, no?
-That's giving werewolf.
-Yeah.
[Silky] In this competition,
there are cliques.
I am closest to the dream girls,
and the dream girls consist
of me, A'Keria, and Miss Vanjie.
You're complicating it
more than what it--
Yeah, you're making it hard.
You're making it
real complicated.
Do something that's gonna
make you look fierce.
The dream girls are gonna
be the top three. Duh.
I'm gonna do
this big mermaid bottom,
'cause ain't nobody
gonna do that.
Okay, bitch, I think I got it.
[Yvie] With Silky,
the judges have been
sort of lenient
on her style issues
because of her personality.
Which like isn't a bad thing,
but I don't think she gets
she can't ride her
personality train to the end,
especially in challenges
where she's not comfortable.
Bitch.
I have to remake this.
I'm not too fond of Halloween.
I'm not a spooky bitch.
If you want to see me in a ball,
honey, just go for realness.
So in this challenge,
I want to emphasize
more on the freak part,
not really a monster.
I just want to show that
there's more than spook to me,
unlike some of the other ho's
in this competition.
You watching, so you know
who the ho's are.
I may be in the bottom
for this round,
but I don't give a fuck.
If I got to lip sync,
bitch, I got to lip sync.
I'm ready.
[Shuga] You look always ready
to lip sync, girl.
That's the only one I know
always want to lip sync.
I'm gonna let y'all
have it, honey.
Careful what you wish for, girl.
How you doin' boo.
Good.
[Brooke Lynn] What kind of
monster are you?
I drew it out here.
[Brooke Lynn] Me and Vanjie,
it's nice having
this thing happen.
But this is work.
We're here for a competition.
It's not personal,
it's drag.
But I'm gonna do it longer.
I was gonna do it short,
but I'm doing it longer.
-Cute.
-I want to make it crystal clear
that ain't no boy gonna
come between me and the crown.
I'm focused.
Hey, cysts.
-Hi.
-Hey, Ru.
How are
my little monsters doing?
Killer.
[all laugh]
Nina West.
Hi, Mr. Charles.
Do you have
any favorite monsters?
Bride of Frankenstein.
Elsa Lanchester.
[Nina] Elegant, gorgeous,
and still scary.
-And iconic. Yeah.
-Yeah.
You know, she did an episode
of Murder She Wrote.
Wait a minute. What episode
are you talking about?
Was that her? No, I'm sorry.
I'm thinking...
Baby, you do not want to test
my Murder She Sat Down
and Wrote knowledge of that,
because she was never on there.
No, she wasn't,
because I confused--
-But you know who was.
-Lillian Munster.
-I confused her.
-Oh, yeah, Yvonne De Carlo.
She played the cook on
the Jessica Behind Bars episode.
Yeah, yeah, when she goes in and
talks to the women in prison.
-Yes.
-I love that show.
Is that what you're going to do,
Bride of Frankenstein?
No, no, I'm going
more corpse bride,
'cause she's
a little decomposing.
I'm campy, I'm theatrical,
and I really want to make sure
that that's part of this look.
But still sexy.
'Cause the idea is that we want
to fornicate with her.
But there's some cobwebs
you have to clear away, but...
-Oh.
-You want to dive right in.
Story of my life.
[laughs]
Now, Nina,
if I remember correctly,
you had an issue
with the design challenge.
I did, I did.
How are you going
to overcome that here?
I'm going to tone down
all of the voices
that make me want to go bigger,
and focus on
delivering something
that is within my ability.
Oh, boy.
How many voices are in there?
Girl, plenty.
-Uh-huh.
-Plenty.
Scares. All right,
I'll see you out there.
-Thank you, Ru.
-Thanks, Nina.
-Hi, Shuga Cain.
-Hi, Mama Ru.
So now, have you won
any challenges?
-I have not.
-Why is that?
Maybe I'm not giving
as much as I should.
So it's allowed me to kind of
really think about
what I'm doing here,
and look at the girls
who are winning stuff.
Like, where is the difference?
So there's definitely a fire.
Now, your history with drag
is that you had been
in the corporate world.
Yeah.
You quit all that
to do drag full time.
Had you done drag before
you were in the corporate world?
No. I mean,
I dabbled a little bit,
and I just kind of--
I got the bug,
and, you know, after trying to
pursue art for so many years,
I finally was like
the cycle has to change.
I can't be in a dead-end job
and just, you know,
wishing I was doing
something that I love.
And I'd saved some money,
so I was like,
I'm just going to do it.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-And see what happens.
I was comfortable.
I had that stable job
making six figures,
and to just risk it all,
there's no turning back for me.
Like everything is on the line.
Well, hello,
Brooke Lynn Hytes.
Hi, Ru.
Where does your design aesthetic
come from?
All over. I just know
what looks good on my body,
and I know what I like to wear,
so I always start there.
When did you find that out?
Probably a couple years ago.
-Just a couple years ago?
-Yeah.
I only started sewing probably
about a year and a half ago.
Yeah. And so
when I say sexy monster,
what's the first thing
that comes to mind?
I actually don't watch
a lot of scary movies,
so the first thing
that came to my mind
was I want to be
a sexy pageant queen.
But I want to be a
first runner up who never wins.
So she scalps
all the other winners
and makes like her own crown
out of their heads.
Okay.
Giving that kind of like
very glassy RuPaul look.
So, you know,
that's an interesting choice.
[Brooke Lynn] It's one of those
things
where you think something's
a really good idea,
and then you start
verbalizing it to somebody,
and you see their reaction.
Okay, I need to do
something else.
-Hi, Plastique.
-Hi, Ru.
Now, you're a sewing bitch,
aren't you?
You could say that.
I really wanted to win
the first challenge.
However, Brooke Lynn,
she took the cake.
But I'm gonna make
this challenge my bitch, so...
Okay. So when I say sexy
monster, what comes to mind?
Like dark angel,
like, this dark lady.
It's past the point of zombie.
Now she's just a beautiful
spirit, just flowing around.
But still looking for the D.
Always and forever.
[RuPaul] Okay, all right.
But you know,
you're a pretty queen.
Thank you.
Can you do monster drag?
Um, I haven't had
the opportunity
to show y'all
that side of me yet,
so I'm very excited.
Yeah.
[Silky] I ain't buying it,
honey.
I just don't buy it.
The bitch gonna give you pretty
all day, every day,
in three fucking corsets.
All right.
Can't wait to see what you do.
Thank you.
-Yvie Oddly.
-Hi, Ru.
So, now, Yvie Oddly,
where does that come from?
I had some other boring
who-gives-a-shit drag name,
but people would say like
she just is so strange on stage.
So I named myself Yvie Oddly,
since I'm even odder
than everyone else, I guess.
[RuPaul] How you gonna snatch
the trophy on this challenge?
I'm gonna take a fashion element
and combine it
with my unique perspective.
I just wanna show that
I can also pull off some glam.
-Uh-huh.
-[laughs]
Is that what you're going to do
in this challenge?
I mean, I'm actually going
to be a voodoo doll, so...
Okay.
She's going to be glamorous,
but I still want to give
a little bit of a nod to my odd.
Well, I can't wait
to see what you turn out.
[Yvie] The girls
have already made it clear
that they see me as a monster.
The judges have seen a lot
with my monster drag.
So I'm a little bit afraid
that if I come out
as entirely monster,
the judges are going
to read me for filth,
and I don't want to be
predictable.
I look across the room,
I see Ariel.
And what she's making
looks like something from Party
City, Little Mermaid section.
I don't see no spook.
How you gonna
make that scary, girl?
And it has to be scary.
Everyone's kind of like
I don't know if that's enough.
You need to make that
like monster.
But I still think that
I want to keep my mermaid
a little bit more cutesy
so it's still true to me.
I wish I had more
of that green tulle,
'cause I don't want it
to look like
I was like I got this
at Spirit Halloween.
So I just need to do something
to it, bitch.
[Plastique]
Yeah, you should.
I'm telling you this
because I love you.
-I know.
-[Plastique] Ariel's my girl.
We've gotten really close.
So I'm very worried about her.
[Scarlet] Ariel lives
in a nineties
Nickelodeon kind of place.
I just don't know
if that's enough.
There's not
very much variety so far.
A similar wig,
a similar makeup.
I'm just not sure
she can pull this off.
What you making, ho?
I'm doing, um...
I heard something about
first runner up or something.
[A'Keria]
So now what you thinking?
I think I'm going to do
the snake wrapped around me.
[A'Keria] Monster it up?
You only got one snake?
[Brooke Lynn] Yeah.
I don't know
where this is leading to.
It's just a snake
wrapped around her head.
I don't... [sighs]
I'm definitely getting
in my head a little bit
because A, I have
a lot of pressure on me
because I won
the last design challenge,
and B, I know how to do sexy,
but I'm trying to figure out
how to make it monster.
Do you think
it's monster-y enough?
It's very glamour.
Brooke Lynn is the frontrunner
for this challenge,
but I think she's starting
to feel the pressure.
Hopefully we'll get her
into some trouble, honey.
This is gonna be cute
when you figure out,
like, what it's gonna be.
[laughs]
Yes. Oh, my God.
I'm living already.
Some of these girls
are doing, you know,
scary, spooky skeleton
glamour lady, you know.
And, like, you know,
just like know your history.
Know what are iconic monsters.
So my MILF eleganza
is the Creature
of the Black Lagoon.
I feel like this is actually
really terrifying, right?
[Shuga] Scarlet is definitely
feeling herself.
She's walking up and down
this joint in her own world.
You can kind of see my face,
kind of not.
Creature of the Black Lagoon
is very this.
[A'Keria] You know how when
you go into a movie store
and they got the dollar bin?
So it's like the generic version
of the movie.
Straight to DVD.
Bitch, you hot glue that
or did you sew it?
I sewed it, girl.
Of course.
[laughs]
This is like
at least like six panels.
[all laugh]
Girl, you love a good panel.
And the panel loves her, okay?
I'm talking about the judges,
of course.
Girl, I think that was one time.
Ooh.
[Scarlet] That's more than
they've loved some of us.
Ooh!
Girl.
Scarlet thinks
she is serving right now,
but the only thing
she's serving is holes.
Booty holes. [laughs]
[Silky] That bitch,
she need a rewind.
Try again.
Happy Halloween!
Yes.
All right,
I need to finish shit.
[Nina] It's here, kids.
The Ball is here.
Give me a kiss.
Miss Branjie.
Ooh.
[laughs]
Are y'all excited?
Yes. This is going to be
so fun.
33 looks on the runway.
[Ariel]
That gags me.
This is a good opportunity
to be able to turn out,
like, fun looks.
I love Halloween.
Like, I don't do, like,
spooky drag all the time,
so that's when I have like
an excuse to like force myself--
Really do it, yeah.
[Yvie] Technically speaking,
I'm halfway a Halloween queen.
Like the first time
I ever cross dressed at all--
Yeah.
Was Halloween, because my mom
dressed up as a pimp.
[laughs]
And then I was her dead hooker.
Okay, that's fabulous.
I love that your mom
was the pimp.
My grandma
was definitely not happy.
I don't like going out in drag
for Halloween.
I started my drag career
on Halloween.
It was my friend, you know,
we had dared each other
to actually get in drag.
And of course,
we was trying to see
who was going to be
the fishiest girl.
Who was the fishiest?
Girl, you know who
the fishiest was, bitch.
Probably because I only had on
like the littlest
amount of foundation.
You know we were Plastique.
Um...
[all laugh]
So you're saying Plastique's
still playing the drag?
-Girl.
-Ooh.
[Ra'Jah] Well, you know she just
found her way into it, right?
[Plastique] These girls,
they're just thinking
I'm just a pretty queen.
But when I first
started doing drag,
I was doing spooky, dark,
very demon-like makeup.
So I guess
we'll just have to see.
Let me go over here and see
what these ho's got going on.
She's giving me
Ursula tease.
Ursula to the runway.
[all laugh]
Ursula.
Now, Yvie, what you
bringing to the runway?
I ain't never seen you
put on pants, bitch.
A dinosaur. I'm trying to be
Silky thick tonight.
Dino to the runway.
Rhino to the runway.
Dino.
Dat-ka-ka-ka-ow.
Dat-ka-ka-ka-ah.
Oh, bitch.
Cha-cha-cha-cha-ah!
Rat-da-da-da-ow!
Bitch, don't come for me.
Not Canada Dry.
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
[RuPaul] And what?
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage, are you
a good witch or a bad witch?
I'm a sandwich.
Gluten free.
Baloney.
[all laugh]
The hilarious Ross Mathews.
Have you ever been
scared straight?
One time in high school,
but it wasn't my thing.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] The super beautiful
Cara Delevingne.
What are you gonna be
for Halloween?
Ooh, Ru, my dear, I would have
to say a slutty supermodel,
although that's not
that much of a stretch.
[all laugh]
And the legendary
Mistress of the Dark, Elvira.
Do you know you're one
of my favorite judges ever?
No, but if you hum a few bars,
I can fake it.
[all laugh]
This week
we challenged our queens
to tuck their halloweenies
and serve three spectacular
looks in the Monster Ball.
That caught us all off guard.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[howling]
[RuPaul] Welcome
to the Monster Ball.
Category is Trampy
Trick or Treaters.
Mm.
[RuPaul] Up first,
A'Keria C. Davenport.
Oh, Michelle,
your dealer's here.
[all laugh]
[A'Keria]
When a lot of girls think sexy,
they run to a nurse
or something like that.
I wanted to see
if I could make a dealer
who sits behind a poker table
look sexy.
And I actually did that,
and I brought the poker table.
[Cara] Ooh, I'd go all in
on that table.
[Ross]
I'm more of a slot guy.
[Michelle] I heard.
[RuPaul] Vanessa Vanjie Mateo.
[Ross] Now with wings.
[Vangie] My trampy
trick or treater concept
is the very first all-inclusive
Victoria Secret model.
I'm in all white, fully stoned,
real Avie crystals.
This angel got a secret.
It's Miss Vanjie.
[RuPaul] Fly me to the poon.
[all laugh]
[Cara] Yes.
[RuPaul] Plastique Tiara.
[Elvira] Oh, look, it's Lady
Bunny's attractive sister.
[all laugh]
[Plastique] I am a sexy Playboy
bunny right off the cover.
My body looks like
a literal hourglass.
This outfit is like
my favorite outfit ever.
[Cara]
That is one yummy rabbit.
[Michelle]
But where is her carrot?
[Elvira] That wasn't bunny.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Scarlet Envy.
[Ross] Walk the plank.
[all laugh]
[Scarlet]
My trampy trick or treater
is stomping the plank,
and she's ready to dive in.
[RuPaul] She's a real
Captain Hooker.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Nina West.
Ooh, her Venus flytrap's open.
[all laugh]
[Nina] This is one of
my very favorite looks
inspired by the legendary
Little Shop of Horrors.
This is the quintessential
Nina West look.
It has high camp.
It's also high drag.
[Ross] I couldn't really see
back there,
but now I can
suddenly Seymour.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Ra'Jah O'Hara.
Hey, kitty girl.
[Ross]
I thought I taw a puddy tat.
[A'Keria] I am
most definitely serving you
pink pussy
the house down boots.
And when I say boots,
you already know
what that means.
Thigh-high boots.
Yes, ma'am. Meow.
[Cara] I would love
to chase that tail.
[all laugh]
Here, kitty, kitty,
kitty, kitty.
[RuPaul] Shuga Cain.
[Elvira] Is it a showgirl?
Is it a harem girl?
What the hell is it?
[Shuga]
My trampy trick or treater
is a sexy troll doll.
I'm giving you
full pastel body color
with the body suit.
I have the troll hair.
Just giving you bejeweled
burlesque realness, honey.
[RuPaul] Ever wonder
what happened to Smurfette?
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Brooke Lynn Hytes.
[Elvira] Oh, she seems
so wrapped up in herself.
[Cara] Are those points?
I mean...whew.
[RuPaul] So gorgeous.
[Brooke Lynn]
It feels amazing
to use my dance training
in the runway.
I don't think there's ever
been a mummy on point
on the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
[Ross] Don't you just hate it
when the neighbor kids
TP your drag queen?
[RuPaul] Yes.
Ariel Versace.
Now, you've heard
of Monét X Change.
This is her cousin,
Needles X Change.
[Ariel] I'm the only punk rock
PVC Silent Hill nurse.
Each syringe represents
every time
I've got my goddamn
lips and cheeks done.
So as you can imagine,
there's a lot of syringes
on my shoulders.
[Cara]
You could prick me anytime.
[RuPaul] Well, do you want it
in the ass or in the shoulders?
[Cara]
Ooh, that's what he said.
[Elvira] I just love bloody
patent leather, don't you?
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Yvie Oddly.
It's Sarah Jurassic Parker.
[Cara] Straight from
T-Sex in the City.
[all laugh]
[Michelle] Oh, no.
[Elvira] You know what they say
about small hands.
[all laugh]
[Yvie] The little kid me
loved dinosaurs.
I thought I was going to be
a paleontologist.
I wanted to hit on that
a little bit.
This is a children's
Halloween costume
that I've cut
the armholes out of
and then I've attached dinosaur
claws to my cute dino pumps.
This look is dino-mite.
[RuPaul] Now, Ross,
is it dinosaur weekend
in Palm Springs yet?
[all laugh]
[Ross] I can get you tickets.
[RuPaul] Silky Nutmeg Ganache
Unicorn Frappuccino.
[Ross] That unicorn is horny.
[Michelle]
She's just happy to see me.
[Silky] I am wearing
a white sequined jumpsuit
with pink cutouts.
This is only
for the grown and sexy,
so if you ain't grown and sexy,
don't join the line, honey.
Fall all the way back.
[Ross] Shantay, you neigh.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Welcome back
to the Monster Ball.
Category is Witch Please!
First up,
A'Keria C. Davenport.
[Michelle] Edgar Allen Ho.
[Ross laughs]
[A'Keria] Babe,
I'm trying to give y'all
Charlize Theron in
Snow White and the Huntsman.
I'm the witch that you
kind of want to be with her,
'cause you want a piece,
but you know she's deadly.
[Ross] She really went out
on a limb with that bird.
[RuPaul] It's nice
to see her branching out.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Vanessa Vanjie Mateo.
[Elvira]
Well, this really proves
that black is the new black.
[all laugh]
[Vanjie] I know they're liking
this interpretation,
'cause I didn't do
the regular-degular
Party City style witch.
I'm taking it
to a high couture runway,
with a fascinator
for the subtleties.
This witch is rich, bitch.
[RuPaul] Witch better have
my money.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Plastique Tiara.
[Ross] Malefi-sensational.
[Cara] Angelina,
eat your heart out.
[Plastique]
I'm Maleficent's Asian sister.
I'm cinched for the gods.
I'm giving them face for days.
I am feeling
my full Maleficent glamour.
[RuPaul] Mirror, mirror
on the wall.
Who's the fiercest witch
of all?
Scarlet Envy.
[Michelle] Somebody likes
to roll around in the hay.
Hay hay!
[Scarlet] My concept
is a Fire Island witch.
She is beachy,
she's kind of swampy,
and she's giving you
pants on the runway
and feeling magical.
[RuPaul] Welcome
to RuPaul's Hag Race.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Nina West.
Well, hello, pilgrim.
[all laugh]
[Nina] My look is inspired
by a good old-fashioned
Salem witch,
with flames
coming up the dress
as if I'm being
burned at the stake.
I am serving old school witch.
Like literally.
From like 1510.
[Elvira] Somebody call
the fire brigade.
[RuPaul] Paging Arthur Miller.
[Michelle laughs]
[Michelle] Abigail!
[RuPaul] Ra'Jah O'Hara.
This outfit
inspires ooze and Oz.
[all laugh]
[Ra'Jah] I'm serving you
Witch Please!
straight out of Oz.
Head to toe emerald green,
with purple-accented hair.
Fuck, it looks good on me.
[Elvira] Why, it's the regular
emerald titty--city.
[RuPaul] Shuga Cain.
[Elvira] She's been framed!
[RuPaul] It kind of makes me
want a Bloody Mary.
[Shuga] I am Bloody Mary,
urban legend, spooky queen.
Snatching up all the kids
from the mirror, honey.
I am giving you
latex dripping blood,
tattered Victorian lace dress,
and my teeth are all nasty
and rotted out.
I'm living for this look.
[RuPaul] Hey, Shuga Cain,
how's your head?
[Michelle] Say it, Elvira.
Say it.
Haven't had any complaints yet.
Oh no!
[RuPaul] Brooke Lynn Hytes.
[Ross]
She is totally two faced.
[RuPaul] Totally.
[Ross] My eyes are up here.
And here.
[RuPaul laughs]
[Brooke Lynn]
This look is inspired
by the Enchantress
from Suicide Squad.
And oddly enough,
the Enchantress from
Suicide Squad, Cara Delevingne,
is our guest judge this week.
It's amazing.
I'm really hoping
she gets the reference.
[Cara] Oh, skull and bone me.
[Elvira] Hey, wait a minute.
Isn't that my opening costume?
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Ariel Versace.
[Cara] Bella Hadid,
someone stole your glasses.
[Ariel]
I am in my Witch Please!
giving you a little bit
of Meryl Streep
from Into the Woods,
Miley Cyrus
from Can't Be Tamed.
Avant-garde.
Very like posh.
It's Ariel, witch.
[RuPaul] Michelle,
have you ever seen
the Witches of Beast-wick?
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Yvie Oddly.
Coven girl,
put the bass in your walk.
[all laugh]
[Yvie] For this look,
I wanted to make sure
that I'm clearly reading
as witch,
but with a fashion twist.
All the other witches
in her coven were jealous,
so they put this curse on her.
But it's not going to stop her
from having a good time.
[Cara] Who said
women can't reverse?
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Silky Nutmeg Ganache.
Nobody beats The Wiz.
[all laugh]
[Silky] I am doing an homage
to black cinema,
The Wiz, as Evillene,
the Wicked Witch of the West.
Don't you bring Miss Evillene
no bad news.
[RuPaul] Ease on down
the runway, girl.
[Michelle] Yes.
[RuPaul] Say hi to Gayle for me.
[all laugh]
♪ We got a mighty love ♪
[RuPaul] Category
is MILF Eleganza:
Monsters I'd Like to Freak.
First up,
A'Keria C. Davenport.
[Ross] Oh, you know,
I've seen her on the web.
[all laugh]
[Elvira]
Quick, call the exterminator!
[A'Keria] Tonight, I am
the queen of the spiders.
I padded my body so that
she definitely has a butt
that you wouldn't mind
taking a ride on.
Definitely freakable.
You want some.
[RuPaul] A'Keria C. Davenport
from Harlot's Web.
[all laugh]
[Cara] I love that look.
[thunder]
[RuPaul] Vanessa Vanjie Mateo.
Her milkshake brings all
the boys to the graveyard.
[all laugh]
[Elvira] I hope the bird
doesn't have an accident.
[all laugh]
[Vanjie] My look
is inspired by Vanity 6
meet apocalyptic dead ho.
If Vanjie
was supposed to be dead,
this is how she would do it.
I would still look sickening.
I would have my plunging
neckline showing skin.
My hair's so coiffed,
I got my tombstone on my head,
because I want you
to know who I am.
This is sexy bitch to the Tee.
[Michelle] Hey, Vanjie,
how's your head...stone?
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Plastique Tiara.
[Ross] I love a queen
who's always smiling.
[RuPaul laughs]
[RuPaul]
Let's get sickle-ing.
[Plastique]
My monster I'd like to freak
is Plastique
Death Goddess glamour.
The makeup is paying homage
to how I started out in drag.
Being drawn
to that more conceptual,
more creepy, spooky makeup.
I hope the judges
can appreciate
I'm trying to do
something different.
[Michelle] She's so handsy.
[Ross] Well, you gotta
give her a hand.
[Michelle] Or two.
[RuPaul] Scarlet Envy.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the shape of wig water.
[Elvira] Wait,
isn't that Roomba's mom?
[all laugh]
[Scarlet] This outfit
is definitely high fashion
meets classic cinema.
The Creature
From the Black Lagoon
meets the New York City
catwalk, darling.
I feel weird.
I feel fashion.
I feel timeless.
[RuPaul] Now, you read about
all the mercury in fish,
but this is ridiculous.
[all laugh]
[thunder]
[RuPaul] Nina West.
Oh, look how pretty.
[Cara] Oh.
[Ross] Oh!
It's a gash, a monster gash.
[RuPaul laughs]
[Nina] This is a look
that I am very proud of.
I got this House of Wax vibe
where my face is falling off,
and underneath is this
decayed, deformed woman
crawling out of the grave,
looking for her long lost love.
I feel so alive...
and dead in this look.
[Ross] Honey, your lipstick
is smeared a little bit.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Ra'Jah O'Hara.
[Elvira] Oh, look at the size
of that snake.
[Ross]
That's her trouser snake.
[Cara] That's the longest
snake I've ever seen.
Well, the only one.
[all laugh]
[Ra'Jah] My MILF Eleganza look
is the bone collector.
Ra'Jah loves to suck
a good bone.
I'm wearing this sickening
pair of pants made of fur,
and then I throw on
some pasties.
I am serving you skeleton
drag queen realness.
[RuPaul] Hey,
when you finish the runway,
could you slip by my house
and snake my drain?
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Shuga Cain.
[Elvira] Somebody forgot
their bikini wax.
[RuPaul] Working the merkin.
[Michelle laughs]
[Shuga] I'm feeling this
sexy wife of Satan MILF.
She is giving you body,
feathers and bones
and full seventies merkin.
I think I'm freakable.
[Ross] She's so L.A. now.
An L.A. Ram.
That's a football reference.
[Michelle] Oh, my God,
I got it.
[RuPaul] Michelle,
have you heard my new song?
It's called
I am a Merkin, a Merkin.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Brooke Lynn Hytes.
[Ross] Sissy that walk.
[all laugh]
[Cara] Citizen Cane?
[Brooke Lynn]
I am a black widow.
This bitch has buried
like five husbands.
My look's
an off-the-shoulder gown,
with this black tulle wafting
around me almost like smoke.
I feel dark. I feel spooky.
I feel sexy.
[RuPaul] Get these
motherfucking snakes
off this motherfucking stage.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Ariel Versace.
[Cara]
Areola, the Little Mermaid.
[Elvira] Now I know why
she calls herself Ariel.
[all laugh]
[Ariel] So a mermaid
and Tinkerbell went into a bar
and the rest is history.
She is a creature from the
Jersey Shore covered in scales.
I know these other queens
are green with envy.
[Cara] Nyes.
[RuPaul] What's that perfume
you're wearing?
[Elvira] Catch of the day?
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Yvie Oddly.
[Cara] She must be
a fellow Brit with those teeth.
[Michelle laughs]
[Yvie] My look is this fashion
forward eleganza voodoo doll.
And I've got pieces of frogs
and old hands stuck in my hair,
and my face has got stitches
and a big ol' button eye.
[Michelle] She's serving
lace, lace, lace.
[RuPaul laughs]
[thunder]
[RuPaul] And now in a scene
from Macbeth, Dr. Ganache.
[Elvira] Out! Out, damn spot!
[Silky]
I am a red she-devil.
Red mermaid gown with leather
and fur hugs all my curves.
And I changed up my makeup.
Through my beauty, I wanted
to show a little beast.
I hope those judges
are horny to see me.
[Michelle]
Elmo, the later years.
[all laugh]
[thunder]
[RuPaul] Welcome, ladies.
Based on your
Monster Ball looks,
I've made some decisions.
When I call your name,
please step forward.
Nina West.
A'Keria C. Davenport.
Scarlet Envy.
Vanessa Vanjie Mateo.
Ra'Jah O'Hara.
Ladies, you are all safe.
You may leave the stage.
What a bunch of monsters.
[all chuckle]
Ladies, you represent
the treats and the tricks
of the week.
[chuckles]
And now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
Up first, Plastique Tiara.
The trampy trick or treater.
Your body was stunning.
Whoa.
By the way, I used to work
at a Playboy club.
I wasn't a bunny.
I was cleaning the restroom.
[all laugh]
Your makeup in all three looks
was incredible.
The MILF Eleganza,
the makeup, the details,
the way you held your mouth,
just perfect.
[Michelle] This look
is the most fuckable.
but I'm missing personality.
There's just a pretty you
walking down the runway,
and I'm missing
some kind of a connection.
All right, let's
move on down to Shuga Cain.
The Witch Please! I loved.
I love horror movies and I want
to watch that movie right away.
[Elvira] Your trampy
trick or treater,
I didn't know
what the heck it was.
The upside is it's something
no one's ever seen before.
[all laugh]
And hopefully
will never see again.
[all laugh]
It was a troll doll.
Those trolls?
So when I was little,
I didn't have a lot of friends,
and I had tons of trolls,
those little ones
with the little crazy hair.
And I used to talk with them
and perform in front of them.
I just wanted to do something
that meant something to me.
It's a beautiful story.
Yet you have to tell a story,
so that means we didn't get it.
This MILF just looks messy.
You're better than this.
And the carpet
is not matching the drapes.
It's hard to want to freak
that Merkin, that's the thing.
I was trying to do
like a tribal,
like, satanic
like wife of the devil.
I love the ideas,
but you have to be able
to portray to us
what you're doing.
[RuPaul] Up next,
Brooke Lynn Hytes.
[Elvira] I particularly loved
the first look,
because I've also
been wrapped up in bandages.
I'm sure you have.
Well, but I also did it
professionally.
[all laugh]
That costume,
it just was amazing.
And obviously you're
some kind of ballerina
or something, right?
Oh, Lordy.
[all laugh]
I could not believe
you were just like la-la-la.
I was just blown away by that.
[Cara] Your Witch Please!,
that kind of looks like
when I played the Enchantress
in Suicide Squad.
That's literally
my inspiration.
-Stop it!
-I found out you were a judge,
and I was like,
oh, fuck off, no way.
-[Cara] No way.
-[Brooke Lynn] Yes.
The way you danced, I was
like I should have probably
taken some lessons
before I'd done the movie,
because that was incredible.
Thank you.
And then,
this look I freaking love.
I like that
it's the counter point.
You're barely moving,
and you still carried it off.
I would borrow this outfit
from you for my day look.
[all laugh]
Up next, Ariel Versace.
I loved the syringes
coming out the shoulders
in the trampy
trick or treater realness.
But the bottom
was ill fitting.
The idea was cute.
The execution was marginal.
And your Witch Please!,
I was getting like saloon.
I was trying to do like
an avant-gardey kind of thing.
But it wasn't avant-garde.
It was 1800s.
The glasses were avant-garde,
which had no place
in that outfit.
And then there's nothing
monstrous about this.
This is a mermaid.
[Ariel] I guess
I was just trying to like
rest on something that I knew.
[Ross] Every week,
it's, you know, it's cute.
But it's just
what do you bring?
-What's your legacy in drag?
-Right.
Are you giving it to us?
[Ariel] I always like
present myself
as somebody
who's like really strong.
And for some reason
that hasn't--
I feel like I haven't
been able to show that yet.
[Ross] Have you ever
watched the show
and heard other queens
say that same thing?
Yeah.
And did you want to scream
at them from your living room?
Yes. Yes.
Here's the deal.
We're five weeks in.
Now's the time to push.
Yvie Oddly.
Your trampy
trick or treater look...
Speechless. Phenomenal.
One of my favorites
in this whole show.
You didn't just come out
as a dinosaur.
You told a story
without any words.
You have little T-Rex arms.
You can't reach it
when you drop it.
[all laugh]
I have seen a lot of drag,
but that really
was in my top 10 list
of most unique,
odd drag moments.
It was just so damn funny.
And you looked
sort of oddly sexy.
[laughs]
Oh, my God, your laugh,
I tell you, you should laugh
all the time,
because every time you laugh,
I laugh.
Unless I'm in a movie theater,
I swear to God.
[all laugh]
The Witch Please! was good
because it was simple,
but it was so tasteful.
You know, the hat going over
one eye, the little glove.
There was something
you could have added,
something just
that little element more.
Next time I'll eat a baby.
Great. That's what we want.
[laughs]
Let's talk about this monster
I'd like to freak.
This is like monster I'd
like to take to a fundraiser.
[all laugh]
You know what I mean?
I don't get it.
I was just trying to go
for a voodoo doll,
but I wanted to try to be
a little bit more glamorous.
So this is glamour to you?
[Yvie] I just didn't execute
everything to one vision.
I kind of picked a few
and was like that's glamour
and that's punk
and that's Yvie, so here we go.
[Ross]
But when you have a challenge
that is monster
I'd like to freak--
and you are a freak...
[laughs]
Freaking do it.
When I call you a freak,
that is the biggest compliment
I can give you.
Oh, girl, I hope so.
Otherwise people have been
insulting me my whole life.
No.[all laugh]
Well, I promise
I won't ever sabotage myself
with glamour again.
Well, we still want to see you
do some glamour.
And, you know,
you've got a couture body.
You could really rock
something gorgeously.
I'll do it when appropriate.
We'll hold you to that.
Up next,
Dr. Silky Nutmeg Ganache.
When you did the little
unicorn, adorable.
It was sort of a cute
children's trick
or treaty thing, you know,
with sex thrown in, which really
doesn't go together, but...
Okay, never mind.
[Ross] Your Witch Please!
It's a reference
to The Wiz, right?
Absolutely.
I liked that
you went to The Wiz,
but your hair, your paint,
you were Oprah.
Now, this last look,
you look so sexy.
You look absolutely gorgeous.
Thank you.
But the dress making
is a bit shabby.
I can kind of see places
where the fur is thicker
on one side, not the other.
It looked cheap.
And I really don't get monster
besides the horns on your head.
[Elvira] And horns do not
a monster make.
Ask anybody who was in
Manos: The Hands of Fate,
an obscure B-movie reference.
I don't do monster well.
I only paint one mug,
and it's a beauty mug.
[Michelle] No, I know.
You are a pageant girl
through and through.
But I have to remind you kids to
really think of the challenge.
[RuPaul] All right, ladies,
I think we've heard enough.
While you untuck backstage,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right,
just between us witches,
what do you think?
Starting with Plastique Tiara.
Those looks were incredible.
Plastique is stunning.
The colors, she's stunning.
[Elvira] It's Drag Race.
You need more than just looks.
You need personality.
[RuPaul] But I love
the fact that her MILF
was actually a monster,
and she took the time
to create a horrific face,
but still kept the beauty.
She did a really fine job.
All right, let's move on.
Shuga Cain.
[Ross]
The looks were just confusing.
She needs to hand out
a pamphlet with each outfit
so I can figure out
what the hell is going on.
I was just lost.
You can see
that she's talented.
She really can
sell a character,
like the Witch Please!,
when she does it properly.
But that MILF Eleganza, I don't
know what was going on there.
She tried to make it better
by licking the thing,
but licking
can only take you so far.
[all laugh]
This was just
not her challenge.
-Uh-huh.
-Mm-mm.
Let's move on
to Brooke Lynn Hytes.
I love, love, love,
love, love, love, love,
love Brooke Lynn Hytes.
How do you really feel
about Brooke Lynn?
I may be a little biased.
Whatever.
All of those looks to me
was someone I want to freak.
[Elvira] Yeah. She captured all
these different macabre looks.
The mummy,
the witch doctor,
and then that beautiful,
elegant,
kind of an Addams Family
character.
The costumes were amazing.
[Cara] Just to watch her move
was hypnotizing.
Yes, that extra element
really pushed it over the top.
Ariel Versace from New Jersey.
I was having
a little bit of déjà vu.
-I've seen it all before.
-Mm-hmm.
[Elvira] Nothing super
different, super unique.
The final look
didn't read monster at all.
Look, I'm Ariel.
I'm a mermaid.
Kind of meh-maid.
[laughs]
Guys, I'm almost
at a loss with Ariel.
I don't think she knows
what she needs to do.
She has an idea of what she is,
but this competition forces you
to rethink everything
that worked back home.
In this context,
you've got to amp it up.
And if you can't,
you shouldn't be here.
[RuPaul] Yvie Oddly.
Yvie brought something to
the party that nobody else did,
and that was humor.
I mean, she put claws on pumps,
you guys.
[all laugh]
Has anyone
ever done that before?
-No.
Then she dropped the head
and she couldn't get it.
[all laugh]
[Ross] But that last look
was so bad.
[Michelle]
There was no monster.
Nothing that you wanted to eff.
Nothing that I wanted
to eff, marry, or kill.
It's unfortunate that the last
look didn't really hit the mark,
but I wanted to single her out
because I was so impressed
with her first two looks.
-Yeah. Me, too.
-[Michelle] So good.
Dr. Silky Nutmeg Ganache
Zeta-Jones.
Her trampy trick or treater,
I actually liked that.
[Cara] But there's something
that could have
made the look better,
more pronounced
on the detailing, maybe.
And I had trouble
with the second one.
I thought it was Oprah Winfrey
going as Dolly Parton
for her Halloween costume.
She was being Evillene
from The Wiz,
but Evillene is evil,
and she didn't capture that.
The dress and the makeup
didn't measure up
to the original at all.
And the final look,
there was no monster in it.
And the dress,
when she turned around,
you saw the undergarments.
It was ill-fitting.
Silky is such a fun queen,
I would have liked to see her
have fun with the monster.
Really go there.
She said
she only paints pretty.
Well, stretch a little, honey.
There's $100.000 on the line.
Get ugly, girl.
Silence.
Sorry.
I've made my decision.
Bring back my ghouls.
[RuPaul] Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Plastique Tiara.
Tonight your three looks
were bewitching.
You're safe.
[RuPaul] Brooke Lynn Hytes.
Tonight you were on point.
Con-drag-ulations.
You are the winner
of this week's challenge.
Yes.
[applause]
You've won a $3.000 gift card
from TravelGay.com.
[Silky] Oh.
You may join the other girls.
[applause]
Yvie Oddly.
You, my dear, are a freak.
And you're safe.
Thank you.
Shuga Cain.
Tonight, Shuga don't bite.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
[Shuga Cain] I'm mad.
I did not come here
to be in the bottom again.
I just worked so hard
to get here.
It breaks my heart.
[RuPaul] Ariel Versace.
The only person
you scared tonight is you.
Silky Nutmeg Ganache.
Tonight you were all beauty,
no beast.
Silky.
You are safe.
You may join the other girls.
Thank you.
Ariel, I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
Two queens stand before me.
Prior to tonight,
you were asked to prepare
a lip sync performance
of I'm Your Baby Tonight
by the great Whitney Houston.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing] for your life!
[Ariel] I go into full
Mortal Combat mode.
I want to be here so badly.
I need to kill this lip sync.
Okay, bitch, it is time
for you to show Mama Ru
why you are meant to be here,
'cause tonight,
you are not going home.
Good luck, and for
the love of Whitney Houston,
don't fuck it up.
[music plays]
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ From the moment I saw you ♪
♪ I went out of my mind ♪
♪ I never believed
in love at first sight ♪
♪ But you got a magic, boy,
that I just can't explain ♪
♪ Well, you got a, you got
a way that you make me feel ♪
♪ I can do, I can do
anything for you, baby ♪
♪ I'll be down for you, baby ♪
♪ Lay all my cards out
tonight ♪
♪ Just call on me, baby ♪
♪ I'll be there in a hurry ♪
♪ It's your move,
so baby, baby decide ♪
♪ Whatever you want from me ♪
♪ I'm giving you everything ♪
♪ I'm your-- ♪
Oh!
Fuck.
[Ariel] Motherfucker.
I just need to get up
and keep it moving.
I need to show them
that I'm not giving up.
I'm gonna be their baby tonight.
I need to stay here.
♪ Whatever I do, boy ♪
♪ It's all about you, baby ♪
♪ And ain't it the truth, boy ♪
♪ I'm helplessly
in love with you ♪
♪ What else can I do, boy ♪
♪ But be there for you, baby ♪
♪ You got a, you got a way
that you're making me ♪
♪ Feel I can, feel
I can do any, do anything ♪
-♪ All right ♪
♪ You do it, baby, you do it ♪
♪ Whatever you want from me ♪
♪ I'm giving you everything ♪
♪ Whatever ♪
♪ I'm your baby tonight ♪
♪ There's no denying, oh ♪
♪ Looks like I'm fatal,
it's all on the table ♪
♪ And, baby,
you hold the cards ♪
♪ You got the magic
and I've got to have it ♪
♪ I don't want the pieces,
I want every single part ♪
♪ I'll be your angel,
I'm ready and able ♪
♪ Whatever you want is fine ♪
♪ Whenever you're ready,
just call on your lady ♪
♪ And I'll be your baby
tonight, yeah ♪
[cheers and applause]
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Shuga Cain, shantay you stay.
You may join the other girls.
[applause]
Ariel Versace,
you are my baby tonight,
and you always will be.
Now sashay away.
[cheers and applause]
[Plastique] I love you,
Ariel I love you!
Nyes!
[all laugh]
[Ariel] I didn't think I should
have gone home tonight.
I have so much to show.
[blows lips]
It sucks that I did not get to
show my true self to the judges
or at least
what they thought they saw.
But can't wait to see
what else I do.
Con-drag-ulations, queens.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
-Amen.
-All right.
Now let the music play.
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪
[RuPaul] Next time on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
You'll be competing in the
first ever Drag'lympics.
[music plays]
♪ Because I'm what? ♪
♪ Sickening, bitch! ♪
You slayed.
It all worked for me.
-Amazing.
-I'm getting bored.
Change up some shit.
If I got to lip sync
for my life,
I'm gonna lip sync
for my motherfucking life.
I'm not fucking coming for you.
I can't wait until they make
that spooky dooky--
Go home.
♪ To, to, to, to, to,
to, to, to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪