[RuPaul] Previously on
RuPaul's Drag Race...
We are throwing a monster ball.
[howling]
[RuPaul] Shuga Cain.
This looks messy.
[RuPaul] Ariel Versace.
There is nothing monstrous
about this.
[RuPaul] Brooke Lynn Hytes.
[Cara] That was incredible.
[RuPaul] Con-drag-ulations.
You are the winner
of this week's challenge.
[Vanjie] Yes.
[applause]
[RuPaul] Shuga Cain,
shantay you stay.
Ariel Versace, sashay away.
Nyes.
Jesus, y'all.
This is like the worst.
But the best, but the worst.
[Shuga Cain] Miss Ariel
just went home,
and I am feeling
some type of way right now.
Ariel, we love you, Jersey.
Love you so much, Ariel.
We love you, girl.
I love you, Ariel.
[Shuga Cain] I thought
coming into this competition
that I was going to do so much
better than I'm doing now.
Bitch, they read me to filth.
And it's like, it's frustrating.
I thought this look was cute.
How does everybody else feel
about, like, critiques, like?
I was in the bottom
for being beautiful.
So you know what?
It works for me.
And if I got to lip sync
for my life,
I'm gonna lip sync for my
motherfucking life beautifully.
[Yvie] But like Ru's been
particularly poignant
about don't be safe.
[Vanjie] I thought
what I brought was fierce.
I thought I looked sickening.
I felt sickening.
But I was safe.
[Yvie] Well, she was safe
because it was still the same
silhouette that the judges
critiqued you on changing.
Let me tell you this.
She wore a corset and a panty
both times.
[Yvie] I'm just saying the Tee
is that the judges already
critiqued you on having
the same silhouette,
so now, bitch,
time to change it up.
Ain't nobody asking for
your opinion, peanut gallery.
Sometimes the old school phrase
if you don't got
nothing nice to say,
just let those bitches go home,
sometimes that applies.
That can be hard for a lot
of people only because
the only thing you have
is what you brought.
You telling Vanjie
to step her clothes up,
but if a person don't sew,
how does she step it up?
Start wearing pillow cases?
Cutting up the couch?
They said Vanjie
bring the same silhouette,
but how can she improve
what she already has?
Hold on. I wore a--the first one
was a panty and a corset.
The second one was a gown.
So I didn't bring the same
silhouette three times.
I'm not fucking coming for you,
and your goddamn
same silhouette.
I'm just saying if you don't
want to be fucking safe again,
then change up some shit.
Is that shit wrong?
You know everything what to say.
Once again, I hear like
these girls making excuses.
Get the fuck over it.
We have a fabric wall.
There's plenty of stones.
There's so many scissors.
If the judges are getting bored
by what you're doing,
then go back into your drag
and change it.
Aight, you gonna give glamour?
My critique this week
was stay true to me, bitch.
You got quite opposite critique.
[Vanjie]
Mama, I heard--I heard the--
Quite opposite.
Don't get defensive, mama.
Miss Yvie bumps her gum all day.
Wigs.
But the bitch
only gives you spooky Tee.
There's not much more
than spook.
And I'll tell you, wait until
they make that spooky dooky...
Go home.
[RuPaul] The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100.000.
With extra special guest judges
choreographer Travis Wall
and Olympians Mirai Nagasu
and Adam Rippon.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
[singing]
[laughs]
[Brooke Lynn] It is a new day,
and there's still
way too many of us left here.
-Oh.
-Suck it, suck it.
It's like a house party
and people just don't know
when to leave.
Silky, how does it feel
to be in the bottom three?
[laughs]
The shade at the beginning
of the day is real, honey.
[Silky] You know what?
I don't believe
that I belong there.
I did motherfucking Evillene,
and some ho's don't know
what Evillene is.
You keep playing
on that Evillene, girl,
but we had three looks
on the runway.
It's always been drama,
'cause bitch hate on my beauty.
I would never be spooky,
but, bitch,
would you ever be glam?
You will never be glam!
Don't come for me.
Oh, girl, I hope
you're not talking to me,
'cause I'm about
to send your ass packing.
Ooh. I can't wait till we're
in the bottom two together.
There's a lot you don't know
about me, bitch.
[Vanjie] Thank God.
[RuPaul] She done already
done had herses.
Attention,
worldwide skorts fans.
This competition isn't just
a race, it's a marathon.
So pop the corn
and feed the children.
Back to you, Bob.
Hello, hello, hello.
[cheers]
Whew.
I've been working out.
I am gagged.
So out of breath.
[all laugh]
Ladies, America's
next drag superstar
needs to keep her charisma,
uniqueness, nerve, and talent
as tight as possible
at all times.
[all laugh]
Which is why I exercise
11 times a day
and eat three sensible meals.
Per month.
[all laugh]
So for today's Mini Challenge,
I'm treating you to the latest
Hollywood workout craze.
Galisthenics.
[all laugh]
Everybody's doing it.
Now you have 15 minutes
to get into your quick workout
drag, and meet me back here.
[cheers and laughter]
Go!
Oh, my God.
[RuPaul] Time's up, ladies.
You know, as a celebrity,
I have access
to some of the most exclusive
fitness regimes in the world.
And today I want you
to meet a person
who has truly changed my life.
Please give a warm
Drag Race welcome to...
Love Connie.
[cheers and applause]
[Nina] I'm really familiar
with Love Connie.
Love Connie is known
for these Jane Fonda-esque
1980s-inspired
workout video looks.
It's partially scag,
it's partially improv.
[shouting]
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
I want whatever she's on.
Welcome, Connie.
You girls ready to get
some hair on your tits?
[cheers and applause]
Now, girls, are you ready
to get physical?
[cheers]
Good, because the two queens
with the best moves win.
Let's go.
I don't know about you,
but I'm ready
for some thigh workouts.
[cheers]
Let's do it.
Now, feel it working
through your cleavage.
That way
you don't have to contour
and you can save on makeup.
All right, step it out.
And lunge, lunge, lunge.
Keep it going. [coughs]
-[laughs]
-Keep going.
I didn't say stop.
Oh, my God.
Who wants a solo?
-Jean jacket, I love you.
-Yes, I love you.
Oh, my God, you make me feel
feminine with that beard.
[all laugh]
Let's Nomi Malone it.
Hup, hup, hup.
It's all you.
[Yvie]
I just love watching Scarlet
get an opportunity to dance.
It's so ridiculous.
[laughs]
-Oh!
Bluebird, are you
gonna be all right?
I don't want you
to get any black eyes.
I wanna see long legs.
Whoa! Oh, my God! Whoa!
Yeah!
It's Pinky Tuscadero.
[all laugh]
And hit it.
It's kick, kick.
Up to the glory of God.
Hey, Jesus. Again.
Hup, hup. This bitch
is trying outkick me.
I quit, I quit.
Last place.
I smell something burning.
It must be Plastique.
Come on down, girl.
Whoo. Get it.
Oh, my God! Wow!
I didn't need those
anyway, honey.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my Lord.
Whoo! Let's curl.
That's not gonna make me
look masculine, right?
No, but your face will.
[Vanjie] Ow!
Whoa! Oh, my God!
Let's do checkerboard, yes.
I am not being racist.
Hey, girl.
Whoo! Wow!
We're gonna jump out
and thrust, thrust.
Out, and thrust, thrust. Out.
Give me a limp wrist.
I need it gayer.
All original.
Come on, let's do it.
Hup and hup and hup
and hup and hup.
Whoa!
Hup and push. Now give it.
You're the last girl.
Take it, girl.
You can still win this.
You can still win it.
I want a winner.
Get it! Get it!
Yes!
[slap]
[laughs]
That'll get ya.
I needed that.
I needed it.
All right, everybody,
let's rock it out.
[RuPaul] Y'all worked that body.
[cheers]
But two of you really
made me feel the burn,
and I've got an ointment
that will knock that right out.
Connie, would you do the honors?
I would love to.
The two winners of
this workout challenge are...
A'Keria.
And oh, my God, Plastique.
[cheers and applause]
[A'Keria] ♪ Do-do-do-do ♪
I finally won something.
Con-drag-ulations, ladies.
You've each won
a $1.500 gift card
from MuLondon
organic skin care.
[cheers and applause]
Thank you, Connie, darling.
You can leave
the way you came in.
As they say in Hollywood,
I think I will.
[laughter and applause]
Ladies, I hope
you're all warmed up,
because for this week's
Maxi Challenge,
you'll be competing
in the first ever
International Draglympics.
[cheers and applause]
[RuPaul] And you'll be doing it
in front of a live audience.
[gasps]
You'll be performing
a freestyle floor program
that includes
compulsory fanography.
-Ooh.
Voguing.
[cheers]
And shablam.
No, baby,
the AARP don't cover that.
[all laugh]
Now, you'll be competing
in two teams of five.
A'Keria and Plastique,
you won the Mini Challenge,
so you are the team leaders.
A'Keria, you go first.
I'm gonna go
with Brooke Lynn Hytes.
Thank you.
[applause]
-Plastique.
-Ra'Jah O'Hara.
Ayy.
Silky Ganache.
[all laugh]
Miss Vanjie. Miss Van--
Ahhh!
[all laugh]
Yvie.
Thank God.
-Nina West.
-Yay.
That leaves Scarlet Envy
and Shuga Cain.
Give me some of that Shuga.
Yay.
And that means Scarlet Envy,
you are Team Plastique.
Yes.
[applause]
Errr! Put the brakes on,
because Scarlet is on our team,
and we are in trouble.
S.O.S. She's not a dancer.
Help.
Now, ladies, the Draglympics
are an international event.
Very prestigious.
Did I say puss-tigious?
[all laugh]
Very puss-tigious.
So Team A'Keria,
you'll be representing
the sovereign nation
of Tuckpantistan.
Ooh.
And Team Plastique,
you'll be representing
the People's Republic
of Glamazonia.
Nice.
And you'll be coached
by Emmy Award-winning
choreographer Travis Wall.
-Yes!
-[gasps]
And U.S. Olympic
figure skating champion
Adam Rippon.
[cheers and applause]
Gentlemen of the world,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[cheers and applause]
-Thank you.
I'm worried.
There's too many iffies
in this group.
We got Scarlet.
We got Nina.
She ain't a dancer.
She ain't solid gold,
and this ain't comedy.
Ra'Jah, temperamental.
This ain't America's
best dance crew right here.
We can't even make
the auditions.
We are fucked.
[Vanjie] Lead us to victory.
Win this Olympic medal, bitch.
-We're taking the gold home.
-Yes.
For this week's Maxi Challenge,
we have to perform
in the Draglympics.
[Plastique] This challenge
is super physical,
but I'm so excited for it
because I can
buck the house down.
Gakita, gakita, ga-ga-ga.
When Ru said choreographer,
I was like, wait, oh, no, bitch.
Not again.
-Up, one, two--
-Oh, I'm sorry.
Ra'Jah,
you shouldn't have told me
you had this dance
experience, mama.
I'm going back into
my Kameron Michaels shell.
I have never seen
a dance floor at all.
-I've never done nothing.
-Right.
I am the Tee
when it comes to dancing,
but after working with
the other choreographer,
I really don't know
what to expect.
Oh!
I'm shook.
[Scarlet] I'm just a little
nervous for myself.
We all know I can't dance.
I mean, I haven't done
a lot of death drops,
but if I don't do it well
but I do it,
and they know how out
of that comfort zone it is,
I think that might
speak for itself?
No, because if you
still do a death drop
and you don't do it well,
I think they're going to be
like, what the hell was that?
-I was the last picked.
-One, two, three, four.
And I can tell that none of them
wanted me on the team.
Out. Out?
So that's a hard place
to start from.
Help, literally, help.
I did choose my team
for a reason.
I wanted to pick people
who I know actually
can pick up choreography.
And even if you can't, you know
how to make it look good.
[Brooke Lynn]
My team is feeling really good
going into
the Draglympics challenge,
but I'm a little worried
about the drama
between Yvie and Silky.
Now, are you two going to
be okay working together,
because we got a little heated
this morning.
We have to address this issue.
Because at this point in time,
we are a team,
and we're all on a mission.
I can put all
my personal things aside.
Like this is work for me,
so like, I'm coming into work.
Okay. I just wanted to check.
We're not gonna have any--
[A'Keria]
Yeah, because it's five of us,
and I think everybody's aim
is they're trying to be their
number one or their top three,
because that's what's
gonna get us through this.
Look, I don't want
any drama going forth.
Like, I don't have time
for the B.S.
We trying to win.
Now, if y'all wanna slice
each other's throat afterward,
by all means.
But as of right now, we're
not finna have none of that.
So do anybody have
any special skills?
-I mean--
-Ballet.
Yeah, I know
you have your baton.
That could be incorporated
into some type of hand motion.
-I got a trick or two.
-Yeah, you do?
She a bendy girl.
[Yvie] Any given
performance of mine,
you can expect me
to be flying from the ceiling,
hanging off of something,
contorting into boxes.
I was born super flexible
because I don't produce
a whole lot of collagen,
so my joints go every which way.
[A'Keria] Do you think that
you could teach somebody
who, you know,
ain't as nimble as you--
[Yvie] Yeah, the shablam?
-[A'Keria] Yeah, that.
-Yeah.
The shablam is what
you're supposed to do,
which is supposed to be
kind of like a surprise.
So it should come out
of like a twirl,
and then you just
bend your knee down,
and you find your way
to the floor and point.
[Brooke Lynn]
Show me how to do that.
I'm very ballerina,
so I don't really like just
throw myself into things.
Like death drops terrify me.
Which way do you go
when you turn?
When I turn,
I turn to the outside.
So you go bam, bam, bam.
And then whatever leg
you are going to be falling on
is the leg
you should be spinning on.
I could do that.
[Yvie] Yeah, girl.
Oh, no, I'm not doing it
on that concrete, baby.
Y'all keep the concrete
right now.
I am not a dancer,
but I have a team
full of dancers,
and now I have to lead them
to victory.
My goal is to show those judges
that I can be a leader.
-Hi.
[Yvie] It's time to rehearse
our choreography
for the Draglympics.
Not only do we have an Olympian,
but we have an Emmy
Award-winning choreographer.
I'm feeling so solid.
[Travis] Yes.
We're stealing that move today.
I'm here to give you a show,
so you want a good show?
I'm gonna come find you, yes.
No, you found me.
[all laugh]
I'm ready.
[Travis]
This is the Draglympics.
There's three
compulsory elements in this,
so we have to all
dance with fans,
and then we all have to vogue,
and then we all have to have
some version of a shablam.
Whatever the dance is,
you guys need to sell it.
It's a performance.
[Travis] So we're going
to start teaching you
a little bit
of the fanography first.
Please come grab a Daftboy fan.
You're going to take the fan,
one, point, two.
Three. You're going
to open your fan on four.
Five, six, you're going
to turn and close the fan.
And then you're going to open it
and do arched back on eight.
One fan down.
Here we go.
Boom, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, back.
-How'd you do?
-Great.
Slapped myself.
A'Keria, would you do it
by yourself?
Yeah, I sure can try it.
Five, six, seven, and...
-Step, cross, three.
-One, two.
Then keep going.
One, two, three, four.
-Now fan on four.
-Okay, fan on four.
[Travis] That was almost it,
yeah.
Now, I can pop a fan
all day long.
But to pop a fan
and remember to move this way
and step with this foot
and then do this hand...
Don't get in your head.
Just like, relax,
and even if you do mess up,
don't make
any sort of like facial.
-Right.
-If you give like a facial,
everybody's gonna know
when you're like uh-uh-uh.
[Travis] All right,
so let's learn
some of the voguing section.
Touch and a release.
Touch and release.
So, bitch,
get out of my way, ha.
Think about touch this skin,
darling.
Brooke Lynn, can you do it once?
-Sure.
-Five, six, sell it, great.
One and a two,
three and a four,
and a right and a left
and a right and a left.
And a circle to the back,
circle to the hip,
step and pull, step and pull.
Brooke Lynn, that looks so good.
-It's sick.
-Thank you.
Everyone has to come up to
your level, but it looks good.
My eye's gonna be on Brooke Lynn
to see what she can deliver,
because we're expecting a lot.
From there, you're going
to go one, snap, two.
Three, snap, four.
Five, snap, six.
Now, seven and an eight, and ha.
You're going take it
all the way to the floor.
[A'Keria] I need help.
So, listen,
this is not a death drop.
The idea is it's a smooth
transition to the floor.
Travis is telling me
to go down graceful.
It's like a whoo.
Bitch, there's no graceful.
There's a pam!
Or you won't get nothing,
honey.
Silky, here we go.
Five, six, seven, and.
Go step, ha, ah, mm, ah.
Circle to the back.
Yeah, girl.
[cheers and applause]
So everyone get to the floor.
We're gonna do a little
five and six
to cross your legs,
Then you're going
to whip around.
Seven, eight,
to the right knee down,
and then you're going
to pull up on one.
Let me see it from the floor.
Boom, ha, ha, seven,
and back one.
Come up, flick, flick,
down, through, and go.
Not bad. Maybe
this becomes your solo,
and they get up on one,
and then we all come around you.
-Uh-huh, I'm gonna get up.
-Okay.
-Imma get it.
-Yes, you are.
I'm a big bitch, but
I ain't not scared big bitch.
Here we go, back on one.
Six, seven, eight.
Back one, two, come up,
three, four.
Go flick, flick, down,
through, drop, come up.
That was a disaster.
Let's do that one more time.
Silky's flopping around
on the floor
looking like
The Greatest Catch. [laughs]
The thing about Silky
is she fucking works it.
She's like, yeah, I look crazy,
but I'm doing it.
And the bitch is committed.
I feel like
a skinny bitch today.
[Brooke Lynn]
Maybe you will be by tomorrow.
[all laugh]
Silky, she's gonna
have to work really hard
to keep up with everybody else
in her group,
but that personality alone,
she's explosive.
And I think that
she's going to do
really well
in this challenge.
One more time to the floor.
Come up, flick, flick,
down, through, and go.
Not bad.
Yvie, you okay?
I'm going to have to cheat
specifically the turn today.
Tomorrow I can do death drops,
splits, kicks, everything.
[Yvie] During rehearsals,
I'm a little bit rattled
by the fact that
all of my joints are hurting.
But I'm just gonna have
to grind through it.
Thank you, guys,
for your hard work.
I really appreciate it.
I want to push you guys
as far as possible,
so there's a lot to do.
I'm just so thankful
that all of you guys
have some rhythm in you.
Some seasons, it's like,
oh, it's like Bambi and...
Bitch, you gonna hate
the next team.
Oh, you gonna be angry.
[all laugh]
Yvie, can I talk to you
for a second?
-Yeah.
-Cool.
-You all right?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
It's just I want to give myself
one more day to rest, though.
What happened to it?
Like was it just from
the last challenge or...
Yeah, it was just
from the last challenge,
I was standing in heels
for all day.
Okay. I don't want to, like,
take it to the next level
where you're not going
to be part of the competition.
[Yvie] Because of my condition,
I know that I shouldn't be doing
all of my contortions right now.
I just would
rather not bring it up,
because I don't want
to be babied.
Just make sure, like,
stay as honest as possible,
and then we're going
to get through this.
-All right.
-Awesome.
-Thank you so much.
-Take care.
[Yvie] I'm frustrated
having to hold myself back
because I didn't come here
to play safe.
Safe gets you sent home.
-Hi.
-Hey.
-There go the boys.
This challenge in particular
I'm excited for
because I started out
my drag career
in backup dancing
for all those chickenheads.
Like I'm excited, and I feel
like I can do good with this.
At this point,
I know I have to stand out,
'cause I want to win something.
What we're going to do first
is we're going
to work on the voguing.
So let's learn these hands.
This is going to be fun.
Up and out, up and out,
and a voom, badda-ba,
badda-boom, badda-ba.
Five, six, seven,
and up and out, up and out.
And an up and a down,
and an up and a down.
Nice. I just want more body.
Ra'Jah, one more time.
Five, six, seven.
And up and an out,
up and an out,
and a boom, tadda-ba,
badda-boom, badda-ba.
And a hip and a hip,
and a step and a back.
Five, six, seven, and boom.
[cheers]
[Scarlet] Good work.
That's really great
comparatively to everybody else.
But I still want you
to push yourself further.
-Okay.
-Vanjie, can you show me?
Five, six, boom-tadda-da,
boom-tadda-da.
And an up and a down
and an up and a down.
And a boom, boom,
step, ha.
Five, six, seven, and ha.
Amazing.
I have no notes.
I'm coming for you, Ra'Jah.
[all laugh]
Next up we're going
to work on the fanography,
so please come grab a fan.
Guess who's back in the house.
[pop, pop]
Five, six, seven, ha.
You're going to step across.
One, you're going to pull
the fan across on two,
then you're going to step three,
you're going to swipe on four.
Here we go.
Five, six, seven, jump, eight.
Step past eight,
step to the out.
Step across.
Feet, feet, a knock-knock, go.
Know exactly
what the fan is doing.
Your execution score
is going to up or down
dependent on what these fans
are doing.
-Scarlet.
-Oh, God.
Ready? Here we go.
Seven, jump, eight.
One and two, three and four.
Five and six, seven, eight,
one and two.
Let's try it again.
It's like, snap.
Give me that.
Just do that part.
On two. One, hop.
I just want to see this.
One, hop.
Act like you're in drag, girls.
It's a snap.
Give me something there.
-It was not very good.
-No.
-But we're gonna get there.
-Okay.
Scarlet
is definitely the weakest.
However, why do I feel
like she's gonna, like,
come forward tomorrow
and like win the challenge?
One and two, three and four.
You lost it.
Let's try again.
Of course we still have
the struggle bus with Scarlet.
[Travis] And up.
In the way.
Oh, I'm sorry.
[Ra'Jah] Bitch, could you find
your spot so I can get in mine?
Thank you. Move, bitch.
Here we go.
This is our last time.
Then we gotta wrap it up.
Here we go.
Five, six, seven, go.
In, up, out, down, hit,
through, oh, my God.
I thought someone
was going to get it.
No one did, though.
All I know is
I'm looking at Travis's face,
and he looks like he just saw
Michael Jackson's ghost.
Out of the two groups,
you guys did have a harder time
picking up choreography,
but you have to get those steps.
Those steps are part of
your compulsory elements.
This is becoming a disaster.
I'm praying that
these girls get hit
by the Rhythm Nation stick.
This was my chance
to do something good.
Like what did I do
to deserve this?
-Silky, why you fart?
-Did you fart?
You farted.
Yes, you did, bitch.
You nasty bitch.
Today is the Draglympics.
We got to do fanography,
vogueography, and shablam.
Oh, get my wig, girl,
get my wig!
[Ra'Jah]
Come on twerk.
-Come on, pancake.
-[Silky]I'm coming in.
Come on, pancake.
[Vanjie] This why
I love y'all nasty ho's.
They got an ass
but I got a stomach.
[all laugh]
[Vanjie]
Oh, Lord, Jesus.
How do you feel
about your team, bitch?
Girl, you know some of us
are not as strong dancers,
but I have to make sure
I'm doing my part.
You know my theory.
You got it,
or lip sync for your
motherfucking life.
Yeah.
[Vanjie] It's important for
me to do well in this challenge
because I've been close,
but I haven't been able
to like hit the home runs.
[Silky]
I can't wait to see
what you're going to wear
on this runway, bitch.
[Vanjie]
Sometimes I don't think
my runways go over that well,
So I need to make sure
I at least sell it
and am confident on the runway.
I want to do it,
one, for Mama Ru,
because, you know,
she brought me back,
and I feel like I been
letting her down a little bit.
Uh-uh.
Just like, lately,
I've been feeling like
I haven't been improving,
like, girl, we're like halfway
through the competition,
I haven't even won
a Mini Challenge.
I feel like
it's a lot of expectations
from like a lot of people.
I don't...like, I feel like
I should be doing better.
So it frustrates me
because I know what I can do.
And I feel like I just have
been like kind of scared.
Like I'm like, bitch,
I need to do something,
because I want people to know
that I'm not like here
just to kiki and hang out
you know.
We all came to do--
-A job.
-To perform our best, yeah.
Trust me, you're doing just
what you're supposed to do,
which is each day
handle each challenge
the way you're supposed to,
and continue to fight in this.
Yeah.
[Vanjie] I'm frustrated
with myself
because I know
what Yvie said was true.
Like I need to step it up,
because I've been safe.
Brooke Lynn, babe,
how did you get started in drag?
I started doing drag
professionally when I was 25.
And I moved to New York,
and I danced
with Ballet Trockadero.
Oh, yes. I have some friends
in Trockadero.
[Brooke Lynn] Ballet Trockadero
de Monte Carlo,
it's an all-male ballet company,
and they do drag.
So I got to be a ballerina for
four years and travel the world.
I performed for royalty,
performed for Karl Lagerfeld,
Princess Caroline of Monaco.
So that was a life-changing
experience for me.
I danced there for four years.
So fierce.
I love that.
[Shuga]
So how you feeling, girl?
I know your body was kind of
messing with you today.
Honestly,
I have this joint disorder
that gives me all of these
crazy flexible abilities.
But it's a double-edged sword
because some days I wake up
and I can just feel my bones,
like, sliding apart.
Oh, shit.
And that's how I felt
the day we got this challenge.
I felt my body being like, girl,
today is not the day.
[Yvie] Growing up,
my bones were always hurting
to an unnecessary amount.
We thought it was
growing pains.
I remember being like 13 or 14
when I finally got,
like, the full diagnosis
of what exactly
is going on with my body.
[Nina]
What is it called?
It's called Ehlers-Danlos.
Oh, wow.
And it's just, my body
doesn't produce enough collagen,
which is why
I've got all of these
and all of this at 24.
[Nina] Really?
My condition is something
that is eventually
going to take me out
of drag commission,
at least in the way
that I'm doing it now.
Is it not curable?
Is that what it--
It just gets worse and worse
over time.
I met somebody who has
the same disease as me
and is 10 years older.
They're in a wheelchair.
-They have heart complications.
-Are you serious?
So I get to like--I get like
a little vision of my future.
Mama, I'm so sorry.
That's so wild.
[Yvie] That's why every year
I've auditioned for Drag Race.
I was like, I have
to get on this year.
I have to do it,
because I'm like,
I'm losing my skills as I go on.
Does it bother you,
like, a lot of the time?
It's always kind of there.
Like, I'm literally
always in pain.
It's just
it's not always at a 10.
It's usually at
like a four or five.
Even though drag is something
that's been really hard
on my body,
and it's definitely something
I'm not going to be able
to do forever,
it's so liberating
that if I have to go
out on stage in a wheelchair,
girl, like, I'll do it.
She has all this pain,
but have you seen the bitch?
She acts like nothing is wrong.
You never know
what someone's going through.
So for those of us who don't
have weird joint disorders,
how are your bodies feeling?
[all laugh]
Well, now I'm not complaining.
[laughs]
So...
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
[cheers and applause]
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage,
are you an athlete?
No, darling, but I'm a very
large athletic supporter.
If loving you is thong,
I don't wanna be right.
[all laugh]
The amazing Travis Wall.
Now are you carrying a torch
for my girls?
I'm positively flaming, Ru.
[all laugh]
I knew that.
My champion, Olympic
figure skater Adam Rippon.
Oh, Ru, you'll always be
my champion.
You know I danced
to Sissy That Walk
on Dancing With the Stars.
Yes. Available on iTunes.
[RuPaul]
Olympic superstar Mirai Nagasu.
Did you ever think
landing a triple axel
would land you here?
I've been waiting
a long time for this, Ru.
I watch all the time.
I'm obsessed.
Wait till I show you
my triple axel.
[all laugh]
This week,
we challenged our queens
to wave their freak flags high
at the 69th International
Draglympics.
[all laugh]
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
We're here
at the RuPauley Pavilion
for the 69th International
Draglympics.
[Michelle]
Tonight, we will experience
the thrill of victory
and the agony of defeat.
Now, the judges will be scoring
on the three
compulsory elements:
fanography, voguing,
and shablams,
as well as overall showmanship.
[applause]
[Adam] It's time for
the freestyle floor program.
In an appeal
to end global warming,
Team Tuckpantistan is performing
to Shade, by DJ Shyboy.
Get it?
Shade, global warming?
[Adam] The stakes
have never been higher,
and the heels
have never been shorter.
Amen.
[music plays]
[RuPaul] Ladies, quick poll.
Raise your hand
if you believe
in climate change.
[Alyssa Edwards] It's real sunny
up here,
but I do like
a little bit of shade.
[RuPaul over music]
Well, there you have it.
97% of slantists,
and four out of four
Drag Race judges agree.
The shade is real.
Shade is real.
[voice over music] I can't deal
because reading you
is like reading
a Walt Disney book.
It's simply too easy.
I'm fixing to call you out.
I hate backstabbing bitches,
bitches, bitches.
I'm fixing to call you out.
[Bianca Del Rio] Beauty fades.
[all laugh]
Beauty fades.
Dumb is forever.
Don't be throwing
no shade, sir.
Don't, don't be throwing
no shade, shade.
No shade, sir.
All right.
Oh, I see where this is going.
Don't, don't, don't, don't,
don't, don't,
don't, don't, don't,
don't, don't, don't.
D-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-don't...
[cheers]
Don't be talking
about no shade, sir.
And you.
[all laugh]
Legendary you think you are.
Looks like leg and dairy.
[all laugh]
Read to filth.
Read.
Read, bitch.
I want you
to read these bitches.
Not today, Satan, not today.
Bitch.
You shady bitch.
-The shade.
-Bitch.
You shady bitch.
Just shake it off.
Shade.
You shady bitch.
Don't be shady.
Be a lady.
[all laugh]
[Aja] You're perfect,
you're beautiful.
You look like
Linda Evangelista.
You're a model.
Everything about you
is perfect.
Did you stone those tights?
Oh, you're smiling.
They eat her up
every single time.
[Jasmine Masters] No Tee,
no shade, no pink lemonade.
No, no, no Tee, no shade.
No, no, no pink lemonade.
All Tee, all shade.
Bitch.
The shade.
No Tee, no shade.
All Tee, all shade.
The shade, the shade.
[cheers and applause]
Tuckpantistan!
[Michelle] Legendary.
We'll be talking about that
performance for years to come.
In a plea to end world hunger,
Team Glamazonia is performing
to Serve the Children
by DJ Shyboy.
Love this one.
[music plays]
[RuPaul] You know,
we as gay people,
we get to choose our family.
You know, we get to choose
the people that we're around.
You know what I'm saying?
[all laugh]
I am your family.
We are family here.
I love you.
Mother...
has arrived.
Because I am what?
Sickening, bitch.
[cheers]
[Adore Delano] Laganja,
I didn't want to make it
that everybody
was attacking you.
[Laganja Estranja]
I feel very attacked!
Ooh, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
[all laugh]
[cheers]
[Jasmine Masters] You gotta pop
them corns so the kids can eat.
Gotta pop your corns.
Gotta pop,
pop to be the jush.
[William Tell Overture plays]
[Pearl] Do I have something
on my face?
[Valentina] I'd like to keep
it on, please.
[Tammie Brown]
And I don't see you out there
walking children in nature.
[Mystique]
Bitch, I am from Chicago.
[cheers]
Boo! Who cares?
[Latrice Royale]
I want people to realize
that it's okay
to make mistakes.
It's okay to fall down,
fall down, fall down.
Get up, look sickening,
and make them eat it.
[Michelle laughs]
Feed, feed, feed,
feed the children.
[cheers and applause]
Glamazonia! Glamazonia!
[Michelle] Hard to believe,
but we've come to an end
of another Draglympics.
Yvie seems to have
injured her ankle.
She looks like Kerri Strug.
-Ouch.
-Yikes.
[Yvie]
During the dancing,
I slipped a little bit
and hurt my ankle.
But it's not so extreme
that it should hinder
my progress in this competition.
Adam, it's time for
the Draglympics closing anthem.
[music plays]
You know, this always
brings a tear to my eye.
Due to the fact that her thighs
spread just like...
Peanut, peanut, peanut,
peanut, peanut butter.
P-p-p-peanut, peanut,
Let me see y'all.
Let me, let me,
let me see y'all.
Peanut butter.
Come on, come on.
♪ We got a mighty love ♪
[RuPaul] Category is
all that glitters.
First up, A'Keria C. Davenport.
[Michelle] Ru?
[all laugh]
[A'Keria] Baby, I am giving you
the miniature life-size
version of Ru.
Very curvaceous,
eleganza at its finest.
I feel like
I can barely breathe,
but I feel beautiful.
[Adam]
I hope that turkey in her ass
thaws out before Thanksgiving.
[RuPaul] Gobble, gobble, girl.
[Michelle]
Someone say Butterball?
[all laugh]
[RuPaul]
Brooke Lynn Hytes. Ooh.
[Adam] Oh, my God.
[Michelle] I'm ready
for my closeup, Mr. Charles.
[RuPaul] Erté okay?
[Brook Lynn]
I love my look.
I'm channeling Norma Desmond,
old Hollywood glamour.
I'm looking into
that spotlight,
oh, like this is drag.
[RuPaul] Oh, the drama.
[Mirai] I'll buy
whatever she's selling.
[Michelle] Eat your heart out,
Glenn Close.
[RuPaul] Silky Nutmeg Ganache.
[Travis] Take me to church.
[RuPaul] Oh, let the church
say amen.
-Amen.
[Silky] I am wearing
a good old sanctified
church lady jumpsuit.
Look at me.
Don't I look like
a big tall glass of water?
You look thirsty, honey.
Take a sip.
[Adam] Oh, I thought
it was hot in here.
[RuPaul] I'll see you
at the covered dish luncheon.
[all laugh]
[Michelle] Love it?
I don't even know it.
[RuPaul] Yvie Oddly.
[Adam] Oh, drop it
like it's hot.
[RuPaul] Tyler Perry
presents The Golden Girls.
[all laugh]
[Michelle]
Bring back my grills.
[all laugh]
[Yvie] Because I need support
when I walk right now,
I'm just going to milk it.
So I've got this
cute little gold cane
hobbling down the runway,
showing the judges a Japanese
underground drug lord,
like she runs
some shady business.
[RuPaul] What are those?
Make it rain, girl.
-Oh!
-Oh, my God.
[Adam] Her knees are broken,
but she's got a crack
in her ass.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Shuga Cain.
Birds of a feather
frock together.
[all laugh]
[Shuga] This runway
is my battleground
that I am ready to slay.
I am an Aztec goddess warrior
today, honey.
This look is classic Shuga.
My body is right.
I'm showing you the gold
and the shimmer, bitch.
I live for a sparkle, honey.
[Travis]
The eagle has landed.
-[Rupaul] Yes.
-[Adam] Beautiful.
[Michelle]
It's the flight of bitcheress.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Plastique Tiara.
[Adam] She can watch Drag Race
from space with those antennas.
[Plastique]
This look is like Plastique
like evolved
into mega evolution.
This is the ultimate
Plastique form.
I'm feeling
my Alyssa Edwards fantasy,
where she's got 25 things on
at once.
I'm feeling the best I've ever
felt walking down this runway.
[Mirai] Have I died
and gone to heaven?
[Travis] Light as a feather,
stiff as a strap-on.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Ra'Jah O'Hara.
[Michelle] I was wondering
where my other ball went.
[all laugh]
[Ra'Jah]
I'm serving you this catsuit
that I actually made myself.
I'm feeling my head to toe
shimmer and sparkle.
Mary J. Blige at the Met Gala
meets old money, baby.
[Travis] Woman on the go.
[RuPaul] Yes.
[Michelle]
They eyes of Tammy Heyy.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Vanessa Vanjie Mateo.
[Michelle]
Bee-boop-beep-beep.
[all laugh]
[Adam] Ooh, she's got
somewhere to go.
[Vanjie] Miss Vanjie all
gold glitter robot bunny ho.
My thighs is out, legs is long.
I'm corseted for the guys.
I can't feel my genitals.
Robotic pussy shit.
I don't even know, child.
I just look good, baby.
[Adam] 24 carrots.
[RuPaul] Yeah.
[all laugh]
[Mirai]
I think I'm in love.
[Travis]
The future Mrs. Hefner.
-Well...
-Not much future in that.
-No.
[RuPaul] Nina West.
[Michelle]
A striking Viking.
[Adam] I'm feeling horny.
[Nina] This is a quintessential
Nordic Nina, yah.
I don't think I've ever seen
anything like this
saunter down
the Drag Race stage.
Remember, it ain't over
till the fat lady sings.
♪ Ahh ♪
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Scarlet Envy.
[Travis] Death becomes her.
[Michelle]
Calling Dr. Bombay.
[Scarlet] My runway look
is giving you expensive hippie.
Lucille Ball
meets Brooke Shields
meets Ann-Margret.
She is sexy, she is funny,
she is straight up gorgeous.
Lana Del Rey, when
is your album coming out?
Soon.
[all laugh]
[Adam] Just my best dress
and a few butterfly clips.
[Michelle]
Butterflies, oh, no.
[RuPaul] Welcome, ladies.
You all did
an outstanding job tonight,
and you've made my job
very difficult.
[RuPaul] The winning team is...
From Tuckpantistan,
Team A'Keria.
[applause]
-Good job, y'all.
-Yeah, bitch. Congrats.
You are all my sheroes,
but one of you
earned Draglympic gold.
A'Keria, con-drag-ulations.
You are the winner
of this week's Maxi Challenge.
[cheers and applause]
You've won a $2.500 gift card
from Daftboy,
and a $2.500 gift card
from Elea's Closet.
[A'Keria gasps]
[A'keria] Baby, listen,
I feel like Tony the Tiger.
I feel great!
[RuPaul] A'Keria,
you picked a kickass team.
Thank you.
And that includes
the handicapped hooker.
[all laugh]
-Handi-capable.
-Handi-capable whore.
[all laugh]
So, Yvie, what happened?
What'd you do?
My heel slipped out
from under me a little bit,
and I rolled it.
-Are you okay?
-I'm gonna be fine.
I want to take it easy
until the next challenge,
and then get ready, bitches,
because she's a fast healer.
And for crying out loud,
no kick fucking.
[all laugh]
All right, Team A'Keria,
you may leave the stage.
Thank you.
Team Plastique,
I'm sorry, my dears,
but you're all up
for elimination.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques,
starting with Plastique Tiara.
Your look tonight is just
really well put together.
The accents, the wings,
it all works for me.
[Michelle] You,
in particular, Plastique,
tonight, I felt more from you,
so I'm very happy.
But I am going to ask for more,
'cause you know
I'm a greedy-ass bottom.
[laughs]
[Travis] I just think
you could just
bring up the volume
in your performance.
I felt like
some of the other queens
have a bigger personality,
and I just think
you need to like
turn up that knob
as much as possible.
[Michelle]
Keep going where you're going
and push yourself
to get there quicker,
because tick tock,
you don't stop.
[RuPaul] Ra'Jah O'Hara.
[Michelle]
Tonight on the runway,
I think you look really fun.
I'm not always a fan
of something covering the face,
but it's see-through enough
that we can see your expression.
[Adam] Performance-wise,
you still need to take it up.
[Travis]
Yesterday, I felt like
you had some of the most tools
in your box
compared to
the rest of your team.
Today, I felt that you were
just slightly unmemorable.
You're an amazing dancer.
I think you just need
to embody all of that
and deliver it forward.
Hearing that from you
kind of means the world to me,
because a couple weeks back...
[laughs]
I had a situation
with another choreographer
that really just tore me down.
Whew.
[Mirai] You know,
you're competing
against big personalities,
and so, in future challenges,
instead of looking to the past
and thinking on the negative,
just be you.
[RuPaul] Up next, Vanjie.
Your energy in rehearsal
was infectious.
It definitely portrayed
onto the stage
in the main challenge.
You slayed
the performance 100%.
Tonight on the runway,
it's sort of like
Drag Race 101,
where you shouldn't just
wear a leotard and tights.
Do you know
what I'm going to say?
I know. Sorry.
[Michelle]
It's either a leotard
or a corset and a panty
and some kind of pasty.
-Right.
-And then glitter on the chest.
I know what
you're going to be wearing
when you come around the corner.
I shouldn't be doing that,
and I'm getting bored.
[Mirai] So I get it.
Like maybe put a dress on.
But tonight, like,
I like the way you look.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
[RuPaul] All right,
up next, Nina West.
Even if you aren't
the best dancer up there,
I didn't really give a shit.
You were selling
every single moment.
[Michelle] I could not take
my eyes off of you.
You were enigmatic.
[RuPaul] What did you call her?
Sorry. I'm going to help you
with something now.
-You're a big girl.
-I am.
-And you have big shoulders.
-I do.
-And a big kind of chest.
-Yeah.
I think you need to focus more
padding on the bottom half
to balance out the top half.
It's just going to make
a more pleasing figure.
Okay, absolutely.
I totally see that.
Michelle is right. Maybe you
could put your tits on your ass.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul]
All right. Scarlet Envy.
You were actually the one
that I really lost.
You were like gone for me,
and I don't know why.
I know what you can do
in a performance.
I've directed you.
Were you insecure
about the dancing?
-Very.
-There we go.
[Travis] Yesterday I felt like,
you know,
it was hard for both of us.
However, today,
you were the most improved.
Were you the weakest at
retaining the choreography
and the steps? Yes.
Were you the weakest
at performance? No.
[Michelle] And tonight
on the runway you look pretty,
but it kind of
is not right for me.
Think grand, baby.
[Adam] The outfit
is a little bit basic.
The earrings
going into the necklace,
that one is gold and one is--
-There you go.
-Take it off.
-Gorgeous.
-Already better.
It's already much better.
It was just like
very hard for me this week.
I feel like I've been
so incredibly confident
through this process thus far,
I think maybe it almost gets on
my sisters' nerves occasionally.
And it just vanished.
[RuPaul] Thank you, Scarlet.
Ladies, I have a final question.
Who should go home tonight...
And why?
Starting with Plastique Tiara.
Just based on the critiques,
my sister Scarlet Envy.
All right. Ra'Jah.
If it were my choice,
I would send Scarlet.
A lot of the times,
when I was losing my way--
well, well, I won't blame her
for some of the mistakes
that I made, but Scarlet.
[Vanjie] I would have
to also say Scarlet,
just based on
what has happened.
Nina West.
I would also say Scarlet.
I will say this, though.
Nobody has worked harder,
so I think
that should be noted.
Scarlet, who should go home
tonight?
I can't say any of them.
But I'm not going to say me.
[RuPaul] So who should go home?
I guess Ra'Jah's
been in the bottom
a lot.
Well, thank you, ladies,
for your honesty,
and for your hard work.
While you untuck backstage,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right, now just between
us squirrel friends,
what do you think?
Let's start
with Plastique Tiara.
Tonight on the runway, she
looks like an anime character.
She's gorgeous.
[Michelle] I think
she has spent all this time
perfecting what's on the outside
that she's forgetting
about what's on the inside.
I still need more,
or else she's just going to be
that pretty girl over there.
[RuPaul] Ra'Jah O'Hara.
In the performance,
I kept losing her.
[Michelle] When you're with
four other girls,
you can't get lost in the mix.
You just can't.
It's do or die here
on RuPaul's Drag Race.
[RuPaul] Vanessa Vanjie Mateo.
Listen, on the opposite end of
the spectrum, very memorable.
[Adam] But tonight on
the runway was a total miss.
[RuPaul] Nina West,
our Viking queen.
You can't win a challenge
if you bring a look like that
to RuPaul's Drag Race.
It wasn't just something
you can buy off the rack.
Are you sure?
Those breasts
were the size of mine,
which are not buyable
off the rack.
You have to go to a doctor.
[all laugh]
But the performance tonight,
I'm a huge Nina fan.
[RuPaul] Scarlet Envy.
Tonight on the runway,
her paint was pretty,
her hair was pretty,
it just wasn't enough.
It needed to be bigger.
She gave us butterfly clips.
Butterflies
are a very tender subject
here at RuPaul's Drag Race.
[all laugh]
She was definitely
the hardest person
I've ever worked with
in my career.
-What?
-You're kidding. Really?
To like to get
to do steps. Yes.
[RuPaul] Because
there's the counting?
[Travis]
It's just the counting.
It was just a really hard
disconnect from brain to foot.
In her defense, your left foot
and your right foot,
they look very similar.
-They're very similar.
-Yeah.
And they're
right next to each other.
-[Michelle] Yes.
-[Adam] I know. I know.
[Travis] It must be really hard
to stand on stage
and have all of your sisters
say your name to go home.
I don't know
what that feels like.
Ru, who do you think
should go home?
-Travis Wall!
-[laughs]
All right, silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back my golden girls.
[RuPaul] Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Plastique Tiara,
you found your wings.
Now take me higher.
You're safe.
You may join the other girls.
Scarlet Envy, you are beautiful,
but tonight your performance
didn't score with the judges.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
Vanessa Vanjie Mateo,
you're a funny bunny,
but stop relying
on that bodysuit.
-You're safe.
-Thank you.
Ra'Jah O'Hara, tonight
you got lost in the crowd.
Nina West,
we have one word for you.
Proportionizing.
Nina West...
You are safe.
Thank you very much.
Ra'Jah, I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
[Ra'Jah] Here we go again.
I'm so sick
of being in the bottom.
[RuPaul] Two queens
stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing] for your life!
[Scarlet] I'm gonna give this
everything I have.
I'm not ready to go home.
Good luck...
and don't fuck it up.
[music plays]
♪ Last dance ♪
♪ Last chance for love ♪
♪ Yes, it's my last chance ♪
♪ For romance ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ I need you ♪
♪ By me ♪
♪ Beside me ♪
♪ To guide me ♪
♪ To hold me ♪
♪ To scold me ♪
♪ 'Cause when I'm bad ♪
♪ I'm so, so bad ♪
[Ra'Jah] Oh, girl, yes,
this is about to be
your last dance.
We'll see you
at the reunion. Bye.
♪ So let's dance ♪
♪ This last dance tonight ♪
[Vanjie]
All right, bitch, yeah!
♪ Last dance ♪
♪ Last chance for love ♪
♪ Oh, I need you by me ♪
♪ Beside me, to guide me ♪
♪ To hold me, to scold me ♪
♪ 'Cause when I'm bad,
I'm so, so bad ♪
♪ So let's dance
the last dance ♪
♪ Let's dance ♪
We all know I can't dance,
but I'm pulling out
all my tricks.
I'm determined to survive.
[cheers]
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
Whoo!
♪ Let's dance tonight ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
[cheers and applause]
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Ra'Jah O'Hara,
shantay you stay.
[applause]
Scarlet Envy,
trust me when I say
this ain't your last dance.
Now sashay away.
Thank you.
I never thought bell bottoms
would land me in the bottom,
but I will never stop dancing.
[applause]
[Vanjie] Come on, Scarlet.
Last dance, bitch.
The world wants me,
and the feeling is mutual.
Mwah.
[cheers and applause]
I don't think
I deserved to be eliminated,
but I look forward
to an incredibly bright future.
I'm very grateful.
And I'm just very reflective
right now.
Figuratively and literally.
Don't let anybody tell you
you can't dance,
even if that someone
is sometimes yourself.
Con-drag-ulations, ladies.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
-Amen.
-All right.
Now let the music play.
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪
[RuPaul] Next time
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
You need to create
a farm-to-runway look.
Bitch, why are you
putting my shit
on your garment
in the first place?
You have a really pretty face.
Honey, that's everything.
It doesn't suck,
but it could be better.
Make me lip sync for my life.
♪ To, to, to, to, to ♪
♪ to, to, to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪