[RuPaul] Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
You'll be starring in LADP.
[siren]
-Get it.
-Ma'am, ma'am.
Oh!
Ma'am, get off the car.
-Grab him.
-Yeah, oh, yeah.
Oh god, hold on.
I switched roles
with Brooke Lynn
so she would feel
more comfortable,
and it kind of threw me
off my game.
[RuPaul] Vanjie and Plastique.
There was no way
for anyone to get in there.
With both of you,
it was a bit of a free-for-all.
[RuPaul] A'Keria C. Davenport.
You always had
new bits happening.
Working with you was one of the
highlights for me yesterday.
Con-drag-ulations. You are the
winner of this week's challenge.
[applause]
Vanjie, shantay you stay.
Plastique Tiara, sashay away.
Whew.
Bitch.
Oh, Lord, girl.
[Shuga] Plastique
has been eliminated,
and we are just all so surprised
that she is no longer with us.
[Vanjie]
The bitch has nice handwriting.
Not only is she pretty,
but she got pretty handwriting.
That is a true diva.
[Shuga]
How you feeling, Vanj?
Girl, like
I'm not done fighting.
[Vanjie] So I have a lot of
thoughts going through my head.
A lot of the times,
the judges are telling me
you have this natural born gift,
and they'll praise me on that.
But then I go to do that
in a challenge,
and it's almost like,
oh, I just need Vanjie.
I'm trying to figure out
exactly what they want from me.
Like I'm just confused.
[Brooke Lynn]
Congrats, A'Keria.
Who would have thought
your thot twerking ways
would get you a good old win.
Baby.
[laughs]
Do not take that roach with ya.
[all laugh]
They thought you was a roach.
[Silky] I got called a roach
today, bitch.
A roach.
I guess one thing about roaches,
we don't die,
we multiply, bitch,
so get used to me, honey.
I ain't dying
in this competition.
[Shuga]
Brooke Lynn, how you feeling?
You like
redeemed yourself today.
[Brooke Lynn] I did. I feel
fantastic that I'm still here.
I worked really hard,
and it fucking paid off.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I feel amazing.
I didn't know
what to expect going in,
and I couldn't be more happy.
[Nina] She's talking about how
she was so proud
to be in the top,
but in this challenge, I
worked really closely with her.
She didn't even acknowledge
the work that I helped her with,
and I was kind of like...
that was kind of bullshit.
I mean, I think
Brooke Lynn and I
did a lot
of really good work together,
and I'm proud that Brooke Lynn
was in the top and almost won.
I did. I brought myself
back from the dead.
[Nina] As much as we're friends,
I made some sacrifices
that I probably shouldn't have.
Brooke Lynn is in it to win it.
I have to focus on myself.
Now let's get
the fuck out of drag.
-All right.
-Done.
Done.
[all laugh]
[Yvie] The way it stands
right now,
Brooke Lynn, Silky,
and A'Keria
are leading our pack
with two wins apiece.
Made it out alive.
Ain't gonna be
in the bottom no more.
[A'Keria] There are
girls falling behind.
At this point,
get it together or get lost.
Plane ticket, train ride, Uber.
Go on back to the house.
[RuPaul] The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100.000.
With extra special guest judges
Katherine Langford
and Gina Rodriguez.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
[laughs]
Come on, Calgary stampede.
It's a brand new day,
ladies and gentlemen,
and there's only seven ho's
on the chopping block.
And this ho ain't going nowhere.
[alarm]
[RuPaul] Ooh, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
My magical queens.
Hocus pocus,
y'all ready to steal focus?
Just add
some bippity boppity Ru,
and you can make
the competition disappear.
[cheers and applause]
Hello, hello, hello.
-Hi, Ru.
-Oh, shit.
[RuPaul] Ladies, now if a queen
wants to go all the way,
she needs to learn how to work
well other people and shit,
because what happened was
they would tell her,
you ain't working well
with people.
[all laugh]
Speaking of others,
♪ Oh, Pit Crew ♪
[cheers and applause]
-Oh.
[cheers]
Delta!
Oh, my wig.
Delta Work,
what are you doing here?
I figured it was a good day
to come check out the set.
[all laugh]
Well, darling,
you have impeccable timing.
No, just a really good
sense of smell.
[all laugh]
Ladies,
for today's Mini Challenge,
we're playing a game
called Balls to the Wall.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Now each of you
will be paired
with one of these gorgeous,
hot menseses
who are wearing underwear
provided by Dirt Squirrel.
[chuckles]
Now, the queen
who gets the most balls
in the sack fastest wins.
Oh, and one more detail.
You can't use your hands.
Now, instead, I'll pick a card
to determine
each pair's position.
You know, hip to hip,
shoulder to butt,
ass to ass.
[cheers]
Yeah!
Don't worry, girls.
I got this.
Now, Delta, would you be willing
to be our ball girl?
I'm everybody's ball girl.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Okay, first up,
Shuga Cain and Jason.
Your position
will be head to butt
using the blue ball.
Assume the position.
Yes, baby.
My husband's gonna be mad
as hell, but I can't help it.
He's so beautiful.
All right, go.
Ball to the wall.
[cheers]
Put that ball in your face.
[bell dings]
[RuPaul] Disco ball ass to ass.
Actually disco ball ass to ass
is the name of my new album.
[all laugh]
Hip to hip with an 8 ball.
Ooh, sounds like
a Saturday night to me.
[all laugh]
Oh, yeah, teamwork.
[Shuga] Yes, bitch,
that's how you do it.
Let him lead, honey.
Oh![buzzer]
And go.
[bell dings]
[buzzer]
Ooh, look at that
cute little chicken leg.
[bell dings]
That's fine,
but they still move.
They still move, baby.
And go.
-Balls to the wall.
-Yes.
Oh.
[bell dings]
[RuPaul] Well done.
I'm determined and I know how
to work these balls, baby.
Wait, bitch, where we going?
Hold on, Barry!
[all laugh]
Drop the thing.
[bell dings]
Yes!
We got in there, baby.
Come on, come on,
hold my wig, hold my wig.
Hold on, put it in the back.
[bell dings]
I might win something!
[all laugh]
Okay, ear to hip.
Now, Silky, that's your ear
to his hip.
Oh, I got this.
[all laugh]
[Vanjie] What the heck?
[bell dings]
[cheers and applause]
What the--
Yo, ladies,
don't you wish gym class
had been this much fun?
[all laugh]
Yes, ma'am.
I wouldn't have quit.
The queen
that buried the most balls
in the shortest amount of time
is...
Vanessa Vanjie Mateo.
[cheers and applause]
Thank you, Jesus.
I won something.
It's a Mini Challenge,
but it's something.
You've won a $2.500 gift card
from Dirt Squirrel.
Delta, Pit Crew,
thank you so much
for dropping by.
We had a ball.
-Bye.
-Bye, Delta.
Ladies,
for this week's Maxi Challenge,
you need to razzle-dazzle,
mystify, and amaze,
as you star
in your very own magic show.
[cheers and laughter]
Now, you'll be performing
in two teams.
Now, Vanjie,
you won the Mini Challenge,
so you get to choose
your magical sisters.
So, Vanjie,
who is your first choice.
Big Silk with the alacazam milk.
Yeah
[all laugh]
Come on, bitch.
All right.
Who's your second choice?
A'Keria.
And who is your third choice?
I'm going to choose Yvie.
All right, so you're going
to play the race card.
[all laugh]
No.
[RuPaul] That means Nina West,
Shuga Cain,
and Brooke Lynn Hytes,
you are the competing team.
All right.
Now, in addition to performing
professional illusions,
you need to name your magic act,
write captivating patter,
and create a magical look
using makeup provided
by Anastasia Beverly Hills.
[Nina] This is what I do.
I produce and I write shows.
Look out, David Copperfield,
because I'm about to do
the best reappearing act
in this competition.
Challenge agenda.
Our main challenge this week
is a drag magic show.
I cannot wait.
This is a great opportunity
for us to really be cheesy.
We have to essentially
produce a show.
It requires scripting.
It requires producing.
It requires
learning a magic trick.
So this a huge undertaking.
-I think we can turn this out.
-Absolutely.
[Nina] After last week, I don't
want to fade into the back.
I want to be at the forefront.
So let's figure out
what our storyline is.
Like, what's our relationship?
Are we a sister act?
Are we...
like maybe we're like
all left in an orphanage,
and we're left
to our own devices.
And we grow up
in the alleys of Vegas.
I don't know.
So my team
is a team of over-thinkers.
[laughs]
I think
we should be single ladies.
I think we should be older.
We're taking a long time
to get where we need to be.
Oh, my God, what if we're like
three sorority sisters?
-Like in that fall act.
-Yeah.
Our sorority is what?
This is the one thing
I was worried about.
Because Nina loves
to second-guess.
Brooke loves
to get in her feelings.
And I already do that,
so it's like the blind
leading the blind today, girl.
I don't know.
[laughs]
Like, some da-da-da-da-da.
Um...
"You will create a name
for your magic troupe,
the order of illusions, and who
will perform which tricks."
[Yvie] What are some
of the individual illusions?
Okay, so we have
the appearing bra trick.
The milk pitcher trick.
The milk magically vanishes
into to the newspaper.
I kind of want to do the milk.
Okay, so I can do
the appearing bra trick.
This is a whole lot
of abracadabra, bitch.
[all laugh]
Let's create a magical name.
We could make a joke about
how we got all the ethnic girls.
[laughs]
The Dark Sided Magicians
or something?
Black Magic.
I think it should be
Da Black Magic, with D-A,
and when something happens,
say, Da Black Magic.
[all laugh]
[Yvie] But for real, though,
do you guys think
the other team is at all peeved
with how things were split up?
[Silky] If they upset,
they're only upset because
we are Team Personality.
Like let's be honest about it.
Damn, Vanjie, you put all
the girls with the most talent,
the most charm,
the most character,
and the most beauty,
minus Yvie, on the same team.
They destined
to motherfucking fail,
and I live for it.
Hey, cysts.
-Hi.
-Hi, Ru.
How are tricks?
[all laugh]
Business is good.
Shazam, ladies.
-Hi, Ru.
-Hi.
Hi. So you two
have worked together before.
Yes, we have.
Actually quite a bit.
Why do you think Vanjie
didn't you put you on her team?
Aren't you guys very close?
She didn't want
our romantic connection
getting in the way of our work.
Is there really
a romantic connection?
Yeah.
We have a situation-ship.
Have you slipped her the tongue?
Several times.
Really?
Have you slipped her
your pinky finger?
[laughs] My God.
You're making me blush, Ru.
No pinky fingers.
And you weren't shocked
that you weren't chosen
for Vanjie's team?
[Brooke Lynn]
This is a competition,
and I don't expect
anything like that.
I don't expect to be chosen
for her team just because...
You're sticking her the pinky.
[all laugh]
I feel like a 12-year-old girl.
[laughs]
Now, do any of you
have any experience in magic?
-None.
-Really?
I can make my eyebrows
disappear.
Yes, you can.
And that's the magic of drag
right there.
You know, I love drag
because of the magical aspects.
And how we, like Auntie Mame,
can create an illusion
out of some duct tape
and paint and powder.
And that's really
what we want to see
in this challenge, you know.
Do you all have a narrative?
-We have several.
-We have several. Yeah.
I think we're finally deciding
to hone in on one, right?
Yeah, we're trying to work
on a couple--an idea.
Now, you haven't won
any challenges.
Not yet.
How are you going
to make that happen?
You know, I think
I'm a little funny.
I do funny sometimes.
Yeah, no, that's why
you're here.
You've got it all.
It's just how do you excel
with all the other girls
who have it all?
Absolutely.
The judges said that Silky
overshadowed me
in the last challenge.
So for this week,
I have to make sure that
I'm going in as a wrecking ball.
And if I feel like I'm doing
enough, I need to do more.
Hey, colored girl magic.
-Hey.
I was surprised
you didn't choose Brooke Lynn
because apparently
you two are an item.
I'm not gonna put my man
in my group.
You know, get your own--
go on your side with, you know.
When he had the chance
to pick people,
he picked Nina, and I
wasn't pressed about it.
He's doing good
in this competition.
I need to worry about myself.
I'm thinking what's
going to make me win
and excel in this challenge?
I'm thinking with this,
not with this or this.
Do any of you have experience
with magic?
You know, I made some men
disappear in my day.
[Vanjie] Right, right.
I go from trucker
to a woman in 25 minutes.
Like that is true magic.
Do you really see yourself
as a trucker
before you get into drag?
[all laugh]
I would like to know
what scares you
about this challenge.
Probably what happened
last week,
which was just watching
a train wreck happening,
not being able to stop
the train from wrecking.
Yeah. You started at 10.
There's nowhere to go
from there.
Planning out in advance is going
to be something you need to do.
[Vanjie] Right. I completely--
I want you to know
that I am listening.
I understand
exactly what you're saying.
[RuPaul] Well, listen, ladies,
I cannot wait
to see Da Black Magic.
Let me get right back
to writing.
Let me get back
to writing my script.
All right.
I have a lot to prove still.
I just need to make sure
when we slay this,
that I'm like
slam dunking this thing.
You know, I need to go
Michael Jordan on them.
That's a straight reference
for the people out there.
Superbowl Sunday Beyoncé this.
I need my moment.
-Hi.
How's it going?
[Shuga] It is time for us to
learn some magic tricks, honey.
My name is Kyle Marlett.
I'm a magician and a magic
creator from Las Vegas,
and Ru invited me here
to teach you guys some magic.
You guys all ready
for some magic?
-Yes.
[all] Aah!
All right.
[cheers and applause]
[Kyle] All right, let's get
started doing some magic.
What trick
are you going to be doing?
-I'm doing the swallowing sword.
-Oh, boy.
Now, this one is technically
actually kind of dangerous.
I'm going to show you first.
What?
[Shuga]
Is he really doing this?
-So you actually swallow that?
-Mm-hmm.
[muffled] It's in my throat.
Girl.
What?
Hmm.
So it's like...
Mm.
Now you try. Okay, so go ahead
and put it in your mouth.
And just kind of nom on it,
basically.
Oh, nothing has happened.
Okay.
[all laugh]
I have tricks fail on me
all the time.
But it's important to hide that
in your presentation.
You cover up your mistakes
with comedy.
I'll just ask for the Pit Crew.
Maybe I can try
to swallow those instead.
All right.
We'll move on
to the next person.
Step up up.
[laughs]
I love it, I love it.
Perfect.
All right, the milk trick.
It's very important
that it's 2%.
I'm kidding.
That has nothing to do with it.
[all laugh]
So you can roll it up
into a cone like so.
And now you're going
to take some milk.
You're slowly going to pour it.
Now you say the magic words.
What are the magic words?
-Mm, boom.
-Right, right?
Boom!
-It's gone.
-What?
Oh! Oh, my goodness.
-It's pretty cool, right?
-You ready for me to try it?
Yeah. It's actually
really, really easy.
-I'll tell you when.
-Ooh.
I don't know why you're moaning,
but keep going.
More. More, more.
-Shit.
-Okay. All right.
[all laugh]
Now, you know,
at the end of the day,
you got to let
the trade know, you know--
oops--there's
a little bit there still.
Okay. And now you snap
and say boom.
Boom!
Ain't shit there.
[all laugh]
Where the milk at, bitch?
[Kyle] And what's your
presentation during this?
Your patter and everything.
So, you know, uh,
you know, the gentlemen
like to skeet all over your--
They milk all over your--
your face and stuff.
No more.
Aim for the cone,
and it will be gone.
That's obviously for more
of an adult audience, right?
We gonna have children here?
Work on your script,
work on your presentation.
[Shuga] What I'm noticing
from Team Personality
is that a lot of their stuff
is really off-color.
It's kind of filthy.
The magic show
is supposed to be PG-13,
and right now, it's just
reading kind of tasteless.
So this one's a little tricky,
but it's definitely fun.
So I'll show you first,
all right?
-Okay.
-Glass over here.
Wine bottle here.
Empty tube, right?
Ready?
One, two, and three.
What? Okay,
but how do you do that?
All right, so you try it,
and really fast.
Boom. You did it.
I'm a magician.
I'm trying, I'm trying,
Mary, I'm trying.
Oh, no.
No, that's not right.
That's not what
you're supposed to do.
[all laugh]
I'm really trying
to get my trick down,
and add these nuances
of almost like this
Chris Farley-esque magician.
And what is your presentation
for this?
So won't we look prettier
if we're all drunker.
Shots all around.
That's pretty good, right?
I mean, that's pretty good.
[Yvie] As we watch
the other team,
I'm like, fuck,
they've got humor,
they've obviously
got rehearsed lines.
It's definitely making me
nervous for my team.
[Kyle] All right, we'll move on
to the next person.
So hold this
in your dominant hand.
And take the lid,
put it on top of the pan.
Yep, all the way down.
Do your magic wave,
your presentation.
-Shabam, alacazam.
-Yeah.
Oh!
-Pretty good, right?
-That is great.
So this is a really,
really easy one, right?
So it's all presentation
with this one.
[Shuga] My magic trick,
it's actually pretty easy.
Thank the Lord, honey.
So now I can just focus
on putting on a show
so that it looks like fantastic.
Thank you.
This is amazing.
[snoring]
Yes.
[laughs]
So I'm going to show you
with the playing cards,
but you can use
anything you want, all right?
I will be honest.
This is probably
one of the hardest tricks
that you could do.
[Brooke Lynn] Good.
So I'm glad
you picked this one.
So happy, too.
What?
[laughs]
Where--wh-what?
Take the card.
[Brooke Lynn] What?
Whew. Whooch.
I'll let you try.
So hold it between your fingers.
Give it a spin.
And--okay.
I don't--
I've never seen
this technique before.
[all laugh]
Don't be so awkward, okay?
Just remember, you've got
to use your presentation,
you understand, right?
I don't want you
to be stressed out though.
-I'm not.
-I know magic's hard.
I stress out about everything.
Take the card,
and let me know how that goes.
-All right.
-I hate this.
[Shuga] Brooke is struggling.
She hates it.
She don't want to it.
She can't get it.
She is over this trick.
And we have to be amazing,
because we are up against
Team Personality.
[Nina] I feel really
confident about what I'm doing,
but there's no doubt in my mind
that Brooke Lynn,
after watching the other team
and seeing
gigantic personalities,
I think she's in her head
a little bit
and saying
how do I sell the trick?
This could derail our
whole team's goal of winning.
This is like
a do-or-die situation.
I'm not going home
after the challenge.
[humming]
Disappear, disappear, disappear.
After learning our magic
and watching
the other team's production,
it's quite clear that we need
a hell of a lot more structure.
Ugh.
[Yvie] So we should start
working on the format.
I think yours is going to be
the biggest segment
where we're going
to need to pad it up
since A'Keria's
going to have her mouth full.
Like we should have
some jokes prewritten
so that we
can just pop those out.
[A'Keria] I think it should be
one of those situations
where it just comes
straight off the head
versus us writing it down now.
Well, like, obviously
we can talk and kiki,
but like I think it needs
to be a little organized.
I think it should be
like we casually talking,
and it's just like, you know--
I think we just need like some
transitions between our pieces.
We have some people
that want to improv
and some people that want
to write their parts down
and I'm trying
to people-please everybody.
So I'm not saying we need
to maybe make a specific.
[Yvie]
But like it goes wrong--
[Vanjie]
We need to have something--
[Yvie]
Stuff to lean back on.
But everybody can just
play off of each other,
because we do have
that chemistry.
[Yvie] Silky and A'Keria
want to improv their way through
this whole challenge.
I'm just kind of tired
of fighting all of them.
But in the back of my head,
I still know we need
some more structure.
The only thing I think that does
super need to be written down
and rehearsed is the intro.
Now let's go over
this intro for sure.
[Yvie] Okay. I'm going to
write out these lines then.
My group is a bunch
of strong, opinionated girls,
and I thought that
was going to be the bonus.
It might be the downfall.
[cheering]
Come on.
Oh, Lord.
[Vanjie] Today
is elimination day,
and we have to perform this
magic show for the judges.
I feel like somebody
gonna disappear tonight.
Bippity-boppity-bye.
[Silky]
Can I put my magic in you?
Oh, you can put your magic in me
any time, Silk.
Wherever you want
to put your magic.
Brooke Lynn and Nina are
definitely feeling better today.
We practiced last night.
It came together.
Ah, it's gonna work.
♪ Whoo ♪
[A'Keria] I'm having a bad day.
There's so much
running through my head.
I'm definitely still worried
about my team.
I'm just really like not
in a good space right now.
[Yvie] Hey, Miss A'Keria,
how you feeling?
I'm not in my spirit.
Like I'm just--I don't know.
[Yvie]
Why not? What's the Tee?
[A'Keria] I'm just not
myself right now.
Yeah, because you seem
a little mellow for you today.
Yeah. I'm just
kind of like in my head.
[Nina] I noticed A'Keria
is really down.
Like you can tell
she's frustrated,
and obviously
it's regarding the challenge.
Silk, how you guys feeling?
[Silky]
I'm not sure if I even know.
We basically had to change
our entire show last night.
Why?
Because our jokes
were a little too dirty.
We were too explicit.
Rated R.
[all laugh]
[Yvie] We're just going
to have to make sure
that it's on in there
for the cameras when it counts.
[Nina] Yeah, that's true.
Of course,
the competition mind in me
is like, okay, well, one
of them's got a clipped wing,
and it sounds like they're
working on a completely new act.
So A'Keria could be in trouble.
[Silky]
I got a question for you all.
If we could use magic to
change one thing in the world,
what would it be?
I think by taking away war,
we could solve
so many problems in the world.
[Silky] Brooke Lynn, you're not
competing for a Continental.
Give us a real--[all laugh]
How about if you could
change something
that's happened throughout
this competition so far,
what would it be?
[Yvie] Ooh.
[Shuga] I would have burned
that troll outfit, girl.
Yeah.
You still should.
[all laugh]
Shady as hell.
[Silky] What would you
have changed, Vanjie?
If I could go back in time,
I would not pack 46 swimsuits.
[all laugh]
[giggles]
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
[applause]
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage, now, can you
pull a rabbit out of a hat?
No, but I can make
a snake disappear.
Several many snakes
disappear, honey.
[all laugh]
The hilarious Ross Mathews.
Now, do you know any tricks?
Ru, watch this, ready?
[blows]
[laughs]
And the lovely
Katherine Langford.
How you doing?
I'm good.
Glad to be here.
Are you from Australia?
Whereabouts?
I am. I'm from Perth.
Ah, you got Perth-onality,
do ya?
[all laugh]
You bet.
I'll meet you down at Cottesloe.
Be there.
See ya, mate.
[laughs]
[RuPaul] Good on ya, mate.
Hilly dilly.
And Gina Rodriguez.
Now, are you
a Drag Race virgin?
My legs are not crossed
under this table.
[laughs] Prove it.
Rrrrrrr.
So excited you're here.
It's great to be here, Ru.
This week,
we challenged our queens
to put on a drag-tastic
magic show.
And tonight on the runway,
category is Caftan Realness.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[cheers and applause]
[RuPaul] Let the magic show
begin.
[Gina] Yes. [laughs]
Ladies and gentlemen...
Boys and girls.
I am Shuga Shablam Alacazam.
And I'm Bubbly Brooke.
[all laugh]
Girl, where is Nina?
Football practice?
[all laugh]
I'm checking her dressing room.
Open sesame.
Girl, she is not
even fucking in here.
Well, like they say
in show business...
-Fuck her.
-No, Mary.
Magic waits for no queen.
-We're titillating.
-We're tantalizing.
We're dudes.
[laughter and applause]
Better late than pregnant,
I always say.
I'm Naughty Nina,
and our journey begins
five years ago,
where three young ladies
had blue eye shadow,
duct tape, and a dream
of...[whispers] magic.
[all laugh]
Now, there are a few rules
at every drag show.
So rule number one:
the more you drink,
the prettier we look.
But, Shuga,
this is a drag magic show,
so I actually think
the first rule is
the more we drink,
the better they look.
Touché.
Which leads us to our first
trick, ladies and gentlemen.
Bippity, boppity,
glug-glug-glug-glug, booze.
We take a bottle of Merlot
and a shot glass.
All I want to do is replace
the bottle with the shot glass,
the shot glass with the bottle.
We all on the same page?
Great.
[all laugh]
I cover the bottle
with this lovely empty canister.
You can shove your fist
in it, too.
It's been lubed with Crisco.
Then we take
this other empty cani--
I'll save this one
for after the show.
We cover our shot glass.
Now, ladies and gentlemen, I'm
gonna need your help here, okay?
When I count to three, I need
you to say that magical word
that's going to make it
all happen:
tucktastic.
One, two, three.
[all] Tucktastic.
Aah!
Wow.
[cheers and applause]
Magic!
[all laugh]
Shall we do it again?
Do you dare me to do it again?
We will do it again,
ladies and gentlemen.
One, two, three.
Tucktastic!
Oh.
I think there's an alcoholic
in our midst,
and it's me.
But looks like
I have a bottle for Ross...
a bottle for Michelle...
a bottle for Mama Ru...
a bottle for Gina...
a bottle for Katherine...
a bottle for Brooke...
a bottle for Shuga...
and a shot for me,
ladies and gentlemen.
That is bippity, boppity, boo.
[cheers and applause]
Rule number two is cleanliness
is close to goddessness.
Now, if only there was a queen
who had some dirty,
raunchy tights around.
[all laugh]
Ooh, pee-eew.
How long's it been since
you've washed your tights?
September...2015.
[all laugh]
[grunting] Aah!
Whew. Those are fragrant.
Now I know
what Vanjie feels like.
[all laugh]
These definitely need
some magic detergent.
Ooh, shablam.
-Ooh.
-So does this, girl.
Shuga Slablam. Alacazam.
Fresh tuck panties.
[cheers and applause]
[whispers] Magic.
[all laugh]
That brings us to Rule three:
illusion is everything.
Now, me and these bubbles
have a lot in common.
You see, these bubbles dance.
They are light and flowy
like air.
[whispers] Magic.
We both move with the power
of a thousand seas.
[all laugh]
[whispers] Magic.
The thing we have the most
in common is my tuck.
[whispers] Magic.
You see,
they're soft to look at,
but hard to the touch.
[applause]
Ladies and gentlemen,
no stunt has been pulled on
the Drag Race stage like this
since Valentina said "I'd
like to keep it on, please."
[all laugh]
Now, Brooke Lynn Hytes
doesn't know this,
but she's going to step ever so
gently into this big wooden box.
What?
-Go ahead, baby.
-What's happening?
-Don't worry about it.
-Oh, don't worry, sweetheart.
What--what--what?
Oh, I feel very uncomfortable.
Saturday night for me.
Get in the box.
I feel very attacked
right now!
[all laugh]
Also, Shug, this is a great way
to get it down to a final six.
Amen. Eliminate the competition.
Oh, thank you, dear.
I haven't been on top
in a while.
We know.
[all laugh]
-One.
-Two.
Three!
[cheers and applause]
Magic!
It's a heavy flow day.
Halleloo, I'm back, bitches.
Ladies and gentlemen,
you've just witnessed
the reverse Shangela!
[all laugh]
[Shuga] I'm a little brown
woman in a big brown box.
Oh!
[all laugh]
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
Halleloo times two.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm Bubbly Brooke.
I'm Naughty Nina.
And I'm Shuga Shablam Alacazam.
And together we are...
[all] The Mighty Tucks!
[cheers and applause]
[all] Magic.
Magic...
Magic.
And the tricks
just keep on coming.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
Thank you all for coming.
Ladies and gentlemen,
boys and squirrels,
I welcome you
to our dark mystical world.
Deeper than my tuck,
but hotter as hell.
It's even worse than a cold
blank stare from Michelle.
[laughs]
Straight from the light
and all that is tragic,
and you'll find my sisters.
We are Da Black Magic.
The Black Magic.
Ooh, Da Black Magic.
Da Black Magic.
[Yvie] Da Black Magic.
-Oh, Da Black Magic.
-Mm-hmm.
Da Black Magic.
[cheers and applause]
I am Yvie the Oddball.
I'm Big Silk Boom.
And I'm Vanishing Vanjie.
All right,
now let's get this--wait.
One, two, three.
Where's Miss Thing?
-She--
-Can we go get her?
She better not be gone.
Bippity bop
and titties that flop.
Look out, girl,
it's Azakazam A'Keria.
-Yeah.
-Oh, girl.
And together, we are...
[all] Da Black Magic.
[cheers and applause]
We are the world's
first troupe of magicians
who travel
from barbeque to barbeque.
It's a little cold
in here, baby.
I'm feeling the breeze.
That's 'cause you don't have
a bra, a panties, anything.
How indecent--
When do I ever?
True.
This is a children's
function, though.
And where there are kids,
there are baby daddies,
which means I can find
the Adam for my Yvie.
But I know it's not easy
to tie the knot.
Look, I did it. I did--
That's a real knot, y'all.
[all laugh]
Come on.
Ooh, now let's see
if I can whip up a bra
for my baby over here.
Ooh...oh...
Bippity, boppity, bra.
[cheers and applause]
Look at this cute
over-the-shoulder
boulder holder.
She'll hold some jugs.
Did someone say jugs?
Jugs of milk...shake?
[all laugh]
My milkshake brings
all the boys to the yard.
And so I gotta get that
to the barbeque
as soon as possible, honey,
so I got to teleport it
with this sheet of paper.
Ooh, baby.
Ahh, baby.
Roll it up, baby.
Wind it, baby.
-Wind it.
-Ooh.
And now we pour.
Oh.
[A'Keria] Oh, girl.
No drop left behind, baby.
[Vanjie] I've never seen you
this concentrated.
Mm.
-Oh, girl.
-She's feeling her Elsie.
[Yvie] Oh, it's still going.
Oh, how much can you fill?
Now let's feel if she's dry.
I feel a little thirsty.
-Thank you, sis.
-I got you, girl.
I got you, girl.
All right, fee fi fo fum.
Look out, throat, here it comes.
Oh, where'd it go, baby?
That's some good shit
right there.
Oh, I know there's going
to be a lot of boys
at this barbeque, honey.
Speaking of the barbeque,
if this bitch don't have
condiments at this barbeque,
I'm gonna beat her ass,
because I had to have
a dry hot dog last time.
Girl, y'all won't believe
what just happened to me
-at the grocery store.
-Tell 'em, boo.
I went in there trying to get
the condiments for the barbeque.
The lady said, ma'am,
whatever you have in that bag,
you didn't pay for.
I said,
what are you talking about?
She said, open up the bag,
show me the ketchup.
I said, what are you
talking about, this?
She said, yeah, that.
You didn't pay for it.
I said, ain't nothing--
no ketchup in here, baby.
I had to get it together,
and I said, look,
what's in the bag, Christine?
What's in the bag?
I know you gagging.
I can see you.
And I said I don't got ketchup
in the bag.
I got mustard in the bag.
Okay, I see y'all are gagged.
Ain't nothing in the bag.
She said, well, flip it
to the other hand, Mary,
if you think you so cute.
I said, okay,
ain't nothing in the bag still.
You know what?
I'm about to show you
what's really in the bag.
Da Black Magic, mama.
Ain't nothing in the bag.
Ain't no ketchup.
Ain't nothing.
Now, A'Keria, what you
bringing to this barbeque?
Oh, girl, you know,
I got to bring to this barbeque
my old trick.
I'm gonna show you
why I am the most popular girl
at the barbeque.
Just gonna pump this
right on up.
All right, just like that.
'Tis a jiggle,
and hip that do, too.
Watch out, y'all, I'm gonna
take this down to the zoo.
[Yvie] Oh, girl.
Oh, my. Ooh.
-How's she doing that?
-I don't know.
[Michelle]
She must be popular.
Oh, you're almost there, girl.
Just the tip.
Girl.
[applause]
You know, it also works
for a low cal diet.
[Vanjie]
Girl, after watching that,
y'all know I got
a little bit of the itis,
'cause that means
you done ate a lot of food,
and you're getting
a little sleepy.
Well, I just got a lot of gas.
Well, lucky for you,
I know the oldest trick
in the Black Magic book.
Okay, girl, you're gonna need to
lay yourself on this magic table
so that
we can get you some rest
that's light as a feather,
but stiff as a board.
Magic table?
Let's wrap her up tight
so she gets that good sleep.
Mm-hmm.
What's the Tee, Christine?
What's the--?
Yeah, still works.
Oh, oh, I feel
Da Black Magic in me.
Girl, I think it's time.
Oh!
-All right.
-Keep pulling on out, girl.
Oh!
[cheers and applause]
[Michelle] Wow.
It's Da Black Magic.
[cheers and applause]
But wait. We're gonna be late
for our next barbeque.
We'd better fix this table
and wake her up.
Oh, girl.
Oh.
Girl, I need my plate.
Time to wake Miss Vanjie.
[all] Miss Vanjie.
Miss Vanjie. Miss Vanjie.
Da Black Magic!
[cheers and applause]
Girl, come on, we gotta
get to the next barbeque.
[Shuga] This really Da Loud
Magic.
[cheers and applause]
We are Da Black Magic.
♪ We got a mighty love ♪
Category is Caftan Realness.
First up, the Dr. Reverend
Silky Nutmeg Ganache.
Why y'all gagging so?
She bringing to you every ball.
[all laugh]
[Silky] Bitch, I am the Tee,
and I know I am the Tee
in this caftan.
Big old balls on my head.
Now, that's a magic trick,
'cause I know
all of you wondering
how I got them
to stick on my head.
Alacazam, that's all
you need to know, ho.
[Ross] She's going ball.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] This is the mahogany
fantasy, darling.
I'm a winner, baby.
Yvie Oddly.
Holy caftan.
[Katherine]
Hello, Your Holiness.
[all laugh]
[Yvie] Because it's
a fabulous caftan challenge,
I want to serve
100% enlightened monk realness.
Just gliding down the runway
spreading peace.
It's got this train that
sweeps the runway behind me.
[Michelle] Crochet!
[all laugh]
-What? Ow.
-Ooh.
[RuPaul] My goodness.
[Ross] She deserves
a pat on the back.
-She certainly does.
-From herself.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] A'Keria C. Davenport.
That bitch is fly.
[Michelle] Yes, honey.
Fly, fly, fly, fly.
[A'Keria] So, baby,
mama is feeling
so fierce on this stage.
My caftan is a pantsuit
with butterfly wings.
The fabric is flowing,
and I just feel like
I am going to take flight
at any moment.
[Ross] You butta fly.
[RuPaul] She just
came out of her cocoon.
What did I just call me?
[all laugh]
[RuPaul]
Vanessa Vanjie Mateo. Ooh.
[Michelle] From
the Jackie Stallone collection.
[RuPaul] Yes.
[Vanjie] I'm extra, extra,
caftan all about it.
Cheetah print head to toe.
I'm a white lady on vacation.
I put that turban on
just in case a little
splash of water, bitch.
I made sure my little
baby hairs are laid down.
I'm looking like when those
bitches go on a vacation,
and they put all their shit on.
[Ross] If you like it, then you
better put a nose ring on it.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Brooke Lynn Hytes.
[Gina]
That's a plum choice.
[RuPaul]
It certainly is. Ooh.
[Brooke Lynn] I'm giving you
fucking sexy caftan realness.
It's like
a little bit Studio 54,
a little bit Sarah
Jessica Parker in Abu Dhabi
in Sex and the City 2,
a little bit Wonder Woman.
I'm just shaking that chiffon
behind me,
and then I just throw it.
Yes.
[RuPaul] Oh, yes, honey.
Sell the garment.
[Michelle] Eat it, Barney.
[RuPaul] Ooh, purple rain,
purple train.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Shuga Cain.
[Michelle] Anna Karenina
no she betta don't.
[RuPaul] Oh, meet you
in Gorky Park.
[Michelle laughs]
[Shuga] I am giving you magic
on this runway.
I'm feeling luxurious
in my faux fur.
I'm ready to cuddle up
by the fire
in this gorgeous caftan.
And voila, it is spring, honey.
I am feeling my fruit fantasy.
She is blossoming
all over this runway.
I'm showing you all the legs,
the sun's out.
I'm ready to catch
these boys, honey.
-Oh.
-Ooh.
[Michelle]
Beach blanket bang-a-ho.
[RuPaul] Shuga Cain,
now de-caftan-ated.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Nina West.
Welcome to Caftanistan.
[all laugh]
[Ross] Bea Arthur?
More like A+ Arthur.
-Yes.
[Nina] I'm really
trying to sell
the luxury of this lifestyle
in my elegant Elizabeth Taylor
seventies caftan.
I'm feeling loose and free,
and I can feel the wind
go up my ass, which is amazing.
I haven't felt that in weeks.
This woman is a woman of means,
and she's getting ready
for a busy day of sitting.
[Michelle] Lady Bunny
never looked so good.
[RuPaul] Mm. See you later
at the Regal Beagle.
[all laugh]
[Michelle] Yes, Mrs. Groper.
All of those references
were too old
for everybody in this room.
[RuPaul] Well, you're
educating children.
Ladies,
welcome to Caftanistan.
[all laugh]
And now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
Starting with the Dr. Reverend
Silky Nutmeg Ganache.
When you came out,
it was such a statement,
and I think it made all of us
kind of gasp a little bit.
The eyelashes are crazy to me.
It looks like they're
just in the middle.
So like
if you're looking one way,
it looks like you're
not even wearing a lash.
You were great
in the magic show.
You made me laugh over and over.
The spins were giving me life.
Your connection to the audience
and to everyone
was really, really epic.
Your personality was in it,
and that's what we eat up.
But it seemed messy.
Your jacket looked wrinkly.
Your padding, you could see
the outlines of your hip pads.
Like, girl, we saw everything.
I recognize that I had
body issues in my padding.
Like, I had people
trying to help me
push them down and reshape them.
And my body
just did not work today.
Well, let me
just stop you there.
I mean, there are things
you could have done.
Mm-hmm.
Throw on more tights
so it smooths it out.
At this point
in the competition,
we're splitting hairs.
And these
are the kinds of things
that could get a girl
put into the bottom two.
Up next, Yvie Oddly.
Tonight on the runway,
I absolutely love this.
Givenchy. Very chic.
[Michelle] Your performance
was kind of flat.
There was a tenseness,
you know, at times.
Even though
it sort of came across
that you were a little nervous,
you had really bold choices.
From an actor's perspective,
that's essential
in a performance.
But it seemed to me
like you were thinking
or like you weren't
enjoying yourself.
I guess I was
a little bit stressed
because like we had
to rewrite a lot of stuff.
And in the kindest of ways
to the rest of my team,
I'm the only one
who thinks that way.
Thinks what way?
Uh, in planning things out.
My team was basically like,
well, we work better
with improv,
and it was very obvious
that it didn't work
being improv-ed.
So I wrote
most of our intro, our exit.
If there was a place I was at,
it was just, I guess,
just trying to make sure
that all went right.
All right.
Thank you, Yvie.
Um, Mama, I did not do improv.
So I didn't write down
what I was going to say?
I'm not saying you didn't write
down what you were going to say.
You said the rest of us didn't.
You guys didn't plan
as much as I did, girl.
-That's the Tee.
-I did plan.
I'm not gonna go through that.
[Vanjie] I'm like, girl,
how you gonna sit there
and say that to the judges
knowing that's
the particular critique
that has been given to me?
[RuPaul] Up next,
A'Keria C. Davenport.
I live in Palm Springs, so
I take caftans very seriously.
Okay.
[Ross] I love this outfit,
but a caftan it is not.
I'm sorry to get mad about it.
[all laugh]
Now wait. In my defense,
I Googled caftan.
Now, there's a caftan with a C
and a kaftan with a K.
And I saw some caftans
with pants.
Not in my religion.
[all laugh]
Your magic show was great.
The only thing I would
have wanted to see more of
was when you did your trick.
The way that all four of you
were around,
I would have loved to have seen
more hype from your teammates,
because I think that would have
helped sell the moment more.
[Ross] Your team struggled
a little bit.
I was having a bad day at first,
because there was
a lot going on, but...
What was going on?
Going into it,
we all had the mindset
of the, you know, improv.
At the last minute, some of the
decisions and the routes we went
wasn't going to be suitable
for television.
[laughs]
So at the last minute,
we did have
to rearrange some things.
You cleaned up the magic act,
and the deep throat balloon
stayed in?
[all laugh]
Was it--how dirty was it?
Oh, girl, it was filthy.
[all laugh]
But tasty, too.
Up next, Vanjie.
First and foremost,
I want to say
this is my favorite caftan
up here tonight.
-Aw.
-I would wear that caftan.
Yeah, you look my titi Sepha,
my titi--
Girl, I was already thinking
we look family, mama.
Don't do it to me.
[all laugh]
It's to die for.
The challenge, though.
I didn't really get much
from the performance,
and when you did talk,
I was like there's Vanjie.
Wait. Right.
There's no character
development.
Okay, yeah.
I feel like we hit a wall.
I did write down
what I wanted to say
and what I was going to do.
Like I've been trying
really hard to push myself.
Like whatever critiques
you guys say, I do listen.
And, um, that's why
I went a different route
with just writing it down
and stuff.
That's not the problem.
There's gotta be some kind
of elevation in performance.
It's just at this level.
You need to give us more
or else it's done.
Thank you, Vanjie.
Up next, Brooke Lynn Hytes.
Let's talk about
this runway look.
I love it so much.
I wish I had a gold bra.
[all laugh]
I was really captivated
by the way that you walked.
Whipping it around,
leg out, pose, turn.
It was delicious.
And that magic show
was phenomenal.
Really, really funny.
[Michelle] They were
realized characters,
you had choreography,
which I'm attributing to you.
I laughed the entire time.
[ Katherine] And one of my notes
I wrote for you was,
baby, you're a star.
Oh.
[RuPaul] Up next, Shuga Cain.
You look absolutely
beautiful in this.
It's Game of Thrones.
Like, it's just giving me
queen everything.
I wish you would have
kept this on.
I felt like it got
progressively not as cute.
In the magician's production,
you weren't bad,
but you paled in comparison
next to two juggernauts.
It was not quite good enough.
[Ru] There was a point where
you had a few jokes to land,
but you never quite landed
those jokes.
You guys did a better job
than the other team.
You always want to be
on the best team,
but the risk
is being overshadowed.
[RuPaul] Up next, Nina West.
Tonight on the runway,
it's exactly the caftan
that I've been dreaming of
my entire life.
I really enjoyed your
performance in The Mighty Tucks.
Magic!
The eighties shoulder pads,
the life was everything.
Obviously
Brooke Lynn's a dancer,
and you're back there cheesing
it up just as much as she is.
I was dying of laughter.
You were, from the beginning
to the end, hysterical.
[Katherine] Your energy
was so up,
and your command of the stage
and what you were doing
was great to watch.
[Ross] It was so funny.
And you created
this other character.
That's how you do it.
Thumbs up to you.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
While you untuck backstage,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right, now, just between
us squirrel friends,
I wanna know what you have
to say about my girls.
Silky Nutmeg Ganache.
She really kept the energy high,
and her personality
definitely shone through.
She was counting on her charm.
Now, I bought it,
but I couldn't get over looking
at how sloppy she looked.
It really was messy.
It just didn't work for me.
You gotta come strong
all the time.
[RuPaul] Yvie Oddly.
[Katherine] Yvie seemed
a little nervous to me
on stage tonight
for the magic show.
I felt like she was just
thinking about the words,
getting it done, and then moving
to the side of the stage.
If she was the one that wrote
something to open and close,
then she could have been
the only saving grace
in that performance.
Didn't look like the other girls
thought it was true, though.
Did you see Vanjie?
She was not having that.
[Gina] Well, yeah,
there was disconnect
definitely in that group,
and you felt it
in the performance.
[RuPaul] A'Keria C. Davenport.
The team had a bit of
a tough time cohesively
putting that performance
together,
but I'd really like
to see more of her.
Tonight on the runway,
it's a caftan challenge,
and there's nary a caftan
to be found.
You know, some of these caftans
were so good
they were making me pant.
Like...[pants]
But A'Keria
was making me...pant?
[laughs]
I don't know if I've ever been
this mad in my entire life.
[all laugh]
Caftan it was not.
Let it go, Ru.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Vanessa Vanjie Mateo.
This has been week
after week after week
where we're trying
to get character development,
and we're not.
[Katherine] Her personality
is definitely something
that is really magnetic.
[Ross] I just find her so
interesting and so funny.
But I don't disagree
that at a certain point
you've gotta bring more
than just one gear.
[RuPaul] Brooke Lynn Hytes.
She's been great
in this competition.
I feel very attacked right now!
And nobody owned the runway
like she did tonight.
The dance background she has
has really come in handy.
[Gina]
Brooke Lynn is a star.
Not just kind of, sort of.
She is a star.
[RuPaul] Shuga Cain.
Shuga gave me comedy blue balls.
You know, when it came time
for her punchline,
I was right there ready for it.
So does this, girl.
It just didn't happen.
On the runway, she went
from pretty to worse
to, no, girl, stop.
She was the least favorite
of that group,
and the runway as well.
In this competition, she's
not really hit her mark yet.
Nina West.
For me, she was
a real standout tonight.
It was literally a sketch
from Saturday Night Live.
It was that good, you guys.
We know.
I just want to cast her in the
lead of a TV show immediately.
She slammed the performance
out of the park.
Grand slam,
bring everybody home.
Nina West at the plate.
That was a sport reference.
Silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
[RuPaul] Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Brooke Lynn Hytes.
Poof, you're safe.
Thank you very much.
Nina West, abracadabra,
I want to reach out
and grab ya.
Con-drag-ulations.
You're the winner
of this week's challenge.
[gasps]
Well, thank you very much.
You've won a $3.000 gift card
from Marek & Richard,
and a $3.000 gift card
from outofoffice.com.
Thank you. Thank you.
Holy shit. Holy shit.
I just won my second challenge.
This is insane.
Shuga Cain, in the magic act,
the judges thought
you disappeared.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
Aah! I cannot believe
I'm in the bottom two.
I ain't gonna lie.
I am mad as hell.
To me, this makes
absolutely no sense.
[RuPaul] A'Keria C. Davenport,
you're safe.
Thank you so much.
Yvie Oddly.
You're safe.
Thank you.
[RuPaul] Silky Nutmeg Ganache.
You milked it in the challenge,
but your look
didn't do a body good.
Vanessa Vanjie Mateo.
Your caftan was spicy,
but your magic act
didn't cut the mustard.
Silky Nutmeg Ganache,
you're safe.
You may join the other girls.
Miss Vanjie,
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up for elimination.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself...
from elimination.
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing] for your life!
[Vanjie] I'm sorry, Shuga, but,
baby, it's gonna be a fight.
I ain't leaving.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
[music plays]
♪ So tired ♪
♪ Tired of all this drama ♪
♪ You go your way ♪
♪ I go mine ♪
♪ No more, no more ♪
♪ Girl, why'd I play
the fool ♪
♪ Go through ups and downs ♪
♪ Knowing all the time ♪
♪ You wouldn't be around ♪
♪ Or maybe I like the stress ♪
♪ 'Cause I was young
and restless ♪
♪ But that was long ago ♪
♪ I don't wanna cry no more ♪
♪ No more pain, no more pain ♪
♪ No more game ♪
♪ No more game
messing with my mind ♪
♪ No drama... ♪
[Yvie] Vanjie is like losing
bracelet after bracelet.
She's like, oh,
I'm so sick of this shit.
It's Mary J. everything.
♪ I don't know ♪
♪ Only God knows
where the story ends for me ♪
♪ But I know
where the story begins ♪
♪ It's up to us to choose ♪
♪ Whether we win or lose ♪
♪ And I choose to win ♪
♪ No more pain ♪
♪ No more ♪
♪ I'm tired, no more games ♪
♪ No more games ♪
♪ I'm tired, I'm so tired ♪
♪ No drama ♪
♪ No more, no more ♪
♪ No more in my life ♪
♪ No more, no more, no more ♪
♪ No more drama ♪
♪ I'm tired of all this drama ♪
♪ Lord, help me, help me ♪
♪ No more drama ♪
♪ I need somebody ♪
♪ Need somebody ♪
♪ I need ♪
♪ Oh, no, oh, no ♪
♪ No more, no more ♪
♪ No more drama ♪
♪ In my, in my ♪
♪ Life ♪
[Michelle] Yes!
[cheers and applause]
Ladies,
I've made my decision.
Vanjie, that was magic.
Shantay, you stay.
[applause]
Shuga Cain,
parting is such sweet sorrow.
Now sashay away.
I just want to say thank you
for seeing something
in this old lady.
Thank you so much.
[applause]
-Love you!
-Love you, Shuga.
Remember, Shuga is so sweet,
and I'll see you real soon.
[applause]
[Shuga] Of course I'm sad.
I wanted to be here
till the end.
Oh, girl, I wanted it so bad.
But, you know,
sometimes your dreams
work out in different ways.
Bitch, you better watch out.
This is just the beginning.
There's so much in store.
I can't wait.
Con-drag-ulations, ladies.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
-Amen.
-All right.
Now let the music play.
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪
[RuPaul] Next time
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
You need to make over
one of the returning queens.
[cheers and applause]
We're back, back, back.
I really feel bamboozled.
I bought the whole thing.
Beyonce-esque.
Who should go home tonight
and why?
I pray that they're not
gonna replace some of us
with some of them.
♪ To, to, to, to, to,
to, to, to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪