[RuPaul] Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
You'll be performing
in your very own magic show.
[cheers]
Aah!
Wow.
I said ain't nothing--
no ketchup in here, baby.
[RuPaul] Shuga Cain.
You never quite landed
those jokes.
-Oh.
-Vanjie.
You need to give us more
or else it's done.
[RuPaul] Nina West.
Your energy was so up,
it was great to watch.
Con-drag-ulations. You're the
winner of this week's challenge.
[applause]
Vanjie, shantay, you stay.
Shuga Cain, sashay away.
Vroom.
I'm a unicorn.
It's a rhino, mama.
Wait a minute.
Did you call me a rhino?
[all laugh]
So Shuga's gone,
and I'm definitely saddened,
because Shuga's very talented
and she's a sweetheart
through and through.
"You all hold a very
special place in my heart.
Make Nana proud. Shuga."
We love you, Shug.
I'm still shook
from the lip sync.
Child, I'm just, whoo.
Baby, when I tell you all
the words was speaking to me,
I was just making sure they knew
Miss Thing is out of the drama.
All right, you lip synced twice.
No more, Mary.
Wake up and smell the coffee.
You get a new opportunity.
Don't take it for granted.
[A'Keria]
So, Silk, how you feeling?
'Cause I know like tonight
was one of those nights
where they really added
some pressure on your back.
Like, you almost was
gonna have to lip sync.
[Silky] I guess that's
what I have to work on
in this competition, right.
Did I do everything I
could have done in that moment?
But it's like I kinda
accepted the defeat.
And that's what
I'm kinda disappointed
in myself in right now.
Because, like, I'm a girl
that will fight to the very end.
After last week's
roach critique
and this week's body critique,
I'm completely embarrassed,
my pride is bruised,
and it makes me feel like
I'm getting worse and worse
in this competition.
But, bitch, I cannot fold and
crack under this damn pressure.
I just can't give up.
[Brooke Lynn]
Nina, congrats.
Oh, I feel fucking great.
I feel so good.
And I had a lot of fun
in this challenge.
I just want to soak up this win.
But I am not resting.
I have to bring everything
that's Nina and kill it.
Because everyone
who is here right now
is absolutely gunning
for top four.
And we've seen really
shocking things happen before.
No one is safe.
It's anybody's game
at this point.
Oh, my God, ow.
Bitches better
step our pussies up.
[RuPaul] The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100.000.
With extra-special guest judges
Lena Waithe and Wanda Sykes.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
Y'all come on, bitches.
Prance to the beat.
-Yeah.
-Come on.
Walk faster, bitch. Damn.
At this rate,
it'll take forever.
Baby, it is a new day
and I'm feeling good.
Reset, reboot, and I'm leaving
behind the bottom two.
Mm.
So we at six.
How bad do y'all
want to be in that four?
-Desperately.
-Oh, my God.
I'm gonna show you how bad
I wanna be in the four.
-Uh-oh.
[all laugh]
[alarm]
[RuPaul] Ooh, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
My queens, as my play cousin
June Bug used to say,
sometimes the past can come back
and bite you in the ass.
So if you want to be
America's next drag superstar,
I sure hope you got
some extra padding, okurr?
[cheers]
Wait a minute. They said
somebody from the past.
Hello, hello, hello.
[cheers]
Ladies, if I could pass on
just one life lesson
to each and every
single one of you,
when the going gets tough,
the tough gotta know
when it's time to fake
bitch-slap a mother tucker.
Yes!
So for today's mini challenge,
I'm bringing back
a little game we call
[imitates Cher]
Slap Out Of It.
[all laugh]
But since I'm still
in litigation
over allegedly slapping
a queen last season...
[all laugh]
You'll be fake-slapping
each other.
-Oh.
[RuPaul] This is how it works.
You come up
with some sassy lines
that inspires
your fellow queens
to fake-slap
the crap out of you.
And in the end,
the queen with the most
compelling reactions wins.
[cheers and applause]
All right, then.
I got this one.
First up, Nina West.
Assume the position.
All right, Dr. Ganache,
your patient is here.
[all laugh]
You big old chaperone-looking
grilled cheese
motherfucker, you.
I love grilled cheese.
I bet. Aah!
[all laugh]
You wanna hit people
with trash cans?
What?
You bot spiderville
beetle-looking motherfucker.
Aah!
[all laugh]
Beep, beep, beep.
I actually want you
to do something.
All right. You got it.
Get the hell
out of Brooke's ass.
That's Vanjie's position now.
Oh.
The shade.
Aah!
Ooh!
This is fun.
[all laugh]
I just know how easy
this all is for you,
since you only got
the same fucking character
every time she--
So do you. You always play
an ugly Naomi Smalls.
Aah!
Wrong week, ho.
Wrong week.
Can I get some baby powder?
Hold on.
I've been waiting to slap
your ass since week two.
-Aah!
-Oh, my goodness.
[groans]
It's so nice that you finally
gave Miss Celia her hair back.
I told you this bitch
wouldn't say it.
No, Ru, it's okay.
I'm gonna lead with love.
Oh, you feel
just like a water bed.
[all laugh]
Aah!
I think I speak for everybody
and really say that we all love
hearing your opinion.
Good, 'cause I've got plenty
where it came from.
Aah! Aah!
There's one you can take home.
I love your head.
It reminds me of my testicles
after two hours in the bath.
Oh, bitch.
Well, I'll give you a few hours
to soak into that.
Your makeup looks like
a kindergarten art project.
Aah!
[all laugh]
Are you skeered?
I wanted to talk
about her toupee
and how she ain't got
no edges to mesh.
-I ain't got no edges?
-Mm-mm.
That's 'cause all of your--
-[laughs]
-Honey, oh, no.
Oh, bitch,
we taking something off--
I ain't scared of you
or that little brillo pad
you got in your hand.
You're still ugly as hell.
Oh, shit.
You made
your whole country proud
by completely terrorizing
Celine Dion.
How's that make you feel?
[both laugh]
Oh!
Everything's
a little easier in Canada.
That's what I'm feeling
right now.
-Yeah.
-[laughs]
What you got, bitch?
I'm gonna show you
a dancer's slap.
[all laugh]
Keep spinning, bitch,
right out of the competition.
I don't know a whole lot about
Canada or the people in it,
but judging by your
Snatch Game, neither do you.
Ohh.
[all laugh]
This feels wrong.
Am I allowed
to slap a homeless person?
-I think it's okay.
-Thank you.
Oh!
She slapped
the fuck out of you.
I think you broke my jaw.
[laughs]
Game over.
All right.
Y'all some slap-happy queens.
[all laugh]
But one of you served
some major drama, mama.
Brooke Lynn Hytes.
Con-drag-ulations.
You've won nails and lashes
from Kiss USA
and a wig and styling package
from luxelab.
Amazing.
Glue not included.
[all laugh]
Ladies, you've all come so far.
But it's lonely at the top,
so I've arranged
a playdate for you
with some of my favorite queens.
[laughs]
Are you intrigued?
-Yes.
[imitates Jerry Lewis]
Hey, ladies!
[cheers and applause]
What the fuck?
I really feel bamboozled.
Done brought all these old
stale-edge dry-ass bitches back
with bad mugs and beards.
Like literally beards.
What are y'all doing here?
Aah!
Hey, cyst.
We're back, back, back.
Bitch, hold the fuck up.
Why they brought
these bitches back?
I don't like games.
I don't play Uno, checkers,
fucking Monopoly.
I don't know what's going on.
Last time they brought other
girls that were eliminated in,
it ended up scaring Vanjie.
I worry and I pray
that they're not gonna replace
some of us with some of them.
Ladies, welcome back
the eliminated queens:
Shuga Cain, Plastique Tiara,
Scarlet Envy, Ariel Versace.
Yes.
-Honey Davenport.
-What's good?
Oh.
And Soju.
This is crazy.
Now, for this week's
maxi challenge,
you need to make over
one of the returning queens
and transform her into a member
of your own drag family.
#DragRace.
Now, to my top six queens,
let me be clear.
This is your challenge
to win or lose.
The returning queens
are here for a makeover only.
They will not be returning
to the competition.
In fact, during crucial moments
of the makeover,
they'll have to wear
these stylish pink mittens
to assure all the work is yours.
May God help us.
[all laugh]
Now, Brooke Lynn,
you won the mini challenge,
so you get to pair up
the queens.
So first, who do you pick
for yourself?
I'm going to pick Plastique.
Yay.
[A'Keria]
I'm definitely not surprised
that Brooke picked Plastique,
because, I mean,
it's an easy makeover.
Plastique's an easy canvas.
Which queen
do you pick for Nina?
I'm gonna say Shuga Cain.
Wha!
[both laugh]
Which queen do you pick
for Yvie?
I'm going to say Scarlet.
-Come ova.
-Hi.
My chemistry lady.
Which queen do you choose
for A'Keria?
Honey.
-What's up?
-Hey, cousin.
That's right,
Davenports in the house.
It seems like Brooke Lynn
is trying to pair everybody up
with somebody that she thinks
would physically work out
or, you know, just have
a chemistry together.
And who do you pick for Silky?
Soju.
[A'Keria] But Silky and Soju?
Chicago queens.
Mm-mm. Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
Mama plays
a very strategic game.
This might work out for you,
Brooke.
[Brooke Lynn]
What is your face?
I'm smiling.
[all laugh]
[Soju]
You're not happy to see me?
I'm really happy
to see you, girl.
Bitch, that quiet-ass,
shady-ass Brooke Lynn,
that bitch put me with Soju,
the bitch that went home first,
the bitch that came in week one
looking like Ronald McDonald.
You ain't gave me
shit to work with.
Obviously Brooke Lynn sees me
as a top competitor for her,
so that bitch trying
to get me out of here.
[RuPaul] That means Vanjie
will get Ariel Versace.
Just as I cyst-pected.
Yay!
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Now, ladies,
to help you create
a strong family resemblance,
you can use materials
from the F&S Fabrics wall,
Fierce! Drag Jewels,
Rock Star Wigs,
and your own drags.
Ooh, this is gonna be fun.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
Girl, I'm not gonna lie.
I'm happy I got you.
Well, yeah, hello.
How are you holding up?
Listen, the last few weeks
has been a fight.
It's getting down to the wire.
It's just a few of you.
Yeah. It's stressful.
If you have one stray hair
flying the wrong the way,
it could be the reason,
you know--
Speaking of hair,
I hear some of my hair's gone.
Right, what happened?
Girl, I just left it
by accident.
In the midst of things,
when I was eliminated,
I was like super, like,
emotional packing everything,
and I literally forgot
I had an entire rack of my wigs.
My wigs are like my babies.
And then when I got back home,
I realized, oh, my God,
I left a bunch of wigs.
They all thought you left hair
for real for them.
I left that red one for Silky,
and other than that,
those were all just by accident.
Yeah.
So I'm sure that's going to be--
There's been some drama
about the hair.
What happened with the hair?
People were fighting over it.
Are they all gone?
Yeah. I don't know
where they are.
Yeah.
So I guess some of these queens
thought that I left these wigs
behind for them.
I love that they all flock
to them like flies on shit,
but I want to know
who the hell's
snatching up my damn wigs.
So, Lucy, they got
some 'splaining to do.
Well, it could be Bad Girls Club
Season 11, hello.
Child, I need Ariel
to focus on the challenge,
'cause I need a win.
That's mine.
That's definitely mine.
[Vanjie] She's looking
for her tumbleweeds
that done went into
somebody else's station,
and she's freaking
the fuck out.
Aah, Lord, can I catch a break?
Well, the Jersey
will come out. Hello.
Oh, my God.
[Shuga] Ariel, she's been
waiting to stir the pot.
Get ready, honey.
It's about to blow up.
I love that.
This week's maxi challenge
is makeover time.
We have to do one of these
eliminated girls
in our drag style.
Who this man, miss ?
This is a full-on
dick magnet, honey.
[A'Keria] Oh. [laughs]
So I've got a really strong
concept for this.
Okay.
We're going to be actually
from the same denim tribe.
Okay.
I like the idea
of tribes and villages
more than I do
a traditional drag family.
It takes a village
to raise a queen.
A lot of the other girls
are going to serve
super-high glamour.
Uh-huh.
And even though I know you love
some super-high glamour--
I do love my glamour.
You're now going
to tap into the Odd-sizers.
Yeah, I can get weird.
These looks say
the House of Oddly
in the way that they are
deconstructing a material.
[Scarlet] Gorg.
[Yvie]
I love the beauty of things
that look like they're
just falling off of you.
But the danger is
I'm really just going to have
to fine-tune everything.
Yes, something magical.
-Yeah?
-Oh, ma'am, yeah.
That's the Tee.
[all laugh]
Oh, my gosh.
Jesus.
She's back in the workroom.
That's for sure.
[Vanjie]
Hide your mirrors, girls.
What the fuck is that?
A winning look.
[Shuga]
Yes, bitch, you betta.
Yvie is, in her own odd way,
very high fashion.
I'm very confident
in what Yvie and I
are going to bring
as fashion girls.
Yvie and I
are going to take this.
Somebody give her a mirror,
darling.
Yeah, it ain't working for me.
But nice.
E for effort.
I don't want you
to look like half-assed.
I'd rather
you look the prettiest.
I just need to excel,
because I just came
fresh off the bottom again,
and haven't had this wow moment
since the talk show,
where the judges are like,
Miss Vanjie is here.
And I want that
more than anything.
I have to take it in from
the bottom to bring it up.
Why don't you just put it
on the mannequin form?
[Vanjie]
Because it's already darted,
but I need to bring it in more.
So I'm tailoring it to her body.
I'm sewing it and making sure
I make this dress
fit her like a glove.
I want to make sure I do good,
'cause I'm listening,
believe it or not.
Oh, it fits you way better.
Oh, you brought my doughnuts.
Oh, yeah, I got them.
You know, I used these
to sit down when I had my cyst.
I was like
I could not sit on the hard,
so I sat like this
because it was hurting so bad.
What's the first thing
this bitch wanna talk about?
Her goddamn cyst.
I have a cyst.
I'm currently oozing.
Why did you bring it up
on the runway?
Well, the judges were like
you're having a hard time.
And I was like, yeah, I kinda
am having a hard time.
Like, I'm literally leaking
as we're speaking.
Now, another thing
is I don't wear big shoes,
because I have tendonitis
so I can't wear high heels.
[Silky] What kind of heels
you be wearing?
I wear those, um,
basic grandma heels.
But, you know, I just
call them sensible heels.
If my tendonitis are really
really bad, then I wear flats.
Child, now she's talking about
she's got tendonitis.
The motherfucking challenge
is to put a drag queen--
excuse me--
an experienced drag queen
in motherfucking drag.
Why do I feel like I'm about
to put somebody in drag
for the first motherfucking time
in their life?
I'm gonna see
if we can get a pair of shoes
from this wall, honey.
I mean, I can try it.
You gonna learn today, honey,
because I ain't going home.
You're gonna learn
how to walk in heels today.
Oh, my God, I've never worn
heels like this high.
Oh, no.
Oh, my goodness.
Bitch, oh, hell--
Go back. Uh-uh.
You're walking like this, honey.
[Vanjie] Girl,
she had on jelly slippers
when she was on the runway.
Aah. Call me out.
Nobody could see them.
I could not believe
you had on jelly slippers.
[laughs]
She looks like a Teletubby
trying to strut
for the first time.
I can't walk
in heels like these.
[Vanjie] Wait, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
What heels
do you walk in, then?
I walk in like very small heels.
[Vanjie] Oh, my God.
There is no words
to describe the gag that I'm--
I'm at a state--
I've never been this gagged.
Girl!
And I thought
it was going to be halfway easy
because we're making over drag
queens that already do this.
How you gonna come
on Drag Race and not--
and they weren't like--
they weren't like stilettos.
They were like
a regular six-inch heel.
Uh, uh, uh, uh.
[laughs]
Oh.
Yes.
Listen, that walk.
[laughs]
Can we be like, you know,
like street?
[Silky]
Bitch, get your baby shoes.
Let's see
what you can do in those.
Yeah, girl, this is a setup.
Hey, twisted sisters.
-Hey!
It's a family reunion.
[cheers]
Question. Who brought
the potato salad?
-Oh.
-Okay, good.
The Davenports
are in the house.
How are you related?
You're Texas, you're New York.
Yes. Sahara Davenport
and Asia Davenport
both left
and moved to New York City,
which is how
I became a Davenport.
Well, how different
are the New York Davenports
from the Texas Davenports?
[Honey]
It's completely different.
It's definitely like more
of a pageant-y, pageant-y town.
New York, like,
while we have pageants,
it's more of a like fashion,
you know, kind of vibe.
She don't know nothing
about that Texas drag just yet.
I've gonna give her
a little A'Keria feel.
-Yeah.
-That Chanel La Bella feel.
Okay. This is
another design challenge.
Your last design challenge
was not good for you.
It was not.
Of course,
I've got to redeem myself.
I just want to make sure
that I embody
what it is
that I have to do this time,
because I want to make sure
Honey is a replica of A'Keria.
[RuPaul] Who do you think's
in trouble here?
Who do you think
is going to have a hard time
relaying their
family resemblance?
I'd probably have to say Silky.
I would say hers
would probably be a challenge,
because I know Soju
really doesn't walk in heels,
number one.
And also, I've never saw Silky
paint anybody else,
and, you know,
mama kind of blind.
[all laugh]
Well, listen, I can't wait
to see the Davenports
hit the runway.
Good luck,
and we'll see you out there.
-Thank you.
-All right.
Brooke Lynn and Plastique.
-Hi, Ru.
Why'd you pick Plastique?
Well, my walk on the runway
is something
that's very important to me
and my aesthetic.
And I knew she has a great walk,
and she's around my height
and around my build,
so I knew costuming
would be a lot easier.
What is the family aesthetic?
[Brooke Lynn]
We are pageant queens.
The walk, the look,
the elegance, the poise.
Mm-hmm.
That's a huge part
of my family aesthetic.
[RuPaul] Now, Brooke Lynn,
did you have a strategy
in pairing the other girls?
[Brooke Lynn] Not really.
I was really looking at
the girls who had just come in
and the girls
who were still here,
and kind of seeing
who would work well together.
Really, bitch?
I mean, Soju and Silky?
[laughs] Well...
What you mean to say
is, yeah, I'm a shady bitch.
[laughs] I'm not.
Honest, like,
Silky's a wonderful performer,
but I think in terms of looks,
I think putting her
with anybody,
it would have been
a bit of a struggle.
I'm a nice person.
[RuPaul] All right.
Well, give one for Toronto.
-Thank you, Ru.
-Thanks.
Silky and Soju.
-Hi, Ru.
-Hey, baby.
[RuPaul] Both from Chicago.
Now, Silky, you won
two challenges so far.
How are you going
to make a third?
Ganache girls,
we are a look queen
that moves around, honey.
Okay.
So I'm going to go
to what I love and enjoy,
and that's disco.
Ooh.
We're gonna be two disco queens,
and give, like,
our personality, our charm.
I love that.
Now, last week, you were read
because your padding
was visible.
There were
several many complaints
from the judges' table.
I know.
[Michelle]
Your jacket looked wrinkly.
You could see the outlines
of your hip pads.
Like, girl, we saw everything.
How you gonna avoid
that same mistake?
Um...
The first thing I did
this morning
was went to my pads
and I prayed.
And I said, you're gonna work
for me this time, honey.
Well, the pads worked.
It was just that you
didn't have enough leggings on
to covers up the ridges.
I, um, still got to figure
that out, honey.
I've been doing it in--
It's not rocket science,
is it?
I mean,
everybody wears pads.
[Silky] Right.
And we just wear enough tights
to smooth it out.
-Okay.
-Uh, this--
I got more pads.
Okay, so in hindsight,
the mistake was what?
My pads needed work,
and whether that's gonna be
to add more layers on
or to see if my pads inside
the thing was like just bumpy.
It's a lot of things--
Bitch, we could literally
see your pads on the runway.
I know!
And that was the first time
you have in this competition.
I--
You have no answer for me?
Really?
Girl, let me tell you.
This whole situation
got me like frazzled.
Like it just don't
come to words.
In the great words
of a wonderful singer...
What singer?
Who are you gonna quote?
[Silky] Girl,
I had the guy so frazzled,
I couldn't even
get the lyrics out.
[all laugh]
In the fabulous words
of Bruno Mars,
"Don't believe me, just watch."
Huh.
Now, Brooke Lynn
paired you with Soju.
Do you think she's being shady?
Do you think
she was helping you out?
Um, you know what?
I am very glad
that she put me with Soju,
'cause I think
we both need redemption.
Redemption from week one,
redemption for my pads.
Yeah, yeah.
Y'all know I'm a church lady
and a pageant queen,
but, bitch, the true Tee is,
Miss Brooke Lynn,
you done gave me
motherfucking Soju,
the bitch
that can't walk in heels,
still talking about
her motherfucking cyst,
when you know I'm gonna
struggle bust my damn self.
She done set me up.
All right. So I can't wait
to see you out there.
Strong family resemblance.
-Get it, girls.
-Yeah.
-All right, see you later.
-Thank you, Ru.
-Hi, Nina.
-Hi, Ru.
-Hi, Shuga.
It seems like only yesterday.
-Right?
-That you were here.
I was saying the same thing.
Nina, you won
the challenge last week.
How are you going
to keep that momentum going?
I'm just going
to continue to bring me,
and what a great challenge
to bring me to, right,
as the House of.
Yeah. This is something
you do a lot of,
You have 17 children
in your house?
-House of West, yeah.
-House of West.
My drag mother's Virginia West,
and I have a bunch of daughters.
What is the sort of creed
of the House of West
that we'll see
on the main stage?
Yeah, our drag family
is really charitable,
and we're activists,
and that's the one thing
that I'm really holding true to
in this challenge.
So I see a rainbow dress there.
Like the rainbow flag.
The drag flag,
and then the trans flag.
I really believe
in lifting people up,
and I really believe
in celebrating all of us,
because the second
one of us is pulled down,
we're all pulled down.
-Oh, I love it.
So can I see your outfit?
Let's see what you got there.
So mine is a corset,
some shorts,
and some fabulous boot covers.
This is a little cute bodysuit
with the flag.
Let me see.
It's got the transgender flag.
And then it has
the boot covers as well.
And this is really reflective
of kind of who we are.
We're showgirls, and I'm
constantly inspired by theater.
This is like kind of a wink
to Kinky Boots,
but still something that's
very familiar to my world.
All right. Well, I can't wait
to see y'all on the runway.
-Thank you.
I love the message,
but do I feel like
they look circus-y?
Mm.
Are they cute? Mm-mm.
[Soju] Your padding's
going to have to look right.
Oh, girl, trust me.
I'm gonna prove a point, honey.
That's one thing it will be:
right, honey.
[Soju] Is it true
that you paint with sharpies?
[Silky] I do my eyebrows
with a sharpie.
Are you going to do my eyebrows
with a sharpie?
[Silky] Yeah, sure.
Family resemblance, ho.
[all laugh]
You know, not every family
look the same.
[laughs]
Miss Soju, bitch, now
you ain't been here to know.
I done won a few challenges
and I got a lot of compliments
about my makeup.
So that's one thing that
you ain't got to worry about.
-I use my natural brows.
-I know.
You gonna get
a little sharpie on them.
-Okay.
-[laughs]
[Vanjie] You better
count your blessings
and hope that Silky don't put
no sharpie on your lips, too,
'cause you know
she do that, too.
[Soju] You do not put sharpie
on your lips.
[Vanjie] Yes, girl,
yes, ma'am, honey.
Wait. Does it erase
off your lips?
Do I got it on my lips now?
Do you do it every time?
Every time.
[laughs]
And she's saying
like it ain't nothing.
Like, yes, girl, what you mean?
Like, girl,
you offended her, eh?
Good God.
How dare you, Miss Soju,
question my skills
because I use
a permanent marker?
I can beat a mug.
Even when I'm at home, bitch,
I make some ho's beautiful.
I mean, like, ho's that look
like Wesley Snipes,
like John C. Reilly,
ho's that look like Lil Wayne,
and I make them ho's
look beautiful.
It's an honor that I put
makeup on your face any day.
[Vanjie]
Girl, you're gonna have
a lot of cyst-tivity going on?
[all laugh]
All I'm gonna say is, bitch,
take care of you.
You come first, cyst.
[all laugh]
Question.
When you walked in the room,
is there anyone that you were
surprised was still here?
Silky.
-Really?
-Oh, yeah.
Her personality is good enough
to get on the show,
but I think that she's honestly
just in over her head.
[Nina] Anyone else
you were surprised by?
Vanjie, kind of.
I mean, when Michelle told her
"I know what you're gonna
wear on this runway
before you even
come out on the runway,"
I don't know
how you come back from that.
So Miss Scarlet has some
opinions about Vanjie and Silky.
Well, girl, what's the Tee,
Christine?
Yeah, those are the two.
And I honestly think that
those are the two to next go.
But y'all know me.
I'm gonna call her out.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Come on, cysts.
Come on, cyst.
Guess what we're doing today?
Makeovers.
We gotta drag up
the eliminated ho's
in our own drag styles.
-Are you excited?
-I am excited.
I can't wait to be a Hytes.
Not only do we have
to make over these girls,
but they can't touch themselves.
I'm so nervous.
Make me a woman.
I ain't no magician.
[laugh]
You can do it.
[Brooke Lynn]
They can't do their makeup.
They can't touch their hair.
Whatever we give them
is what they get.
My face is going to be
bruised up by the end of this.
All right, ladies and gents,
boys and girls.
I have a question.
[Yvie] Uh-oh.
Y'all know I'm the girl
that likes to clear the air.
What was said about
the whole wig situation?
[Ariel] Oh, God, the wigs.
Oh, it's about to be
some shit,
and I'm not in it.
Thank God.
So what's that Tee?
You guys took all of
Ariel's wigs after she left?
Now, bitch, you've been gone
from the very beginning.
How you know all the Tee?
[all laugh]
What were you told?
[Soju] That Ariel
left a lot of wigs.
And it wasn't meant
for everyone to take it.
Am I clearing out
the wig bullshit?
Sure, you might as well,
since it's your wigs, baby.
Go ahead.
Well, all right.
So when I was packing,
I left those wigs
all on that shelf by accident.
And the only wig
that was actually left behind
was that big old red wig
for Silky.
-Uh-huh.
-And that was it.
[Ariel] But I heard there
was a lot of shit, like--
-Did you leave some for--
-Oh, this is for me.
[A'Keria] Did you leave some
for your best friend?
'Cause after we took the wigs,
Plastique said that
the wigs were left for her
because y'all
were best friends.
She put all that hair
at my station.
-Did she write you a note?
-No.
But we were best friends.
So we were trying
to get to the bottom of that
and see what was actually the
truth with that whole situation.
We squashed this.
I made a comment.
Apparently
we didn't all squash it.
Because I did not care.
But it was brought up
yesterday again,
even though if it was squashed.
That was the thing.
So that's why
I'm clearing the air now
that the actual horses
are in the building.
But, guys, the wigs--
[A'Keria] So, Ariel,
are y'all best friends,
and did you leave the wigs
for her?
I mean, obviously
I consider myself closest here
with Plastique.
-We bonded a lot.
-Okay.
But the wigs were left behind
by accident.
But I just want to know
where the fuck they all are,
because I don't see any of 'em.
Okay, well, your black wig
and your purple wig
is right there at my station.
No, no, no. I don't care
about the purple wig.
I know that Miss Ra'Jah
left with a bunch of them.
Only wig I knew Ra'Jah had
was the big purple crinkly one.
[Ariel] That's what
I'm pissed off about.
All of a sudden, it's okay.
She really just wants one wig,
and it just so happens
to be from the person
who is not in the workroom,
Miss Ra'Jah.
[Silky]
But Ariel, I make it known.
I did grab one or two more
because they was there.
Ariel's silent
as a fucking mouse.
So all that huffing and puffing,
and now it's all like
a misunderstanding.
[Shuga]
I did feel like, Ariel,
you were a little more mad
about it yesterday
than you are right now.
[Shuga] That's what
I was going to say, too.
Ariel was pissed,
and now she's very calm.
[laughs]
Yeah, legit,
you were saying like,
I'm getting in there
and pop off,
and then you ain't really
pop off just now.
Okay, well, it's not like
the wigs are $5.00,
so I fucking want
the wigs back obviously.
So now as I'm addressing it,
she's backpedaling and quits
popping all over the place.
Say what you mean, mama,
and mean what you say.
I got another question.
Oh, God.
I heard yesterday that
Scarlet was surprised
Vanjie and Silky were still here
in this competition.
Is that true?
That is true.
And what were you
surprised about?
Now, before
I read your eyeballs out,
go ahead and tell me why.
Especially with Silky.
Come on, girl.
Well, um...
Well?
Why, Miss Scarlet,
you got my motherfucking name
in your mouth?
The world wants to know
at this point.
Because you've had the most
assistance from the other girls.
You got to clear that up
for me, honey.
Because in this competition,
as people have helped me,
I have helped
every bitch in here, too.
So what do you mean by that?
It's the top six,
and I feel like--
But, girl,
don't go around the issue.
What have I had assistance with?
Because I want to say
one thing to everybody.
I have been nice
to every bitch up in here.
And for y'all to run my name
through the mud,
I have done mostly everything
for myself, so clear the air.
Well, I do think
that your runways are held
to a different standard.
Bitch, your runways look worse
than mine, so clear the air.
[Yvie] You guys act like
if somebody has
a negative opinion about you,
it means they goddamn hate you,
and that's not the Tee.
Scarlet, I would never say this,
but, you know,
you came for me a little bit,
so I will say that
you should have went home
the first time you lip synced
in that six-way.
[Silky] You should have.
[Vanjie]
Because I don't know
how you're gonna come
to Drag Race
and think
you're gonna survive a lip sync
without knowing how to move.
Yeah, I'm going tit fo tat.
At this point
in the competition,
the last thing I need
is for people to be kicking me
while I'm down.
So you gonna come for me,
I'm gonna come for you
a little bit, too.
[Silky] This is my thing.
To come back here in this time
is a privilege and an honor.
Had I come back,
I wouldn't have said
a damn thing negative
to any of you all.
Bitch, you literally
just talked about
how you thought Scarlet
should have been home
after the first fucking dance.
That's my opinion.
-Exactly. Exactly.
-And that's her opinion.
You need to stop taking
everything so personally.
Well, I take
that shit personal,
because when you say
everybody's helped me,
how, Mary?
All my shit is right here.
None of this shit
is borrowed.
Most of it I made.
So how did people help me?
Silky, you have been getting
a lot of help
throughout the competition.
But how?
You and the rest
of your dream girls
have all been there
for each other's back.
So has Nina.
Nina's been getting help.
It's the truth.
Silky has had the help
of the dream girls all season.
And I'm not saying
it's a bad thing
to have help from your sisters,
but Scarlet's not wrong
in saying
that Silky hasn't done
all of this by herself.
This bitch can't even say what
anybody has ever done for me.
Bitch.
[Silky] Say what somebody
has done for me
in this competition
other than them.
Okay, your hair.
Your hair, for starters.
You went to half of the girls
for sewing this and sewing that.
That is not true.
I sew everything of my own.
Yeah, we have the dream girls.
But what they give me
more so than anything
is emotional support
for bitches like that
who say shit about me.
Fuck.
[Shuga] Y'all are crazy.
You'll be fighting this
to the death, honey.
It's just an opinion, girl.
You can't get
so pressed about it.
And I just
answered the question.
No, you just got super salty
'cause a bitch
put your name out.
I did.
Look, everyone has opinions.
Scarlet had an opinion.
Why are you offended, and why
you jumping down her throat?
Goddamn.
Scarlet's just hating.
That's it, that's all.
Y'all look like some
salty maltese up in here.
So I'm a salty malty today.
Well, I'll be a salty malty,
so you can be a pressed panini.
Opinions are like assholes,
you know.
Most of them are on my face.
[Vanjie laughs]
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
[RuPaul] And what?
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage, six of
the eliminated queens are back.
Security.
[all laugh]
And the hilarious Ross Mathews.
Now, what's different
about you today?
Oh, you noticed.
Michelle did my makeup.
[laughs]
Emmy-winning actress,
producer, and writer,
Lena Waithe.
I hear you're
a Drag Race superfan.
Oh, yes, honey,
and, bitch, I'm from Chicago.
[all laugh]
But, no, seriously,
I actually am from Chicago.
Emmy-award winning actress,
comedian, and writer,
Wanda Sykes.
Girl, I have loved you
since Pootie Tang.
Well, I didn't know
you smoked weed.
[all laugh]
Now, how is your
Oh, Well tour going?
-Oh, well.
-[laughs]
Now, this week,
we challenged our queens
to make over
their twisted sisters.
And tonight on the runway,
category is Drag Family Values.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
♪ We got a mighty love ♪
[RuPaul] First up,
Yvie Oddly and Scarlet Envy.
Oh, my God, this place
is crawling with drag queens.
[Ross] Clearly they're sisters.
They have the same jeans.
[all laugh]
[Lena]
Occidental fingernails.
[Wanda] I just remembered.
I gotta get my car washed.
[all laugh]
[Yvie]
The outfit Scarlet is wearing
is actually the first outfit
I've ever made.
And then I'm modeling
a more recent redo of it
because I want to show the
judges I can do some elevation.
And these wigs are literally
every pair of jeans I had,
so... [laughs]
Scarlet is really
selling this fantasy.
She's got my denim back like
she's my real denim sister.
This is as odd as it gets.
[laughs]
[evil laugh]
[both laugh]
That was LOL.
[all laugh]
You know,
this is the same designer
who made Justin Timberlake
and Britney Spears outfit.
-Yes.
-Yeah.
[RuPaul laughs]
Up next,
Nina West and Shuga Cain.
[Michelle]
The insane drag posse.
[all laugh]
[Lena] It's like Skittles
and Chiclets.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] You know, these
outfits fit them to an LGBT.
[all laugh]
[Nina] I really wanted
to use this runway walk
as our very own pride parade.
These outfits
are quintessential Nina.
They're inspired
by Kinky Boots from Broadway,
so they're very fun,
but there's also
a message behind it.
And Shuga
is making me so proud.
She's doing her best
Nina West impression,
which is really amazing.
She's serving
and turning on the runway.
[Lena]
I love a gay superhero.
-Amen.
-Come on, Kay.
[Wanda]
One of the twins disappears.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul]
Next, A'Keria C. Davenport
and her sis, Honey Davenport.
[Lena] Yellow and orange
make fabulous.
[Ross] Gorg.
[Lena]
Melon-ated Marilyn Monroe.
[A'Keria] I'm giving you
very Davenport style
high fashion eleganza.
I'm wearing a keyhole
with the jewels that sit
almost to my breast,
and my sister Honey,
she has on
a little old piece of ruffle
covering up
all those man muscles.
And of course, gotta have on
some Texas hair, baby.
This makeover
is definitely a success
We know we the Tee, baby.
[RuPaul] The Landers sisters
are still going strong.
[Wanda]
So slow, though.
Like The Real Housewives
of Molasses.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Up next, Dr. Reverend
Silky Nutmeg Ganache,
and her sister Soju.
[Lena] Studio 69.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Remember when Nell
Carter was on The Cher Show?
[Michelle] Yes.
[all laugh]
My favorite episode.
[Silky] The Ganache family
is going to the disco.
I have my sister, Miss Soju,
wearing a full bodysuit
that shows all her curves.
Her bell bottoms are pointed
to show a little bit
more character,
and so you can get a sneak peek
that that bitch is actually
wearing heels, baby.
[RuPaul]
All right, sister Soju.
[all laugh]
[Silky] And I'm wearing
a jumpsuit
with my bell bottoms
on the sleeves, honey.
I got a little belt to give you
a little more shape,
a little bit more curve.
We on this runway showing shape
and eating grapes, honey.
And we're waiting
on the after party.
The pads are messy again.
[Lena]
Cagney and Lacey.
[Ross] Gag-me and Lacey.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Vanessa Vanjie Mateo
and Ariel Versace.
-Ooh.
-Nice reveal.
[RuPaul] Two little girls
from Glitter Rock.
[all laugh]
[Ross] I feel awful.
I can never remember.
Which one's Tia,
which one's Tamera?
[all laugh]
[Vanjie] Tonight on the menu
is the Mateo Vanjie takeover.
Me and Ariel are pumping down
the runway Miss Vanjie style.
Looking disco
extra-greasy shortening.
Blonde waved hair,
bombshells down
with a good old breast sequin.
Very sparkle, bling, bling.
We got disco pants on me,
a beautiful gown on Ariel.
I'm looking sickening,
she's looking fierce,
and I'm living for it.
[both] Miss Vanjie.
Miss Vanjie.
-Uh-huh.
[both] Miss Vanjie.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Brooke Lynn Hytes
and Plastique Tiara.
[Michelle] Whatever they have,
I think it's spreading.
[all laugh]
[Lena]
Somebody call the gardener.
[all laugh]
[Michelle] Some bushes
need to be whacked.
[all laugh]
[Brooke Lynn] This week,
the Hytes family legacy
is being carried on
with my new drag sister
Harlem Hytes.
We are serving you
classic Hytes pageant glamour,
with a lovely velvet gown
with sequin appliques,
1940s movie star hair,
looking unbothered
sauntering down the runway.
The concept is very like
pageant-y evening gown walk
with floating and some dance.
I just wanted to be very
graceful and beautiful.
[laughs]
I taught Plastique a couple
Hytes evening gown moves:
kick the train, you do
a little rond de jambe
and the train kind of
flows in front of you.
I want her to take her time
to just really move her hips
and let the light bathe you.
Alyssa Edwards
better watch out.
She might have a daughter
jumping ship.
[Lena]
There she is, Miss America.
[Ross] I just feel bad
for the ugly sister.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul] Welcome, ladies.
It's time for
the judges' critiques.
First up, Yvie Oddly.
I thought it was really fun
when you guys came out.
Obviously you guys
are rock stars.
I thought the look
was really great, you know,
feeling a bit of an Ursula denim
situation happening,
and I loved watching you guys.
What I'm struggling with
is the construction of this.
It's almost chic in
a futuristic almost kinda way,
but it just looks
a little crafty.
[Wanda] I mean,
I buy that you're sisters,
except that it's like the little
sister trying to tag along.
And you're giving her
your scraps of your scraps.
This is the best that
my sisters have ever gotten.
[all laugh]
Right, right.
Up next, Nina West.
-Hi, Shuga.
-Hi, Ru.
Well, look, I know all about
wearing a rainbow, okay.
[all laugh]
I wear my pride
on my sleeve a lot,
so I appreciated
that you guys did that tonight.
You know, we have the rainbow
and you have the trans flag,
but really we're sisters.
So I got the message,
and I loved it.
But I feel like
Shuga's lost in this.
The hairdo, mm, mm.
And Shuga's makeup.
I just know
how beautiful Shuga is and...
-Okay.
-You know.
And I can imagine
how hard it was
for all of you queens to have
another queen do your face
when you can't do a thing.
Unfortunately, Shuga,
it's almost bordering on clowny.
And you're--
Fashion should say something,
and you're certainly
saying something
on the runway tonight.
The issue is this.
These look like costumes
for a pride parade,
not fashiony for a runway.
There's just certain boxes
you have to check
in this challenge.
Up next, A'Keria C. Davenport
and her sister Honey.
-Hey.
I buy that you're sisters.
It's very pageantry in
a Vanessa Williams kind of way.
[all laugh]
The hair's the same color,
styled similarly, but different.
You painted her beautifully,
and I like what you did
with the keyhole.
I have an affinity for it.
There's just a lot that's
simple but effective here.
And I love this kind
of pageant drag.
You're not reinventing the wheel
with this,
but sometimes the wheel's
just fine as it is.
Up next, the Dr. Reverend
Silky Nutmeg Ganache
and Soju.
-Hi, Soju.
-Hi.
I missed you.
I have to ask you,
how is the cyst?
Haven't had any complaint, Ross.
Haven't had any complaints.
[all laugh]
I thought you guys
were a lot of fun.
I really liked
the seventies of it all.
That's my favorite era.
But I do think there's
something about the costuming
that felt
a little bit too Halloween.
[Wanda]
I agree with Lena.
I mean, it was more of a theme
instead of sisters.
It's like somebody threw
Sonny and Cher in a blender
and threw in a Jackson Five,
and this is what,
you know, what we have.
I made all of this.
Probably the only queen
that made both looks.
I just wanted to showcase Soju.
Soju was the first one
to go home,
and I wanted her to come out
in a different light
and to be beautiful.
But I'm going to call you out
again, Silky,
'cause your makeup is gorgeous,
Soju's a little rough.
That cheek is very heavy.
Looks like it was blended
with a Dremel.
And I see issues with your
padding again in the back.
Also, I didn't feel like
I was looking at the Silky
I've come to know and love.
It felt like you kept
like looking over at Soju
and being like,
oh, that's right,
I'm supposed to go
like this now.
You felt a little lost to me.
I know that I can go
like at a thousand
and leave my partner behind.
-Uh-huh.
And so tonight I wanted to
bring it down a few notches.
But unfortunately I guess
I brought it down too much.
Up next, Miss Vanjie
and her sister Ariel Versace.
You made me so proud tonight.
-Ariel...
-Hi.
She absolutely
looks like your sister.
She looks better than me.
I was like...
[Ariel laughs]
She took a lot of time
to like really tailor this dress
in to like perfectly fit me
and put a lot of detail
into everything.
I didn't pay her
to say that, either.
Y'all came out
and dropped those coats,
and it was just stunning.
Truly. It was very
Beyoncé-esque. It was good.
And what I love about this
is how well executed it is.
It's so smart to put
one of you in a dress
and one of you in pants.
It's so good.
I just really wanted
to make you guys proud.
It was getting frustrating.
Up next,
it's Brooke Lynn Hytes
and her sister Plastique.
Silky, this is a great example.
So we have an Asian sister,
and though we're not twins,
you can tell there's
a family resemblance.
And what I also liked
about the performance tonight,
you told a story out there.
When Plastique
stepped in front of you
and there was a look--
no, no, no--
it was so funny.
[Lena] It was so classic.
It was so beautifully done.
It was fantastic.
You took my breath away
when you guys walked out.
[Brooke Lynn] Sorry.
I'm just really happy
the story came across,
'cause this was kind of
a love letter to my drag mother,
because she taught me
everything I know,
and she's the reason
I'm here today.
So it just really means
a lot to me that you got it.
So thank you.
Whoo.
All right, ladies.
One more question.
Who should go home tonight...
and why?
Start with Yvie Oddly.
Silky is the one girl
who's gotten the same critiques
a few times,
and hasn't ever polished out
the things that
you want to see from her.
Scarlet Envy.
Well, it came out
in the workroom today,
so Silky knows, I guess,
already.
Nina West.
Based on her critique tonight,
I'm going to have to say
Yvie Oddly.
Shuga.
Unfortunately, Silky.
Just because the critiques
that you've given her
you've given her before,
and today was an opportunity
for her to really pay attention
to those and execute,
and it didn't happen.
A'Keria.
I'm gonna have to say Yvie,
and that's based on
overall growth.
At this point
it should be only elevation.
Honey Davenport.
Silky's outfit was the least
polished on the runway tonight.
Silky.
I would choose Yvie.
As America's
next drag superstar,
you have to be kind to people,
and she has not been
the most kind or the most nice.
Soju.
I would also have to Yvie,
because I don't think her drag
is on the level
of everyone else in the top six.
Vanjie.
Based on tonight,
I would say Yvie.
Just because I feel like
she kind of left her sister
a little behind.
Ariel.
I would also have to say Silky,
just based off the critiques.
-Brooke Lynn.
-I would have to say Silky.
I just didn't think
the look was finished,
and I just don't think there
was a great family resemblance.
Plastique.
I agree.
Silky just fell short.
Thank you
for your honesty, ladies.
Now, while you
untuck backstage,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right, now just between
us squirrel friends,
what do you think?
Let's start with Yvie Oddly.
Yvie is an original.
That is the toughest thing
to do in show business.
-Don't I know it.
-[laughs]
And when I look at this outfit
from way back here,
I go, yeah,
that's an Yvie Oddly look.
The problem is
when you get a little close.
[laughs]
It looks like she put
a lot of time in her outfit--
well, I mean, the scraps.
But she put some time into 'em.
But it's just like some
hand-me-down for her sister
and told her to just
bring a pair of shoes.
[Michelle]
Crystal shoes with that
was not as good
as the denim shoe with that,
which seems like little,
but at this point, it's not.
[RuPaul] Up next, Nina West.
I love a rainbow look,
but it can be hit or miss.
[Michelle] I mean,
she was wearing bike shorts.
[chuckles]
That she used her time
on this runway
to make that kind of statement
is gorgeous.
Unfortunately,
the outfits weren't.
And whilst I appreciate
so greatly
the rainbow flag
and the trans flag
coming together as a statement,
at the end of the day,
this is a drag family
resemblance challenge,
and there was no resemblance.
[RuPaul]
A'Keria C. Davenport.
Those two sold it,
and they looked beautiful.
I think it kept true
to a Davenport.
They got it right.
[RuPaul] The color scheme
was beautiful.
They looked like
they were from the same house.
In fact, I think Honey
has never looked better.
That's really not Honey's style.
She's a New York
sort of edgy queen.
I told them
they didn't reinvent the wheel,
but there's nothing wrong
with the wheel.
You know, it's round, it works.
You know,
if it ain't broke--
-Put a wig on it.
-Exactly.
[all laugh]
The Dr. Reverend
Silky Nutmeg Ganache.
I think we should call Issa Rae,
because that whole thing
was a little insecure for me.
[all laugh]
I didn't like that she tried
to use Soju as an excuse.
She said, well, I had to
bring it down to help Soju out.
She didn't need to do that.
Soju's red hot.
Nope, sorry, that's her cyst.
[laughs]
Tonight, Silky had some issues.
She was looking a bit lumpy.
The outfits
were a bit tattered,
and I felt like there was
no family resemblance.
These were two girlfriends
going out to a disco.
[Ross] I love Silky.
I think she has what it takes
to get to the finish line.
I just hope
she's not running out of gas,
'cause it kind of
feels that way.
[RuPaul] Miss Vanjie.
I think they just came out
with such confidence and swag
that we were immediately
won over.
[Wanda] They were
just gorgeous, stunning.
I bought the whole thing.
Loved the whole
Gentlemen Prefer Blondes look
that Marilyn
and Jane Russell had.
[Michelle]
Everything was on point.
The way they were walking.
The way that she did Ariel
was beautiful.
[Ross]
I warned all the queens
use every tool in your toolbelt
before it's too late,
and Vanjie this week,
she pulled out a hammer
and a wrench and a screwdriver,
and that's all the tools I know.
-So proud of you.
-Yes, thank you.
[all laugh]
But she did it.
[RuPaul] Brooke Lynn Hytes.
Listen, what they did tonight
was classic Brooke Lynn,
and it worked.
There's no edge
to what she's bringing,
which is the one thing
that I'm sort of missing
from Brooke Lynn.
But what she does
is so well done.
You can't deny it.
And I really liked
the story behind it.
There was meaning to it.
She didn't just pull something
out of her ass.
She really wanted
to tell a story.
Well, I mean, she really is
pulling something
out of her ass.
Oh, that's true.
[all laugh]
Hey-oh.
All right. Silence.
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
[Michelle laughs]
[RuPaul] Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
A'Keria, tonight you did
the Davenport family proud.
You're safe.
Thank you.
-Yay.
-You're my winner, boo.
[RuPaul] Miss Vanjie.
Welcome back to the competition.
Thank you.
You're safe.
[gasps]
-I thought she was gonna win.
-Me, too.
I thought
she was gonna win, too.
[RuPaul] Brooke Lynn Hytes.
Tonight, you gave us
two sophisticated ladies.
Yes.
Con-drag-ulations. You're the
winner of this week's challenge.
Yes, bitch, work.
You've won a trip to Aruba,
including airfare
and a five-night stay
at the Aruba Marriott Resort
and Stellaris Casino.
Come on, Aruba.
We're going to Aruba.
Ah-ah-ah.
Vanjie, we're going on vacation.
Oh, yes.
And Plastique receives
a $2.000 gift card
from Klein, Epstein & Parker.
Yes!
[cheers and applause]
Suits made to measure.
Come on, new suits.
[applause]
Silky, we love your soul sister,
but this week,
you dropped the disco ball.
Nina, you wear your pride
on your sleeve,
but the judges weren't feeling
your rainbow connection.
[sighs]
Yvie, being odd
is in your jeans,
but your denim drag
gave us the blues.
Yvie Oddly...
You're safe.
Yes!
[cheers]
You may join the other girls.
Thank you.
[RuPaul] Nina, Silky,
I'm sorry, my dears,
but you are both up
for elimination.
I'm fighting.
I want to be here.
I want to make the five.
I will not give up on this.
-Has Nina lip synced yet?
-No.
Neither one of them have.
Silky hasn't lip synced, either.
First time for both of them.
[RuPaul] Two queens
stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing] for your life!
This big body
can get really high,
it can get really low,
it can split, deal,
so I ain't worried for me.
The bitch might as well pack
before I even get started.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
[music plays]
♪ A scrub is a guy
that thinks he's fly ♪
♪ And is also known
as a busta ♪
♪ Always talking about
what he wants ♪
♪ And just sits
on his broke ass ♪
♪ So, no,
I don't want your number ♪
♪ No, I don't want
to give you mine ♪
♪ And, no, I don't want
to meet you nowhere ♪
♪ No, I don't want
none of your time ♪
♪ And, no,
I don't want no scrub ♪
♪ A scrub is a guy that
can't get no love from me ♪
♪ Hanging out
the passenger's side ♪
♪ Of his best friend's ride ♪
♪ Trying to holla at me ♪
♪ I don't want no scrub ♪
♪ A scrub is a guy that
can't get no love from me ♪
♪ Hanging out
the passenger side ♪
♪ Of his best friend's ride,
trying to holla at me ♪
♪ If you don't have a car
and you're walking ♪
♪ Oh, yes, son,
I'm talking to you ♪
♪ If you live at home
with your mama ♪
♪ Oh, yes, son,
I'm talking to you ♪
♪ If you have a shorty... ♪
[A'Keria] Nina looks like
a little Christmas bear.
If you press the button,
they move like this.
♪ Wanna get with me
with no money... ♪
She's just a don't,
and then Silky's like
a walrus out of water.
And good night,
you're just a-flopping
across these people's stage.
♪ No scrub ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ No, I don't want no scrub ♪
♪ A scrub is a guy that
can't get no love from me ♪
♪ Hanging out
the passenger side ♪
♪ Of his best friend's ride ♪
♪ Trying to holla at me ♪
♪ I don't want no scrub ♪
♪ A scrub is a guy that
can't get no love from me ♪
♪ Hanging out
the passenger side ♪
♪ Of his best friend's ride ♪
♪ Trying to holla at me ♪
[cheers and applause]
-Ooh.
-Yes, Miss Nina.
Yes, Silky.
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Meh.
Silky Nutmeg Ganache...
shantay, you stay.
I'm not a mess
and I'm not a roach.
This is just who I am,
and I'm gonna improve this.
And I promise you,
you will know it.
I promise you that.
God knows my destiny.
Thank you.
[RuPaul] Nina West.
You, my dear,
are the pride of Season 11.
Now sashay away.
Thank you.
[applause]
[Vanjie] We love you.
Adventure is out there.
Go big. Be kind.
Fucking go West.
Thank you so very much.
[applause]
I'm disappointed
that I'm going home,
but I totally understand
the critiques.
I think they understood
my message.
It just wasn't fashion,
and I totally get that.
I might not have
the perfect makeup,
and I might not have
the most fashion-ready runways,
but I definitely showed me,
and I'm so proud of that.
I'm really so excited for
the adventure that awaits me.
Con-drag-ulations,
my top five queens.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
-Amen.
-All right.
Now let the music play.
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪
[RuPaul] Next time
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
This is the final test
to see if you make it through
to the grand finale
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
-Whoo!
-I am ready to give all I got.
Five, six, seven and eight.
Five, six,
seven, eight. Wait.
I'm confused as hell
and lost as a billy goat.
Only four of you
will be going through
to the grand finale.
It's now...
or never.
♪ To, to, to, to, to,
to, to, to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪
♪ To the moon ♪
♪ Come on and take me away ♪
♪ To, to, to, to the moon ♪