>>> WELCOME TO THE GRAND FINALE
OF "RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE."
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, RuPAUL!
떰
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> WHY DON'T YOU TAKE A
PICTURE?
IT WILL LAST LONGER.
WAIT.
SOMEONE'S MISSING.
RAJA, MAY I BORROW YOUR PHONE?
HELLO?
IT'S RuPAUL.
HOW SOON CAN YOU GET HERE?
GOOD.
>> I JUST WANT TO SAY, I LOVE
YOUR MAKEUP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ENOUGH CLOWNING AROUND.
GENTLEMEN, START YOUR ENGINES.
AND MAY THE BEST WOMAN WIN!
THE WINNER OF RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE
RECEIVES A ONE-YEAR SUPPLY OF
BEVERLY HILLS COSMETICS AND
$100,000.
MAY THE BEST WOMAN
BEST WOMAN WIN
>> FROM THE ORPHEUM THEATER IN
DOWNTOWN LOS ANGELES, WELCOME
THE QUEENS OF "RuPAUL'S DRAG
RACE SEASON 8."
THE QUEEN OF ALL NERDS, DAX
EXCLAMATIONPOINT.
SHE'S PUNKY YET FUNKY, IT'S
LAILA McQUEEN.
STILL SPREADING THAT CUCKOO.
CYNTHIA LEE FONTAINE.
THE BEAUTY HAS ARRIVED.
GIVE IT UP FOR NAYSHA LOPEZ.
SHE'S BITCH PERFECT.
GET READY TO TRIP WITH ACID
BETTY.
SHE'S HELL ON WHEELS, IT'S
ROBBIE TURNER.
떰
LOOKING GOOD, FEELING THORGEOUS.
IT'S THORGY THOR.
SHE'S NOT THAT INNOCENT.
SHE'S DERRICK BARRY.
SERVING LOUISIANA GLAMOUR, MISS
CHI CHI DEVAYNE.
AND NOW OUR TOP THREE QUEENS, IS
THE TRAIN STILL RUNNING?
IT'S BOB THE DRAG QUEEN.
DO NOT COMFORT HER.
IT'S KIM CHI.
AND LAST BUT NOT LEAST, CHECK
YOUR LIPSTICK BEFORE YOU COME
FOR HER, IT'S NAOMI SMALLS.
떰
ONE MORE TIME.
GIVE IT UP FOR THE QUEENS OF
SEASON 8.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
AND NOW, RuPAUL!
떰
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> WELL, WELL, WELL.
LOOK AT YOU.
EVERYONE IS WEARING IT WELL
TONIGHT.
WELCOME TO THE GRAND FINALE OF
"RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE."
YES, THE TRIBE HAS GATHERED.
I KNOW WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE OF A
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION, BUT
TONIGHT THIS IS THE RACE
EVERYBODY'S TALKING ABOUT.
BECAUSE TOGETHER RIGHT HERE ON
LOGO TV, WE CAN MAKE AMERICA GAY
AGAIN!
AND I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU, IN
THIS THEATER, YOU HAVE MY
PERMISSION TO USE ANY DAMN
BATHROOM YOU WANT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WELL, EXCEPT MINE, OF COURSE.
YOU HEAR THAT, JIGGLY?
TONIGHT, OUR LEGENDARY JUDGES
ARE HERE.
FRESH FROM THE DROP-OFF AT
CALABASAS JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL,
IT'S MICHELLE VISAGE!
ALSO HERE ARE ROSS MATTHEWS AND
CARSON KRESSLEY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
NOW, THIS SEASON WE'VE BEEN TO
OZ AND BACK, BUT THE COMPETITION
AIN'T OVER.
BOB THE DRAG QUEEN, KIM CHI AND
NAOMI SMALLS, TONIGHT, ONE OF
YOU WILL BE CROWNED AMERICA'S
NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR.
BUT I HAVE NOT MADE MY FINAL
DECISION.
AND BECAUSE WE'RE STILL KEEPING
IT 100, I'VE ASKED EACH OF YOU
TO PREPARE A LIP-SYNC
PERFORMANCE TO A SONG CREATED
JUST FOR YOU.
LADIES, THIS IS YOUR LAST CHANCE
TO IMPRESS ME AND TO SHOW THE
WORLD THAT YOU DESERVE TO BE
AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR.
SO GOOD LUCK AND DON'T FUCK IT
UP.
떰
CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> COMING UP -- LIVE
PERFORMANCES BY OUR TOP THREE.
LATER, THE SEASON 8 QUEENS
REUNITE AND LET IT ALL HANG OUT
WHEN THE GRAND FINALE OF
"RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE" CONTINUES.
떰
>>> IT'S "RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE"
THE RUSICAL.
NOW YOU CAN OWN THE SOUNDTRACK
THAT GIVES YOU LIFE!
TAKING YOU BY SURPRISE
떰
>> THE MUSIC LIBRARY IS OPEN.
SUGAR BABY
떰
ALL I WANT IT EGGS
EGGS EGGS EGGS EGGS EGGS
ALL I EVER WANTED
>> AND THERE'S NOT A DOG IN THE
BUNCH.
떰
I'M THE BIGGEST STAR
AND I'M GOING FAR
>> "RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE: THE
RUSICAL" AVAILABLE WHERE FINE
MUSIC IS SOLD.
떰
>>> WELCOME BACK TO THE GRAND
FINALE OF "RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE."
NOW, OUR TOP THREE QUEENS HAVE
SNATCHED YOUR ATTENTION ALL
SEASON LONG.
AND TONIGHT I'VE CHALLENGED EACH
OF THEM TO SLAY THE STAGE ONE
LAST TIME.
FIRST, A NEW YORK CITY GIRL WHO
PUTS THE TAIN IN ENTERTAINMENT,
GIVE IT UP FOR A
DEMURE LITTLE LADY WE CALL BOB
THE DRAG QUEEN.
I DON'T GO OUT LOOKING FOR THE
SPOTLIGHT
THE SPOTLIGHT FINDS ME
UH, OVER HERE.
TONE IT DOWN
TUCK IT IN REAL TIGHT BUT IT'S
NOT THAT EASY
IT'S NOT THAT EASY
SINCE I WAS A CHILD
PEOPLE KEEP SAYING I'VE BEEN
DOING TOO MUCH
MAMA ALWAYS SAID HOLD YOUR
HEAD UP HIGH
YOU'VE GOT THAT MAGIC TOUCH
MAGIC TOUCH
WHETHER IT'S ACTING, COMEDY,
BODY, SINGING, DANCING OR
SERVING CHOCOLATE CHIP COOKIES
I DON'T LIKE TO SHOW OFF
I KEEP IT HUMBLE 'CAUSE
IT'S NOT MY GIG
I LIKE TO KEEP MY TALENT
STUFFED UNDER MY WIG
OOH I DON'T LIKE TO SHOW OFF
DON'T SHOW OFF
ALL THE OTHER BITCHES CALL ME
SASSY
YOUR WIG TOO BIG
I'M THE ONLY ONE
IF YOU COME
YOU MUST BE AN S.O.B.
EVERYONE'S A HATER BUT I'M
MAKING MY STATEMENT IN FRONT OF
Y'ALL
HA, HA, HA
I DON'T LIKE TO SHOW OFF
KEEP IT HUMBLE BECAUSE IT'S
NOT MY GIG
I LIKE TO KEEP MY TALENT
STUFFED UNDER MY WIG
OOH I DON'T LIKE TO SHOW
OFF
OH 떰
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> WOW!
WORK IT OUT FOR TEAM HUMBLE.
NOW, WHILE YOU CATCH YOUR
BREATH, LET'S TALK TO THE
JUDGES.
MICHELLE VISAGE, WHAT YOU THINK?
>> THAT WAS AMAZING!
COME ON, CHOREOGRAPHY!
PHENOMENAL.
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
AND I LOVE THAT YOU PLAYED SAFE.
EVERY ONE OF YOUR DANCES WEARING
A HARD HAT.
I LOVE THAT.
IT'S IMPORTANT.
>> I THINK YOU NEED TO
CHANGE YOUR NAME TO BOB THE
SUPERSTAR.
>> OH.
>> WELL, THANK YOU, JUDGES.
NOW, BOB THE DRAG QUEEN, FROM
THE MOMENT YOU ENTERED THE
WORKROOM, YOU HAD UNIQUE AND
TALENT WRITTEN ALL OVER YOU.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
>> MY NAME IS BOB THE DRAG
QUEEN.
I'M HILARIOUS.
BEAUTIFUL.
TALENTED AND HUMBLE.
>> THAT'S THE BIGGEST PEARL
NECKLACE I'VE EVER SEEN.
>> HOW YOU DOIN', RuPAUL?
I'M SORRY THAT I'M LATE, BUT
UZO A BOO-BOO LEFT THE STAGE.
WELL, THEN WHY DID I WASTE MY
TIME PUTTING ON THIS?
THIS?
>> SOMETIMES YOU BORDERLINE ON
SHOWBOATING.
>> INSERT SHADY RATTLESNAKE
NOISE HERE.
>> BOB, HOW'S YOUR HEAD?
>> NO COMPLAINTS.
>> I'M BOB THE DRAG QUEEN.
A QUEEN FOR THE PEOPLE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> NOW, BOB, WHEN DID YOU FIRST
BECOME AWARE OF DRAG?
>> I USED TO WATCH "TOO WONG
FOO."
I SAW THIS GLAMAZONIAN GODDESS
COMING DOWN FROM THE CEILING
WEARING A BIG CONFEDERATE FLAG.
I WAS, LIKE, OH, THIS BITCH --
WHEN I SAY BITCH, I MEAN IT LIKE
THE WAY YOU'D CALL YOUR
GRANDMOTHER A BITCH.
I WAS, LIKE, THIS BITCH IS
PUSHING BUTTONS.
I LOVED IT.
>> YOU EXCELLED AT SO MANY OF
THE CHALLENGES.
DID YOU STUDY THE SHOW BEFORE
YOU CAME ON?
>> NO, I'M JUST REALLY TALENTED.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> NO.
LISTEN, THIS IS MY FAVORITE
SHOW.
THIS IS WHAT I THOUGHT I WAS
SUPPOSED TO BE DOING MY WHOLE
LIFE WHEN I WAS PERFORMING IN
BARS IN NEW YORK CITY, DODGING
BEER BOTTLES LITERALLY.
I WAS, LIKE, THIS DOESN'T FEEL
RIGHT.
THERE'S SOMETHING BIGGER COMING.
LO AND BEHOLD, I FOUND SOMETHING
BIGGER AND IT WAS RuPAUL, AND
SHE'S BLESSED ME.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> NOW, BOB, AT ONE POINT IN THE
SEASON, THE OTHER QUEENS WERE
ROOTING FOR YOU TO FAIL.
>> MM-HMM.
>> WHAT DID THAT FEEL LIKE?
>> IT FELT LIKE I WAS DOING IT
RIGHT.
I MEAN, NO ONE'S ROOTING FOR THE
PERSON DOING THE WORST.
NO ONE'S, LIKE, OH, YOU'RE DOING
BAD.
THEY'RE, LIKE, SHE'S DOING SO
WELL.
GET HER THE FUCK OUT OF HERE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO WE'VE GOT SOME FAN QUESTIONS
OVER THERE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> BOB!
TUCKER FROM FLORIDA WANTS TO
KNOW, DOES YOUR HUMOR COME FROM
OVERCOMING A DARK PLACE IN YOUR
LIFE?
>> YEAH, I HAD THE STRUGGLES
THAT A LOT OF Y'ALL HOMOSEXUALS
HERE HAD.
>> WHAT?
WAIT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> A FEW.
I HAD THE SAME HARDSHIPS THAT
EVERYONE ELSE HERE HAS, AND WE
ALL DEAL WITH IT IN DIFFERENT
WAYS.
IF YOU FIND SOMETHING TO FILTER
YOUR PAIN AND YOUR ANGER, IT
WILL FLOURISH.
IT REALLY WILL.
>> THANK YOU.
NOW, BOB, YOU BLEW EVERYONE AWAY
WITH YOUR SNATCH GAME
IMPERSONATION.
NOW, DID YOU EVER HEAR FROM UZO
OR CAROL CHANNING?
>> WELL, UZO TWEETED AT ME, LIKE
THIS WAS AMAZING.
I WAS, LIKE, THANK YOU.
AND I AM OBSESSED WITH CAROL
CHANNING, BUT SHE'S 95 AND HARD
TO GET OUT OF THE HOUSE WHEN
YOU'RE 95.
I'M 18 AND IT'S HARD FOR ME TO
GET OUT.
>> I KNOW.
I KNOW.
WE DID HEAR FROM THE ONE AND
ONLY CAROL CHANNING.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> THANK YOU, BOB, FOR YOUR
COLORFUL IMPERSONATION OF ME.
I'M SO HONORED TO BE A PART OF
YOUR HISTORY.
AWW, I'M PROUD OF THAT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> YES.
SO BOB, AND THERE ARE YOUR
BROTHERS OVER THERE, RIGHT?
>> HE'S THE ONE WHO'S JUST A
SHADE DARKER THAN ME.
I'M 11:00 HE'S MIDNIGHT.
>> JUSTIN, WHAT WAS IT LIKE
GROWING UP WITH BOB?
>> BOB USED TO CRY ON MY
BIRTHDAY BECAUSE IT WASN'T ABOUT
HIM.
>> NOW, BOB, I KNOW THAT YOUR
MOTHER COULDN'T BE HERE BECAUSE
OF HER HEALTH.
>> YES.
>> YOU KNOW, IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
A GREAT OPPORTUNITY FOR US TO
HAVE A TAPED MESSAGE OR
SOMETHING, BUT WE DON'T HAVE --
WAIT A MINUTE.
OH, ACTUALLY, WE DO HAVE A TAPED
MESSAGE.
LET'S ROLL THAT.
>> BOB, THIS IS YOUR MOTHER.
I'M VERY PROUD OF YOU.
I'VE ALWAYS BELIEVED IN YOU EVEN
WHEN YOU DIDN'T BELIEVE IN
YOURSELF.
I'VE SEEN YOU WORK HARD AT YOUR
CRAFT, ALWAYS RESPECT YOUR FANS,
REACH FOR THE STARS, DO THE BEST
YOU CAN.
LIKE ALWAYS TELL YOU AND YOUR
BROTHERS, KEEP FIRST THING THE
FIRST THING, AND I LOVE YOU.
>> YOU GOT ME.
YOU GOT ME.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
>> NOW, BOB, WHAT WOULD IT MEAN
TO YOU TO WIN $100,000?
>> MONEY COMES AND GOES, BUT
WINNING THIS TITLE, THAT MEANS
SOMETHING.
YOU GET TO GO FORTH AND CARRY A
LEGACY AND DO SOMETHING AND MAKE
A CHANGE IN SOMEBODY'S LIFE AND
PUT FIRST THINGS FIRST AND DO
SOMETHING.
>> RIGHT, RIGHT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> NOW, I'VE WATCHED ALL 109
EPISODES OF "RuPAUL'S DRAG
RACE," AND I'VE NOTICED YOU HAVE
NEVER ONCE WALKED INTO THE ROOM
FIRST.
>> OH, MY GOD!
LOOK AT THIS!
OH, AND IT MATCHES MY OUTFIT.
IT'S PERFECT.
I LOVE IT!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
FIRST FIRST.
GIVE IT UP FOR BOB THE DRAG
QUEEN!
>>> ARE YOU TEAM BOB?
TWEET US NOW WITH #DRAGRACE.
>>> NEXT, WE'RE GOING TO KIM CHI
THAT WALK AND GO BIG WITH NAOMI
SMALLS AS THE GRAND FINALE OF
"RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE" CONTINUES.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO THE GRAND
FINALE OF "RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE."
UP NEXT, WE'VE GOT AN INSTAGRAM
SUPERSTAR WHO'S ABOUT TO
LIP-SYNC FOR HER LIFE.
NOW SERVING KIM CHI.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
떰
I CAME HERE TUESDAY
A BRAND-NEW CHANCE FOR YOU
REALLY EASY TO DO
IT'S A NEW SENSATION
ONLY THREE THINGS YOU NEED
TO DO IT JUST LIKE ME
COUNT IT LIKE ONE TWO THREE
EVERY GENERATION
BEYONCE
MADONNA
GOT NOTHING ON THIS TRIPLE
THREAT
DO THE
THE NATION
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
SENSATION
SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
ONE TWO THREE
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
BRITNEY
RIHANNA
GOT NOTHING ON THE TRIPLE
THREAT TO THE
THE NATION
UH-HUH
떰
THE NATION
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
떰
THE NATION
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> WOW!
KIM CHI, I LOVE THAT SONG.
IT'S GOT A GOOD BEAT, AND YOU
CAN'T DANCE TO IT.
ALL RIGHT, KIM CHI, LET'S HEAR
FROM THE JUDGES.
MICHELLE VISAGE, KIM CHI?
>> I LOVE THAT YOUR PURITY AND
YOUR BEAUTIFUL ENERGY TOOK
SOMETHING THAT WAS NORMALLY
CONSIDERED NEGATIVE AND TURNED
IT INTO SOMETHING FUN AND
BEAUTIFUL.
>> YES.
NAILED IT.
>> KIM CHI IS ON THE MENU.
AND YOU ARE THE MAIN COURSE!
WHO'S HUNGRY?
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> NOW, KIM CHI, YOU CAME TO
THIS COMPETITION HUNGRY.
YOU WON THE FIRST CHALLENGE.
AND THEN YOU STAYED HUNGRY.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
>> MY NAME IS KIM CHI.
I CAME TO THE COMPETITION.
I'M KNOWN FOR CRAZY,
OVER-THE-TOP ANIME FANTASY.
ANIME-ZING.
I MAY COME ACROSS SHY BECAUSE
I'M SOFT-SPOKEN BUT DO NOT
COMFORT ME BECAUSE I'LL DESTROY
YOU.
>> I DO GET CONCERNED ABOUT YOUR
WALK.
IT'S VERY STIFF, DARLING.
>> MY MOM.
DOESN'T KNOW THAT I DO DRAG.
>> WHAT?
>> KIM CHI, YOU DIDN'T JUST GET
BETTER.
YOU GOT FIERCE.
>> I DON'T WANT TO BE AMERICA'S
NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR.
I AM AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG
SUPERSTAR.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> NOW, KIM CHI, YOU ARE SO
HONEST AND VULNERABLE THIS
SEASON.
IN FACT, WATCHING THE SHOW BACK,
AT ONE POINT YOU MADE ME UGLY
CRY, GIRL.
SO I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND IF I
ASK YOU SOME VERY PERSONAL
QUESTIONS.
FIRST ONE, WHEN WAS THE LAST
TIME YOU FELL DOWN?
>> ACTUALLY, EARLIER TODAY.
I'M NOT EVEN JOKING.
I TRIPPED ON MY SKIRT.
AND I FELL OVER THE CRAFT
SERVICES TABLE.
>> NOW, EVERYONE IS GAGGING ON
YOUR LOOK.
JUST SO MANY AMAZING.
WHAT INSPIRES YOU?
>> MY INSPIRATION COMES FROM A
LOT OF RANDOM PLACES.
I COULD BE WALKING DOWN THE
STREET AND SEE A ROCK AND BE,
LIKE, OH, THAT ROCK IS PRETTY.
LET ME MAKE A GOWN INSPIRED BY
THE ROCK.
SO THERE'S NO ONE SET
INSPIRATION.
BUT EVERYDAY LIFE AND NATURE.
>> IS IT TRUE YOU GAVE THE
$3,000 YOU WON IN THE FIRST
CHALLENGE TO YOUR MOTHER?
WHY'D YOU DO THAT?
>> MY MOM WORKS REALLY HARD TO
PAY THE BILLS.
AND SHE WORKS AS A SERVER AT A
KOREAN RESTAURANT CURRENTLY.
AND I WANT TO DO EVERYTHING THAT
I CAN TO HELP MY MOM
FINANCIALLY.
>> YEAH.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
HAVE YOU TOLD HER THAT YOU DO
DRAG YET?
>> I STILL HAVE NOT, BUT, YOU
KNOW --
>> SHE DIDN'T WATCH THE SHOW?
>> SHE'S KOREAN-AMERICAN AND
SHE'S REALLY NOT OPEN TO
AMERICAN CULTURE AT ALL.
SO I DON'T THINK -- YEAH, I
DON'T THINK SHE'LL EVER FIND OUT
ABOUT "DRAG RACE."
>> WELL, LISTEN.
I AM A FIRM BELIEVER IN THINGS
HAPPEN WHEN THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO
HAPPEN.
SO RIGHT AFTER THIS, WHY DON'T
WE DRIVE OVER TO YOUR MOTHER'S
HOUSE, AND I TELL HER MYSELF.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ROAD TRIP?
ROAD TRIP.
>> ROAD TRIP, YES.
>> WHO'S HERE SUPPORTING YOU
TONIGHT?
>> I HAVE MY FRIEND RYAN, DIANA,
AMY AND TRIXIE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> SO WHAT DO YOU THINK OF KIM
CHI'S JOURNEY?
>> I THINK KIM CHI IS THE MOST
CREATIVE, TALENTED AND
HARDWORKING PERSON I KNOW.
I'M SO HAPPY TO BE HERE WITH
HIM.
>> ALL RIGHT.
NOW, WE'VE GOT SOME FAN
QUESTIONS FOR YOU, KIM CHI.
OH, LOOK, AND YOU FORGOT YOUR
PANTS, GUYS.
>> KIM CHI, SIERRA FROM FACEBOOK
ASKS, IF YOU COULD LOSE YOUR
VIRGINITY TO A MEMBER OF THE PIT
CREW, WHO WOULD IT BE?
>> I'M NOT TRYING TO CATCH
ANYTHING, SO I'M GOING TO SAY
NONE OF THEM.
BUT --
>> HEY.
THANK YOU, PIT CREW MEMBERS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY AFTER
THAT.
ALL RIGHT, KIM CHI.
WELL, WE HAVE ONE MORE QUESTION.
ACTUALLY, IT'S MORE OF A
STATEMENT.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> KIM CHI, I AM SUPREME LEADER,
BUT YOU ARE SUPREME DRAG QUEEN.
YOU BETTER WORK, OR ELSE I PUT
YOU IN A LABOR CAMP.
>> KIM CHI, IT'S MARGARET CHO.
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
YOU ARE SO BEAUTIFUL, SO FUNNY,
AND I THINK YOU ARE A GOOD
DANCER.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> SO KIM CHI, WHAT WOULD IT
MEAN TO YOU TO BECOME AMERICA'S
NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR?
>> IT WOULD OBVIOUSLY CHANGE MY
LIFE.
I'D BE ABLE TO NOT BE BROKE.
I'D BE ABLE TO AFFORD GUACAMOLE
IN MY BURRITO BOWL.
I'D BE ABLE TO START MY OWN
MAKEUP COMPANY.
WHICH I WOULD LOVE TO DO.
AND IT WOULD MEAN THAT ANYBODY
WHO'S EVER FELT LIKE THEY
WEREN'T PART OF ANYTHING,
ANYBODY THAT FELT LIKE THEY
COULDN'T BE ANYTHING, AS LONG AS
YOU STAY TRUE TO WHO YOU ARE, BE
CREATIVE, BE ORIGINAL AND YOUR
DREAMS WILL EVENTUALLY COME
TRUE.
>> WELL, KIM CHI, READ MY LIST.
WE LOVE YOU.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN GIVE IT UP
FOR KIM CHI!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> ARE YOU TEAM KIM CHI?
THEN TWEET ALL ABOUT IT.
#DRAGRACE.
>>> UP NEXT, NAOMI SMALLS IS
GOING TO STRETCH HER LEGS WHEN
THE GRAND FINALE OF "RuPAUL'S
DRAG RACE" CONTINUES.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> WELCOME BACK TO THE GRAND
FINALE OF "RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE."
NOW, IT'S TIME FOR OUR FINAL
PERFORMANCE OF THE NIGHT.
OH, AND BY THE WAY, KITTEN, YOU
CAN BUY THESE TOP THREE SONGS
RIGHT NOW WHEREVER FINE MUSIC IS
SOLD.
AND YOU CAN WATCH THEM AGAIN AND
AGAIN AT LOGOTV.COM.
NOW, OUR NEXT QUEEN STRUTTED HER
STUFF ALL THE WAY TO THE TOP.
PLEASE GIVE A BIG SUPERMODEL
WELCOME TO NAOMI SMALLS!
>> THEY TRIED TO PUT ME ON THE
COVER OF "VOGUE," BUT MY LEGS
WERE TOO LONG.
EVERY DAY IS LIKE THAT
MONDAY TUESDAY WEDNESDAY
THIGHS CALVES ALL THE WAY
THURSDAY FRIDAY SATURDAY
SUNDAY IS THE ONE DAY
I GET ON THE RUNWAY
READY FOR IT
I'M LEGENDARY
ALL LEGS NO DERRIE
LEG LEGS
THAT'S WHAT'S ON THE MENU
ON THE MENU
LEG LEGS
LEGS LEGS
ON THE MENU
LEGS
LEGS LEGS
EVERY DAY IS LEG DAY
LEGS
WATCH IT WHILE YOUR HEART
EVERY DAY IS LEG DAY
BREAK
WATCH IT WHILE YOUR HEART
SUNDAY IS THE ONE DAY
BREAK
I GET ON THE RUNWAY
SUNDAY IS THE ONE DAY
READY FOR IT HUMP DAY
I GET ON THE RUNWAY
I'M LEGENDARY
READY FOR IT HUMP DAY
ALL LEGS NO DERRIE
I'M LEGENDARY
LEG LEGS
ALL LEGS NO DERRIE
WHAT'S ON THE MENU
LEG LEGS
LEGS LEGS
WHAT'S ON THE MENU
LEGS
NAOMI SMALLS
CHRISTIE
CINDY
NAOMI SMALLS
CLAUDIA
NAOMI SMALLS NOELT
LEG LEGS
WHAT'S ON THE MENU
LEGS LEGS
LEGS 떰
WHAT'S ON THE MENU
>> WOW!
LEGS 떰
LEGS FOR DAYS.
>> WOW!
OKAY, NAOMI, LET'S TALK TO THE
LEGS FOR DAYS.
JUDGES.
OKAY, NAOMI, LET'S TALK TO THE
MICHELLE VISAGE.
JUDGES.
>> HONEY, WHATEVER'S ON THE
MICHELLE VISAGE.
MENU, I'M BUYING TWO.
>> HONEY, WHATEVER'S ON THE
>> LOOK HOW FAR YOU'VE COME,
MENU, I'M BUYING TWO.
HONEY, AND YOU HAVE PROVEN
>> LOOK HOW FAR YOU'VE COME,
TONIGHT THAT YOU HAVE LEGS UP ON
HONEY, AND YOU HAVE PROVEN
THE COMPETITION.
TONIGHT THAT YOU HAVE LEGS UP ON
YES, YOU DO.
THE COMPETITION.
>> YOU CAME, YOU SAW, YOU
YES, YOU DO.
CONTOURED, AND YOU CONQUERED.
>> YOU CAME, YOU SAW, YOU
>> YES.
CONTOURED, AND YOU CONQUERED.
>> THANK YOU, NAOMI SMALLS.
>> YES.
NOW, AS THE YOUNGEST QUEEN TO
>> THANK YOU, NAOMI SMALLS.
COMPETE THIS SEASON, YOU'VE COME
NOW, AS THE YOUNGEST QUEEN TO
A LONG WAY, BABY.
COMPETE THIS SEASON, YOU'VE COME
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
A LONG WAY, BABY.
>> I AM NAOMI SMALLS.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
NAOMI HAS LEGS ALL THE WAY UP
>> I AM NAOMI SMALLS.
TO HER ASSHOLE.
NAOMI HAS LEGS ALL THE WAY UP
NAOMI IS A FASHION GIRL.
TO HER ASSHOLE.
SHE'S FUCKIN' FIERCE.
NAOMI IS A FASHION GIRL.
>> OH, ALL OF THAT RIGHT THERE.
SHE'S FUCKIN' FIERCE.
>> I'M GIVING YOU NAOMI CAMPBELL
>> OH, ALL OF THAT RIGHT THERE.
STRUTTING DOWN A VERSACE RUNWAY.
>> I'M GIVING YOU NAOMI CAMPBELL
>> I JUST THOUGHT IT WAS
STRUTTING DOWN A VERSACE RUNWAY.
PERFECTION.
>> I JUST THOUGHT IT WAS
>> THIS IS HOW YOU WIN THIS
PERFECTION.
COMPETITION.
>> THIS IS HOW YOU WIN THIS
>> I HAVE EIGHT BROTHERS AND
COMPETITION.
THREE SISTERS.
>> I HAVE EIGHT BROTHERS AND
>> WHOA!
THREE SISTERS.
>> THAT IS CRAZY.
>> WHOA!
>> THIS IS MY MOM.
>> THAT IS CRAZY.
SHE'S, LIKE, THE BEST MOM EVER.
>> THIS IS MY MOM.
>> DO YOU HAVE A MESSAGE YOU
SHE'S, LIKE, THE BEST MOM EVER.
WANT TO SAY TO YOUR MOTHER?
>> DO YOU HAVE A MESSAGE YOU
>> THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING
WANT TO SAY TO YOUR MOTHER?
YOU'VE EVER DONE.
>> THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING
AND I HOPE I CAN REPAY YOU FOR
YOU'VE EVER DONE.
THE REST OF MY LIFE.
AND I HOPE I CAN REPAY YOU FOR
>> I'M NAOMI SMALLS, AND I
THE REST OF MY LIFE.
PROMISE TO REPRESENT YOUTH
>> I'M NAOMI SMALLS, AND I
FIERCELY.
PROMISE TO REPRESENT YOUTH
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
FIERCELY.
>> NAOMI, YOU HAVE THE FEVER AND
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THE FLAVOR FOR FASHION.
>> NAOMI, YOU HAVE THE FEVER AND
NOW, WHERE DOES THAT COME FROM?
THE FLAVOR FOR FASHION.
>> I HONESTLY DON'T KNOW BECAUSE
NOW, WHERE DOES THAT COME FROM?
I GREW UP IN, LIKE, A FAMILY
>> I HONESTLY DON'T KNOW BECAUSE
THAT WAS -- SORRY, GUYS, NOT THE
I GREW UP IN, LIKE, A FAMILY
MOST FASHION FORWARD OR ANYTHING
THAT WAS -- SORRY, GUYS, NOT THE
LIKE THAT.
MOST FASHION FORWARD OR ANYTHING
BUT I JUST REMEMBER, LIKE,
LIKE THAT.
LOOKING AT MAGAZINES WHEN I WAS
BUT I JUST REMEMBER, LIKE,
A KID AND JUST BEING SO OBSESSED
LOOKING AT MAGAZINES WHEN I WAS
WITH THEM.
A KID AND JUST BEING SO OBSESSED
I WANTED TO LOOK LIKE THESE
WITH THEM.
AMAZING SUPERMODELS THAT WERE IN
I WANTED TO LOOK LIKE THESE
THE GLOSSY PAGES.
AMAZING SUPERMODELS THAT WERE IN
>> SURE, YEAH.
THE GLOSSY PAGES.
NOW, HALFWAY THROUGH THE
>> SURE, YEAH.
COMPETITION, YOU SEEMED TO COME
NOW, HALFWAY THROUGH THE
TO LIFE.
COMPETITION, YOU SEEMED TO COME
WHAT HAPPENED?
TO LIFE.
>> I WAS SO SCARED IN THE
WHAT HAPPENED?
BEGINNING OF STANDING OUT FOR
>> I WAS SO SCARED IN THE
THE WRONG REASONS.
BEGINNING OF STANDING OUT FOR
WHEN IT COMES TO SNATCH GAME,
THE WRONG REASONS.
YOU CAN'T HIDE ANYWHERE.
WHEN IT COMES TO SNATCH GAME,
AND BEING IN THE BOTTOM TWO AND
YOU CAN'T HIDE ANYWHERE.
HAVING TO TAKE CHANCES AND STAND
AND BEING IN THE BOTTOM TWO AND
OUT FOR ALL THE RIGHT REASONS.
HAVING TO TAKE CHANCES AND STAND
>> YEAH.
OUT FOR ALL THE RIGHT REASONS.
YOU DID REALLY WELL.
>> YEAH.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU DID REALLY WELL.
NOW, NAOMI, WE HAVE A TAPED
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
MESSAGE FROM ONE FIERCE QUEEN.
NOW, NAOMI, WE HAVE A TAPED
TAKE A LOOK.
MESSAGE FROM ONE FIERCE QUEEN.
>> HI, NAOMI.
TAKE A LOOK.
NOW, THERE'S ONLY ROOM FOR ONE
>> HI, NAOMI.
QUEEN.
NOW, THERE'S ONLY ROOM FOR ONE
BUT IN RU'S QUEENDOM, GIRL, I
QUEEN.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU TAKE THAT
BUT IN RU'S QUEENDOM, GIRL, I
CROWN.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU TAKE THAT
THAT WALK.
CROWN.
CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THAT WALK.
>> I LOVE THAT.
CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> SO GOOD.
>> I LOVE THAT.
>> NOW, WE HAVE SOME FAN
>> SO GOOD.
QUESTIONS.
>> NOW, WE HAVE SOME FAN
G-G-G-GIA.
QUESTIONS.
>> FROM MEXICO.
G-G-G-GIA.
WOULD LIKE TO KNOW, HOW DID IT
>> FROM MEXICO.
FEEL WHEN NAOMI CAMPBELL TAGGED
WOULD LIKE TO KNOW, HOW DID IT
YOU ONLINE?
FEEL WHEN NAOMI CAMPBELL TAGGED
>> IT WAS, LIKE, THE BIGGEST
YOU ONLINE?
MOMENT OF MY LIFE.
>> IT WAS, LIKE, THE BIGGEST
>> WHAT DID SHE SAY?
MOMENT OF MY LIFE.
>> WELL, SHE FOLLOWED ME ON
>> WHAT DID SHE SAY?
INSTAGRAM.
>> WELL, SHE FOLLOWED ME ON
THEN SHE HAD, LIKE, THIS
INSTAGRAM.
INTERVIEW SAYING "I REALLY AM
THEN SHE HAD, LIKE, THIS
LOVING THAT NAOMI SMALLS."
INTERVIEW SAYING "I REALLY AM
>> I LOVE THAT.
LOVING THAT NAOMI SMALLS."
>> TELL ME THIS.
>> I LOVE THAT.
WHAT WOULD IT MEAN TO YOU TO
>> TELL ME THIS.
BECOME AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG
WHAT WOULD IT MEAN TO YOU TO
SUPERSTAR?
BECOME AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG
>> IT WOULD MEAN THE WORLD TO
SUPERSTAR?
ME.
>> IT WOULD MEAN THE WORLD TO
TO BE AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG
ME.
SUPERSTAR.
TO BE AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG
JUST TO GET THAT STAMP OF
SUPERSTAR.
APPROVAL FROM YOU AND CARRY ON
JUST TO GET THAT STAMP OF
YOUR LEGACY WOULD BE THE BIGGEST
APPROVAL FROM YOU AND CARRY ON
GOAL EVER MET IN MY LIFE.
YOUR LEGACY WOULD BE THE BIGGEST
>> I LOVE IT.
GOAL EVER MET IN MY LIFE.
NOW, BEFORE WE GO, I WANT TO SAY
>> I LOVE IT.
HELLO TO YOUR MOTHER.
NOW, BEFORE WE GO, I WANT TO SAY
WHERE IS SHE?
HELLO TO YOUR MOTHER.
>> SHE'S RIGHT THERE.
WHERE IS SHE?
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> SHE'S RIGHT THERE.
>> THERE SHE IS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
HI.
>> THERE SHE IS.
SO JUNE, WHAT WAS IT LIKE
HI.
RAISING A LEGGY SUPERMODEL?
SO JUNE, WHAT WAS IT LIKE
>> WELL, I'M A LITTLE SHOCKED
RAISING A LEGGY SUPERMODEL?
THAT HE DIDN'T GET FASHION TIPS
>> WELL, I'M A LITTLE SHOCKED
FROM ME.
THAT HE DIDN'T GET FASHION TIPS
I HAD NO IDEA.
FROM ME.
HE HAS ALWAYS BEEN AMAZING.
I HAD NO IDEA.
>> REALLY?
HE HAS ALWAYS BEEN AMAZING.
>> YES.
>> REALLY?
>> DID YOU BUY THE FASHION
>> YES.
MAGAZINES, OR DID --
>> DID YOU BUY THE FASHION
>> NO, BUT I DID START BUYING
MAGAZINES, OR DID --
THE WIGS AND THE SHOES.
>> NO, BUT I DID START BUYING
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THE WIGS AND THE SHOES.
>> NOW, BESIDES NAOMI, HOW MANY
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
KIDS DID YOU RAISE?
>> NOW, BESIDES NAOMI, HOW MANY
>> 12 ALL TOGETHER.
KIDS DID YOU RAISE?
>> WOW!
>> 12 ALL TOGETHER.
WOW.
>> WOW!
[ APPLAUSE ]
WOW.
NAOMI, WHERE ARE YOUR OTHER
[ APPLAUSE ]
BROTHERS AND SISTERS TONIGHT?
NAOMI, WHERE ARE YOUR OTHER
>> THEY'RE ALL OVER THE WORLD.
BROTHERS AND SISTERS TONIGHT?
THEY'RE ACTUALLY ALL OVER THIS
>> THEY'RE ALL OVER THE WORLD.
THEATER, TOO.
THEY'RE ACTUALLY ALL OVER THIS
>> LET'S BRING THEM OUT, THE VON
THEATER, TOO.
TRAPP FAMILY SINGERS, COME ON
>> LET'S BRING THEM OUT, THE VON
OUT!
TRAPP FAMILY SINGERS, COME ON
WHERE ARE THEY?
OUT!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WHERE ARE THEY?
>> OH!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
HOW ARE YOU?
>> OH!
>> YOU KNOW, LIKE I ALWAYS SAY,
HOW ARE YOU?
THE FAMILY THAT DRAGS TOGETHER
>> YOU KNOW, LIKE I ALWAYS SAY,
SLAYS TOGETHER.
THE FAMILY THAT DRAGS TOGETHER
LET'S HEAR IT FOR THE LEGENDARY,
SLAYS TOGETHER.
ALL LEGS, NO DERRIE, NAOMI
LET'S HEAR IT FOR THE LEGENDARY,
SMALLS!
ALL LEGS, NO DERRIE, NAOMI
>>> ARE YOU TEAM NAOMI?
SMALLS!
THEN LET THE WORLD KNOW.
>>> ARE YOU TEAM NAOMI?
TWEET IT WITH #DRAGRACE.
THEN LET THE WORLD KNOW.
>>> COMING UP, THE QUEENS
TWEET IT WITH #DRAGRACE.
REUNITE.
>>> COMING UP, THE QUEENS
WE ANNOUNCE MISS CONGENIALITY
REUNITE.
AND MORE WHEN THE GRAND FINALE
WE ANNOUNCE MISS CONGENIALITY
OF "RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE"
AND MORE WHEN THE GRAND FINALE
CONTINUES.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO THE GRAND
FINALE OF "RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE."
NOW, WE'RE JUST MOMENTS AWAY
FROM CROWNING AMERICA'S NEXT
DRAG SUPERSTAR.
BUT FIRST, IT'S TIME TO BRING
BACK MY GIRLS!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
STARTING WITH A NERDY BIRD, A
GLAM ROCK REBEL AND ONE CUCKOO
QUEEN.
>> MY NAME IS DAX
EXCLAMATIONPOINT.
WHAT'S UP, NERDS?
MY LOOK IS VERY INSPIRED BY
SCIENCE FICTION AND COMICS,
STRONG, BAD BITCHES WHO DON'T
TAKE CRAP FROM ANYONE ELSE.
>> SHOW ME YOUR EXCLAMATION
POINT.
>> ALL RIGHT, LADIES, LET'S TURN
UP THE JUICE AND SEE WHICH STAYS
LOOSE.
>> LAILA IS LIKE A WHORE
QUASI -- I DON'T WANT TO SAY
GOTHY, BUT, LIKE, GOTHY.
>> MY BIGGEST CONCERN IS THAT
I'M GOING TO FADE INTO THE
BACKGROUND.
>> I'M HERE, TOO.
>> DAX EXCLAMATIONPOINT.
LAILA McQUEEN, NEITHER ONE OF
YOU SURVIVED THAT LIP-SYNC.
>> BOTH OF US?
REALLY?
>> HOW YOU DOING?
MY NAME IS CYNTHIA LEE FONTAINE.
DO YOU WANT TO SEE MY CUCKOO?
I NEED A PLACE FOR JUNK IN THE
TRUNK.
>> I'M SEXY AS A GODDESS AND
FUNNY AS A CLAM.
I AM CINDY
DO MY TITS LOOK JELL-O?
NO.
>> DAX EXCLAMATIONPOINT AND
LAILA McQUEEN, WELCOME BACK.
>> HELLO.
>> DAX, I HEAR THAT THE SONG "I
WILL SURVIVE" IS HAUNTING YOU
EVERYWHERE YOU GO.
IS THAT TRUE?
>> YES.
LIKE LITERALLY, EVERYWHERE I GO,
IT COULD BE GAS
STATION, GROCERY STORE,
ANYWHERE, IT JUST HAPPENS TO
COME ON.
>> LISTEN, IF I WERE YOU TWO, I
WOULD SEIZE THE MOMENT.
I WOULD RECORD ANOTHER SONG.
I WOULD CALL IT "I DIDN'T
SURVIVE."
YOU KNOW.
IT WOULD BE A HUGE HIT.
BUT SERIOUSLY, THERE ARE NO
LOSERS ON "DRAG RACE."
DAX, WHAT'S LIFE BEEN LIKE SINCE
YOU WERE ON THE SHOW?
>> HONESTLY, LIFE HAS BEEN
ABSOLUTELY AMAZING.
LIKE THE FANS HAVE BEEN
PHENOMENAL.
OBVIOUSLY I DON'T HAVE AS MANY
FANS AS KIM CHI OR BOB OR NAOMI,
THAT'S FINE.
BUT THE ONES I DO HAVE ARE
PHENOMENAL.
>> NOW, I'VE GOT A CONFESSION TO
MAKE.
LAILA McQUEEN AND I HAVE A
SECRET PAST.
I DENY IT, BUT THERE'S PROOF.
TAKE A LOOK.
THAT LITTLE PIXIE TO THE RIGHT
OF ME IS LAILA McQUEEN WHEN I
WAS NOT RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT IN
MANCHESTER, NEW HAMPSHIRE.
>> YOU KNOW, MY GRANDMOTHER
CALLS YOU RON PAUL.
>> NOW, DID YOU EVER IMAGINE AT
THAT POINT THAT YOU WOULD BE ON
THIS STAGE?
>> OH, ABSOLUTELY NOT.
I MEAN, I WAS PERFORMING IN,
LIKE, FUNCTION HALLS AND MEXICAN
RESTAURANTS.
I COULD NEVER IMAGINE BEING HERE
OR ANYWHERE ELSE AROUND THE
WORLD.
>> SO, NOW, WHAT'S HAPPENED TO
YOU BECAUSE OF "DRAG RACE"?
>> I GET TO GO EVERYWHERE AND
MEET THE PEOPLE THAT LOVE THE
WORK I DO AND EMBRACE SO MUCH
LOVE THAT I NEVER THOUGHT I
WOULD RECEIVE.
>> ALL THAT AT THE TRUCK STOP?
SO DAX, LAILA, YOU AREN'T JUST
SURVIVING, YOU ARE THRIVING.
THANK YOU.
NEXT UP, STRAIGHT FROM SANTEE
ALLEY, CYNTHIA LEE FONTAINE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
NOW, SINCE THE SHOW, YOU'VE BEEN
THROUGH IT, HAVEN'T YOU, GIRL?
>> YES.
ACTUALLY, THE EPISODE THAT I WAS
ELIMINATED, I WAS EXPERIENCING
SYMPTOMS.
I'M A LIVER CANCER SURVIVOR,
STAGE 1.
I'M HERE TO CELEBRATE.
>> WOW!
HOW DO YOU FEEL RIGHT NOW?
>> I'M IN THE DISCHARGE PROCESS
ALREADY RIGHT NOW.
>> YEAH.
>> SO I FEEL AMAZING.
I FEEL FANTASTIC.
>> GOOD.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
DID ANY OF YOUR DRAG SISTERS
REACH OUT TO YOU?
>> YES.
ONE SPECIAL PERSON, AND IT'S
ACID BETTY.
>> THAT ACID BETTY?
>> THAT ACID BETTY.
YEP.
ACID BETTY.
SHE CAME TO VISIT ME AS SOON AS
SHE KNEW THAT I WAS DIAGNOSED.
SHE WAS TAKING CARE OF ME.
SHE WAS, LIKE, BITCH, YOU'RE NOT
ALONE.
I'VE GOT YOUR BACK.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I THINK THE POSITIVE ATTITUDE
FROM ALL MY SISTERHOOD HELPED ME
TO RECOVERY AND HELPED ME TO BE
MORE POSITIVE EVERY DAY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> WOW.
I LOVE IT.
WELL, CYNTHIA LEE FONTAINE, WE
ARE CUCKOO FOR YOUR CUCKOO.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU.
>> NOW A QUEEN WHO ALWAYS PICKS
UP WHEN I CALL AND A BADASS IN
TOTAL CONTROL OF HERSELF, LET'S
TAKE A LOOK.
>> THE BEAUTY IS HERE.
>> MY NAME IS NAYSHA LOPEZ.
I SAID,
HONEY, I DON'T DO DRAG ON A
DIME.
>> NAYSHA LOPEZ.
HOW SOON CAN YOU GET HERE?
>> BABE, BODY, GLAMOUR.
>> YOUR ASS IS REAL, YES.
>> REALNESS.
>> THIS ASS IS ALL REAL.
>> MY DRAG STYLE IS COMPLETELY
OVER THE TOP.
>> PUNK UNICORN REALNESS.
>> THE MAIN BULLET POINT OF ACID
BETTY IS SHE'S A BITCH.
>> ACID BETTY, YOU'VE TAKEN US
ON ONE WILD TRIP.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
NOW, NAYSHA LOPEZ, MICHELLE AND
I HAVE A RUNNING BET, OKAY?
THAT ASS OF YOURS, IS IT REAL?
>> LISTEN, RU, I EAT WELL.
I WORK OUT.
I HAVE TEN CCs OF MEDICAL-GRADE
SILICONE.
NO --
>> SO ON THE SHOW, YOU SAID YOUR
ASS IS REAL.
>> MY ASS IS REAL.
HOWEVER, HAVE I HAD SOME
ENHANCEMENTS?
>> YEAH.
>> YES, I HAVE.
>> AH.
NOW, YOU MISSED THE MADONNA
RUNWAY STORY LINE.
WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE WORN?
>> I'M A VERY CREATIVE PERSON.
AND WHAT I HAD GOING ON WAS
ANOTHER KIMONO.
>> WHAT?
WHAT IS IT WITH THESE QUEENS AND
KIMONOS?
NAYSHA, THANKS FOR GRACING US
WITH YOUR GORGEOUS BEAUTY AND
THAT BOOTY TWICE.
NEXT, ACID BETTY.
NOW, ARE YOU REALLY HERE, OR AM
I HAVING A FLASHBACK?
NOW, YOU TURNED OUT SOME KILLER
LOOKS THIS SEASON.
>> THANK YOU.
>> HOW HAVE FANS BEEN TO YOU?
>> I LOVE THE FANS.
THEY ARE THE BEST.
THE BEST.
THE BEST THING OF THIS SHOW ARE
THE FANS.
THE LOVE IS SO INTENSE AND
SPLENDORFUL.
I ACTUALLY HAVE A KID THAT I MET
AT DRAG CON, AND THEY DECIDED
THEY WERE GOING TO GO INTO
FASHION AND GOT A FULL
SCHOLARSHIP TO FIDM BECAUSE OF
SEEING ME ON THIS TV SHOW.
>> WOW.
>> IT'S REALLY GREAT.
>> NOW, ACID BETTY, YOU TOOK A
LOT OF HEAT FOR YOUR NANCY GRACE
IMPERSONATION.
BUT SOME PEOPLE REALLY, REALLY
LIKED IT.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> ACID BETTY, I LOVED WATCHING
YOU BE ME, BUT FRANKLY, SPEAKING
PROFESSIONALLY, YOU GOT A RAW
DEAL.
YOU WERE ROBBED.
UNLEASH THE LAWYERS!
WE'VE GOT A CASE HERE.
>> THAT'S FIERCE.
I LOVE IT.
>> ACID, I COULD GO ON TALKING
TO YOU ALL NIGHT BUT I REFUSE TO
SAY ANYTHING FURTHER UNTIL I
LAWYER UP.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, ACID
BETTY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> COMING UP, GET INTO THE
GROOVE WHEN ROBBIE, THORGY AND
DERRICK AND CHI CHI RETURN.
FIND OUT WHO SNATCHES MISS
CONGENIALITY.
>>> PLUS, ARE YOU TEAM BOB?
TEAM KIM CHI?
OR TEAM NAOMI?
I CAN'T HEAR YOU.
TWEET US WITH #DRAGRACE AS THE
GRAND FINALE OF "RuPAUL'S DRAG
RACE" CONTINUES.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO THE GRAND
FINALE OF "RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE."
NOW, THE BEST WAY TO DESCRIBE
OUR NEXT THREE QUEENS IS BRASSY,
BROOKLYN AND BRITNEY, BITCH.
>> GOOD MORNING.
MY NAME IS ROBBIE TURNER, AND
I'M THE KINDEST QUEEN YOU'LL
EVER MEET.
WANT YOU TO BE HOT AND SAUCY
>> YES.
>> SHE'S IN A LEAGUE OF HER OWN.
>> I WOULD WEAR THE HELL OUT OF
THAT JUMPSUIT.
>> TOO REAL.
떰
>> THORGY AND I FEEL INCREDIBLE!
>> I'M COLORFUL, I'M FUN AND I'M
A FASHION QUEEN.
>> OH!
>> THIS IS HARDER ON ME THAN IT
IS FOR YOU GUYS.
NO, IT'S NOT!
>> I CAN BE CAMPY, BUT ALSO I
CAN BE, LIKE, FUCKING FIERCE.
>> I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
GREAT JOB.
>> IT'S DERRICK, BITCH.
I MAY LOOK ANGELIC, BUT I AM NOT
THAT INNOCENT.
I ALSO HAVE A CAREER WITH MY
WIGS ON.
YOU'LL HAVE A CAREER ONCE YOU
START GLUING YOURS DOWN.
>> YOU HAVE TO GIVE US MORE.
THAT IS NOT A BRITNEY REFERENCE.
>> THAT'S HOW YOU GO OUT IN
STYLE, GIRLS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> NOW, ROBBIE TURNER, HOW DOES
SOMEONE SO YOUNG KNOW SO MUCH
ABOUT PLASTIC HOLLYWOOD?
>> MY MOTHER AND FATHER WOULDN'T
ALLOW US TO WATCH CONTEMPORARY
FILMS.
WE WATCHED CLASSIC HOLLYWOOD
FILMS ALL THE TIME.
SO I THOUGHT THEY WERE
CONTEMPORARY.
SO YOU CAN IMAGINE LITTLE BABY
ROBBIE WHEN SHE'S, LIKE, JUDY
GARLAND DIED MANY MOONS AGO.
AND IT'S, LIKE, WHAT?
>> NOW, WHAT WAS YOUR FAVORITE
MOMENT ON THE SHOW?
>> ON MY BIRTHDAY, I WON THE
SINGING CHALLENGE WITH THE
CHICKEN WING.
AND DEBBIE HARRY CAME BACK AND
SAID HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO ME.
I'M, LIKE, UM, I DON'T SEE THE
PROBLEM WITH THIS BIRTHDAY AT
ALL.
"DRAG RACE," DEBBIE, CHICKEN,
WING.
>> ROBBIE, THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
ALL THE CLASSIC SASS.
AND BY THE WAY, I WILL BE
SENDING YOU A BILL FOR THAT
BROKEN LIGHT BULB THAT YOU DID.
UH-HUH.
UP NEXT, HEY THERE, THORGY GIRL.
>> HEY!
RU!
YEAH!
>> NOW, LIKE MICHELLE AND I, YOU
AND BOB HAVE A VERY COMPLICATED
RELATIONSHIP.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
>> I LOVE TO ARGUE AND FIGHT
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
I LOVE IT AS ALWAYS A WAY TO
TEAR THINGS APART AND MAKE IT
BETTER.
BOB CAN TAKE IT FROM ME.
HE WILL JUST LISTEN TO ME TALK
AND GO, "I STILL DON'T LIKE
YOU."
BUT WHEN PEOPLE SEE ME AND BOB
DOING THAT, THEY'RE, LIKE, YOU
GUYS REALLY DON'T LIKE EACH
OTHER.
I JUST LOVE FIGHTING WITH HIM SO
MUCH.
I'M JUST IN LOVE WITH BOB VERY
>> NOW YOU HAVE DREAMS OF
MUCH.
STARTING A THORCHESTRA, IS THAT
>> NOW YOU HAVE DREAMS OF
RIGHT?
STARTING A THORCHESTRA, IS THAT
>> YEAH.
RIGHT?
>> WHAT'S A THORCHESTRA?
>> YEAH.
>> EVER SINCE I STARTED PLAYING
>> WHAT'S A THORCHESTRA?
VIOLIN AND GOT INTO DRAG, I
>> EVER SINCE I STARTED PLAYING
WANTED TO CONDUCT A 40-PIECE
VIOLIN AND GOT INTO DRAG, I
ORCHESTRA, TRAVEL THE WORLD.
WANTED TO CONDUCT A 40-PIECE
I WANT, LIKE, RUFUS WAINWRIGHT
ORCHESTRA, TRAVEL THE WORLD.
TO WHEEL OUT ON A PIANO AND BE,
I WANT, LIKE, RUFUS WAINWRIGHT
LIKE, OH, MY FRIEND RUFUS IS
TO WHEEL OUT ON A PIANO AND BE,
HERE TO SING A SONG.
LIKE, OH, MY FRIEND RUFUS IS
>> THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
HERE TO SING A SONG.
WILL YOU PLAY A LITTLE SOMETHING
>> THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
FOR US RIGHT NOW?
WILL YOU PLAY A LITTLE SOMETHING
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
FOR US RIGHT NOW?
>> SURE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
OH, MY GOD!
>> SURE.
떰
OH, MY GOD!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
떰
>> THANK YOU, GUYS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> WELL, THORGY, I CANNOT WAIT
>> THANK YOU, GUYS.
TO SEE WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO DO
>> WELL, THORGY, I CANNOT WAIT
NEXT.
TO SEE WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO DO
[ APPLAUSE ]
NEXT.
UP NEXT, THE 100th QUEEN TO
[ APPLAUSE ]
PRANCE INTO MY WORKROOM.
UP NEXT, THE 100th QUEEN TO
HEY DERRICK
PRANCE INTO MY WORKROOM.
NOW, YOU STRUGGLED TO GET OUT OF
HEY DERRICK
THE BRITNEY BOX, AS IT WAS
NOW, YOU STRUGGLED TO GET OUT OF
CALLED.
THE BRITNEY BOX, AS IT WAS
WHAT'S YOUR RELATIONSHIP WITH
CALLED.
BRITNEY NOW?
WHAT'S YOUR RELATIONSHIP WITH
>> I WILL ALWAYS DO BRITNEY.
BRITNEY NOW?
I'M NOT LEAVING IT BEHIND.
>> I WILL ALWAYS DO BRITNEY.
OF COURSE, I WANTED TO COME ON
I'M NOT LEAVING IT BEHIND.
THE SHOW TO EXPAND WHAT I
OF COURSE, I WANTED TO COME ON
ALREADY DO AND TAKE IT TO THE
THE SHOW TO EXPAND WHAT I
NEXT LEVEL.
ALREADY DO AND TAKE IT TO THE
AND I FEEL LIKE NOT ONLY CAN I
NEXT LEVEL.
DO BRITNEY NOW, I CAN DO DRAG.
AND I FEEL LIKE NOT ONLY CAN I
I'M DOING DRAG RIGHT NOW.
DO BRITNEY NOW, I CAN DO DRAG.
>> NOW, DERRICK, THROUGHOUT THE
I'M DOING DRAG RIGHT NOW.
SEASON, YOU WERE NOT AFRAID TO
>> NOW, DERRICK, THROUGHOUT THE
SPEAK YOUR MIND LOUDLY.
SEASON, YOU WERE NOT AFRAID TO
ESPECIALLY WITH BOB AND NAOMI.
SPEAK YOUR MIND LOUDLY.
DO YOU HAVE ANY REGRETS ABOUT
ESPECIALLY WITH BOB AND NAOMI.
THAT?
DO YOU HAVE ANY REGRETS ABOUT
>> EVERYTHING?
THAT?
GOSH.
>> EVERYTHING?
IT'S HARD BECAUSE I WATCH IT
GOSH.
BACK.
IT'S HARD BECAUSE I WATCH IT
I'M, LIKE, OH, WOW, I SHOULDN'T
BACK.
HAVE SAID THAT.
I'M, LIKE, OH, WOW, I SHOULDN'T
PROBABLY SHOULDN'T HAVE HAD THAT
HAVE SAID THAT.
DRINK AND UNTUCK.
PROBABLY SHOULDN'T HAVE HAD THAT
AND YES, I HAVE A HARD TIME
DRINK AND UNTUCK.
TAKING CRITICISM BECAUSE I'VE
AND YES, I HAVE A HARD TIME
NEVER BEEN CRITICIZED LIKE THAT
TAKING CRITICISM BECAUSE I'VE
BEFORE.
NEVER BEEN CRITICIZED LIKE THAT
DOING BRITNEY WAS WHAT I'VE
BEFORE.
ALWAYS DONE.
DOING BRITNEY WAS WHAT I'VE
AND I WAS PRAISED FOR THAT.
ALWAYS DONE.
AND NOW COMING INTO THIS
AND I WAS PRAISED FOR THAT.
COMPETITION, IT WAS ALMOST
AND NOW COMING INTO THIS
LOOKED DOWN UPON THAT THAT WAS
COMPETITION, IT WAS ALMOST
SOMETHING THAT I WAS KNOWN TO
LOOKED DOWN UPON THAT THAT WAS
DO.
SOMETHING THAT I WAS KNOWN TO
AND I LEARNED SO MUCH FROM
DO.
NAOMI.
AND I LEARNED SO MUCH FROM
AND SHE TAUGHT ME HOW TO BLOCK
NAOMI.
MY BROWS, AND I THINK I'M DOING
AND SHE TAUGHT ME HOW TO BLOCK
IT NOW.
MY BROWS, AND I THINK I'M DOING
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
IT NOW.
>> THANK YOU, DERRICK.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
AND I WILL ALWAYS THINK OF YOU
>> THANK YOU, DERRICK.
AS MY GENIE IN A BOTTLE.
AND I WILL ALWAYS THINK OF YOU
YES, I KNOW THAT'S A CHRISTINA
AS MY GENIE IN A BOTTLE.
SONG, BUT I'VE RUN OUT OF
YES, I KNOW THAT'S A CHRISTINA
BRITNEY REFERENCES!
SONG, BUT I'VE RUN OUT OF
GIVE ME A BREAK!
BRITNEY REFERENCES!
>> YES.
GIVE ME A BREAK!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> YES.
>> WE LOVE YOU, DERRICK BARRY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> "RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE"
>> WE LOVE YOU, DERRICK BARRY.
CELEBRATES "DRAG ACROSS AMERICA"
>>> "RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE"
PRESENTING THE KENZIE SIX.
CELEBRATES "DRAG ACROSS AMERICA"
RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE
PRESENTING THE KENZIE SIX.
START YOUR ENGINES
RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE
MAY THE BEST WOMAN WIN
>>> COMING UP, STRAIGHT OUT OF
SHREVEPORT, HURRICANE CHI CHI
DEVAYNE.
PLUS, TATIA RETURNS TO NAME MISS
CONGENIALITY.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "RuPAUL'S
DRAG RACE" GRAND FINALE.
WE ARE MOMENTS AWAY FROM FINDING
OUT IF BOB THE DRAG QUEEN, KIM
CHI OR NAOMI SMALLS WILL BE
CROWNED AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG
SUPERSTAR.
FIRST, THE QUEEN WHO HAS TURNED
THIS SEASON ON ITS HEAD, LET'S
TAKE A LOOK.
>> LAISSEZ LE BON TEMPS ROULER.
LET THE GOOD TIMES ROLL.
MY DRAG IS THAT REAL SOUTHERN
DRAG-OUT STYLE OF DRAG.
>> PROVE TO US THAT YOU'RE A
CHAMPION.
>> NOT ONLY HAVE YOU GUYS TAUGHT
ME HOW TO BE A BETTER
ENTERTAINER BUT YOU HAVE TAUGHT
ME HOW TO BE A BETTER PERSON.
AND $100,000.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> YES, LOUISIANA GLAMOUR.
WHEN YOU CAME TO "DRAG RACE,"
YOU HAD QUIT TWO JOBS TO BE ON
THE SHOW.
HOW MANY JOBS DO YOU HAVE NOW?
>> I HAVE ONE JOB, RU.
AND I'M A FULL-TIME DRAG QUEEN!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THAT'S WHAT'S UP.
MEET YOU?
>> OH, MY GOD.
THE FIRST TIME IN NEW YORK, I'M
IN TIMES SQUARE.
AND THE SHORTEST LITTLE HISPANIC
WOMAN STOPPED ME IN THE STREET,
AND SHE JUST INSTANTLY STARTED
CRYING.
>> WOW.
>> SHE EXPLAINED TO ME THAT I
REPRESENTED ALL OF THE PEOPLE IN
THE WORLD TO HER THAT ARE OUT
THERE STRUGGLING TO MAKE ENDS
MEET AND WHO HAVE A DREAM, AND
THE DREAM HAS COME TRUE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
DREAMS COME TRUE, Y'ALL.
DREAMS COME TRUE.
>> AND SPEAKING OF DREAMS, THE
DREAM GIRLS LIP-SYNC THAT YOU
DID -- OH, HONEY.
THAT WAS LEGENDARY.
AND I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE WHO
THOUGHT SO.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
>> YOU, CHI CHI DEVAYNE, ARE A
TRUE INSPIRATION.
I TELL YOU THAT
YOUR HEARTFELT RENDITION, HONEY,
RIGHT AFTER YOU AND I HIT OUR
HIGH NOTE, HONEY, YOU GAVE ME
LIFE, AND I'M GOING TO MAKE YOU
AN OFFICIAL DREAM GIRL.
[ CHEERS AND PLAUZ ]
>> DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING ELSE
YOU'D LIKE TO SAY?
>> THANK YOU FROM THE BOTTOM OF
MY HEART.
YOU HAVE CHANGED MY LIFE.
FOREVER.
YOU MADE MY DREAM COME TRUE.
>> THAT IS THE SWEETEST THING.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
I'VE BEEN WATCHING YOU FOR A
LONG TIME.
AND TO HAVE YOU FINALLY ON THE
SHOW IS REALLY MY HONOR.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT.
NOW IT'S TIME TO ANNOUNCE THE
WINNER OF THIS YEAR'S MISS
CONGENIALITY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL THE WAY FROM MOSCOW BY WAY
OF BOSTON AND A PIT STOP, IT'S
KATIA.
떰
DOWN DOWN DOWN DOWN
>> HI, KATIA.
>> HI, RU.
LISTEN, I BROUGHT YOU SOME
WATER.
ARE YOU THIRSTY?
>> SO KATIA, WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN
UP TO?
>> OH, MY GOD, WHAT HAVEN'T I
BEEN UP TO?
LISTEN, I LEARNED HORSEBACK
RIDING.
I'VE BEEN DOING MACRAME.
I VISITED, LIKE, SIX OUT OF THE
12 CONTINENTS IN THE WORLD.
IT'S BEEN A WHIRLWIND.
>> IS THERE SOMETHING YOU WANT
TO TELL ME?
>> OKAY, YEAH, I'M NOT
TECHNICALLY BISEXUAL.
I MEAN, I'M OPEN.
>> NO, NO, NO, NO.
>> I AM OPEN -- LISTEN --
>> I'M TALKING ABOUT WHAT YOU
CAME OUT HERE FOR.
REMEMBER?
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
OH, LOOK AT THIS THING.
OH, YEAH.
WILL YOU HOLD THIS WATER?
>> YEAH, SURE.
>> THE WINNER OF SEASON 8 MISS
CONGENIALITY AND A CASH PRIZE OF
$5,000, COURTESY OF THE ALL-NEW
FIAT 500X CROSSOVER -- CYNTHIA
LEE FONTAINE!
떰
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> CYNTHIA, IS THERE ANYTHING
YOU'D LIKE TO SAY?
>> THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT FOR ME
BECAUSE EXPERIENCING CANCER GAVE
ME THE OPPORTUNITY NOT ONLY TO
BE STRONGER THAN EVER AND
REPRESENT MY COMMUNITY THE BEST
THAT I CAN, AND THE ONLY WAY
THAT WE CAN DO THAT IS FUNNY AND
SHOWING THE CUCKOO TO THE WORLD.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU TO MY FANS.
>> THANK YOU.
AND THANKS TO ALL OF YOU FOR
VOTING.
>>> ARE YOU TEAM BOB?
TEAM KIM CHI?
OR TEAM NAOMI?
SOUND OFF NOW.
NEXT, "DRAG RACE" LEGENDS ARE
STANDING BY TO HELP RU CROWN
AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR
WHEN THE GRAND FINALE OF
"RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE" TOPS OFF.
떰
>>> WELCOME BACK TO THE GRAND
FINALE OF "RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE."
ALL RISE FOR YOUR TOP THREE.
BOB THE DRAG QUEEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
KIM CHI.
NAOMI SMALLS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
떰
THERE ARE ONLY EIGHT PEOPLE ON
EARTH THAT KNOW WHAT IT FEELS
LIKE TO BE THE WINNER OF
"RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE."
AND THEY'RE ALL HERE TONIGHT TO
SHARE THEIR WORDS OF WISDOM.
WELCOME BACK MY CHAMPIONS.
BEBE ZAHARA.
>> CAMEROON, WELCOME TO THE
ROYAL FAMILY, DARLING.
REMEMBER, ALWAYS GIVE THEM FACE,
FACE, FACE AND MORE FACE.
>> TYRA SANCHEZ.
>> BE THE BIGGEST, BADDEST BITCH
OF THEM ALL.
A ROYAL BITCH.
LOVE AMERICA'S SWEETHEART.
>> RAJA.
>> IN THE PROPHETIC WORDS,
OF A WISE ONE,
EXPRESS YOURSELF.
IT IS NOW YOUR DUTY TO HONOR A
DIVINE LEGACY AND TO LEAVE AN
INDELIBLE IMPRINT IN HERSTORY.
>> SHARON.
>> MY ADVICE, JUST BE YOURSELF.
WELL, UNLESS NOBODY LIKES YOU.
IN THAT CASE, JUST --
>> MICHAELS.
SNAP OUT OF IT, LADIES.
JUST DO YOU.
OR WHEN IT DOUBT, JUST DO CHER.
BITCH!
>> WHEN THE BITCHES COME FOR
YOU, MURDER THEM WITH KINDNESS.
AND DON'T FORGET, THE BEST THING
ABOUT PONTOON SEASON IS IT
HAPPENS ANNUALLY.
>> BIANCA DEL RIO.
>> I'VE GOT SOME ADVICE FOR THIS
YEAR'S WINNER.
ENJOY THE RIDE.
AND PAY YOUR DAMN TAXES.
RIGHT, SHARON?
JINX.
RAJA.
>> AND AMERICA'S REIGNING DRAG
SUPERSTAR, VIOLET SHOTSKI!
떰
>> WOW!
VIOLET, WHAT HAS YOUR YEAR BEEN
LIKE?
>> MY YEAR HAS BEEN INCREDIBLE.
I'VE WORKED WITH SOME OF THE
BEST PEOPLE IN THE INDUSTRY, THE
FASHION WORLD, THE BURLESQUE
WORLD, THE ART WORLD.
I'VE GOTTEN VALIDATION FROM
PEOPLE THAT I'VE RESPECTED FOR
YEARS AND YEARS AND YEARS.
IT'S BEEN THE MOST PERSONALLY
GRATIFYING YEAR OF MY LIFE.
I AM SO THANKFUL TO RuPAUL, ALL
THE FANS, THANK YOU FROM THE
BOTTOM OF MY HEART.
I LOVE YOU GUYS.
>> THANK YOU, VIOLET.
SO IN ADDITION TO THE TITLE OF
AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG SUPERSTAR,
THE WINNER OF RuPAUL'S DRAG RACE
WILL RECEIVE A CROWN AND SCEPTER
PROVIDED BY FIERCE DRAG JEWELS,
A SUPPLY OF MAKEUP FROM
ANASTASIA BEVERLY HILLS, AND A
CASH PRIZE OF $100,000.
NOW, THE TIME HAS COME TO CROWN
OUR QUEEN.
BOB THE DRAG QUEEN.
KIM CHI.
NAOMI SMALLS.
AS ALWAYS, I CONSULTED WITH THE
JUDGES AND THE FANS.
BUT THE FINAL DECISION IS MINE
TO MAKE.
THE WINNER OF "RuPAUL'S DRAG
RACE," AMERICA'S NEXT DRAG
SUPERSTAR IS -- BOB THE DRAG
QUEEN.
떰
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
MY QUEEN, IS THERE ANYTHING YOU
HAVE TO SAY?
>> YES.
I HAVE TOO MUCH TO SAY.
BUT I'M GOING TO KEEP IT TO ONE
THING.
TAKE WHATEVER YOU LOVE ABOUT
YOURSELF AND WALK IT TO THE
WORLD!
EVERY SINGLE MOMENT
IT WILL COME TRUE
>> LISTEN, IF YOU CAN'T LOVE
YOURSELF, HOW IN THE HELL ARE
YOU GOING TO LOVE SOMEBODY ELSE?
CAN I GET AN AMEN UP IN HERE?
>> AMEN!
>> ALL RIGHT!
NOW, LET THE MUSIC PLAY!
EVERYTHING I WANNABE
ALL THE POSSIBILITY
IT WILL COME TRUE