Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
I wanna introduce you
to a fabulous queen
who will be joining you
in the competition.
Uh-uh!
Someone I don't think
got a fair chance last week.
Hello!
Elliott with 2 Ts.
Guess who's back in the house?
What the fuck?
♪ Condragulations,
you're number one ♪
♪ Condragulations ♪
Olivia Lux.
You're somebody that
I could not take my eye off of.
Symone.
You're fierce,
you're filled with attitude.
You've got star quality.
This week, there are no bottoms.
The rest of you are safe.
Symone, you're a winner, baby.
My gosh.
Girl.
Oh, my God.
We are just walking back into
the werkroom and guess what?
We're all safe.
This is, like,
RuPaul's Drag Race Tornado.
Like, there's a cow flying by.
Like, here comes a fence.
Twister. I'm, like, what next?
Y'all just did that.
Oh, my God, y'all!
Congratulations.
Thank y'all.
So, Miss Symone,
the first official winner.
Uh-huh.
How does it feel
to get the critique
that you got from RuPaul?
- Oh, my God.
- About your star quality?
It felt amazing.
It felt like I had...
Like, one of the things
I came here to do
and I've been validated to do,
and it came from RuPaul,
like, one of my idols, one
of the people I've looked up to.
So if nothing else happens...
But it will...
If nothing else happens,
that's all I needed.
I could die happy.
I mean, kudos to my sis
for getting that,
you know, that critique,
but, bitch, I know I'm the shit.
That motivates me
to even go harder.
Like, I can't get
complacent at all.
I can't even tell you,
when Ru said that
we were all safe,
like, literally,
like I couldn't handle it.
My heart was just, like, uh.
Going into elimination,
I really thought
that me and you were gonna
go head-to-head tonight.
Me, too.
All that crying for nothing.
Girl, I fucked
that performance up,
and I just felt so upset,
because I came here to prove
to America and the world
that Kandy Muse
is a fierce entertainer.
I need to step it up.
I couldn't see,
now getting to know you guys,
us voting anybody...
Each other off at all.
- I couldn't see that.
- It's, like, so crazy to me.
- That's insane.
- Yeah.
But that said, now knowing
what they did to you,
if you had to pick one girl
out of that group to send home,
who would it be and why?
I would be happy
to see them all go home.
Okay?
One by one.
The porkchop group doesn't
even know that I'm still here.
They think that
they sent my ass packing.
But RuPaul felt the need
to put me
in the winner's circle, girl.
What's up, B squad?
I just wonder when the fuck
they're showing up, though.
What are they doing,
when they're showing up,
when are they gonna go home?
Whenever we cross
these little monsters,
they're probably
gonna have a lot to prove.
That must be a weird place
to start the competition,
already a notch down.
So now they're gonna have to
double-notch to get ahead of us.
You gotta jump twice as high
to beat me,
and I am a tall bitch.
This is the first week,
so we all have to put
our hands in here real quick.
- Have a moment!
- Come on, bitches.
One, two, three,
winner's circle!
When the other girls come back,
it's gonna be
a little difficult,
because we named ourselves
the winner's circle.
Tina, you need help?
I'm fine. Just leave me!
So there's only another name
for their group.
I'm up!
Eee.
The winner of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100.000.
With extra-special
guest judge Nicole Byer.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
Whoa!
Oh, my God, we're here!
Yeah!
Let's do it. We back!
- Hi, werkroom!
- We all up in here!
Going into the werkroom,
it's a new day,
and it's six of us.
We're excited,
but at the same time,
you know, we feel
for that seventh person,
because we know we all worked
hard to get to this point.
But when you give a person
a second chance to fight,
oh, the fight is on.
Aren't you so grateful,
like, we're here?
I've never been more grateful
to be anywhere in my life.
The fact that we get
a second chance is crazy.
Second chance!
There is a fire now
that is definitely ignited.
Which gives us an advantage.
We had a really good
wake-up call,
and the other group
has not felt that yet.
So I don't think they're ready
for what our group
is gonna bring.
It's so crazy seeing
all of you out of drag.
I'm just gonna say it.
I don't know
how the other team looks,
but I'm gonna say
we've definitely
got the trade of the season
right in here.
- Yeah.
- We got some snacks here.
- Oh, my gosh.
Everyone is really cute.
For me, it's a little difficult
to focus sometimes,
because I'm just like, wow, mm.
And it's great, because
I'm the tallest of them,
so I just get to look down
at all the gorgeous little...
Little... little nuggets.
Come on, losers!
Ooh, girl!
She done already
done had herses!
Last time this happened,
it didn't go well.
My queens,
sometimes an early win
can make you soft and easy.
But we don't do nothin'
'round here soft and easy.
We like to do it hard and rough.
- Period.
- Word.
So make me proud, Mary,
and you can become
a Drag Race phenomenon-
non-non-non-non-non-non.
- Phenomenon!
- Phenomen-omenom-enon!
Hello, hello, hello!
- Whoo!
- She's a snack!
Welcome to RuPaul's Drag Race,
the emotional
rollercoaster edition.
Now, do you all feel
a little dizzy
after what we put you through?
- Of course.
- Yes.
If I gave you a little scare,
I'm sorry.
But sometimes the best way
to get where you are going
is a firm kick in the tuchus.
Now, in your past I'm sure
you've survived things
a whole lot crazier than
our lip sync for your life.
True.
And it's that drive
and determination
that can make you
a winner, baby.
Ladies, I know you are ready
for your first mini-challenge,
am I right?
- Let's do it!
- Okay.
So get ready to serve two
different looks on the runway
in a killer fashion show
we're calling Lady and the Vamp.
#DragRace.
I'm really excited,
because I am a look queen,
and this is what I do best.
When I walk out on the runway,
their jaws will drop.
Remember, top designers
and fashion editors
are watching this show,
so show us what you got.
I will see you on the runway.
Let's go.
Aah!
- I got it!
- Get the drag!
All right, y'all,
I'm about to do something
I've never done before:
paint a face in one hour.
Oh, Kahmora. Okay,
let me just say this.
Shut up!
Kahmora is notoriously known
in Chicago
for taking, like, maybe,
what, five, six hours?
Oh, my God, shut up!
Five or six hours?
I love my sister Kahmora
to death,
but it's this kind of joke
amongst the rest of our cast
whenever we're working
with Kahmora,
is that, oh,
our call time is 10:30?
Oh, she started getting ready
after lunch.
Girl, beauty can't be rushed,
but today it will have to.
Girl, listen, you are
a beautiful woman,
but it does not look like you're
wearing five hours of makeup.
- Exactly.
- It's not caked on.
I'm that good at blending, huh?
I like to just splat it on
and be done with it.
It's like a process for me,
you know?
It's a very spiritual
transformation.
I like to take my time.
Sis, we're on Drag Race.
It's not called Drag Walk.
I'm a little wary
to see what the other group's
gonna be like.
They've already got their noses
in the air a bit, I'm sure,
from winning that lip sync.
Ladies, promise me
that the winner's gonna be
from our group, okay?
- She's right here.
- Ooh!
I ain't mad at you!
I am.
Oh, my God,
I look so gross. Eew.
This is the biggest
struggle bus ever,
and I feel like
the hot mess express.
Oh, I'm doomed.
I'm just, like, girl,
get it together.
Okay. Fuck!
Aah! I'm freaking out.
I hear another "ugh."
Aah! Oh, my God. Fuck.
She's over there losing it.
She's just overwhelmed.
I'm scared, Denali.
You'll be okay, baby.
Don't get hung up on,
like, the small details.
Just keep going.
Oh, fuck.
We're on a strict time limit.
I mean, the bitch is stunning,
but if she can't
get ready in time,
I don't know if she's
gonna make it to the runway.
Oh, fuck.
- Oh, my.
- Jesus Christ.
Everybody set, we're rolling.
Here we go.
In five, four, three, two...
I look around.
All the other queens are poof.
They have left
for the main stage.
Like, man, this is
my second chance,
and I'm already screwing it up.
It's sinking in. I blew it.
Judges, stand by.
30 seconds to runway.
So it's time
for the mini-challenge,
and it is a fashion show,
and I am so fucking excited.
The theme is Lady and the Vamp.
So I hope
we're all ready for this.
Category is Lady.
Up first, Denali.
Lady Sings the Blues.
This look is classic Denali.
I love being
that ice queen girl,
so any shade of blue
is my color.
It is just a blue
dainty doll dress dream,
and I'm also in
fully rhinestoned blue pumps
on my dainty little feet.
She's got
a killer case of blue leg.
There's an ointment
that will clear that right up.
I wanted to give
a shoutout to my Alaskan roots
and state flower,
the forget-me-not.
So to be covered in this
blue, feminine forget-me-nots
made me feel my full fantasy.
So all this time,
Smurfette was a drag queen?
Joey Jay.
Don't you hate when
you miss a spot shaving?
I don't wear wigs very often,
so I'm giving some classic
Joey Jay buzz cut realness.
I've got my shades on
because the sunlight
is just so bright,
but so am I.
I'm wearing a vest.
The boots go all the way
up to my thigh.
I'm out running errands,
my kids are off at daycare.
I'm feeling good.
Is she fur real?
I'll take one, and I'm
wearing it to bear week.
Rosé.
Not right now, thanks.
I'm working.
Oh, honey,
she is arty for the party.
Rosé's lady runway
is a Moschino-inspired
paper doll fantasy.
I'm serving bright colors,
lots of geometry.
This is a hand-painted dress
with a matching bag.
Those kidney-shaped sleeves
scream "I'm an organ donor."
I've donated an organ before.
- Have you?
- Yes.
I'm not usually a queen
who tends to be ladylike,
but, bitch, I feel like
a woman right now.
And my ass has a huge secret.
"Osé." Hmm. Who's Osé?
Oh!
She saw this in the store
and said, "Oh, it has
my name on it!"
Tamisha Iman.
- Ooh, ooh, I love harem pants.
- Mm-hmm.
My look is very
summertime by the pool.
I got on my lace flowing coat,
my very Joan Crawford look,
you know, with my Capri pants
and I'm jeweled,
because you ain't drag
if you ain't got no stones on.
I'm looking rich,
I'm looking expensive.
If they would have got in close,
they would have smelled
the Chanel that I was wearing.
Gorgeous.
This color
is called "dazzleberry."
I was thinking "dingleberry."
Tastiest kind of berry.
She is the fuchsia of drag.
Idica? Huh. Utica.
Balls to the wall.
Oh, my cat will love this look.
My dog will love this look.
So this is my lady fantasy,
and this is the most classic
Utica you can get.
Balls, balls, balls,
balls, ballsity-balls,
fresh out of the playpen
ball pit from McDonald's.
And I am living
my mod sixties fantasy.
It's about the goof,
the woof, and the aloof.
If I put a quarter in her slot,
do I get a gumball?
I don't know what
will come out of that slot.
Y'all, now that's a bubble butt.
Let's roll, please.
Kahmora Hall.
Ooh, girl,
Kahmora has all the tea.
I barely made it
on time to the runway,
but I have to stand tall
and don't show them any fear.
And so I am just smiling
and looking beautiful.
I am serving you Kate Middleton
going out to lunch
with the queen.
I am taking my time so
the judges can see this dress.
It's very fifties
Christian Dior.
I've got this
cute little low bun on,
with a matching fascinator.
I want them to have
a sip of this tea.
Smells like Earl... Earl Grey.
Earl Gay.
Category is V-A-M-P.
Vamp!
Snap out of it!
First up, Denali.
She is singed for the gods.
50 shades of cray.
For the vampy runway,
I'm giving you
Moschino fall 2016.
Jeremy Scott
did an entire runway
of women emerging
from a burned ballroom.
Somebody's drunk uncle spilled
his drink on the candelabra,
the whole place
went up in flames,
and I am emerging now,
but still looking fierce.
You know, I don't know
if you guys noticed,
but in a certain light,
you can sort of
see through her dress.
Just a little bit.
Joey Jay.
- Joey Jay!
Yeah, honey, she just dropped
the kids off at the strip club.
I'm giving you Game of Thrones,
scale sleeve,
dragons are sleeping,
it's time to go out
with my little witches.
We're gonna kiki.
I'm giving you
a black silhouette,
and I've got these stupid,
ignorant earrings,
with chain and spikes on them.
I can't whip your ass, but I
look like I can fuck you up.
You got a backyard
for that swing, baby?
Yes, honey,
the dominatrix sleeps tonight.
Rosé.
Welcome to the main cage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
There are some looks
that you put on
and you just know that
nobody can tell you shit.
That's how I feel in this.
It's absolutely
fucking everything.
It is Alexander McQueen
inspired.
I feel like the high priestess
at a funeral
who's about to go out
and get a cocktail
by herself at 6 A.M.
I can never find
the switch on this lamp.
Yeah, I know.
Does anyone still wear
a lazy Susan?
Tamisha Iman.
All right, Miss Hairy J. Blige.
This is the hairway to heaven.
You wanted vamp,
I'm giving you the vampiest
of vamp: Elvira.
I took it to the next level,
though,
because in Atlanta, we like
weaves, we like long hair.
But if I'm gonna do
a hair costume,
I'm gonna do
a full hair costume.
So I'm rocking 84 inches
on this runway.
This is definitely the D-I-V-A.
I am totally
the diva of the night.
She's not just
the hair club president.
She's also a client.
You don't have to brush.
Slow down.
Okay, come on, Kahmora Hall,
giving us
Miss Sonia Rock-ay-elle.
Kahmora is serving you dark lady
on the prowl for her next meal.
I feel very sultry.
I got my wet blood orange hair,
I got my vintage
Mugler dress on,
with a Dracula collar top.
And at the waist,
I am sparkling with Swarovski.
Like, Kahmora loves
a good sparkle.
Who's ready for a bite of this?
Now, is that
a Cross-Your-Heart bra?
She's losing her
religion right before our eyes.
Utica.
Well, her balls
have finally dropped.
For this vamp catwalk,
I am bringing the attitude
of I own the night.
I am serving elastic fantastic
with this Edwardian feel
and this burgundy dream
as I creep down the runway.
I love to play
with the light and dark
within my fashions
and within myself.
This is a prime example
of what I do best.
Yay, now we'll get
all the channels.
Ru, wanna go to
the after-party with me?
Well, are you gonna
be wearing that?
Yeah.
Whoo!
- Whoo, mama.
- All right.
Mini-challenge, good.
- Check.
- We did it.
Now get me outta this geish!
We are back in the werkroom,
and I just feel, like,
a sense of relief.
I barely made it on time
for the runway,
but in the end,
I did feel really beautiful,
and I'm glad that
I was able to show the judges
that, hey, this is
what I'm bringing.
And that was just
the mini-challenge.
Like, that felt like a pretty
big fucking mini-challenge.
It felt like
a real challenge to me.
But now I feel like I'm here.
I have arrived.
We're here, bitch.
We're all here.
I feel like I was finally able
to walk in front of RuPaul,
like, feeling good.
- Comfortable.
- Feeling prepared.
Not just some, like, drag bus
that I was pushed in front of.
- Right.
- Not a drag bus.
I think a big catalyst for that
is that I feel like
I have sisters in y'all.
- Exactly.
- It's so nice.
I know we're competing,
obviously,
but I'm not, like...
I'm not so wound up by that.
- Right.
- Well, that's what I came for.
You came for sisterhood?
Then I'll take the crown, okay?
I've been in the business
a long time.
A lot of pageants under my belt.
How many? How many pageants
have you done?
Oh, my God, I've done over...
At least 200 pageants, and I...
You're fucking kidding.
200 pageants?
Yeah, I've won
at least about 95.
- Are you serious?
- 95?
Been doing it 30 years.
Tamisha, if you don't mind,
like, how old are you?
I'm 49.
- 49.
- Wow.
Oh, we got some prehistoric
ladies up in here.
Damn.
49 years young.
You must have had
a skin transplant, bitch.
Thank you.
That skin
does not look 49 years old.
You might cut into it
and find rings like a tree,
but the outside is nice.
Okay, how old are we? 25.
I'm 28.
- I'm 31.
- 28.
All of you are younger
than my biological kids.
That's crazy.
You have kids?
Like, biological kids?
Yeah, I have three.
You have kids?
- That's everything.
- Okay.
I cannot fucking believe
Tamisha also has literal
biological children.
Her pussy is literally on fire,
because several humans
have popped out of it, bitch.
Do we know how old
any of the other girls are?
I know they're not 49.
It's just crazy,
because everyone else
is so much younger than myself.
These are babies.
But guess what?
Age is just a number.
I haven't lasted
for 30 years for nothing.
I'm a bad B,
and you're gonna see it.
Hey, supermodels.
- Uh-oh!
- Hey, Ru!
Ladies, for your first
maxi-challenge,
you'll be performing
the song Phenomenon,
an original anthem
from the RuPaul's Drag Race
Live in Vegas soundtrack.
- Oh!
And this week, queens are wild
as each of you needs to write
your own original verse.
Okay? Move over, Britney Spears.
Okay.
Then you'll work together
to create choreography
that says, bitch,
I'm sickening, no?
This is the kind of shit
I do back in New York.
I am a singer, I am a dancer,
and there is a whole bonfire
under my ass
after almost being
sent home last week.
I have got to slay
this challenge.
Queens, this is your chance
to show the world
that you are a phenomenon.
- Hello.
- That's right.
Racers, start your engines,
and may the best drag queen win.
Are you guys, like,
singing or rapping?
I'm doing both.
- You're doing both?
- Both?
I'm just excited
to now be, like,
let me show you
what I can actually do.
We're all writing
our own verses,
and at this point,
there's a passion
that's ignited from losing
the first lip sync.
When I start
to get mad at myself
is when I push myself
even harder.
It's definitely something
that athletes do a lot.
So this is my redemption moment.
I'm gonna show
what I am capable of.
What are you doing, Rosé?
- I'm gonna sing.
- You're singing!
- She can sing.
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I feel like
I should use my chops
and put my musical foot forward.
Are you sure, though?
Do you think
that's a wise decision?
Yes, I do.
Utica, what you gonna do?
This farm girl's gonna rap.
- Shut up.
- Okay.
♪ Old McDonald had a farm ♪
I don't have a lot of experience
with writing lyrics.
This is my first time.
But I'm a weird queen,
and weird lyrics kinda
have to coincide with that.
I'm not a singer or a rapper,
but I'm gay.
So I'm just gonna take that
and, like, run with it.
I don't write music,
but I'm gay as fuck.
I'm gonna shit rainbows
and glitter,
and it's gonna be everything.
Okay, so we also have to
come up with choreo for this.
Is anybody not a dancer?
I am not a dancer.
I have, like, two left feet.
My experience
is mostly in modern dance.
- Word!
- Really?
So it's a lot of,
like, clean lines,
squishing the grapefruit,
praise the sun.
Open your pores
and run in circles.
Exactly.
You know, I'm a choreographer,
I'm a dancer.
But keep in mind these babies
are 20 years younger than me.
And there's certain things
right now physically
I can't do
that I used to be able to do.
So I'll follow their lead.
Well, who's a dancer?
Raise your hand.
Who's a dancer?
This is, like, what I do
outside of drag
is I'm a choreographer.
Yeah, we've talked.
Like, we have
in experience choreographing.
Is anybody else, like,
choreographing before?
Yeah, I used to teach
ballroom for six years.
Okay, cool.
In terms of ensemble choreo,
we should definitely
keep it simple
so that we all look the most...
We can just take
the choreography from the chorus
and copy and paste it
for the next one.
We can copy/paste it, but,
like, switch up our formations.
Something that's really
important to me
when I choreograph
is just making sure
things grow and grow.
Yes.
Three of us are dancers
and choreographers.
It's me, Rosé, and Joey Jay.
But outside of drag, I am
a professional choreographer
for both dance
and figure skating.
So I really wanna
take this delegation role.
Six is a good number, too,
because even numbers
are a lot easier to work with.
Yeah, honestly, though,
on that stage, so is five.
I'd also love
to use the catwalk.
Where they can have
their moment on one side,
while the other five
are in a formation on the other.
I know what I'm capable of,
and so I am not backing down.
- All right.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Let's go, let's go.
- Time to choreo.
Let's do this. It is now time
to figure out choreography
for our Phenomenon track.
I'm a professional
choreographer,
so I know I can take charge.
But I am a little nervous
about some of the other girls.
When it comes to a group show,
if there's one bad egg,
it can bring
the whole team down.
Okay, divas, we got 60 minutes.
So you think we can kind of
take it from the top
and block
something simple there?
So it's gonna go
five, six, seven, eight.
We can all start to walk on...
Everyone feel comfortable
with right foot?
I definitely feel Denali
trying to take the lead,
but trust me,
if it's not feeling cute,
I'm gonna step in
and say something.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One. Perfect. That's great.
Are we gonna keep that speed?
One, two, three, four.
Well, let's milk that.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven...
Can we do one, two,
three, four, five?
Girl, we have 60 minutes,
and I gotta get this done.
Unh! Let me do this.
What do you think about
not going on the first one?
So it could be, like,
one, two, three, four.
Why don't we just slo-mo that
five, six, seven, eight?
I see that,
but I want us to build
and not kind of slow down.
Rosé's like, "And
I think we should do this,
and what about this,"
and Denali's like,
"Okay, we gonna do this
and this and this."
And Joey's like,
"Well, hey, I'm here, too,
so we're gonna do
this, this, this."
They are in competition
right now.
I'm, like, no, bitches,
that's not gonna work.
You can't have
too many cooks in the kitchen.
too many choreographers
on the dance floor.
Five, six, seven, eight,
and then hit the pose.
How many rows are there of us?
Could we ripple the head?
Should we do a half-circle?
Let's stay in a line.
No. You could go
in front of her,
because you're
so much, like, shorter.
And maybe it's like
a shhhhw pose.
Who do I look at?
Who do I listen to?
Five, six, quick now,
one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, pivot.
- Missed it.
- Does that make sense?
No.
Kahmora is blank-faced.
Kahmora is actually playing
ping-pong ball with her eyes.
She's...
Can you do the pivot again?
So it's like you're gonna step,
and you see someone
you don't like,
and you're like, oh, shit.
And then you're, like,
ball-change going the other way.
Kahmora is really struggling.
She's not taking in
the choreography
as quickly as the rest of us,
and she's focusing on
the little details
when we need to be focusing
on the big picture.
Three, four, five, six, fast.
- One, two, three, four...
- Oh, I messed up already.
I messed up, I messed up!
Wait, I messed up.
Keep in mind we have someone
who's not a dancer.
So we have to keep that in mind.
- Right, no, no, no, yeah.
- I don't wanna confuse her.
Can we lift her?
Kahmora is not a dancer,
but she's stunning.
So I thought let's
not give her choreography.
Let's pick the bitch up.
She don't gotta do anything.
All you have to do
is really tense your armpits.
Five, six, seven, eight.
I'm so tall!
Oh, my God, you're so light.
So then for mine, I wanna try,
like, a trick thingy.
I'll take your hand.
I wanna, like...
like, spin like that,
and then I can just end.
Oh, bitch,
this is Cirque du Soleil.
We all over the place. Okay.
I'm in the daycare,
and the children are excited.
I don't know
who gave them this candy.
On one. One.
Let's all do the right.
- Or I could do the left, yeah.
- That would look cool,
to do one and one,
and we're both out here.
Are we splitting?
No, you're behind.
You guys, maybe you can.
I think she could be behind.
This ain't gonna work.
When you're trying
to choreograph,
you have to stay focused
and get the job done.
All of a sudden
it's 10 minutes left,
and it's not getting done.
From right where we are,
we should just point.
Boom, from Russia to L.A.
Why don't we all point
in a different direction?
With, like, different levels?
Like, boom, Russia.
Oh, should I just,
like, stay down?
From Russia to...
Just walk and count.
Oh, yeah, we could just march.
Switch, you go over there.
Y'all start first
and we come second.
Five, six, seven, eight.
From Russia.
You should be going with her.
- You're gonna switch with me.
- Okay, I got it.
This is a good idea.
Listen to her.
Mama Tamisha, she is, like,
okay, let the pro come in,
and let me tell you
what needs to be done.
Five, six, ready, go.
From the... nuh-uh-uh. We're next.
- We're after that, okay?
- I'm living for it.
One more time, y'all. Ready, go.
From Russia to UK.
Sashay, shantay, you stay.
Why don't we just be,
like, sashay, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Sashay, shantay, you stay.
Listen, all we need to do
is "stay" together.
We got your line now.
One accord,
let's get on one accord.
- Okay.
- And in the end,
how about we walk in the circle
and tighten it
and come in to basically,
like a kind of windmill blob,
with, like, arms out.
Lord, I'm hoping
we pull this off.
But the way we're looking
right now,
I'm worried like hell
we all going home.
- Ooh-ee!
- All right, let's do it.
Today we are going
to be getting judged
on our dancing,
group-ass challenge
to RuPaul's song Phenomenon.
And, honey, I'm feeling
really good about this.
#Blessed.
I think this routine
is so strong.
They're gonna probably think
the other group
is the ones that went home
after the fact.
- Honestly.
- I agree.
I don't know what
the other girls did,
but I feel like ours
is real strong.
We were so fun
when working together.
We worked together, and we all,
you know, used our voices.
Are y'all serious?
I think sometimes
your confidence
can exceed your abilities.
On one hand, I'm appreciative
to see that they are hungry.
On the other hand, a bitch
is still scared to unpack.
Sorry. I don't know
how this is gonna go.
I'm already late.
- Kahmora.
- Yes, ma'am.
Make sure you breathe, baby.
- I know.
- Breathe.
There was
a lot going on yesterday,
just from struggling
to get to the runway on time.
And then, like, not being,
like, the dancer of the group,
I felt, like, a lot of pressure.
And I don't wanna let myself,
you girls, and the judges down.
Baby, guess what? We with you.
We understand.
Kahmora, you really impress me.
You're gonna slay.
Like, the support
you girls have given me
has been, like, amazing.
I wish I had this kind of
same support back home.
Like, don't get me wrong.
Like, my boyfriend does support
me in everything that I do.
But sometimes, like,
when I do come back
after, like, the gig,
like, sometimes
you do feel alone, you know?
I know my boyfriend
wouldn't want to date,
like, a full-time drag queen.
And so I think that's why
I kind of held myself back
in terms of first doing drag,
like, full-time.
I only do drag, like,
maybe once or twice a month.
How long have y'all
been together?
Eight years.
Holy shit, girl, word.
In gay years, that's a lifetime.
I try to keep,
like, my drag life
separate from,
like, our home life.
Like, whenever I do drag, I try
to do it, like, away from him.
I keep everything in,
like, my own storage unit.
Like, whenever I had
downtime at work,
I was always working on looks,
because I knew that my boyfriend
didn't wanna be around drag.
Sometimes I do feel like I'm
living, like, a double life.
It gets me, like, emotional.
Because I really wanna, like,
prove to him that I can do this.
- Mm-hmm.
- You can.
- You're here.
- You're gonna kick butt.
It's, like, you're sickening.
God, I just started
my makeup, too.
I just feel like my whole life
I've always been hiding,
like, a part of myself,
and minimizing my drag career
for others
has become, like, a hurdle
for me to get over
in this competition.
I just don't wanna let
anyone down again today,
so I'm just trying to, like...
Look, baby,
at the end of the day,
you're in a competition.
- Right.
- Don't let yourself down.
Just gotta worry about hottie.
Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you.
Tamisha's definitely
the mother of the group.
It's just nice
to have that, like,
mature spirit there with you,
and she is very comforting.
You're gonna make mistakes.
That's what makes you great.
We made a mistake,
and look where we are.
We're still here fighting.
My kids know that I have moments
when I'm good,
and I have moments
when I'm okay.
But at the end of the day,
I don't give up on me.
Right.
So I know you said you have,
like, biological children,
but, like, do you have
any drag kids?
Well, I started my dynasty,
the House of Iman.
Yes.
It actually started
when I started years ago.
All of my kids that
are in the pageant realm
are all national title holders.
Bitch!
But a lot of my babies
have passed on.
But we never let
their memories fade.
One of my daughters,
she has this famous video.
She's performing as Super Woman.
Wait, stop it!
Tandi Iman Dupree!
- That's your daughter?
- Yes.
- Are you kidding me?
- Yeah, Tandi's my daughter.
I'm so shook right now.
Tandi is the one that made
the lasting impression.
So at the end of the day,
if you see my legendary
daughter, then guess what?
You know what
Iman's drag is about.
She was very soft-spoken,
like, "Mama, I got an idea."
She was, like,
"I wanna fall out the ceiling."
So we orchestrated how she could
do it without hurting herself.
I don't know how she didn't,
because that's probably
the biggest drop I've ever seen.
My kids are amazing.
And I just wanted to show them,
you know, at the end of the day,
I'm still fighting
the good fight.
And if I can do it,
regardless
of what you go through,
you can do it.
You've shown me that, baby.
Oh, my God, absolutely.
And I'm not
your daughter, you know?
You're my sister, though,
and I appreciate that.
Yes, I am your sister. Forever.
Forever.
- Forever-ever?
- Forever-ever-ever.
Forever?
Yeah, phenomenom-enom-enon.
The sisterhood and the friends
that I'm making here,
it's so lovely.
But I did not come here
to make friends.
I devoted the time onstage
to the group.
But now it's time
to focus on me.
I think there's gonna be
a lot of that,
cultivating a group sensation,
and then figuring out
how to be the best one.
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
And what?
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage.
Now, did you know that drag
is all over the world?
And luckily, Ru,
there's an ointment for that.
And the hilarious Ross Mathews.
Now, do you consider yourself
a phenomenon?
Does fen-phen count?
Yes, it does.
Then, yes, thank you.
She's part of the family now.
Welcome back, Nicole Byer.
Oh, Ru, there's
no place like home.
I tried for days and days
to make my way back,
and then your producers
were like,
"Yeah, bitch, come on back."
You are always welcome.
Oh, thank you.
And bring Toto, too.
Okay.
This week,
we challenged our queens
to deliver
breakout performances,
singing and dancing
to the Drag Race Live anthem,
Phenomenon.
Racers, start your engines,
and may the best drag queen win.
And now the Season 13 edition
of Phenomenon.
Let's go.
♪ Move aside,
it's your girl Denali ♪
♪ I'm cold as ice,
hotter than a tamale ♪
♪ Keep up
and I'm Chi-town tough ♪
♪ Triple lutz on these sluts,
because I like it rough ♪
♪ I'm icy, spicy,
for you I'm too pricey ♪
♪ I'm going for the gold,
so Imma get a little feisty ♪
♪ I'm strong like a Megatron,
long like a marathon ♪
♪ AK to Babylon,
I'm the phenomenon ♪
♪ I'm a gay-ass bitch,
I'm Joey Jay ♪
♪ I do the grapevine splits,
I came to slay ♪
♪ I'm taking them out,
protocol ♪
♪ One by one,
I'm reppin' RuPaul ♪
♪ J-O-E-Y ♪
♪ What? J-A-Y ♪
♪ But where's your wig?
The million-dollar question ♪
♪ Please take it down
and let me give a lesson ♪
♪ From Russia to the UK ♪
♪ Thailand to Paraguay ♪
♪ Vegas, New York, L.A. ♪
♪ Sashay, shantay, you stay ♪
♪ Drag is all over the world ♪
♪ It's a phenomenon ♪
♪ It will live on and on ♪
♪ Drag is all over the world ♪
♪ It's a phenomenon ♪
♪ From the House of Hall,
Chicago's Mackie doll ♪
♪ Serving beads and face ♪
♪ I'm the mo-o-ost glamorous
in this race ♪
♪ The way my beauty shines,
Kahmora's gonna blind them ♪
♪ And snatch the crown-own ♪
♪ Uh, baby, pour a glass ♪
♪ Feast your eyes
on a bonnie lass ♪
♪ She's a fashion clown ♪
♪ Pretty, witty,
a bloke goes down ♪
♪ Highlights never fade ♪
♪ Can't wait to hear
you say it ♪
♪ The winner is Rosé, yeah ♪
♪ From Russia to the UK ♪
♪ Thailand to Paraguay ♪
♪ Vegas, New York, L.A. ♪
♪ Sashay, shantay, you stay ♪
♪ Drag is all over the world ♪
♪ It's a phenomenon ♪
♪ It will live on and on ♪
♪ Drag is all over the world ♪
♪ It's a phenomenon ♪
♪ Tamisha Iman
is coming for you ♪
♪ To show the girls
what I can do ♪
♪ Drag is my game,
and I do it well ♪
♪ That ATL peach
with a story to tell ♪
♪ Bent but not broken,
I'll fight to the end ♪
♪ That old-school diva
shall rise again ♪
♪ Going for the crown
is gonna be tough ♪
♪ But guess what, ladies?
I'm born for this stuff ♪
♪ Spreading love
from here to there ♪
♪ For my secret
is to toss my hair ♪
♪ There's not a bone
in my body ♪
♪ Gonna wiggle to the top,
wig-wiggle to the top, whoo ♪
♪ Utica may be a small town ♪
♪ Farm girl fit for a crown ♪
♪ Lightning striking you down ♪
♪ Strike a pose like that ♪
♪ Strike a pose
like that, whoo ♪
♪ Drag is all over the world ♪
♪ It's a phenomenon ♪
♪ It will live on and on ♪
♪ Drag is all over the world ♪
♪ It's a phenomenon ♪
Yes!
♪ Bring back my girls ♪
Category is
We're Here, We're Sheer.
Get Used To It.
First up, Denali.
It's like
a Georgia O'Keeffe fantasy.
I think you mean
Georgia O'Queef.
I'm serving you
high-fashion sheerness
and queerness.
Lavender on the body,
but black detailing
in the hair, earrings, shoes,
just for some contrast.
This look is inspired by
one of my favorite designers,
Iris van Herpen.
She does a lot of cool,
futuristic-type things.
I feel like
a breath of fresh air
and the woman of the future.
She looks like Nina Hagen.
Nina Haagen-Dazs.
There are
my anal beads: in her hair!
Joey Jay.
Fringe benefits, I see.
I wanted to really show
the Joey Jay
edgy side of things.
I've got my headband on.
No wig. Who dis?
I'm giving you, like,
Sia meets flapper
meets Prohibition ass shit.
Like, this is the sequined
poncho that you can't have.
It's mine.
I'm untouchable, girl.
It was easy. I just YouTubed
"what to do with half
a Liza Minnelli costume."
That reminds me.
I need to get a new Swiffer.
Kahmora Hall.
Kahmora Hall starring in Roots.
My look is a mix
between Cher at the Met Gala,
that iconic look
that Bob Mackie did,
meets a little bit
of Britney Spears' Toxic.
This is classic Kahmora Hall:
big hair, I'm wearing these
big-ass hubcaps on my ears,
a lot of rhinestones.
I wanna look so expensive
that they go broke
just looking at me.
Michelle,
you have your glasses on.
Is she wearing earrings?
I think I saw this
on Sonny and Sheer.
Rosé.
Finally, something to wear
if you have fat wrists.
This look speaks to
what Rosé does on the regular.
Baby, my legs
are all the way out.
I've got my baby pink hair,
which is a signature
option for Rosé.
And I'm playing with
a really fun silhouette.
I'm meeting flowing fabric
with hand-dyed plastic.
I am the only plastic
bubblegum princess
complete with cotton candy,
billowing sleeves.
I feel cute as a button
in this look.
Oh, it's like
a gay loofah fantasy.
Loofah? I hardly know ya.
Tamisha Iman.
Oh, the legend ball.
Sheerly you could see a diva.
You asked for sheer,
I'm giving you
just what you asked for,
but with glamour.
The gown is encrusted
with glitter dots all over,
so it's sparkling
from head to toe.
I added a little drama
on the front part
with the bustle.
The spotlight hits me
just right, as it always does,
and I'm walking into
the Golden Globe,
and I'm ready to accept
the award. Thank you.
Ugh, I have no jokes.
This is stunning.
It's a cross
between Diahann Carroll
and Lola Falana.
Mm.
Sheer brilliance.
Utica.
Guys, this makes me wanna scarf.
I literally was gonna say that.
I am flowing down this runway
in this watercolor eleganza.
I am giving you
this Stevie Nicks nod,
paying homage
to my beautiful mother,
who loves Fleetwood Mac,
and I am just feeling beautiful
and ready to cast a spell.
Very Sleevy Nicks.
Did you say "Sleevy Nicks?"
Yeah. Very Sleevy Nicks.
It's a landslide.
Welcome, queens.
It's time for
the judges' critiques.
Starting with Denali.
So we're gonna start
with your fashion.
You had ladykins,
and you had the vamp.
Ladykins, I liked the idea
because it almost
was a bit of a nod
to your ice skating.
I like how you paired
the yellow hair with the blue,
and I liked how you
brought it down there.
And then your vamp look
is so different.
If you didn't have
those dimples,
I would have been, like,
is this the same girl?
You really are showing us
that you are willing to express
yourself in different ways here.
Keeps us interested.
Tonight in your performance,
I couldn't take my eyes
off of you.
Your kicks are beautiful,
your splits are beautiful.
You have that gift that
you worked really hard for.
Very that.
And it's really amazing
to watch.
It's about time somebody rhymed
"triple lutz" with "sluts."
I was, like, ooh,
I'm a whore, too.
This is a friend. An ally.
Up next, Joey Jay.
In the flesh.
This is my favorite look
I've ever seen you in tonight.
Thank you.
I think it's so beautiful,
I think it's elevated,
I think it's fun, I think...
It's really stunning.
Ugh, I love it so much,
I just wanna, like,
hang it up in a door.
I love it. It's cute.
I think you're cute.
What a treat. I love it.
Oh!
You're actually
really exciting to watch.
You can tell that
you're a performer.
In your lyrics tonight,
you told me
that you don't wear wigs,
and to take a seat and learn.
Why?
I know a lot of people do drag
and they love
having that alter ego.
But when I look in the mirror
and I do wear a wig,
I don't necessarily
quite see myself.
Right now, I feel like Joey,
I feel like myself.
The first time I saw you
without a wig,
I thought, oh, I love that.
I think like Ongina.
It's iconic.
The second time I saw you
without a wig,
I thought, oh,
she did that again.
And the third time in a row,
I thought, really?
And then the fourth time,
now it's something.
I want you to do drag
however you do it.
Just make sure it's unique
and make sure it's gorgeous.
I love this hair.
I don't wanna change it.
But I definitely
would love to see versatility.
- Oh, get ready, sis.
- Good, bring it on.
Up next, Kahmora Hall.
Kahmora Hall, the strongest
earlobes in the business.
You look rich.
I would rob you in a heartbeat.
I would take everything
off of you.
You are beautiful.
You have impeccable taste.
Your ladykins look
was so proper.
That black velvet
was just stunning.
But...
Always a big "but."
Did you ever see that movie
Mannequin?
Kim Cattrall,
she was the mannequin.
She was beautiful,
and she would come to life
when Andrew McCarthy
would show up.
You need to come to life.
What I'm noticing
is that you love your outfits,
and I love that about you.
When I grew up, I would save
every freaking penny
to buy the sluttiest dresses
I could find
at Merry-Go-Round
in the Woodbridge Center Mall
in New Jersey.
This is what I fear
for you, Kahmora.
Sometimes, I feel like
there's just a walking outfit
devoid of personality.
You looked lost.
I was like, "Should I tell her
she's performing?"
But that being said,
if you're not a dancer,
lean into that.
Like, if you are nervous,
put it into your moves,
because then you can just
turn your nerves into comedy.
And according to your lyrics,
you're the most glamorous
in this race.
Take a look around, honey.
You've got some competition.
Where?
I think you've got
a personality. Look at you.
I do, I promise, I swear.
Do you and do you
the way you would wanna do you.
Understood.
Up next, Rosé.
Mmm, doesn't that
sound delicious?
Let's talk about your looks.
Your ladykins look
was so pop-art fun,
and I love that
you branded yourself.
This look tonight I think
is really fun and draggy.
I don't... I think it's, um...
Oh, I don't wanna say
the word "crafty,"
'cause I got dragged in the mud
for that last season.
But I think it's really draggy
and would work well
in, like, a club.
I love this look.
I think you look stunning.
It's not crafty!
Understood.
If there wasn't Plexiglas here,
I'd lean over and say it louder.
Tonight your performance was
where you really won me over.
You command
all of the attention.
You have stage presence,
you can dance, you can move.
Your voice is beautiful.
You're one of those, you know,
queens that I would go to watch,
and, oh, I'm just gonna
sit back and relax,
because I know she's got it.
I think you did
a really good job tonight.
Thanks.
All right, she looks like
one of the Supremes up here.
Tamisha Iman, I love this dress.
Thank you.
It is one of the most
beautiful dresses
that has ever graced this stage.
Oh, thank you.
Did you make this yourself?
- I make all my garments.
- Oh, my goodness.
I cannot believe
you make these yourself.
One day
you're gonna have a dress
on the Oscars red carpet.
Oh, I would love that.
You've really honed
the craft of drag.
This dress...
I want to rip it off of you.
But the only thing it would fit
would be, like, my neck,
and it wouldn't be
a good look out in public.
Stunning.
Let's talk about
the fashion show.
I loved both of them.
That ladykins color,
that raspberry
with that harem jumpsuit,
and that rich-looking robe
over it
was just beautiful and classy.
Thank you so much.
In your performance,
you're the most seasoned one,
and I felt a little
low-key from you.
I need you to make it bigger.
Because I know you come from
a long line of performers.
You have a very legendary
drag daughter.
My baby girl, Tandi Iman.
If she was still alive,
she would be one of your girls,
because she was
a phenomenal entertainer.
I don't know
if you've seen the video...
Oh, no, we've all seen the video
of her dropping
from the ceiling, yes.
Oh, yes.
She was a true entertainer.
Show these girls
what it's about, Tamisha.
Because when I see you here
tonight on this runway,
bitch, I cannot get
my eyes off of you.
So I'm gonna beg of you,
don't go small.
Let us know who Tamisha Iman is.
Okay.
Up next, Syracuse,
Schenectady, Utica.
What I like about you, Utica,
is you are a queen that marches
to the beat of her own drum.
The ladykins look is something
that Lady Bunny
would have worn as a toddler.
And then you came out
in your vamp look,
which was just as odd
and unique.
Your performance look
was also one of a kind.
You know how you drop acid
and you're like,
"What the fuck is that?"
That's you, and I like that.
They won't air that.
Your lyrics
talk about your savior.
Are you religious?
I am a Seventh-Day Adventist.
Okay.
And I'm definitely, like,
a bring-your-own-god
type of human,
so, like, no pressure,
but Jesus is great.
Whoo!
This winter, RuPaul's
Drag Race moves to TBN.
Watching you tonight
in your performance,
I think this is kind of
who Utica is,
quirky, weird, different,
and letting the spirit move her.
Just make sure
it all makes sense
and it's all together
where it should be.
There's something about queens
who are one of a kind.
Stay true to you.
Amen.
Thank you, Utica.
Thank you, RuPaul.
Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
While you untuck
in the werkroom,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right, now,
just between us phenoms,
whaddaya think?
Let's start with Denali.
The thing with Denali
that surprised me
was having the ice skating,
I knew she'd be able to perform,
but I didn't know if she could
bring it to the heels
instead of the blades.
And it was really, really fun
to watch her onstage tonight.
Denali's performance was joyful,
and I felt happier
after watching her.
I agree. Denali
has the charisma,
and she was spittin'
those words in her song.
Denali's somebody to watch.
Joey Jay.
- Joey Jay.
If you line up the four looks,
it's the same look.
It's almost like when you
order a pizza without cheese.
You're like, okay,
if you're hanging out with
your vegan friend, this is fine.
But I don't want that every day.
Wait a minute. They make pizza
without cheese?
I know. I was shocked, too.
- What's the point?
- I know, right?
Put anchovies on the pizza,
Joey Jay!
Where Joey Jay comes to life
is on the stage performing.
What a phenomenal dancer,
but I don't think
she really came through
with the lyrics
in the performance.
I just worry about redundancy.
But Joey said that she's got
some wigs in her arsenal
that she's ready to pull out.
I've got something else
in my arsenal.
I've heard.
Kahmora Hall.
Kahmora knows fashion,
and according to her lyrics,
that's kind of all
she cares about, is fashion.
She is so pretty, but her
performance reminded me
of when I go to the
grocery store without a list,
and you're just, like,
looking around kind of lost.
Totally.
SpaghettiOs? I would never.
And then you have SpaghettiOs
in your basket, you know?
She looks great
at the grocery store,
but she needs to put
some milk, some bread,
some eggs,
and butter on that list.
Kahmora looked unbelievable
tonight.
That dress is gorgeous.
But that dress would look good
on a wire hanger.
And you know what they say.
No more wire hangers!
Yeah, and you can't show up
and be a wire hanger
in this competition, right?
That's right.
She's got the taste level
to be here,
but now she's gotta
entertain us.
There's always time for Rosé.
Rosé came here to play.
Talk about a beautiful voice.
Rosé was truly
just captivating to watch,
and I think really
elevated her lyrics.
I thought tonight
she looked fantastic.
I know, Ross,
you think it was crafty.
I wanna be very clear.
It's not an insult.
It's just, you know,
you're standing next to
Kahmora and Tamisha,
and, yeah, compared to that,
it does look like
a toddler made it.
I see a drag queen
that kind of expresses herself
through what she's wearing,
and almost like her outfits
will tell us
what she's gonna give us.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I love queens like that.
She's an incredible queen.
I like her, and I'm truly
excited to see her blossom.
Tamisha Iman.
Oh, that dress truly
was so beautiful.
But I want a performance
like that dress.
I'm excited to see
what she's gonna do
when she unleashes the beast.
Because we know it's there.
Bitch, take your moment.
She's gotta learn that and
she's gotta learn it quickly,
because we're looking
for the Beyoncé.
We're looking for
the Diana Ross, you know?
We're looking for the star here.
It's weird you said Beyoncé
and Diana Ross.
You didn't say Michelle Visage.
Hold on, say it again.
Michelle what?
Hey, Siri?
Utica.
What I really enjoyed
was the complete opposite
in her vamps.
Like, she went all the way dark.
That's some dark web shit
that she did in the vamps look,
which is so ironic,
because she's so religious.
She looked like a doll
that I would pick up
and go, "I don't know,
it's a little scary,
but I think I'll play with it."
And then in her performance,
I thought she was
really fun to watch.
And then tonight on the runway,
I didn't love it.
It was kind of simple
when you look down the line.
It was very do-it-yourself
Alexander McQueen,
but she makes everything work
because of her quirkiness.
She reminds me
of some of my favorites:
Thorgy Thor, Yvie Oddly,
Crystal Methyd.
When I first saw her,
I almost dismissed her
because she was so out there.
But upon closer look, you know,
she might have the goods.
Silence! I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
Now, based on your performances
in the fashion show
and on the main stage,
I've made some decisions.
When I call your name,
please step forward.
Denali.
Rosé.
Con-drag-ulations. You're
the top two queens of the week.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
Oh, my God.
The rest of you,
I'm sorry, my dears.
You...
are safe.
I did it. I'm not going home,
not going home!
You may step
to the back of the stage.
Thank you.
Good job!
Denali, Rosé,
you both turned out
phenomenal performances
this week.
But there can only be
one winner.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me,
earn your first win,
and a cash tip of $5.000.
I am so ready for this lip sync.
I am not locked
in cinderblock ice skates.
This is a cute-ass song,
and I'm ready
to storm this stage.
Let's fucking do it.
The time has come...
for you to lip sync...
for the win.
I feel a lot of pressure
right now.
This would be complete
redemption from last week.
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
♪ La, la, la, la-la-la, la, la ♪
♪ Oh, baby, baby,
have you seen Amy tonight? ♪
♪ Is she in the bathroom?
Is she smoking up outside? ♪
♪ Oh, baby, baby, does she
take a piece of lime? ♪
♪ For the drink
that Imma buy her ♪
♪ Do you know
just what she likes? ♪
♪ Oh, oh, tell me,
have you seen her? ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm so, oh ♪
♪ I can't get her
off of my brain ♪
♪ I just wanna go
to the party she gonna go ♪
♪ Can somebody take me home? ♪
♪ Ha, ha, hee, hee, ha, ha, ho ♪
♪ Love me, hate me,
say what you want about me ♪
♪ But all of the boys
and all of the girls ♪
♪ Are begging to
if you seek Amy ♪
♪ Love me, hate me, but
can't you see what I see... ♪
Denali is giving you
Britney Spears.
Like, face, face, face, face.
Whereas Rosé is giving more of,
like, a comedy special.
So I'm really excited
to see how this goes down.
Ooh!
♪ So tell me if you see her ♪
♪ Let me know
what she was wearing ♪
♪ And what she was like ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been
waiting here forever ♪
♪ Let me know where
she was going, I don't mind ♪
♪ Oh, baby, baby,
if you seek Amy tonight, oh ♪
♪ La, la, la, la-la-la, la, la ♪
♪ Love me, hate me,
say what you want about me ♪
♪ But all of the boys
and all of the girls ♪
♪ Are begging to
if you seek Amy ♪
♪ Love me, hate me,
but can't you see what I see? ♪
♪ All of the boys
and all of the girls ♪
♪ Are begging to
if you seek Amy ♪
♪ Love me, hate me,
say what you want about me ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ La, la, la, la-la-la, la, la ♪
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Denali.
You're a winner, baby.
Yeah, bitch!
Con-drag-ulations.
You've won $5.000.
I fucking won!
Like, oh, my God,
this is exactly what I wanted.
It feels so good to just
have something go my way.
It sends a great message
to the judges,
and it shows the other girls
if you go against me,
watch the fuck out.
Rosé, you are safe
to slay another day.
Thank you.
Con-drag-ulations, ladies.
Tonight you rocked.
But starting next week,
heads will roll.
Word. I'm freaking out, because
the competition has started
and someone's gonna go home
each and every week.
Ooh, scary.
Now, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an "amen" up in here?
- Amen!
All right,
now let the music play.
♪ I'm a winner ♪
♪ I'm a winner, baby ♪
Next time
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
If it isn't the B squad!
The competition is about
to get next fucking level.
You'll be starring in
cheesy holiday movies
for my new media venture,
the RuPaulmark Channel.
Whoo, come on, bitch!
I'm not joking, bitch!
Aah!
Whoa-ho-ho-ho-ho.
Who cast this ho?
You had your lines,
you had the character.
It was colorful, it was you.
You were a joy to watch.
The winner's circle
feel as though they have
the upper edge on us.
There's several more rounds
to go in this race.
♪ I'm a winner ♪
♪ I'm a winner, baby ♪
♪ Losers, weepers ♪
♪ Finders, keepers ♪
♪ I'm a winner, baby ♪
♪ Losers, weepers ♪
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org