Previously on All-Stars
I think I would've chosen Thorgy to stay
I find Thorgy's concepts much more exciting
Fuck my drag, right?
You'll be improving your way through 'The Bitchelor'
- Boo you is fine.
- Thank you.
Have you ever taken out a catheter?
- Aja.
- I didn't get needy girl at all.
- Chi Chi DeVayne.
- You were constantly overshadowed.
- Milk.
- You were going so fast...
- I can't handle it right now!
- You weren't sharing the stage
Kennedy Davenport,
You're a winner baby
Which queen have you chosen to get the chop?
I had to think about everything that was going on
on and off screen, to make my decision
so I chose
Milk
Milk, sashay, away
[LOVE U GIRLS BUT YA'LL KNOW THIS IS BOGUS! STAY AMAZING!! MILK]
- Ooh Lord.
- Oh my God.
"Love you girls, but y'all know-
- "This is bogus".
- Bogus?
The girls are getting mighty shady
with the mirror this season, aren't they?
First I got told to suck it
Now Kennedy's getting told that her decision is bogus
That was shady, but alright.
Bitch, please.
How is it bogus if you are getting bad critiques?
Let me go on and say why I did what I did
Like the judges, I just wasn't enthused at all.
On a personal note I couldn't relate to Milk
And then for her to sit and say that she would've sent me home
That hurt my feelings.
I totally understand where she's coming from
If someone tried to de-validate my drag
I would send them home too.
Because if milk was in the top, she could've sent home Kennedy.
I just didn't feel nothing genuine from Milk
Ben, who did you choose to go home?
I chose Chi Chi.
One of the things that Chi Chi and I talked about was
- That fire.
- It felt like it dimmed.
I'm not mad at y'know, Ben, for picking me
Obviously somebody up there is keeping me
here for a reason.
Chi Chi can give way more than she is giving
Because guess what now all eyes are on Chi Chi
Sorry.
Time to change.
- I was a little gagged but um, I was a little gagged.
- I was totally gagged.
It's subjective, at some point it comes down
to like what does one person think about a performance.
Or even a person.
That monologue was about what she thought of Milk as a person.
This elimination was so jarring
and it's kinda coming down to personal relationships
But can we get eliminated because we don't talk to someone?
Is that the reality here, like?
It's scary because there's no comfort level
Everybody could go home at any time for whatever reason
Well I don't know what's gonna happen next week, but it's gonna be a great Christmas.
The winner of RuPaul's Drag Race All-Stars receives
a one year supply of Anastasia Beverly Hills cosmetics
a coveted spot in the Drag Race hall of fame
and a cash prize of $100,000
with extra special guest judges
Nicole Byer
and Kristin Chenoweth.
RuPaul's Drag Race All-Stars S3E4
"All-Star Snatch Game"
#Body like WOW, pussy about to end this drought#
Sis, we up in this room
I ain't got no time to be in the bottom
Bitch, it's time to work.
- Hello, hello, hello!
- Hey!
Gingham fantasy
Ladies, this weeks maxi challenge
is an all-stars edition of
"Snatch Game"!
#AllStars3
Every season "Snatch Game"
separates the 'cans' from the 'cannots'
and this time it's even gonna be harder,
Because this is all-stars.
Gentlemen,
Start your engines
and may the best all-star, win!
Lemme guess
I'm going to be doing Patricia Arquette
in the television show 'Medium'.
- No, I'm doing RuPaul.
- Mother Ru.
In my season I was so sad
Because I didn't get to do "Snatch Game"
and I wanted to do
RuPaul in front of RuPaul so bad
and every time I do RuPaul in front of people they think it's hilarious
She likes dad jokes, like I do
She likes puns, bad jokes, be great
- I'm winning the challenge.
- You sound real confident, sis.
- I am.
You do not play with that.
Nobody has been successful doing RuPaul.
I mean just because you do her, on your little show, playing around
It's harder doing it for the competition.
- So who you gonna do?
- Miss Maya Angelou.
- What you doing?
- I'm doing Paul Lynde.
- OK?
- Do you know him?
- No
Paul Lynde was this comedian in the 70s
He was the centre square on "Hollywood Squares"
for a full decade.
At this point
Ben has won so many challenges,
so now it's like, I'm this horse
but then I see this other horse
like now miles ahead of the rest of us.
and it's like, I'm never gonna catch up.
So it's just like, I have to get a win,
I have to get a win so bad.
It's my first "Snatch Game",
so I have nothing to live up to, so I feel like
What's this?
- The thing of like living up to predecessors
- From Thorgy.
- Oh Thorgy wrote this?
- Yeah.
It says: "Fuck this shady bitch, Shangela"
It has my name crossed out.
I didn't show it to you, because I thought it was not helpful
- or appropriate to.
- But you decide to hang it on the wall?
Oh boy, here we go.
My note from Thorgy,
I put it behind Milk's note.
Yeah but this one
specifically talks about me
And then says:
"Fuck this shady bitch"
and then points at my name,
and then you hung it on the wall.
Ooh face crack.
I know Trixie's stomach has fallen out of her ass.
Well I don't care what you think.
She gave it to me because she was sad.
and I'm honouring her.
I like those people.
Trixie you can't tell me,
that you read
Thorgy calling Shangela a bitch
and you just saw the goodness in the letter and wanted to put it up
cut the shit.
I would not do something-
No! Girl leave it now.
Now I know you feel that, that's the way you really feel about someone like me
I wouldn't put that up against someone because I would not want you to feel bad
- like that
- I never ever showed it to you because I didn't want
- But you hung it on the wall, sis
- Oh my God, get out of my station
- But it is what it is
Ooh the drama in the pageant
Bitch I better light an incense around here, clear the air.
How did Thorgy's feelings about Shangela
- make Shangela mad at me now?
- I think she was just upset
because you hung it up and didn't tell her.
Thorgy left a really shitty message to me on the mirror
I took the high road on that.
Then I found out
she double dogged me
in a written note.
Then Trixie hangs the note up on the wall
how much has Shangey got to take?
Trixie is a mess and she, she shouldn't even have that up there
- She put it up there to be a mess.
- What do you mean by a mess?
- Why would you put it up there?
- I wouldn't, but...
That's my point. So her putting it up there, that's being a mess.
I just think maybe she wasn't thinking about it.
- Girl, c'mon Ben.
- Maybe she was just thinking about her friendship
Some things you just do not do.
If we're all supposed to be this sisterhood and stuff
that type of shit don't supposed to fly.
- Hey ladies!
- Hi Ru!
- Look who's here!
- Hi girls!
- Marc Jacobs.
- Oh my God yes!
- Are you ready, Marc?
- I'm ready.
Let's go.
- Hi, mother.
- BeBe.
- Now this is an interesting getup here.
- Very pointy shoulders.
- Any guesses, Marc?
- Oh, I dunno
Grace Jones?
- Oh it is Grace Jones?
-It is Grace Jones.
- I guessed?
- Yes!
-Wow!
This is exciting because then I just get to embody somebody else
that is not necessarily me, you know as much as I love
the way she would talk and the words that come out of her mouth
I'm like 'oh my God did she just say that?' y'know?
But you also have to be funny, which is...
- Gotta make Ru laugh.
- I know
and that's what I'm trying to work on.
I personally think Grace Jones
is a look and an attitude
- Thanks.
- Nice to meet you.
But to make Grace Jones truly funny
I wonder if BeBe can do that.
- Hi, Shangela.
- Hey, Ru!
- Hi!
I see Tarot cards, there's a telephone and a kaftan back there.
- Marc, do you know who this is?
- Who is it?
- This is Miss Cleo. Yes.
- The late, great, Miss Cleo.
That's right, she died a couple of years ago.
- Did she?
- Oh uh, from heart disease.
She didn't see that coming?
- That was my joke, Marc.
- I'm sorry.
- That was my joke!
Now, were there other people that you considered?
For sure. I considered diva Jenifer Lewis
- Who I love so very much
- And you know her intimately.
Yes.
This is actually one of Jen's coats
She let me go diving in her closet before coming here
- and it's Marc Jacobs.
- And you didn't know
- Marc would be here today.
- No, I saw it in the cards though.
- Oh the power of the tarot.
- See the cards never lie.
Call me now darling.
Well actually your accent sounded a little like Ireland for a minute there.
Wait a minute. Miss Cleo is Jamaican
If you thinking she for a four leaf clover fish
I'm maybe going home with Cleo.
Oh darling no.
That didn't say that in the cards.
- But maybe she was Irish...
- Are you hearing an Irish accent?
I've got a lot riding on this, I can't fuck this up.
- Call me.
- Call me now.
I'm going with the backup, Jenifer Lewis.
- Hi, Kennedy.
- Hi.
- Hi Kennedy.
So I see a church lady outfit here.
- She have two boys
- Oh, OK, I know.
You're a "Housewife of Atlanta."
- Yes.
- You're Phaedra Parks.
I love that.
She believe in her lord and saviour Jesus Christ
gonna pray for you, but behind closed doors
she wanna pull out her nasty stuff.
Now, you won as Little Richard
Now if you win this one, you're the first queen in history
- to win two "Snatch Games".
- Two snatches.
Two snatches, I love that.
"Snatch Game" is more important than ever
to determine who is a contender
and who is just, roadkill.
Bring on the pressure.
The struggle is real on my end.
Can I talk to you?
- Can I talk to you?
- Yeah, let's talk.
I can't go forward with the "Snatch Game" thinking that Shangela
is like mad at me.
I didn't even occur to me it hurt your feelings
- It does hurt my feelings.
- I didn't write it.
Alright, sis.
I'm used to girls sometimes
me thinking one way about them and then it totally flipped the script.
The lowest moment in my season was when Ru asked
who should go home?
Who do you think should go home tonight?
I would like to see Shangela go.
She's just a loud mouth, and she's always talking and Hallelu-ing
You should be on season 5 or 6, that's where you should be.
These were people I thought were my friends.
Girl, I was cracked.
I have absolute respect for you and I'm really sorry.
I should've just torn that section off and kept it positive.
I appreciate your apology, I do
Lucky you meeting "all-stars 3" me
"Season 3" me would've snatched that note off the wall
and come for you, but I'm not gonna do that.
Trixie's apology seemed sincere.
But I'm looking at her with this one good eye, like this.
Oh, can I trust you, bitch?
'Cos you giving me very flip flop fish right now.
Let's see which way the cookie crumbles.
- Alright, let's do this goddamn challenge.
-Good luck, RuPaul.
Welcome to an All-Star edition of
The Snatch Game
Let's welcome our contestants
He hasn't worn men's underwear since 1982
Let's welcome Carson Kressley.
Hi, everybody.
Her boob job is so old
her breasts
- are filled with asbestos.
- It's true!
Please welcome Michelle Visage
Contestants, are you ready to meet our celebrities?
- Yes!
- Alright.
Don't be jealous of her boogie
it's RuPaul!
Welcome to the "Snatch Game"
of "RuPaul's Drag Race".
Give it up for our special guest host:
boy RuPaul
Now, RuPaul, do I call you he, or she?
You can call me he, she, Regis and Cathy Lee
as long as you buy "American" on iTunes.
Alright, next up
From "The Real Housewives of Atlanta"
It's Phaedra Parks,
ladies and gentlemen.
Oh hey, hey, hey, Ru
I just got back from the new birth
missionary baptist, church, church of God and Christ, confecational service
Well thank you for being here,
Phaedra.
Thank you and God bless.
Alright.
Straight from the centre square
It's Paul Lynde.
Oh hi there Ru, I'm glad it's you
for a second I thought somebody had gift wrapped Flip Wilson.
Alright, she's one of Oprah's favourite things.
Let's hear it for
"Mya" Angelou?
You know you spelt your name wrong on there
- Oh oh did I?
- Yes.
How you spell Maya?
Oh damn, Chi Chi.
How you gonna be one of the world's most beloved poets
and you can't spell your own name?
Maya,
I've always wanted to know
Why does a caged bird sing?
The caged bird sings, darling
because...
I don't know why the caged bird sings, darling.
Alright.
From the hit show "Blackish"
Jenifer Lewis.
Yes, that's right, RuPaul.
That's Jenifer Lewis.
One "N," One "I",
and a hell of a lot of talent.
Up next,
Star of "The Queen"
Crystal LaBeija.
Ru, where's Sabrina? I will sue the bitch, darling.
Crystal LaBeija,
from the legendary house of LaBeija.
The founder, the mother, the creator.
I am everything and I know I'm beautiful, I don't need anyone to tell me.
Alright, up next,
pull up to the bumper, baby
style and music icon,
Grace Jones
- So, RuPaul?
- Yes?
When are we going to fuck?
You don't like women?
No man can turn down this pussy.
Your Miss Jones was not graceful.
Alright.
Alright, up next
last but not least
she's not just popular
she's won a Tony and an Emmy
Please welcome the gorgeous,
Kristin Chenoweth.
- Hello, Kristin.
- Hello, my darling.
I always thought that one of these queens would do me
and no-one ever did, so I decided to come here
- and do myself.
- That's right.
Yes!
Sweetheart, none of these queens are gonna do ya
I'm so happy that you are here.
I'm so happy to be here, my darling.
Are y'all ready to play the "Snatch Game"?
- Yes!
- Alright.
First question for
Carson.
Kristin Chenoweth
is so tiny
that when she walks into a restaurant
the hostess hands her
a "blank"
Celebrities, go ahead and write your answer down.
Alright, what say you, Carson?
I'm not a doctor, but I'm gonna say growth hormones.
Alright, let's go and see if you have any matches
Alright, Phaedra.
Oh hey Phaedra, what is that?
She's fracking? Is that what she's doing?
Girl, you know I had to take that church stuff off, honey.
Oh yes!#
I said, "a napkin to wipe up"
'cos clearly he's an appetizer
Oh, OK.
Alright, Paul Lynde.
This is the most queens I've been surrounded
by since Charles Nelson Reilly's pool party.
I said, "A cocktail weenie"
'Cos it's to scale.
Sorry, it's not a match, Carson.
- Not a match.
- Circle gets a square.
Alright, Maya Angelou,
poet, activist, actress
Spelling bee winner.
Maya Angelou,
what say you?
Well I said that the hostess hands the poor thing
that same caged bird
fried, died, and laid to the side.
Oh. Maya, thank you for answering my question
from last round, in this round, maybe you'll have a good answer
answer for this question in the next round.
Let's move on down
to Jenifer Lewis.
Well look at lost, cute little Kristen, I love her.
Two Broadway divas
- You know I worked with Kristin way back in the day, that's right.
- Did you?
Yeah, no, I'm lying, I ain't worked with that bitch, but anyhow listen
I think that Kristin has to fit up
in that little bubble in "Wicked".
You saw the show, I saw it
therefore I think that man handed her a "High five"
- when she walked in.
- That would be apropos.
What's a "aproho"?
Who callin' a ho?
I'm about to have a hot flash up in here
Yeah, you know I'm going through menopause
- Are you?
- Yeah, I don't know why they call it menopause
though ain't no man up in here.
Kristin Chenoweth,
what did the hostess hand you?
- A booster chair.
- A booster chair!
- Which I actually brought.
- You brought one?
I travel with my own booster.
Oh wow, that's so smart.
This question is for
Michelle Visage
I'm coming out with a RuPaul cookbook
It includes my famous recipe
for spaghetti and "blank" balls
I'm gonna go with
Spaghetti and tucked balls.
- Those sound delicious.
- Delicious.
You have to kinda dig to find them.
Alright, let's go to the stars and hear what they have to say
- Grace Jones.
- Yes.
My famous recipe for
spaghetti and "blank" balls
- What do you think it is?
- "Steel Vagina"
- Steel Vagina?
- Yes.
- That's the name of my upcoming perfume.
- I see.
This is why I don't keep the company of the ladies.
Yes, Paul Lynde, yes.
- What are those, Grace Jones?
- That's the song
Carson, I've been meaning to get these back to you.
My apologies
I think she's also wearing your gloves
but I didn't recognise them
without the Crisco
What say you, RuPaul?
Well, Michelle, my balls are tucked so tight
that I blacked out, fell down,
woke up a second ago
panicked and just wrote
"Now available on iTunes"
I'm glad you reminded everybody of that
but unfortunately
that is not a match, RuPaul
RuPaul? I wanted to congratulate you
on your Hollywood star of fame
Oh thank you so much, my dear
as we say in the industry:
"Winner winner, chicken...dinner"
Crickets.
Trixie's just like throwing these little RuPaul one-liners
but they're out of place.
It's just not fitting.
Y'all told her on the internet it was funny
I blame y'all.
Let's move on down to
Paul Lynde
My famous recipe for
spaghetti and "blank" balls.
Well Ru, I just said the ones that I found the most delicious
Anonymous.
Your answer was an anon miss.
An-anonymous?
Yes, yes it was.
Wow darling, tell another one.
This one's for
Michelle Visage.
Ricky Martin is so hot
"blank" melts in his mouth
and in his hand
Well, he is of the Puerto Rican descent
I'm going to say
flan
- "Flan" OK.
- Yeah.
Crystal LaBeija.
Are you having a good time, Crystal?
Darling,
I'm having the worst time of my life.
I just want to walk away so bad
darling, let me tell you something about my friend, Monique
she's not here because she's melting in his mouth and his hands
but she called me this morning
and she said
"Crystal, let me tell you about the 'Snatch Game'
none of the true beauties are gonna be there" and darling she was right.
OK
Phaedra,
what do you have?
Ricky Martin, melts, so damn hot
do you think he's hot,
Phaedra?
That's a...yes?
I said, "My candy"
Kennedy won "Snatch Game" her season
but she ain't winning this one.
You've won an uncomfortable phone call to your ex
and a half eaten hot dog from the back of my car.
Oh shut up, RuPaul.
- Carson, this one's for you.
- Yes.
The U.S. Congress is so dysfunctional
they can't pass "blank"
They can't pass, the eight grade.
Alright, Maya Angelou.
U.S. Congress is so dysfunctional
they can't pass "blank"
They can't pass gasses.
'Cos we all know, that they are some uptight asses.
Oh some poetry in that answer, yes
We're gonna move on down to
Kristin Chenoweth
They can't pass "Gun Control"
- Uh huh
- There's only one gun for all of us
- and it's a bubble gun
- A bubble gun!
Look at those bubbles! Nobody can control those bubbles!
Aw shucks, time's up
The winner of today's "Snatch Game" is
the Amish,
because they don't have televisions.
Until next time, I'm everybody
Goodbye, RuPaul!
Guess who owns everything!
Not you.
It's elimination day
We're recovering from "Snatch Game"
and we had a pretty
shocking elimination last week, so I think we're all back into like, pins and needles mode.
Bitch, Trixie
It wasn't the best RuPaul,
I'll tell you that
And she know, that she wasn't the best.
How do you feel, Chi Chi?
I mean, I played the dumbest Maya Angelou in the world.
These challenges are fucking hard.
Also "Snatch Game"
is fucking hard.
It is.
I really wanted to like, do really well in this challenge, so I'm kinda disappointed.
I expected myself to do better and I think the other queens
here expected me to come in like, guns a-blazing
but holy fuck did it not go good.
How do you feel?
As soon as Ru laughed at my first
- joke I was like "Alright, I feel good."
- Oh no, Ru was in it
- to win it with you, girl.
- I feel really pleased and
y'know, I mean,
I kind of felt the other day like
I wound up with Trixie's win
and that felt weird to me,
being in the top two
because I felt like that should have gone to Trixie, and so I was feeling weird about it
Look, game recognise game
she's playing it low because she keeps winning
and when you keep winning
people are gonna start targeting you
so if you are like,
"I didn't think I deserved to win"
"Oh, I wanna give back the award"
but does she give it back?
Oh the girls, honey, the girls,
they're playing games
over here at the "RuPaul's Drag Race All-Stars"
Welcome to the main stage of RuPaul's Drag Race All Stars.
Snatch maker to the stars,
Michelle Visage.
Snatch maker, snatch maker, make me a snatch!
Style superstar,
Carson Kressley.
Now this was your first taste of
"Snatch Game"
It was and I'm really starting to like it!
She broke the girl code
Drag Race superfan,
Nicole Byer.
Thank you.
My God I could literally get hit by a bus tonight and I'm good.
Oklahoma's number one Kristin Chenoweth impersonator
Kristin Chenoweth.
- I've been snatched.
- Thanks, Dr. Zizmor.
This week on the main stage
category is:
Flower Power
Gentlemen,
start your engines
and may the best all-star win!
- Aja.
- L'il Abner and Daisy hey
Shangela.
I love that Beyoncé put the twins back in
- for this.
- She did.
BeBe Zahara Benet.
Cameroon in bloom.
Kennedy Davenport.
This look is really growing on me
Chi Chi DeVayne.
Hi lily hi lily hi ho
Trixie Mattel.
- It's raining flowers.
- Yeah.
BenDeLaCreme.
I can't tell if that's her pistil or her stamen
Welcome ladies
I've made some decisions
when I call your name please step forward
Shangela.
BenDeLaCreme.
Condragulations, you are the top two all-stars of the week.
You've each won a wig wardrobe
from Rockstar Wigs
and a $1000 gift card
from Coolhaus Super Premium Ice Cream
Please step to the back
of the stage
Now it's time for the judges critiques
First up, Aja.
Your look,
Edie Sedgwick comes to life
If I don't get that outfit by the end of this
then you an I will meet in a back alley somewhere, alright?
You embodied Crystal LaBeija
But I wish it was more than just kinda the one note that it was
I didn't think it was super one note
I love that fucking stank face you were serving the whole time
you did a great job.
Up next,
BeBe Zahara Benet.
I can't get over
how stunning you look tonight
You look like a fudgsicle dipped in flowers
and I'm here for it.
Your Grace Jones
was just the right amount
of glamour and weirdness
But I felt it kinda lost its way
I know that you didn't do a snatch game in your season
- It's intimidating, isn't it?
- It is.
It's about staying in the character and being able to deliver in the character
all the time.
- Kennedy Davenport.
- Oh my God, Phaedra Parks.
She's gonna send you a cease and desist letter for looking better than she does
But you were kinda in and out of it
We were losing her.
You know my eyes kept going to other girls
and they weren't going to Phaedra.
And this runway look,
the green leaves on the bottom
the touches in the wig
Maybe that's a little arts and craftsy for me
maybe up the sophistication level
- Up Next, Chi Chi DeVayne.
- What's up y'all
- I've never seen you look better.
- Thank you.
You look like a nice slutty teen
- who's getting married
- Teen?
So let's talk about
Maya Angelou.
you spelt your name wrong
for starters
and then Ru asked you if you knew why the caged bird sings
and it was like tumbleweed.
I would've done a little bit of a later years, Maya
I would've been fuller figured, y'know looked a little
older, because the visual cues weren't there, and that is crucial.
- Up next Trixie Mattel.
- Hi, guys!
Tonight on the runway, very "kawaii"
- but there's a lot going on.
- For me, more is more.
I mean this is great
like I need claritin to just look at this
Now let's talk about your
"Snatch Game"
First thing you did they way you landed with the "American" CD
that was funny, and then I didn't laugh, like the whole time.
It was one note,
literally through the whole thing.
I know you,
there's something that's telling
me you're not all here.
When I get nervous here, it's like, I'm at camp Crystal Lake
and Jason's outside with the machete.
It's like that level panic sometimes.
- Why?
- I don't know, it's, it's um...
it was like,
it was harder than it looks
Sorry.
I thought it was gonna be like, my challenge.
I was like, so excited,
and I got in
there and it was just like, it's like, frozen
It was, it fucking sucked.
Don't forget what you have
and what you offer,
and who you are
whether this continues or not, OK?
Fight for yourself.
I just want more
of Trixie Mattel.
Invite her back here,
because we want her.
Thank you, ladies.
Based on the judge critiques
I've made some decisions
Chi Chi DeVayne.
Kennedy Davenport.
Trixie Mattel.
You are in the bottom three.
That means, Aja, BeBe,
you're safe.
Thank you, mother.
Shangela and DeLa,
each of you
needs to decide which of the bottom three you'll eliminate
if you win the lip sync.
Thank you, ladies,
you may leave the stage.
Alright, sis.
- Careful of that bump.
- There she goes, there she goes.
I'm disappointed,
I thought I was going to win this challenge
and instead I absolutely face-planted.
in front of the person I'm impersonating.
so it's worst case scenario.
Each of the girls, I would love to have a chat with them.
Who wants to go with me?
Come on, Kens.
- Who wants to go with me?
- I'll go.
Sis, what's on your mind right now?
- It was not fun.
- I know baby.
It fucking sucked.
Like I feel like I told the judges and everyone here
like a secret, like I'm so, I'm so scared
and um, I didn't want everybody to know
because I don't think anybody here saw me being afraid of "Drag Race"
because I'm not afraid of drag in the real world.
I love "Drag Race,"
I love being Trixie.
and then to come here and like, to not be the Trixie my fans look for
it's like, fuck, you know what I mean?
Girl, there's nothing to say
I mean, just be fair
I've been here four times, so just be fair.
I'm being real about it
you know I don't want it come off as all the girls just keep saving me
because I'm their good friend,
this is a competition
it's not RuPaul's best friends race.
I'm so proud of what I did
You know what I mean? And what I've got to show
and if I go home, I'm gonna be happy
if I stay, I'm gonna be happy, so
I'm really proud of
you for continuing to plug away at this
Does Chi Chi deserve another chance?
but she does have such a charm
so I wouldn't put it past anybody to save her again.
I'll send the next girl on over.
- First of all I know tonight's an emotional night for you
- Yeah
Like I told y'all,
this is the "Game of Thrones" of drag
The seven kingdoms baby.
You've gotta have alliances.
So I'm trying to figure out
is Trixie John Snow? Or is she Cersei Lannister?
Because I ain't trying to be up in a red weddings situation.
I know how talented you are
but you also know this is a competition
and all of us want to win
and I have to put my allegiance
where I feel I have allies
I feel like it's behind us
and I don't think it would come
up in a lipstick situation,
but I hope that what happened yesterday
isn't like the reason
- You would pick my lipstick.
- No, but even the whole note thing
all that kind of stuff just sits with me in the fact
when I'm thinking like
"If I'm in the bottom,
is she ever gonna save me or not?"
of everybody in the bottom three
you're the one I worry about.
This game is a game based on trust
Kennedy is my sister
and yes, Chi Chi's been in the bottom four times
but at least I know I can trust Chi Chi.
Can I trust Trixie Mattel?
Are you my ally, girl?
- Hi
- What we gotta do girl
there has to be somebody at the top
there gotta be somebody at the bottom
- there's gotta be some people in the middle.
- Yeah.
and I just feel like I fell in the middle
I don't feel like I did a bad job.
I'm the one that was the strongest out of the three
and I'm just being honest,
I do feel that way
but at the end of the day, it's your decision.
This decision feels impossible
Chi Chi's wound up in the bottom a few times now
but she has this can do attitude
which speaks very well for her continuing
Kennedy has been a consistently hard worker
and she has brought her all to everything
but Trixie's just been landing in the middle of this competition over and over
I know that she has more to bring
I wanna see it so badly,
but I don't know if we're gonna get it.
It's never easy to have to choose a girl to go home.
It is not comfortable to feel like I am
in charge
of so many people's fates week after week
I know this is gonna crush someone's dreams
but at the end of the day this is the competition
and I've gotta make some very hard choices.
Welcome back, ladies
Two top all-stars stand before me
Ladies, this is your chance to win $10,000
and earn the power
to give one of the bottom queens
the chop.
The time has come
to lip sync
for your legacy!
If I don't beat Shangela
then I'll be one out of four
that I won
I have to win this.
Good luck and don't fuck it up.
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Shangela.
You're a winner baby.
Yay!
Thank you!
BenDeLaCreme.
You are also a winner baby.
You've both won a cash prize of $5000
- Alright.
- And you've each won the power
to send one of the bottom queens home.
Oh my God!
What!?
There's three of us up for elimination
and there's two lipsticks.
It's bad.
BenDeLaCreme,
which queen have you chosen to get
the chop?
Well, the queens on stage
have very different track records
But Chi Chi is someone
who has landed in the bottom several times
but also somebody who is going to leave this
place ready to set the world on fire.
I chose Chi Chi.
Shangela, it's your turn.
It's a difficult decision
the person I've chosen, I don't want them to feel like
it's anything personal in any way
this person left "RuPaul's Drag Race"
not winning the crown
but definitely going forward as a winner
and creating a career for themselves
and I know they will do that long after this
because I believe in their talent.
But...
I also chose Chi Chi.
Chi Chi, you are and will always be, an all-star.
Now, sashay away.
- Thank you. It's right.
- You're a superstar. You're a superstar.
Thank you guys so much.
- Love you Chi Chi!
- Bye!
I'm sad to go, but I think I did the best that I could
All Stars 3 was so hard!
Thank you!
Blessed be, kitty girl
whatever you do,
don't look behind you.
[Sigh] Why don't they ever listen?
Subbed by Kay
for opensubtitles.org