- Previously
on "All Stars..."
- I think I would have
chosen Thorgy to stay.
I find Thorgy's concepts
much more exciting.
- Fuck my drag, right?
- You'll be improv-ing your way
through "The Bitchelor."
- Ooh, you is fine.
- [laughs]
- Thank you.
- Have you ever
taken out a catheter?
- Aja.
- I didn't get needy girl.
- Oh, my God.
- At all.
- Chi Chi DeVayne.
- You were constantly
overshadowed.
- Milk.
- You were going so fast--
- I can't handle it
right now!
- You weren't sharing
the stage.
- Kennedy Davenport,
you're a winner, baby.
- Whoo!
[applause]
- Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
- I had to think about
everything that was going on,
on and off screen
to make my decision,
so I chose...
Milk.
- Milk, sashay away.
- Ooh, Lord.
- Oh, my God.
"Love you girls,
but y'all know--"
- "This is bogus."
- Bogus?
[chuckles]
- The girls
are getting mighty shady
with the mirror this season,
aren't they?
First I got told to suck it.
Now Kennedy is getting told
that her decision is bogus.
- That was shady,
but all right.
Bitch, please.
How is it bogus if you
are getting bad critiques?
Let me go on and say
why I did what I did.
Like the judges,
I just wasn't enthused at all.
On a personal note,
I couldn't relate to Milk,
and then for her to sit and say
that she would've sent me home,
that hurt my feelings.
- I totally understand
where she's coming from.
If someone tried
to devalidate my drag,
I would send them home, too.
Because if Milk
was in the top,
she could have
sent home Kennedy.
- I just didn't feel
nothing genuine from Milk.
- Ben, who did you choose
to go home?
- I chose Chi Chi.
One of the things that Chi Chi
and I talked about was--
- The fire.
- It felt like it dimmed.
- I'm not mad at, you know,
Ben for picking me.
Obviously somebody up there
is keeping me here for a reason.
- Chi Chi can give
way more than she's giving.
Because guess what?
Now all eyes are on Chi Chi.
Sorry.
- Time to change.
- Whoo!
- I was a little gagged,
but, um, I was a little gagged.
- I was totally gagged.
It's subjective.
At some point
it comes down to, like,
what does one person think
about a performance?
- Or even a person.
That monologue was about what
she thought of Milk as a person.
This elimination,
it was so jarring,
and it's kind of coming down
to personal relationships.
Like, can we get eliminated
because
we don't talk to someone?
Is that the reality here?
It's scary because
there's no comfort level.
Everybody could go home
at any time for whatever reason.
Well, I don't know
what's gonna happen next week,
but it's gonna be
a great Christmas.
- The winner of "RuPaul's
Drag Race All Stars"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
a coveted spot
in the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize
of $100,000.
With extra-special
guest judge Nicole Byer
and Kristin Chenoweth.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race
- ♪ May the best woman
- ♪ Best woman win
- ♪ Party like wow, pussy
about to end this drought ♪
- [laughs]
- Sis, we up in this room.
I ain't got no time
to be in the bottom.
Bitch, it's time to work.
- Hello, hello, hello!
- Hi!
- Hey!
- Gingham fantasy.
- Ladies,
this week's maxi challenge
is an All Stars edition
of "Snatch Game!"
[cheering]
#AllStars3.
- Whoo-hoo!
- Every season's
"Snatch Game"
separates the cans
from the cannots,
and this time
it's even gonna be harder
because this is All Stars.
- Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may
the best All Star win.
- Let me guess.
- I'm going to be doing
Patricia Arquette
in the television show
"Medium."
- [laughs]
- No, I'm doing RuPaul.
- Mother Ru.
- In my season,
I was so sad
because I didn't get
to do "Snatch Game,"
and I wanted to do RuPaul
in front of RuPaul so bad.
And every time I do RuPaul
in front of people,
they think it's hilarious.
She likes dad jokes
like I do.
She likes puns, bad jokes.
It's gonna be great.
I'm winning the challenge.
- You sound
real confident, sis.
- I am.
- You do not play with that.
Nobody has been successful
doing RuPaul.
I mean,
just because you do her
on your little show
playing around,
it's harder doing it
before the competition.
Who you gonna do?
- Miss Maya Angelou.
- What you doing?
- I'm doing Paul Lynde.
- Okay.
- Do you know him?
- No.
- Paul Lynde was this comedian
in the seventies.
He was the center square
on "Hollywood Squares"
for like a full decade.
- Okay.
- At this point,
Ben has won so many challenges,
so now it's like
I'm this horse,
but then I see
this other horse,
like, now miles ahead
of the rest of us,
and it's, like,
I'm never gonna catch up.
So it's just, like,
I have to get a win.
I have to get a win so bad.
So this
is my first "Snatch Game."
I have nothing to live up to,
so I feel like I'm--
- What's this?
- The thing of, like,
living up to a predecessor--
- From Thorgy.
- Oh, Thorgy wrote this?
- Yeah.
- It says fuck
this shady bitch Shangela."
And it has
my name crossed out.
- I didn't show it you
because I thought it was
not helpful or appropriate.
- But you decided
to hang it on the wall?
- Oh, boy, here we go.
- Its my note from Thorgy.
I put it behind the Milk note.
- Yeah, but this one
specifically talks about me
and then says,
"fuck this shady bitch,"
and then points at my name,
and then
you hung it on the wall.
- Oh, face crack.
I know Trixie's stomach
has fallen out of her ass.
- Well, I don't care
what you think.
She gave it to me because she
was sad, and I'm honoring her.
I like those people.
- Trixie, you can't tell me
that you read Thorgy
calling Shangela a bitch,
and you just saw
the goodness in the letter
and wanted to put it up.
Cut the shit.
- I would not do something--
No, girl, leave it now.
I know you feel--
that's the way you really feel
about someone like me.
I wouldn't put that up
against someone
because I would not want you
to feel bad like that.
- I never even showed it to you
because I didn't want--
- You hung
it on the wall, sis.
- Oh, my God,
get out of my station.
- But it is what it is.
- Ooh, the drama
in the pageant.
- Bitch, I've gotta light
an incense around here
to clear the air.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- How did Thorgy's feelings
about Shangela
make Shangela mad at me now?
- I think she was just upset
because you hung it up
and didn't tell her.
- Thorgy left a really shitty
message to me on the mirror.
I took the high road
on that.
Then I find out she double
dogged me in a written note.
Then Trixie hangs the note up
on the wall.
How much does Shangy
got to take?
- Trixie is a mess,
and she shouldn't even
have that up there.
She put it up there
to be a mess.
- What do you mean
by a mess?
- Why would you
put it up there?
- I wouldn't, but--
- My point.
So her putting it up there,
that's being a mess.
- I just think maybe
she wasn't thinking about it.
- Girl.
Come on, Ben.
- Maybe she was just
thinking about her--
- Some things
you just do not do.
If we all supposed to be
this sisterhood and stuff,
that type of shit
don't supposed to fly.
- Hey, ladies!
- Hi!
- Look who's here!
- Hi, guys.
[cheering]
- Marc Jacobs.
- Yes!
- Are you ready, Marc?
- I'm ready.
- Let's go.
- Hi, Mother.
- BeBe, now, this is
an interesting get up here.
- Right.
Very pointy shoulders.
- Uh-huh.
Any guesses, Marc?
- Oh, I don't know.
Grace Jones?
- Oh, it is Grace Jones?
- It is Grace Jones.
- Oh, my God.
- I guessed?
- Yes. Wow.
- Yes, Grace Jones.
- This is exciting,
because then I just
get to embody somebody else
that is not necessarily me,
you know?
As much as I love her,
the way she would talk
and the words that
come out from her mouth,
I'm like, oh, my God,
did she just say that, you know?
- But you also have
to be funny, which is--
- You gotta make Ru laugh.
- That's right.
- I know, and that's what
I'm trying to work on.
- Yeah.
- I personally think
Grace Jones is a look
and an attitude.
- Thanks.
- Nice to meet you.
- But to make Grace Jones
truly funny,
I wonder
if BeBe can do that.
- Hi, Shangela.
- Hey, Ru!
- Hi!
- I see tarot cards,
there's a telephone
and a kaftan back there.
Marc, do you know who this is?
- Who is it?
- This is Miss Cleo. Yes.
- The late great Miss Cleo.
- That's right. She died
a couple years ago--
- Did she?
- From heart disease.
- She didn't
see that coming?
- No.
- That was my joke, Marc.
- I'm sorry.
- That was my joke.
- Now, were there other people
that you considered?
- For sure.
I considered diva Jenifer Lewis,
who I love so very much.
- And you know her intimately.
- Yes.
This is actually
one of Jen's coats.
She let me go diving in
her closet before coming here,
and it's Marc Jacobs.
- And you didn't know Marc
would be here today.
- No! I saw it
in the cards, though.
Hon, the power of the tarot.
- Yeah, see,
the cards never lie.
- Call me now, darling.
- Well, actually,
your accent
sounded a little like Ireland
for a minute there.
- Wait a minute.
Miss Cleo is Jamaican.
If you thinking she for
a four-leaf clover fish,
I'm maybe
going home with Cleo.
- Oh, darling, no.
They didn't say that
in the cards.
But maybe she was Irish--
- Are you hearing
an Irish accent?
- I've got
a lot riding on this.
I can't fuck this up.
Call me.
- Call me now.
- I'm going with the backup,
Jenifer Lewis.
- Hi, Kennedy.
- Hi.
- So I see
a church lady outfit here.
- Mm-hmm. She have two boys.
- Oh, oh, okay, I know.
You're
a Housewife of Atlanta.
- Yes.
- You're Phaedra Parks.
- Phaedra Parks.
- I love that.
- She believe in her Lord
and Savior Jesus Christ,
and want to pray for you.
- Amen.
- But behind closed doors,
she want to pull out
her nasty stuff.
- [laughs]
- Now, you won
as Little Richard.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Now, if you win this one,
you'll be the first queen
in history
to win two "Snatch Games."
- Two Snatches.
I love that.
- Oh, wow.
- "Snatch Game"
is more important than ever
to determine
who is a contender
and who is just road kill.
- Bring on the pressure.
The struggle is real
on my end.
- Can I talk to you?
- Yeah, let's talk.
- I can't go forward
with the "Snatch Game"
thinking that Shangela
is, like, mad at me.
- It didn't even occur to me
it hurt your feelings.
- It does hurt my feelings.
- I didn't write it.
- All right, sis.
I'm used to girls,
sometimes me,
thinking one way about them,
and then it totally
flipped the script.
The lowest moment
in my season
was when Ru
asked who should go home.
- Who do you think
should go home tonight?
- I would like to see
Shangela go.
She's just a loud mouth,
and she's always talking
and halle-looing.
- You should be on
Season 5 or 6.
That's where you should be.
- These are people
I thought were my friends.
Girl, I was cracked.
- I have absolute respect
for you, and I'm really sorry.
I should have just
tore that section off
and kept it positive.
- I appreciate your apology.
I do.
Lucky you're meeting
"All Stars 3" me.
Season 3 me would have
snatched that note off the wall
and come for you,
but I'm not gonna do that.
Trixie's apology
seems sincere,
but I'm looking at her with
this one good eye like this.
Oh, can I trust you, bitch?
'Cause you giving me very
flip-flop fish right now.
Let's see which way
the cookie crumbles.
- All right.
Let's do this goddamn--
- Good luck, RuPaul.
- Coming up...
- RuPaul, when are we
going to fuck?
- [laughs]
- Where's Sabrina?
I will sue the bitch,
darling.
- Carson, I've been meaning
to get these back to you.
- [laughs]
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Welcome to an All Star edition
of the "Snatch Game."
Let's welcome
our contestants.
He hasn't worn men's underwear
since 1982.
Let's welcome
Carson Kressley.
- Oh. Hi, everybody.
- Her boob job is so old
her breasts
are filled with asbestos.
- That's true.
- Please welcome
Michelle Visage.
Contestants, are you ready
to meet our celebrities?
- Yes!
- All right.
Don't be jealous of her boogie,
it's RuPaul.
- Welcome to "Snatch Game"
at "RuPaul's Drag Race."
Give it up for our special
guest host, Boy RuPaul.
- Now, RuPaul,
do I call you he or she?
- You can call me he, she,
Regis and Kathi Lee
as long as you buy
"American" on iTunes.
[all laugh]
- All right. Next up, from
"Real Housewives of Atlanta,"
it's Phaedra Parks,
ladies and gentlemen.
- Oh, hey, hey, hey, Ru.
I just got back
from the New Birth Missionary
Baptist Church Church of God and
Christ convocational service.
- Uh-huh. Well, thank you
for being here, Phaedra.
- No, thank you,
and God bless.
- All right.
Straight from the center square,
it's Paul Lynde.
- Well, hi, there, Ru.
I'm glad it's you.
For a second I thought somebody
had gift wrapped Flip Wilson.
[all laugh]
- All right. She's one
of Oprah's favorite things.
Let's hear it
for "Mya Angelou?"
You know, you spelled
your name wrong on there.
- Oh, did I?
- Yes.
- How you spell Maya?
- Oh, damn, Chi Chi.
How you gonna be one of the
world's most beloved poets,
and you can't spell
your own name?
- Now, Maya,
I've always wanted to know,
why does
the caged bird sing?
- The caged bird sings,
darling, because...
I don't know why
the caged bird sings, darling.
- [laughs] All right.
From the hit show "Blackish,"
Jenifer Lewis.
- Yes, that's right, RuPaul.
That's Jenifer Lewis.
One "N," one "I",
and a helluva lot of talent.
[all laugh]
- Up next, star of "The Queen,"
Crystal LaBeija.
- Ru, where's Sabrina?
I will sue the bitch,
darling.
- Crystal LaBeija from
the legendary House of LaBeija.
- The founder, the mother,
the creator.
I am everything.
And I know I'm beautiful.
I don't need anyone
to tell me.
- [laughs]
All right. Up next,
pull up
to the bumper, baby.
Style and music icon
Grace Jones.
- So, RuPaul?
- Yes.
- When are we going
to fuck?
- [all laugh]
- You don't like women?
No man can turn down
this pussy.
- Your Miss Jones
was not graceful.
- All right.
All right, up next,
last but not least,
she's not just popular,
she's won
a Tony and an Emmy.
Please welcome the gorgeous
Kristin Chenoweth.
[applause]
Hello, Kristin.
- Hello, my darling.
I always thought that one
of these queens would do me,
and no one ever did,
so I decided to come here
and do myself.
- That's right.
- ♪ Whoo
- Yes! Yes!
[applause]
- Sweetheart, none of these
queens are gonna do you.
[all laugh]
- I'm so happy
that you are here.
- I'm so happy to be here,
my darling.
- Are y'all ready to play
the "Snatch Game?"
- Yes!
- All right.
First question for Carson.
Kristin Chenoweth is so tiny
that when she walks
into a restaurant,
the hostess
hands her a blank.
Celebrities, go ahead
and write your answer down.
All right.
What say you, Carson?
- I'm not a doctor, but I'm
gonna say growth hormones.
- [all laugh]
- All right.
Let's go and see
if you have any matches.
All right, Phaedra.
Ooh, oh, hey, Phaedra.
What is that? She's fracking?
Is that what she's doing?
- Girl, you know I had to take
that church stuff off, honey.
- Oh, yes.
- I said a napkin
to wipe up,
'cause clearly
he's the appetizer.
- Oh, okay.
All right. Paul Lynde.
- This is the most queens
I've been surrounded by
since Charles Nelson Reilly's
pool party.
[all laugh]
- Well, I said
a cocktail weenie.
'Cause it's to scale.
- [laughs]
- Sorry, it's not a match,
Carson.
- Not a match.
- Circle gets the square.
- [laughs]
- All right. Maya Angelou,
poet, activist, actress.
- Spelling bee winner,
mm-hmm.
- Maya Angelou,
what say you?
- Well, I said that the hostess
hands the poor thing
that same caged bird
fried, died,
and laid to the side.
- Oh. Maya, thank you
for answering my question
from last round
in this round.
Maybe you'll have a good answer
for this question
in the next round.
Let's move on down
to Jenifer Lewis.
- Well, look at little
cute little Kristin.
I love her.
Two Broadway divas.
You know, I've worked with
Kristin way back in the day.
- Did you?
- Yeah. No, I'm lying.
I ain't worked with that bitch.
But anyhow, let's--
[all laugh]
- I think that Kristin
has to fit up
in that little bubble
in "Wicked."
- You saw the show.
- Sure.
- I saw it,
and therefore,
I think that man
handed her a high five
when she walked in.
- That would be apropos.
- What apro-ho?
Who you calling a ho?
I'm about to have
a hot flash up in here.
- Ooh! Oh, yes, yes.
- Yeah. You know,
I'm going through menopause.
- Are you?
- Yeah.
I don't know why
they call it menopause.
There ain't no men up in it.
- [laughs]
Kristin Chenoweth, what
did the hostess hand you?
- A booster chair.
- Which I actually brought.
- You brought one?
- I travel
with my own booster.
- Oh, wow, that's so smart.
This question
is for Michelle Visage.
I'm coming out
with a RuPaul cookbook.
It includes my famous recipe
for spaghetti and blank balls.
- I'm gonna go with spaghetti
and tucked balls.
- Ooh,
those sound delicious.
- Delicious.
- Oh, yes.
- You have to kind of dig
to find them.
All right,
let's go to the stars
and hear
what they have to say.
Grace Jones.
- Yes.
- My famous recipe
for spaghetti and blank balls.
What do you think it is?
- Steel vagina.
- Steel vagina?
- Yes. That's the name
of my upcoming perfume.
- I see.
- This is why I don't keep
the company of the ladies.
- Yes, Paul Lynde, yes.
What are those, Grace Jones?
- That's the song.
- Carson, I've meaning
to get these back to you.
My apologies.
I think she's also
wearing your clothes,
but I didn't recognize them
without the Crisco.
[all laugh]
- What say you, RuPaul?
- Well, Michelle, my balls
are tucked so tight
that I blacked out, fell down,
woke up a second ago,
panicked and just wrote
"Now available on iTunes."
- I'm glad you reminded
everybody of that,
but unfortunately,
that is not a match, RuPaul.
- RuPaul, I wanted
to congratulate you
on your
Hollywood Star of Fame.
- Oh, thank you so much,
my dear.
As we say in the industry,
winner winner chicken...dinner.
- Crickets.
Trixie's just kind of like
throwing these little
RuPaul one-liners in,
but they're out of place.
It's just not fitting.
Y'all told her on the Internet
it was funny.
I blame y'all.
- Let's move on down
to Paul Lynde.
My famous recipe for
spaghetti and blank balls.
- Well, Ru, I just said the ones
that I found the most delicious.
Anonymous.
[all laugh]
- Your answer
was anony...miss.
- Anonymous?
Yes. Yes, it was.
- Wow, darling,
tell another one.
- This one's
for Michelle Visage.
Ricky Martin is so hot,
blank melts in his mouth
and in his hand.
- Well, he is of
the Puerto Rican descent.
- Uh-huh.
- I'm going to say flan.
- Flan. Okay.
- Yeah.
- Crystal LaBeija.
Are you having a good time,
Crystal?
- Darling, I'm having
the worst time of my life.
I just want
to walk away so bad.
Darling,
let me tell you something
about my friend Monique.
She's not here
because she's melting
in his mouth
and his hands,
but she called me this morning
and she said, Crystal,
let me tell you about
the "Snatch Game."
None of the true beauties
are gonna be there,
and, darling, she was right.
- Okay. [laughs]
Phaedra, what do you have?
Ricky Martin melts--
so damn hot.
Do you think he's hot,
Phaedra?
- Ooh.
Ooh.
- That's a yes?
- Mm, mm, mm.
I said my Candy.
- Kennedy won "Snatch Game"
her season,
but she ain't winning
this one.
- You've won an uncomfortable
phone call to your ex
and a half eaten hotdog
from the back of my car.
- Oh, shut up, RuPaul.
- All right. Now, Carson,
this one's for you.
The U.S. Congress
is so dysfunctional,
they can't pass blank.
- They can't pass
the 8th grade.
- [laughs]
All right, Maya Angelou.
U.S. Congress
is so dysfunctional,
they can't pass blank.
- They can't pass gas,
'cause we all know
that they are
some uptight asses.
- Oh, oh, some poetry
in that answer. Yes.
We're gonna move on down
to Kristin Chenoweth.
- They can't pass
gun control.
There's only one gun
for all of us,
and it's a bubble gun.
- A bubble gun!
Look at these bubbles.
Nobody can control
those bubbles.
Aw, shucks.
Time's up.
The winner of today's
"Snatch Game" is...
the Amish, because they
don't have televisions.
[all laugh]
- Until next time,
I'm everybody.
Goodbye, RuPaul.
- Coming up...
- I wished it was more
than just kind of
the one note that it was.
- I didn't think
it was super one note.
- It was like tumbleweed.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Guess who owns everything?
Not you. Aah! [laughs]
- It's elimination day.
We're recovering
from "Snatch Game,"
and we had a pretty shocking
elimination last week,
so I think we're all back
into, like,
pins and needles mode.
- Bitch, Trixie.
- It wasn't the best RuPaul,
I'll tell you that.
- And she know that
she wasn't the best.
- How do you feel, Chi Chi?
- Well, I mean, I played
the dumbest Maya Angelou
in the world.
- These challenges
are fucking hard.
Also, "Snatch Game"
is fucking hard.
- It is.
- I really wanted to, like, do
really well in this challenge,
so I'm kind of disappointed.
I expected myself
to do better,
and I think
the other queens here
expected me to come in,
like, guns a-blazing.
But holy fuck,
did it not go good.
- How do you feel?
- As soon as Ru
laughed at my first joke,
I was, like, all right,
I feel good.
- Oh, no, Ru was in it
to win it with you, girl.
- I feel really pleased
and, you know, I mean,
I kind of felt
the other day,
like, I wound up
with Trixie's win.
And that felt weird to me
being in the top two,
because I feel like that
should have gone to Trixie,
and so I was feeling weird
about that.
- Look,
game recognizes game.
She's playing it low
because she keeps winning.
And when you keep winning,
people are gonna
start targeting you.
So if you are, like, I didn't
think I deserved to win.
Oh, I wanna
give back the award.
But does she give it back?
Oh, the girls, honey.
The girls,
they're playing games
over here at the "RuPaul's
Drag Race All Stars."
[laughs]
- ♪ Covergirl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Covergirl,
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
♪ Covergirl
- Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul's
Drag Race All Stars."
Snatchmaker to the stars,
Michelle Visage.
- Snatchmaker, snatchmaker,
make me a snatch.
- Style superstar
Carson Kressley.
Now, this was your first taste
of "Snatch Game."
- It was, and I'm really
starting to like it.
[all laugh]
- She broke the girl code.
"Drag Race" superfan
Nicole Byer.
- Thank you.
My God, I could literally
get hit by a bus tonight
and I'm good.
- Oklahoma's number one
Kristin Chenoweth impersonator,
Kristin Chenoweth.
- I've been snatched.
- Thanks, Dr. Zizmore.
[all laugh]
- This week
on the main stage,
category is flower power.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may
the best All Star win.
Aja.
- Lil Abner and Daisy Hay.
- Shangela.
- Ooh.
- I love that Beyonce put
the twins back in for this.
- Yes, she did.
- BeBe Zahara Benet.
Cameroon in bloom.
[all laugh]
Kennedy Davenport.
- This look
is really growing on me.
[all laugh]
- Chi Chi DeVayne.
Hi-lily, hi-lily, hi-ho.
- [Michelle laughs]
- Trixie Mattel.
- It's raining flowers.
- Yeah.
- BenDeLaCreme.
- I can't tell if that's
her pistil or her stamen.
- ♪ Sexy drag queen
- Coming up...
- I've never seen you
look better.
- You look like a fudgsicle
dipped in flowers.
- You and I will meet
in a back alley somewhere.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Welcome, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
When I call your name,
please step forward.
Shangela.
BenDeLaCreme.
Con-drag-ulations.
You are the top two
All Stars of the week.
[applause]
You've each won a wig wardrobe
from Rock Star Wigs,
and a $1,000 gift card
from CoolHaus
Super Premium Ice Cream.
- Ooh.
- [Michelle laughs]
- Please step
to the back of the stage.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
First up, Aja.
- Your look: Edie Sedgwick
comes to life.
If I don't get that outfit
by the end of this,
then you and I will meet
in a back alley somewhere.
All right?
[all laugh]
- You embodied
Crystal LaBeija.
- But I wish it was more
than just kind of
the one note that it was.
- I didn't think
it was super one note.
I love
that fucking stank face
you were serving
the whole time.
You did a great job.
- Up next,
BeBe Zahara Benet.
- I can't get over
how stunning you look tonight.
- You look like a fudgsicle
dipped in flowers,
and I'm here for it.
- Your Grace Jones
was just the right amount
of glamour and weirdness.
- But I felt
it kind of lost its way.
I know that you didn't do
a "Snatch Game" in your season.
It's intimidating,
isn't it?
- It is.
- It's about staying
in the character
and being able to deliver
in the character all the time.
- Kennedy Davenport.
- Oh, my God, Phaedra Parks.
She's gonna send you
a cease and desist letter
for looking better
than she does.
[RuPaul laughs]
- But you were kind of
in and out of it.
- Ooh.
- We were losing her.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know, my eyes
kept going to other girls,
and they weren't
going to Phaedra.
- And this runway look,
the green leaves on the bottom,
the touches in the wig,
maybe that's a little
arts and craftsy for me.
Maybe up
the sophistication level.
- Up next, Chi Chi DeVayne.
- What's up, y'all?
- I've never seen you
look better.
- Thank you.
- You look like
a nice slutty teen
who's getting married.
[all laugh]
- Teen?
- So let's talk
about Maya Angelou.
You spelled your name wrong
for starters,
and then Ru asked you if you
knew why the caged bird sings,
and it was like tumbleweed.
- I would have done a little bit
of a later years Maya.
I would have been
fuller figured,
you know,
looked a little older,
because the visual cues
weren't there,
and that is crucial.
- Up next, Trixie Mattel.
- Hi, guys.
- Tonight on the runway,
very kawaii,
but there's a lot going on.
- For me, more is more.
- Tch.
- I mean, this is great.
Like, I need Claritin
to just look at this.
- Now let's talk about
your "Snatch Game."
The first thing you did,
when you landed with the
"American" CD, that was funny.
- Yeah.
- And then I didn't laugh,
like, the whole time.
It was one note literally
through the whole thing.
I know you.
There's something that's
telling me you're not all here.
- When I get nervous here,
it's like
I'm at Camp Crystal Lake
and Jason's outside
with a machete.
It's like that level panic
sometimes.
- Why?
- I don't know. It's...
It was harder than it looks.
[sobs] Sorry.
I thought it was gonna be,
like, my challenge.
I was, like, so excited,
and I got in there
and it was just, like--
it's, like, frozen.
It fucking sucks.
- Don't forget
what you have
and what you offer
and who you are,
whether this continues
or not, okay?
Fight for yourself.
- I just want more
of Trixie Mattel.
Invite her back here,
because we want her.
- Thank you, ladies.
Based on
the judges' critiques,
I have made some decisions.
- Chi Chi DeVayne.
Kennedy Davenport.
Trixie Mattel.
You are in the bottom three.
That means Aja, BeBe,
you're safe.
- Thank you.
- Shangela and DeLa,
each of you needs to decide
which of the bottom three
you'll eliminate
if you win the lip sync.
Thank you, ladies.
You may leave the stage.
- All right, sis.
- Careful of that bump.
- There she goes.
- I'm disappointed.
I thought I was gonna win
this challenge,
and instead,
I absolutely face planted
in front of the person
I'm impersonating,
so it's worst case scenario.
- Each of the girls, I would
love to have a chat with them.
Who wants to go with me?
Come on, Kens.
- Who wants to go with me?
- I'll go.
- Sis, what's
on your mind right now?
- It was not funny.
- I know, baby.
- It fucking sucked,
Like, I feel like I told
the judges and everyone here,
like, a secret
that, like, I'm so scared,
and I didn't want
everybody to know
because I don't think
anybody here
saw me being afraid
of "Drag Race,"
because I'm not afraid
of drag in the real world.
I love "Drag Race."
I love being Trixie.
And then to come here
and, like, to not be
the Trixie
I know my fans look for,
it's like, fuck,
you know what I mean?
- Girl,
there's nothing to say.
I mean, just be fair.
I've been here four times,
so just be fair.
I'm being real about it.
You know, I don't want it
to come off
as all the girls
just keep saving me
because
I'm their good friend.
This is a competition.
It's not
RuPaul's Best Friends Race.
I'm so proud of what I did,
you know what I mean?
And what
I've gotten to show,
and if I go home,
I'm gonna be happy.
And if I stay,
So...
- I'm really proud of you
for continuing
to plug away at this.
- Yeah.
- Does Chi Chi
deserve another chance?
But she does have
such a charm,
so I wouldn't put it past
anybody to save her again.
- I'll send the next girl
on over.
- First of all, I know tonight's
an emotional night for you.
- Yeah.
- Give me a hug.
- Girl, it fucking sucks.
- Like I told y'all, this is
the Game of Thrones of drag.
The seven kingdoms, baby,
you've gotta have alliances.
So I'm trying to figure out
is Trixie Jon Snow
or is she Cersei Lannister?
Because I ain't trying to be up
in a red wedding situation.
I know how talented you are,
but you also know
this is a competition,
and all of us want to win,
and I have to put my allegiance
where I feel I have allies.
- I feel like
it's behind us,
and I don't think it would
come up in a lipstick situation,
but I hope that
what happened yesterday
isn't, like, the reason
you would pick my lipstick.
- No, but even
the whole note thing,
all that kind of stuff
just sits with me
in the fact
when I'm thinking, like,
if I'm in the bottom,
is she gonna
ever save me or not?
Of everybody
in the bottom three,
you're the one
I worry about.
This game
is a game based on trust.
Kennedy is my sister,
and, yes, Chi Chi's been
in the bottom four times,
but at least I know
I can trust Chi Chi.
Can I trust Trixie Mattel?
Are you my ally, girl?
- Hi.
- Here we go, girl.
There has to be
somebody at the top,
there gotta be somebody
at the bottom,
there's gotta be
some people in the middle.
And I just feel like
I fell in the middle.
I don't feel like
I did a bad job.
I'm the one that was
the strongest out of the three,
and I'm just being honest.
I do feel that way,
but at the end of the day,
it's your decision.
- This decision
feels impossible.
Chi Chi's wound up in the bottom
a few times now,
but she has
this can-do attitude,
which speaks very well
for her continuing.
Kennedy has been
a consistently hard worker,
and she has brought her all
to everything.
But Trixie's
just been landing
in the middle of this
competition over and over.
I know that she has
more to bring.
I want to see it so badly,
but I don't know
if we're gonna get it.
It's never easy to have
to choose a girl to go home.
It is not comfortable
to feel like
I am in charge of so many
people's fates week after week.
- I know this is gonna
crush someone's dreams,
but at the end of the day,
this is the competition,
and I've got to make
some very hard choices.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Welcome back, ladies.
Two top All Stars
stand before me.
Ladies, this is your chance
to win $10,000,
and earn the power
to give one of
the bottom queens the chop.
The time has come...
[thunder]
to lip sync...
[echoing] for your legacy.
- If I don't beat Shangela,
then I'll be one out of four
that I won.
I have to win this.
- Good luck
and don't fuck it up.
[music plays]
- ♪ This was never
the way I planned ♪
♪ Not my intention
♪ It's not
what I'm used to ♪
♪ Just wanna try you on
♪ I'm curious for you
♪ Caught my attention
♪ I kissed a girl
and I liked it ♪
♪ The taste
of her cherry Chapstick ♪
♪ I kissed a girl
just to try it ♪
♪ I hope my boyfriend
don't mind it ♪
♪ No, I don't
even know your name ♪
♪ It doesn't matter
♪ My head gets so confused
♪ Hard to obey
♪ I kissed a girl
and I liked it ♪
♪ Us girls,
we are so magical ♪
♪ Soft skin, red lips,
so kissable ♪
♪ Ain't no big deal,
it's innocent ♪
- Whoo!
- ♪ I kissed a girl
and I liked it ♪
♪ The taste
of her cherry Chapstick ♪
♪ I kissed a girl
just to try it ♪
♪ I hope my boyfriend
don't mind it ♪
♪ It felt so wrong
♪ It felt so right
♪ Don't mean I'm in love
tonight ♪
♪ I kissed a girl
and I liked it ♪
♪ I liked it
[cheers and applause]
- Ladies,
I've made my decision.
Shangela.
You're a winner, baby.
- Yay! Thank you.
- BenDeLaCreme.
You are also
a winner, baby.
- Oh!
- You've both won
a cash prize of $5,000.
- All right.
- And you've each
won the power
to send one
of the bottom queens home.
- Wow.
- Oh, my God.
What?
- There's three of us
up for elimination,
and there's two lipsticks.
It's bad.
- BenDeLaCreme, which queen
have you chosen
to get the chop?
- Well, the queens on stage
have very different
track records,
but Chi Chi is someone
who has landed in the bottom
several times,
but also somebody
who is gonna leave this place
ready to set
the world on fire.
I chose Chi Chi.
- Shangela, it's your turn.
- It's a difficult decision.
The person that I've chosen,
I don't want them
to feel like
it's anything personal
in any way.
This person left "RuPaul's Drag
Race" not winning the crown,
but definitely
going forward as a winner
and creating a career
for themselves,
and I know they will do that
long after this
because I believe
in their talent.
But...
I also Chi Chi.
- Chi Chi, you are
and will always be an All Star.
Now sashay away.
[applause]
- Thank you.
Thank you guys so much.
- We love you, Chi Chi.
- Bye.
- Uh!
[sighs]
I'm sad to go, but I think
I did the best that I could.
All Stars 3 was so hard.
[laughs]
Thank you.
[bell rings]
- Blessed be, kitty girl.
Whatever you do,
don't look behind you.
[floorboards creak]
- Aah!
- [sighs] Why don't
they ever listen?
- Next time
on "All Stars..."
- We're throwing ourselves
a little Andy Warhol ball.
- Yeah!
- Yay, we get to make stuff.
Bam!
- Oh!
- Poor baby.
- All I can say is R.I.P.
to this challenge,
'cause you murdered it.
- You would be definitely be
catching everybody's attention
at Studio 54.
- You can do better
and more.
- This may be the worst thing
I've seen on "Drag Race."
- Someone's feelings
are going to be hurt.
- It's "All Stars," girl.
Anything can happen.