Let's get sickening.
You'll need to survive
the biggest drag disaster
of all time.
[gasps]
The lighting from season one?
- The Rupocalypse.
- Oh, that sounds scary, too.
Yeah.
oh, that's scary.
[screams]
Ooh, [bleep],
it's falling apart.
(Milan)
Jiggly's costume
is a hot mess.
(Rupaul)
Jiggly Caliente...
Lashauwn Beyond...
The Princess, Sharon Needles.
- This is my kind of ghoul.
- Bloody fabulous
Con-drag-ulations, You are
the winner of this challenge.
Thank you.
I'm just in disbelief
that I'm here.
Bitch, you're here.
Yeah, honey,
you better snap out of it.
- Play to win.
- Snap out of it!
Jiggly Caliente,
shantay, you stay.
Thank you.
Alisa Summers, sashay away.
(Rupaul)
And tonight...
you'll be transforming
yourselves into wrestling's
trashiest fighters.
Be a lady.
(Rupaul)
The dolls throw down...
Get out.
Y'all fake-ass hoes.
Get out of here.
[audience oohing]
(Rupaul)
And take flight.
Chicago, bitch.
[screaming]
(Rupaul)
With extra-special
guest judges
NBA stars Rick Fox
and John Salley.
Child, we got some
fine mens up in here tonight.
(Rupaul)
Will receive a lifetime supply
of NYX cosmetics,
a one-of-a-kind trip
courtesy of ALandCHUCK.travel,
headline Logo's Drag Race tour,
featuring Absolut vodka:
cocktails perfected,
and a cash prize of $100,000.
And may the best woman win.
# RuPaul Drag Race #
It's RuPaul's Drag Race
season four Ru-Veal.
Who knew that drag queens
wrestling would be
so much fun?
I did.
[laughs]
# RuPaul Drag Race #
# May the best woman
# Best woman win
[upbeat music]
#
- A gorgeous day.
- Good morning, cluckers.
(Dida)
We walk in the
work room this morning,
and we see Alisa's message,
and it's kind of sad.
I mean, it was official.
Week by week, we're all
going to be going home.
- Officially.
(Kenya) "Keep it cute, ladies!
"Shady sisters 4-ever!
Love, Alisa."
- Look what you've done.
- That's what you've done, baby.
It was either her or me,
and I was not going home.
Let's take a vote.
Can we switch Jiggly for Alisa?
Whoo!
Girl, shady queens.
Shady queens!
(Jiggly)
Being in the bottom two
shook me.
I feel like there's a target
on the back of my head.
And all these bitches are trying
to assassinate me.
They're calling you the silent
killer, bitch, because
everybody thought you
were gonna win the challenge.
I mean, I did think
I was gonna win,
but I understand why
I didn't win.
- Well, after she had said--
- I'm too quiet.
Yeah, you're too quiet.
(Lashauwn)
I was quiet because
I was trying to focus.
My strategy isn't gonna change,
because I know that I prepared
a package to beat these girls.
So, I mean, I'm fine.
- Speak up, Lashauwn.
- Can everybody hear me?
Fly away.
- [siren wails]
(RuPaul) Ooh, girl.
She done already done
had herses.
- [cheers]
- Here we go!
Hello, dolls.
all: Hi.
I've come to pump you up
and I don't mean your lips.
So get ready to beat your mug,
pummel the runway, and fight
for the spotlight.
It's time for some
necessary roughness,
but, remember,
just anything but the face.
I'll get the money, mister.
Just don't hurt my face, please.
[applause]
- Hello, hello, hello.
- RuPaul!
- Hi.
- [cheers and applause]
Now, ladies, as you know,
padding is the foundation
of drag.
A queen's girlish figure
depends on it.
For today's
mini challenge,
I want you to make an ass
of yourself.
Literally.
Oh, pit crew.
You better ass somebody.
You have 30 minutes to put
all this junk
in your trunk.
I'm dividing you
into three groups.
And the one queen
from each group
with the juiciest ass
will win.
Ready, set, style.
[exclamations and shouting]
Give me those foams!
Don't kick over
my packing peanuts.
(Chad)
I make fierce pads,
but this ain't how I usually
make my pads, y'all.
(Dida)
30 minutes is not enough.
You need at least a good hour
to even start making pads.
When making your ass,
always draw the shape of Africa.
That's it.
Or, as Latrice would say,
the homeland.
[Latrice giggles]
I'm Polynesian, bitch.
Get it straight, honey.
I thought we were doing an
athletic challenge,
so I'm in a jock.
Sorry about it.
Okay, lady-kins,
time's up.
All right.
Apple bottoms.
Now Jiggly is serving cellulite
realness.
- [laughter]
- Yeah, that's how realness is.
Now walk that ass.
Bottoms up.
Shake it, don't break it.
Phi Phi O'Hara, now that's what
I call a power bottom.
Seems like your pants
are coming down, Madame.
[screams, laughs]
Madame.
Next up,
the ghetto booties.
Make it pop. Now walk.
Hips don't lie,
but that ass do.
Girl, can I get some fries
with that shake?
- [laughter]
- Damn.
I had a proper ghetto booty,
and I was the only one
wearing lipstick.
Next up, the badonkadonks.
A badonkadonk booty,
it's like a whole bunch of
donkadonkadonkadonkadadadada...
Yeah, what she said.
Ass everywhere, ass everywhere.
Ass everywhere.
Ooh, two scoops.
Ladies, all y'all
is sassy assassins.
But three of you really
killed it.
The winners of this mini
challenge are...
Okay, who's ass
is the hit of the class?
- Miss Phi Phi O'Hara...
- Whoo.
- Miss Willam...
- [applause]
- Miss Chad Michaels.
- Hey.
Con-drag-ulations.
If I were you,
I'd hold on tight
to my padded ass,
because for this week's
main challenge,
you'll be transforming
yourselves
into wrestling's trashiest
fighters--
the luscious ladies
of the WTF.
- Yes!
- Whoo-hoo.
I am a big bitch.
Who is gonna outwrestle me?
Nobody.
You know, she may
have a point.
Oh, my God.
I am not athletic at all.
(RuPaul)
This week, you'll need to
flex your charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent to become
over-the-top
wrestling characters.
You will compete in teams.
Phi Phi O'Hara, Willam,
Chad Michaels,
since you won
the mini challenge,
you are team captains.
You get to pick your queens,
starting with Phi Phi.
I'd have to go with Latrice.
Yes.
Dida.
- I will take Milan.
- Yeah.
- Come on down, baby.
- Kenya.
[growls]
Princess.
- Miss Needles.
- I am a knockout.
- [laughter]
- Uh, ow.
(Phi Phi)
I didn't want Jiggly
or Madame LaQueer because
they're always complaining
that their feet hurt
or they don't want to do
active stuff.
Lashauwn.
- [growls]
- There we go.
All right, Willam,
it's between Jiggly
and Madame LaQueer.
I'm just praying, "Please pick
me, pick me, pick me,
pick me, pick me."
Jiggly.
[grunts]
Yes!
Wah!
[laughter and applause]
All right, so that means
that Chad gets Madame LaQueer.
It feels kind of weird
being, like, the last picked.
You know, the weird boy,
but I'm used to it, though.
Each team needs to decide
which two will play
the heroines, or the faces,
and which two will play
the villains, or the heels.
In a moment, you'll meet
three pros who will coach you
in the art of wrestling.
Gentlemen,
start your engines.
And may the best woman win!
Mama, you got
a dream team here.
I know.
That's why I picked it.
There's something
very important.
I had a previous injury
in my right ankle.
I hurt my right ankle
doing a show.
I didn't saw the step,
and my ankle goes click,
and suddenly
I couldn't walk.
So, are you gonna be okay?
- I mean, like, with your ankle?
- Don't worry about my ankle.
(Chad)
I am gonna worry about it,
because it's important.
If your ankle's hurting
and you can't do something,
you need to let me know--
- Safety first, people.
- Safety first.
(RuPaul) Coming up...
Put me down!
Jeeze--aah!
Wait!
Ugh.
Ouch!
[RuPaul laughs]
This maybe the best
episode ever!
- I'm so happy with this team.
- I know. I'm excited.
(Willam)
This challenge includes
a lot of steps.
We have to come up with
a back story, looks, costumes,
moves, everything.
I'm really good with falls
and, like, being, like, stunted.
I do stairs.
I can do anything.
Willam is in charge.
(Willam)
I usually play people
who get beat up,
and I got my ass kicked on
every major network.
And we
just make sure that we--
attitude, attitude, attitude.
Wrestling isn't my thing.
I'm not a violent person.
So I'm a little concerned.
We are gonna ace this,
you guys.
We gon' kick their ass.
(Phi Phi)
So our challenge
is to become wrestlers.
We're the first team to go up
and practice.
I see three humungous dudes
just going at each other.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh-hoo-hoo, yeah.
Bring on the men!
I'm "Hollywood's Own"
Joey Ryan.
Yo soy Hector
"El Chido" Canales.
I'm Mr. K.O.S. "King
of Submission" Ryan Taylor.
And I'm the queen of all media:
Oprah Winfrey
A little bit of the
choreography.
Go ahead and throw her
onto Ryan.
Oh.
You're gonna catch her
and fall.
This bitch heavy.
And then you fall
on your back.
- Oh, my God.
- Fall, bitch.
Thank you for flying
Air Kenya.
Put the mask on your face
before you put it
on your child's face.
(Phi Phi)
Lashauwn's not gonna
actually get the concept
of what she has to do here.
Come on, girl.
Come on.
- [speaks Spanish]
- [whimpers]
[growls]
(Lashauwn)
Everyone in my group's
personality is so loud...
[yells]
And I'm not really like that.
I'm really quiet
and, you know, soft.
Oh.
[laughter]
(Madame)
Let's go, Latrice.
(Joey)
So the bad guys make
their entrance.
They cannot care less
about the audience, right?
- Make us hate you.
- Be yourself.
I got this.
This is cake.
[bleep] y'all.
I don't give a [bleep].
New York, mother[bleep].
Brooklyn!
Jiggly was very aggressive.
[bleep] y'all.
I've got this [bleep].
And I was like, girl,
take it down a notch.
New York, baby.
I'm not from New York.
Oh, well...
And you were good, too.
(Willam)
Princess is giving
closed-captioning,
while she's in stereo.
(Joey)
We're gonna demonstrate some
holds for you.
We were thinking of
a body slam.
Do any of you guys
have a problem with that?
I'm concerned that something
could happen with my ankle.
and making our team lose.
I have a lot
to be nervous about.
All right,
come on, Madame.
My damn face is sick
of looking at you.
[grunting]
Oh. Oh!
- Get her up.
- [screams]
- Put me down.
- Take your time. Slow.
Jeez Louise.
- Ugh.
- Sorry.
- Ouch.
- You okay?
I'm nervous
about Madame LaQueer.
She's not as physical
as the rest of us.
She really has to push, push,
and push through it.
Push it real good.
- Hello, hello, hello.
all: Hi.
Well,
team Phi Phi O'Hara...
Yes.
Which team is the faces?
It would be me and Lashauwn.
So, of course, these two
are the heels.
What is your story?
They gave us the wrong
treatment,
- and we grew beards instead...
- I see.
And we're a little bitter
about that.
Are you actually gonna
be wearing beards?
Yes.
You know,
that concerns me a little bit,
because the luscious ladies
of the WTF need to be beautiful.
I think our story will get
across, and it's not that they--
But you're not the one who's
gonna be looking hideous,
are you, darling?
People watch wrestling because
they want to be excited,
they want to be turned on.
They want beauty.
Now, Lashauwn, can you give me
a little taste
of what your good guy says?
"Oh, I'm gonna kick your ass."
In wrestling,
the good guys are just
as loud and obnoxious
as the bad guys.
Is it fair to say that you're
still working on it,
you haven't, sort of...
- We are still working on it.
- Figured it out yet?
- I mean, yeah, we are.
I'm gonna let you
get back to it.
- All right.
- Bye, Ru.
Team Willam,
what's going on?
Who on your team
are the faces?
[laughs]
Now what are your costumes
gonna be like?
Was that something that you made
or you already had?
(Princess)
We just embellished
on top of it.
(RuPaul)
Oh, I see.
And I'm embellishing on top
of mine as well.
Jiggly, you took some heat
last week for your costume.
Yeah.
(RuPaul)
You know, we are looking for
the luscious ladies
of the WTF.
Oh, I'll be luscious.
I'm not trying to be in that
bottom two again.
(RuPaul)
Gather around, dolls.
Now, tomorrow at the WTF
main event,
we'll be joined by our
extra-special guest judges...
NBA champions Rick Fox
and John Salley.
Ballars.
I think I'll tuck extra-tight
for Rick Fox and John Salley.
Now, remember, safety first,
but, whatever you do,
don't [bleep] it up.
all: Bye, Ru.
Whoo.
(RuPaul)
Coming up...
Bring on the glamazons!
[crowd oohs]
You can't take it.
[laughs]
This is one of my favorite
Drag Race challenges ever!
[cheering]
Ladies and gentlemen,
are you ready to experience
- a female phenomenon?
- [cheering]
Bring on the glamazons!
This show is crazy, girl.
Oh, my God, can you believe
those Bitter Betties
came in here
to ask us for help?
And I even let them
use, like,
my really good
hair products.
- That product?
- Yeah.
That's the hair-growing
tonic.
- [laughs]
- Stop!
[speaks native language]
You--look what you did
to her hair.
Are you upset because you can't
handle all this fishiness?
Your plastic hair
and your plastic tits
and your plastic ass.
We'll handle you.
We'll get in the ring.
- Bring it. Bring it on.
- Come on, girls. Come on.
[cheers]
(RuPaul)
Mess with these nasty girls
and you'll end up with a bad
taste in your mouth.
Give it up for
Latrice "The Beast"
and "Killer" Kenya,
the Bitter Betties.
- Ooh.
- [booing]
Go.
(RuPaul)
Give it up for L.A.'s finest,
Lashauwn "The Blonde"
and Phi Phi "Fierce."
(Phi Phi)
The crowd was chanting
and all the signs that
had our names everywhere.
It felt so good.
I was ready to beat those
bitches down.
- [bell clinks]
- You tell 'em, girl.
You're so pretty.
- Ooh.
- Whoa!
[booing]
[cheers and applause]
Get up!
[speaks Spanish]
Um, honey, I
don't speak Spanish.
[booing]
I want to teach you
Spanish right now.
Puta!
[exclamations]
[screaming]
Oh, hell, no.
[shouts]
Now I'm gonna show you
how to really
beat a mug, bitch.
[screaming]
[booing]
Let me go! Let me go!
[screams]
- Holy, Jesus!
- Whoa!
[screaming]
[exclamations]
Queen down!
[shrieking]
- [bell rings]
- [booing]
(RuPaul)
Bitter, bitter pill
to swallow.
The Bitter Betties win.
[booing]
Those other teams
better watch out
because me and my girls,
we kicked ass.
[booing]
Touch this skin, honey.
They can't take it.
Mm-mm.
They're overgrown...
both: Orangutans.
Speaking of orangutans.
What are you doing in our
dressing room?
We know it's your dressing room,
as tacky as it is,
like y'all two bitches.
Oh, no,
she better don't.
We don't want to go there.
We saw you two
in Coach Carter's office.
Oh, so that's how we got kicked
out of school?
'Cause of y'all bitches?
- Get out.
- Y'all fake-ass hoes.
Get out of here.
[cheers and applause]
(RuPaul)
Tuck and cover...
(Jiggly)
Shut up!
Get the [bleep] out of here.
(RuPaul)
For "Pucker Up" Princess
and "J-Train" Jiggly,
the Thunder Booties.
Get on the wrong side of these
sexy scissor sisters,
and they'll cut you--
Willamina "Hater"
and Dida "Diddles".
They're DWF.
Come on, bitch.
[bell clinks]
Get 'em, girl.
You plus-sized jujube.
Oh, please.
[exclamations]
Come on, bitch.
Now this is why we watch
Drag Race.
I'm giving it all,
balls to the wall,
badass, crazy,
wrestler bitch.
No!
Whoop her ass.
[cheers]
Get her!
[yells]
The Princess, she's not going
as crazy as I am.
So if I get in the bottom two
because of this bitch,
it ain't gonna be cute.
[shouting]
- What?
- That's not fair.
(Lashauwn)
They're tag-teaming her.
That's not fair!
Television don't get
no better than this.
I'm just saying.
Sumo smash!
[exclamations]
And thank you.
Now what?
- [bell rings]
- Bye.
(RuPaul)
The winner is Thunder Booties.
You go home.
Bye. We won.
Team Willam
put on a goddamn show.
[cheers and applause]
Oh, Milan "LaModel",
I have to be honest with you.
I woke up with
an itch down there,
an itch in my pubic hair.
I've got snatch-scratch
fever, too.
The struggle is real.
Look who it is.
It's the Bitch Kickers.
What's up there,
Knockouts?
How's it hanging,
scratch 'n' sniff?
[speaks nonsense]
They must have gotten our
special delivery we sent in
when we banged
their boyfriends.
[chatters nonsense]
- Boink, boink.
- Oh, my God.
- Eww.
- Those Bitch Kickers.
Oh, those cheap,
terrible girls.
[cheers and applause]
Serving face with
a side of whoop-ass.
Give it up
for Sharon "Shocker"
and Milan "LaModel"--
the Knockouts.
Don't hate these girls because
they're beautiful.
[booing]
Shut your pie hole,
you slut.
Hate them because
they're bitches.
You want some of this?
We got plenty for you, too.
Chadarella
"Chainsaw" Michaels...
My girls just make me
so proud.
- The Bitch Kickers.
- [cries]
[bell clinks]
You skinny little
blonde bimbo.
You can run,
but you can't hide.
All right, well, I'm fast
as a butterfly--
[exclamations]
No!
- [booing]
- [coughs]
(Chad)
I am a little bit worried about
Madame LaQueer's ankle.
I mean, you're the captain
of the ship,
you're going down
with the ship.
All right, Kirstie Alley
before Dancing with the Stars.
[exclamations]
[shouts indistinctly]
This is not in my contract!
If my ankle hurted,
I forgot about everything.
I was Madame "LaCrush"
in that moment.
[cheers and applause]
(RuPaul)
Coming up...
We didn't see any of the rebel
that I know you are.
It's not memorable enough
for me.
- It was fake.
- Fake? My girl? Never!
[laughs]
Stop staring at your phone
and pay attention!
Yay.
Miss Cheesecake.
It's elimination day,
and everyone's really anxious
right now to find out
how they did
in the wrestling challenge.
(Dida)
I think we have a really good
shot at winning.
I hope.
I'm just worried.
(Willam)
What are you worried about?
You did great.
You were so funny.
Were you unpleased
with anything
when you left the ring
yesterday?
With me, no.
(Jiggly)
I am kind of iffy
about Princess.
It is a competition
and they don't like one thing,
the whole team goes down--
it's a team challenge.
(Princess)
That energy you're giving off
is bringing everybody else down.
Girl, I cannot
be bothered right now.
Queen Winnona cannot be
bothered dot com, darling.
I am a little bit nervous.
You might feel some sort
of kind of way,
and then you could
be dead wrong.
Mm-hmm.
Thinking you a sickening bitch
and talented bitch,
and they be like,
"wah-wah-wah."
I'm a little nervous to see
what the judges think about
me in the ring.
I did my best,
but you never know
what they're gonna say.
You sew for all the girls
back at home?
Like, the girls.
The girls the girls.
Just girls like you.
By me sewing so much,
I don't really get a chance
to even be in drag myself.
- Uh-huh.
- So it's like I missed
- my drag childhood.
- Ha ha.
So that's why the competition
is perfect for me,
'cause I'm just filling in
for what I missed out on.
That's sickening,
'cause you definitely
about to make up
for some lost time.
- Ooh.
- Hey, that's what you get.
The ultimate drag
boot camp of life.
Madame, what does your family
think about you doing drag?
I'm not close
to my family at all.
My family, for me,
are my friends.
They're the best friends
in the whole world.
Baby, don't. It's okay, mami.
We're selfish and vain
creatures of beauty,
and isn't it bizarre
how we make
the best friends
in the world?
Everybody say "love."
[RuPaul laughs]
Bam!
#Covergirl #
# Put the bass in your walk
# Head to toe
# Let your whole body talk
# And what?
(RuPaul) Hey, guys.
- Hey, baby.
Welcome to the main stage of
RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage,
my tag-team sister.
I got a Full Nelson for you
right here, Mama.
[chuckles]
Billy B, welcome home.
Thanks, Ru.
Are you wrestling
with something?
Not since I was trying to
get my wallet back
from Michelle in the back.
[chuckles]
Hey, Rick Fox, what did you
think of my girls?
I was impressed.
Think there was a lot of fight.
Good. And John Salley.
Hello, Ru.
BK in the house.
[laughter]
I'm so glad you're here.
This week, our queens were
challenged to hit the mats
as the luscious ladies
of the WTF.
Tonight,
I've asked them all to come
decked out in their best
girly-girl attire.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win!
# Welcome to jungle
First up, Kenya Michaels.
Gorgeous.
You know,
Lil' Kim only wishes.
(Michelle)
It's a pink Monday.
(Kenya)
I love the runway.
I feel amazing
because I love to walk.
(Billy)
Now that is a living doll.
(RuPaul)
Mary-Kate Minaj.
Lashauwn Beyond.
She melts in your mouth,
not in your hand.
(Michelle)
Got a penny?
She's got a ball.
[RuPaul laughs]
(Lashauwn)
I'm serving bubble
gum yum-yum,
just having fun being flirty,
pretty, going girly beyond.
Come through!
(Michelle)
Where is her slot anyway?
(RuPaul) Sharon Needles.
(Michelle) Ooh.
The lost Arquette sister.
(RuPaul)
Oh, wow, she's doing femme.
She got an injection of beauty.
(Sharon)
Playing girly-ish, bouncy,
and sexy is just something
really foreign to me.
Just want to show the judges
that I could bring beauty
to the stage
in this competition.
(RuPaul) Mwah.
For your consideration,
Jiggly Caliente.
(Billy)
Kimora Lee Simmons
has put on some weight.
(RuPaul)
Jiggle it, girl.
(Jiggly)
I'm serving banjee girl
meets sweet 16.
Very new York.
(RuPaul)
It's Jiggly 's quinceañera.
London, Paris, Milan.
I see London, I see France,
I see Milan 's underpants.
(Milan)
I am feeling like black Barbie
meets a valley girl.
But, because John Salley
is there,
- I'd rather be a Salley girl.
- [giggles]
(Michelle)
Once she gets pumping,
it's hard to make the body stop.
(RuPaul)
Madame LaQueer.
Represent Puerto Rico.
[Michelle speaks Spanish]
She's working
the asymmetrical hairdo.
(Billy)
Or a hair show in Mississippi.
(Madame)
I feel great.
I feel like I'm floating.
I think is the most beautiful
I've looked
throughout
all the competitions.
(RuPaul)
Where there's smoke,
there's a pussy on fire.
- [laughter]
- This is why I love this show.
(RuPaul)
Dida Ritz.
(Michelle)
I thought it was
P. Diddy's mom.
- [Rick laughs]
(RuPaul) Janice Combs.
(Dida)
I'm giving fish,
I'm giving face,
I'm giving you vogue.
I know my runway is fierce.
(RuPaul)
Look at those legs. My good--
and they go
all the way up.
(Michelle)
They do? Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- They're not wooden?
(RuPaul)
Chad Michaels.
Lady Chatterley.
Oh, my goodness,
the world according to Paris.
(Billy)
Paris Hilton,
where are they now?
(Chad)
I'm serving up girly-girl
realness fish on a stick.
I kind of look just like
a yummy little cupcake.
Mmm. I'm hungry.
(RuPaul)
She wants her old body back.
The Princess.
She had a little time
for a quick blowout
before she came out.
(Michelle)
It's a windstorm backstage,
I'm thinking.
(RuPaul)
Yes, yes.
(Princess)
The look I'm going for is
very rock star
meets little girl.
I am so pumped
for my look today.
(Michelle)
Rock on.
(RuPaul)
It's like there's something
about The Princess.
[Michelle laughs]
Up next, Phi Phi O'Hara.
(Billy)
Telemundo.
(RuPaul)
Telenovela realness.
(Phi Phi)
I was showing
a little bit of skin
and giving them dragged-out
Miami housewife.
(RuPaul)
Ooh, her legs are like peanut
butter--easy to spread.
Latrice Royale.
Ooh, Crown Royal.
I'll have one on the rocks.
(Latrice)
I am feeling good
and looking gorgeous, darling.
Pretty in pink.
I was very pleased.
(RuPaul)
Star Jones called,
she wants her old body back.
(Michelle)
She can't have it.
It's otherwise preoccupied.
(RuPaul)
Allegedly.
[Rick laughter]
(RuPaul)
Next up, Willam.
(Michelle) Hey.
(RuPaul) Wow.
Look at those shoes.
(Willam)
My look for today
is rich bitch mistress.
I'm serving girly-girl
on a platter
to go,
sauce on the side.
(RuPaul)
Look how her outfit
accentuates her sugar walk.
(Billy)
Toddlers and Tiaras,
where are they now?
(RuPaul)
I think she's Tanya Tucker.
Coming up...
In the ring,
you were freaking hil-ar-ious!
- Baby, baby!
- [laughs]
I'm a fan from the hair
to the dress.
I disagree.
I hate your hair.
Oh, he went there.
[laughs]
[dramatic music]
Let's get judgey.
Mm-kay?
Yesterday,
you changed the face
of professional wrestling
forever.
I smell a spin-off.
But one group in particular
really smacked down
the competition.
The winning WTF team is...
Team Chad Michaels.
- Whoo!
- Jesus.
[laughter]
Thank you, Ru.
Con-drag-ulations, ladies.
But two divas
stole the show.
Madame LaQueer,
Chad Michaels.
- The Bitch Kickers.
(Michelle) Good job, ladies.
You are both the winners
of this week's challenge.
You'll receive a selection
of wigs from Risque Wigs.
(Madame)
Oh, my God,
I feel so great.
I certainly actually
proved them wrong
about having
picking me last.
However, neither of you will
receive immunity next week.
Sorry about it.
You may leave the stage.
Ladies, it's time
for the judges' critiques.
First up, Willam.
- Hey, mama.
- Hi.
Did everything turn out
the way you had planned?
I think our moves kicked ass.
Oh, I thought the competition
was weak in the ring.
The faces she was giving us
just didn't seem believable.
It was fake.
Wait a minute,
wrestling is not fake.
No, that wrestling was fake.
(RuPaul)
Thank you, Willam.
Next up, Dida Ritz.
Now why'd you choose this
as your girly look?
I'm really channeling
Carrie Bradshaw,
so I thought downtown
New York, very chic.
In the ring, you had,
you know,
the girl that sort of walked
around the ring thing perfect,
better than you had
the wrestling down.
(RuPaul)
Thank you, Dida.
The Princess.
I'm a fan from the hair
to the dress.
I think I bought that dress
for my daughter.
I disagree.
I hate your hair.
I think it looks
like a bad hair show.
As far as the performance goes,
we didn't see any of the rebel
that I know you are.
I'm a very Zen person.
Just know that
that was me really trying.
Try harder.
All right,
let's go to Jiggly Caliente.
May I call you Jiggly?
Of course you can, Ru.
How'd you feel on the runway?
I felt so cute.
The lollipop in my mouth,
door knockers in my ears.
The lollipop was more
interesting for me
than what you're doing
style-wise.
And tell me about in the ring.
It was very energetic
and over the top.
Jiggly, what was the hardest
part of this challenge?
The thing is, Princess is very
Zen, she's very quiet.
We needed to be,
like, crazy, badass bitches.
(Michelle)
It's hard when
you're in a team,
and you're trying to make up
for both of you.
Thank you, Jiggly.
Next up, Phi Phi O'Hara.
Hi.
You were reading older
than you have to.
You could be younger
and more modern.
I'm watching you, Phi Phi.
I love you.
I think you're gorgeous,
and in the ring,
you were freakin'
hi-lar-i-ous.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Phi Phi.
- Lashauwn Beyond.
- Hi, Ru.
- How are your balls?
- My balls are great.
On the runway,
the gumball machine told me
exactly what those balls
were doing on your chest.
(Michelle)
Better than on her chin.
Ha!
I couldn't disagree more.
Your hair and your makeup,
you look like
a backup singer
for Luther Vandross in 1988.
Rick Fox, what'd you think?
The ring?
It's not memorable
enough for me.
[booing]
I would have liked
a little more story
and color to the character.
- Next up, Kenya Michaels.
- Hola.
I thought it was Nicki Minaj.
I'm not joking you.
Except she doesn't have the ass
of Nicki or the money.
What about as a wrestler?
As "Killer" Kenya?
It was like it was Biggie Smalls
and Lil' Kim all over again.
- Baby, baby.
- [laughs]
You look like a star,
you look modern,
you look fashionable,
and I think
you're the one to beat.
Ooh, she turned it out.
- Latrice Royale.
- Hello, Ru.
Shag-quille O'Neal
Latrice.
[laughs]
You set the tone
for the whole afternoon.
Oh!
- You had me at splat.
- [laughs]
(RuPaul)
Thank you, Latrice.
Well, ladies, I think
we've heard enough.
While you girls untuck
in the Interior Illusions
Lounge,
the judges and I will
deliberate.
You may leave the stage.
All right, just between us
brothers and brother-lovers...
- Thank you.
- Let's start with Willam.
I think Willam is extremely
fierce and extremely talented
and very freakin' funny.
But I also think there's
a borderline of smarminess.
I think there might
be an attitude in there
that can get in the way.
She seemed like a team captain
that didn't lead.
I think she did a good job
of leading.
I don't feel that The Princess
did a good job of following.
All right, let's talk
about The Princess.
Her performance
was really flat.
I kind of thought
there was a rock star in there.
She's not charismatic enough
to be a rock star.
(RuPaul) Dida Ritz.
- She's pretty.
It's just the wigs are not
styled, they're not done.
You know, she was going
for Sex and the City,
and it was more like
Sex in the Alley.
Oh, okay.
Well, I'm not gonna turn
that down either.
- [laughs]
- [clucks like chicken]
Jiggly Caliente.
In the ring, she uses
everything she has.
I thought that was an outfit
until I realized that was
really her belly.
[laughs]
Phi Phi O'Hara.
I don't know what's under
all that makeup,
but she doesn't
paint herself pretty.
I know she's heavy-handed
on the makeup, but hey...
who isn't?
That's right, Mama.
Lashauwn Beyond.
Now, it was remarked that
Lashauwn's personality
was kind of shy.
She'll get out of that shyness
when she realizes
- it doesn't get her anywhere.
(Billy) She's a mess.
And her personality is like a...
Like a brick.
All right, Kenya Michaels.
Little Puerto Rican sweetheart.
(Billy)
She's half the size
of any of them
with double or triple
everything else.
There was nothing wrong.
(Michelle)
Her performance
was flawless as well.
I thought she did a great job
as "Killer" Kenya.
(RuPaul)
Latrice Royale.
She owned that role
in the ring.
It was hard for anyone else
to do better than that.
I was very happy with her,
and I do really like her
and her personality,
so she's gonna be fun to watch.
All right, silence.
Bring back my girls.
More will be Ru-Vealed
Don't go away.
[laughs]
The time has come.
(RuPaul)
Based on your presentation
in the main ring
and on the main stage,
I've made some decisions.
Latrice Royale,
Kenya Michaels,
Phi Phi O'Hara,
you ladies jumped
on this wrestling challenge
and came out on top.
- You are all safe.
- Thank you.
You may leave the stage.
Okay, see, now it's
gon' get tense.
Jiggly Caliente,
we want to know
is there more to you than just
a queen from the 'hood?
You are safe.
Thank you. Thank you.
You may join the other girls.
The Princess.
You were channeling P!nk,
but your performance
was beige.
Well, if that's how
you really feel.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
I'm shocked.
My outfit was on it today,
whether Billy B
liked my hair or not.
And I worked my ass off
yesterday in the ring.
There's no reason why I should
have been in the bottom two.
Willam...
you're safe.
- Bye.
- Oh--okay.
Lashauwn Beyond,
as a wrestler, you were more
mumble than rumble.
Dida Ritz, your Sex and the City
couture
does not deserve a sequel.
I mean, who comes up
with this stuff?
Dida Ritz...
You're safe.
Thank you.
Lashauwn Beyond,
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up
for elimination.
My whole body
started pumping.
I'm nervous because I want
to stay in the competition
and I know this dictates
if I will or not.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies,
this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come
to lip-sync...
for your life.
I'm pretty amazing
and I'm ready to show it.
Bring it on.
Good luck
and don't [bleep] it up.
I said--I said,
don't [bleep] it up.
# Beep, beep
Okay, here's a tip,
you better keep them heels on
during the lip-sync.
Ain't no pussyfootin'
around, girl.
#Sad girls #
# Sad girls
# Talking 'bout bad girls,
yeah #
(Lashauwn)
I want to show Ru that I can
give more personality.
It's not over yet.
I'm not ready to go.
# Now you and me
# We're both the same #
# Both the same
# But you call yourself
# By a different names
# Different name
# Now your mama
won't like it #
# When she finds out,
finds out #
(Princess)
I'm telling myself,
soak up this moment right now.
Live in it.
Balls to the wall do it.
# Toot, toot
# Hey, beep, beep
(Willam)
To do the whole song
with no shoes
in closed-toed pantyhose
like a web-footed duck?
Lashauwn's drag mother's
gonna read him for not even
starting the song in shoes.
# So you want
to spend some time #
# Yeah, beep, beep
# Talkin' 'bout bad girls #
# Beep, beep
# Toot, toot
# Haa
# Beep, beep
[cheers and applause]
Ladies...
I've made my decision.
The Princess...
Shantay, you stay.
You may join
the other girls.
Lashauwn...
you are a young queen.
May this experience lift you
to new heights
above and beyond.
Now sashay away.
Thank you.
It's bittersweet, but
I'm happy for me to be so young
and I've only been doing it for
such a short amount of time.
Some of these girls
being 40 and 50
and, so, it was sickening.
Okay, Lashauwn gave us
the classic line:
This is not RuPaul's
Best Friend's Race,
and I gotta tell ya,
the line lives on forever!
Can I get amen up in here?
- all: Amen!
- Amen! Byee!
Let the music play!
[RuPaul's The Beginning plays]
#
# This is the beginning
# The beginning
# Of the rest of your life