- Previously on "All Stars"...
You'll be auditioning
to be part of the Kitty Girls.
Wait a minute.
I've decided to audition
a few other girls.
[cheering]
- Hey, yo, sis, I'm back!
- In the end,
one of the top five All Stars
will get the chop
and be replaced by
one of the eliminated queens.
My top five All Stars,
con-drag-ulations,
you're the winning team.
[cheers and applause]
BenDeLaCreme,
you're a winner, baby.
[applause]
Which queen have you chosen
to bring back
to the competition?
- There's one queen
who didn't have
as much of an opportunity...
So Morgan.
- Con-drag-ulations, Morgan.
You are back in the game.
Which of your All Star teammates
have you chosen
to get the chop?
- This is the easiest choice
that I have had to make
this entire season.
I'm going home.
- What?
- I wanted this opportunity
to come back,
to fight hard to show myself
what I can do.
I've accomplished that.
I feel like
I'm going home winning.
- DeLa, sashay away.
- The whole room
is actually shaken.
BenDeLaCreme just left
the Spice Girls Geri style.
The person who's won
the most challenges,
who nobody would send home,
left "Drag Race"
on her own accord.
I'm gagged.
- I was not expecting that.
- No.
- At all.
I wasn't even expecting
my name to be called.
I'm happy that DeLa
chose me to come back,
but did DeLa pick me
because she sent me home first
and felt guilty about it?
And why the fuck would she
leave a competition like this?
Did she waste someone's time?
Girl, everybody else
is here for the crown.
We want to win.
- Having had
conversations with her,
I feel like the process
was getting too much for her.
- Also, she hated
having to draw lipsticks.
- Right.
- It's a lot of ways
that you could look at it
as to why he did what he did.
He could've did it because
he was just tired of it.
He could've did it to keep
his name as Miss Congeniality.
It could've been
a promotional move for her,
but Ru like people
that's gonna fight.
Ru like people
that's interested in winning,
competing, staying in the race,
being fierce,
and not playing the radio.
If you wanna leave, leave.
- I just...
I just wish that
she could've fought, you know?
- Even in her final moments,
honey,
DeLa was still using
her little strategy.
You don't only throw
yourself to slaughter,
you save the lion
that was gonna eat you
for lunch yesterday.
She said, oh, I may be going,
but y'all will remember me
as Miss Congeniality.
- The show much go on, girls.
- We've lost
our clear frontrunner,
so now the rest of us
are like, oh, my gosh,
the likelihood of me winning
has just skyrocketed.
This is like your pretty friends
not going to prom,
and now you're, like,
don't forget to write.
I'm gonna write you a letter
on one of my $100,000.
- Morgan, I got to come back
on "Drag Race,"
and I know it's a super gag.
- It is, and I feel like
I'm the luckiest bitch
in the fold.
I'm happy as fuck
that I'm here,
but I missed
a lot of challenges,
and I'm going to have
to work my ass off
to prove that
I deserve to be here.
- BeBe, whose lipstick
did you pull?
- Out of respect for DeLa,
I'm not going to reveal
who I was going to send home
or I was gonna bring in,
just so everybody knows.
So don't come asking me.
- We do this every week, girl.
You don't want to say?
Girl, what the fuck.
We've all had to show
a lipstick.
- And I would just
really, really appreciate
if everybody just lets that be.
I'm not scared, but
at this point we need peace.
We need people to be focused
because it's now
a journey to the top.
So if anybody
is curious about anything,
just know you'll be curious
for the rest of your life.
- She's not gonna tell.
- Let's not talk about it then,
thank you.
- Let's get out of drag, bitch.
- Yes, let's get out of drag.
Oh, baby, Miss BeBe,
she don't want to piss off
whoever the girl is
whose lipstick is sitting up
in her bra tittie, okay?
She said, I ain't pulling
the lipstick from the bra tittie
because I will still need
allies in this game. Oh.
So that Cersei Lannister.
I see now,
but here come the dragons.
I'm Daenerys, bitch.
- The winner of "RuPaul's
Drag Race All Stars"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
a coveted spot
in the "Drag Race" Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize of $100,000.
With extra-special guest judges
Garcelle Beauvais
and Chris Colfer.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race
- ♪ May the best woman
- ♪ Best woman win
- Hey, guys.
- Hi there, darling.
- Halle-loo.
- I'm super ready
for this next challenge.
I'm back, back, back again.
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Hi!
- Hi, All Stars.
Are you decent?
- Yes!
- Oh, my God!
- Well, please give
a "Drag Race" welcome
to Democratic leader
Nancy Pelosi.
- Hey!
- Hi.
- Nancy Pelosi?
I'm dying.
I just want to say
thank you to her,
I want to hug her, I want
to be, like, kick their ass.
Nancy Pelosi is spearheading
the way through.
- Congresswoman Pelosi
is a strong woman
who knows how
to get things done.
- Halle-loo.
- And for 30 years,
she's been a champion
for LGBT rights.
- Yes!
- Welcome!
- And thank you.
- Well, when I got
the invitation
to visit the workroom,
I couldn't resist.
- Wait, did somebody
just say "resist?"
[all laugh]
- Resist.
- Yes!
- Come on.
- I'm honored to be here.
You're an inspiration,
I hope you know,
because you really know
your power.
It's about taking pride,
and that's what you do,
take pride in yourselves,
so you know your power.
- And don't forget to vote.
- Voting is everything.
I mean, people sacrificed
so much in our country
for people to have
the right to vote.
It's a blessing,
but we have to use it.
If you don't vote,
you don't count, and you count.
- Every time you get in drag,
you're making
a political statement.
We live in a world where
a high-power politician
will walk into the workroom,
and it makes you feel hopeful.
- So I know you have to run,
but before you go,
on behalf of my girls
and all the patriotic
Americans watching,
I have one thing to say.
You better work.
[cheers and applause]
- Whoo!
- Thank you so much.
- Bye, Nancy.
- We love you!
- Bye-ee!
[laughs]
Well, speaking of strong women,
I love me a serious Meryl Streep
Oscar-winning drama.
And I also love me
a filthy Amy Shumer comedy,
which got me thinking.
What would happen
if they made a movie
that could be
a little bit of both?
Hmm. Well,
we're about to find out.
For this week's maxi challenge,
you'll be playing important
award-winning female characters
starring in the raunchiest girl
comedy blockbuster of all time.
The working title is...
Rolls off the tongue.
- [laughs]
- Okay. Hey.
- Now, our story features
the most gag-worthy ensemble
of characters ever.
There's Sharon Frockovich,
a busty whistleblower
who fights the power.
There's her Royal Majesty,
the Queen.
She's reigned for decades
with the motto, "Keep calm
and carry a big purse."
- [laughs]
- There's Actavia,
the pie-making maid
turned rocket scientist
who doesn't take crap
from anybody.
And there's the Beige Swan,
an unhinged prima ballerina
obsessed with winning.
And last but not least,
there's LaLa,
a young actress
singing and dancing her way
to movie stardom.
Now, Morgan,
as a welcome back gift,
you get to assign the roles.
- Oh, shit.
- Now, to help y'all
get into character,
feel free to use hair
provided by RockStar Wigs,
and jewelry provided by
Fierce! Drag Jewels.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best All Star win.
- Morgan, do you want
to hand these out?
- Morgan, it doesn't mean
you're the boss.
Don't get too cocky now.
- Ooh, yes, bitch,
I'm feeling very fair,
but, you know,
a little powerful.
I'm just gonna assign the roles
to who I think is gonna
be good in that role.
- I can already see
by the description,
I'd love to have Actavia.
- I'm gonna
read through it first.
- Okay, sorry.
Look, doing well in this
challenge is very important.
Whoever comes out on top on this
goes on to the top four,
so I'm very vocal
about saying, Miss Morgan,
I'm gonna need a heavy role.
I would love to have Actavia,
but I'd be fine with Sharon,
because Sharon
looks like a lot of dialogue
and I'm good at memorizing a lot
in a very short amount of time.
- I think I want LaLa
or Beige Swan,
but I really like LaLa.
- Kennedy?
- I was actually looking
at Beige Swan and LaLa.
- I would love to try LaLa.
I went to school
for musical theater,
and I feel like
I know this girl.
- How about BeBe
doing the Queen?
- Seems fitting.
- I wonder why
I'm being given the Queen.
She's very uppity tight,
very stiff and kind of
very unapproachable.
I don't get it.
- I like Beige Swan just 'cause
I'm, you know, mental anyway.
- [laughs]
- You could do Actavia.
- Thank you.
- You're a singer and a dancer,
so you could do LaLa,
and Sharon Frockovich
can be Trixie.
- Morgan's, like, what roles
are you guys drawn to?
And I'm like, well, I like
this one and this one,
and she goes, great.
I'm gonna give you
this other one.
Not only do I not think
this role is very funny,
but it's a million lines.
Also, I didn't want to wear
brown hair.
Oh!
- Coming up...
- All right, bridesmaids,
who's hungry?
- [laughs]
- Wow, jazz!
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Hello.
- It's time for us to film
the new blockbuster,
"My Best Squirrelfriend's
Wedding--"
What?
"My Best Squirrelfriend's
Wedding" something.
"Dragsmaid's Wedding Strip."
Let somebody else
have that line, baby.
- Welcome to the Ross Mathews
Drag School of Overacting.
- Oh.
- All right.
- This is our beautiful
bridal suite
with furnishings by Objects.
Are you ready to snatch all
the trophies of award season?
- Yeah. [laughs]
- Places!
Places, ladies!
Okay, action!
- All right, Bridesmaids,
who's hungry?
Oh, hey, Queen.
- It appears
we are first to arrive.
- No shit, Sherlock.
- [laughs]
your Royal Highness?
- Don't you mean no, shit,
- Cut. Sorry.
BeBe, can you just be louder?
Can you just project
a little more?
Look, I know you're being
proper, but let us hear it.
- Okay.
I got here a bit early
because I planned
to be assuming the role
of Sharon's matron of honor.
- Cut. BeBe,
some of the line readings
are feeling a little stiff.
It's the School of Overacting.
Exaggerate. Got it?
- Okay.
- Now, I never met the Queen,
but I'm noticing
that BeBe's character
is just BeBe doing BeBe.
Where is the damn queen?
- Sorry I'm late.
I was down at City Hall
shaking my tits
for the sake of justice.
I'm so happy y'all are here.
- Mwah.
Okay, I forgot.
Not a hugger.
- [laughs]
- Sharon Frockovich
is not the role I asked for,
but once I get out there
and I get the laughs,
I'm, like, this role
is actually a gift.
- Sorry I'm late.
Traffic was crazy,
the sky was hazy,
my driver was lazy,
and, wow, jazz!
- I'm so glad you're here.
I thought you were coming
with Beige Swan.
- She did that.
- Cut. Real quick,
Morgan, when you come out,
are you gonna do any,
like, noises or anything?
Because it's your big entrance,
your big moment.
- Okay.
- Let's try again.
- I thought you were coming
with Beige Swan.
- [hisses]
- Girl, that ain't--oh.
- [hiss]
[hiss]
- All right.
- Okay, cut.
Morgan, honey,
are you loving the hissing?
Is there something funnier?
Because it's like
you're coming in
and you're, like, clearly
kind of off your rocker
a little bit, right?
But we're going for funny.
A swan noise. I don't know.
I don't know what it is.
- They only actually hiss.
That's if humans come near them.
- Oh, wow, you are method.
Whatever you're gonna do,
I want you to commit to it.
I mean, because
remember "Black Swan?"
She was kind of like--
- She was a nut job.
- You can make it campier,
just do it a hundred.
- Morgan, dead on arrival.
I actually saw her
as a Sharon Frockovich,
like a slutty
kind of confrontational,
so I'm just like, big mistake.
Huge.
- Coming up...
- You nailed it.
- You were so much fun.
- I got a little excited.
I'm single.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Aah!
- Another day!
It's time to get ready for
today's runway, Red for Filth.
The elimination tonight
is gonna be super important
because next week RuPaul
crowns an All Star.
- Tell you what.
After Adam Lambert last week,
I was trying to smile at Ross
the whole time.
[laughs] Hah.
- It felt like you were,
like, over me being there.
- Were you bothered when Adam
said that you were standoffish?
- Well, only because
people have told me before
that my tone is just so dry
that they thought I was angry.
- Sometimes, Trixilicious,
you don't mean to give that off.
- Yeah.
- But it's unintentional.
- Oh, girl, because
perception is reality.
I might accidentally sometimes
come off as standoffish.
I mean, Trixie on stage
is fun and bubbly,
but me and in real life,
a lot of the times I'm just,
like, a boring white dude
who doesn't like hugs,
so I get how that can read.
It's something I always have
wanted to change about myself.
Our whole industry
is interpersonal communications.
If you're not friendly enough,
someone thinks you're a jerk.
Remember that thing
in West Hollywood, Morgan,
when I got tweets
from other "Drag Race" girls
saying that I was acting grand?
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm not super social,
so a lot of times I'm just
saving it for the audience.
- Look, out
of the "Drag Race" alum,
there are queens
that are definitely known
for being generous with
local queens and the fans,
and then there are also queens
that are the exact opposite.
Trixie has been called out
about how she treated them
when she was in their company.
As much as I love her,
if she thinks that
she's not, like, a little grand,
she's fooling herself.
- They say that about me.
"Oh, she's too bougie."
- BeBe, you don't think
you come off a little bougie?
- Do you think I do, girl?
- Yes.
You are a little bougie, and you
give the girls looks, like this.
- [laughs]
- Brava. You would think
that she is of the royal family
of Zamunda, bitch.
Go to Wikipedia.com.
Mama, you are the definition
of bougie.
- I have this side that
is always very regal, but--
- Oh, yeah.
- I am very goofy.
- Mama, I know.
I'm not--
Please don't take it
the wrong way.
I'm not saying that--
- No, not at all.
- I'm just saying,
you do have an air.
[all laugh]
- Oh, she can't be bothered?
Oh, okay. Okay.
- See, I'm the opposite.
My favorite thing
in the entire world
is when I'm at Mickey's
and there's girls
in the audience
and I get to
bring them up on stage,
even if it's just to watch.
- You're very that girl.
You will call out girls
even though we don't want
to be called out sometimes.
- Girl,
I'd be trying to hide.
I like to go to drag shows
where they don't know
I'm there,
and they don't know,
you know--
I just want to see
the drag show.
- My thing is that I really--
my features are so distinct,
as soon as I open my voice,
they're like, ooh.
- See, that's my whole purpose
of being in "All Star 3."
I want to be that girl,
because before All Stars,
it was like, oh, yeah,
Kennedy's here, yay!
Second thought.
I'm trying to be
their "first thought" queen.
Since Season 7, when
we are all booked together
and we have a meet and greet
and everybody
be in line for them,
and I be by myself.
And then five minutes
before it's time to wrap,
they want to rush over
and grab a picture.
That's what I mean
by second thought.
- Kennedy,
I felt on our season
you did nothing but
a great, great, great job.
- Thank you.
- Well, and I think
that all of us
that have
gotten to this point
feel like that Ru-demption
that maybe we didn't even
come for, we've gotten.
- That's why I just--
I just feel good about it all.
I want to be that queen
that people know immediately
who I am.
It's gratification, validation,
and I believe in working hard
to get what I want.
- ♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Cover girl,
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
♪ Cover girl
[applause]
- Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul's
Drag Race All Stars."
It's Miss Golden Globes,
Michelle Visage.
- Gladiator.
[all laugh]
- Funny man, and our director
this week, Ross Mathews.
- Ru, I love directing so much,
I'm changing my name
to Martin Scor-sissy.
[all laugh]
- Members of the Academy,
for your consideration,
Garcelle Beauvais.
- Ru, you are giving me life
in that dress.
- And you look gorgeous.
- Thank you.
- "Drag Race" superfan
Chris Colfer.
Are you filled with "Glee"
to be here?
- I'm filled with something,
and boy does it itch.
[all laugh]
- This week,
we challenged our queens
to serve award-winning
performances,
and tonight on the runway,
category is Red for Filth.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best All Star win.
First up,
BeBe Zahara Benet.
- Oh, dear,
someone forgot their SPF.
- Kennedy Davenport.
I hope those aren't
blood diamonds.
[all laugh]
Morgan McMichaels.
- Whoa, she showed us
her bag and her pipe.
- [laughs]
Shangela.
- Wow, are you happy to see me.
- Trixie Mattel.
- She clearly
likes to be reamed.
[all laugh]
- ♪ Sexy, sexy drag queen
- Coming up...
- You are a vision.
- I live
for moments like this.
- I would have loved bigger
and more ridiculous.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Welcome, All Stars.
Let's begin with a sneak peek
of your movie,
which has already been banned
in 47 countries.
[all laugh]
- Glamazon Studios presents
the most important film
of all time.
[cell phone rings]
- I know you're busy,
so I'll keep this quick.
I'm getting the old gang
together,
and I want you guys
to be my maids.
- Oh, hell, no.
I'm a rocket scientist now.
- My bridesmaids!
I'm getting married.
- Coming this summer,
all your favorite award-winning
actresses come together in...
Trixie Mattel
is Sharon Frockovich.
- Yeah, that's all
you got, lady,
two big feet
and ugly fucking shoes!
- Here comes the bride.
- Poisoning
the wig water supply?
Big mistake. Huge.
- BeBe Zahara Benet
is the Queen of everything.
- Don't you mean
Your Royal Highness,
Elizabeth Alexandra
Mary Stuart
Masterson Mastroantonio
Bolina Brown?
[all laugh]
- Kennedy Davenport is LaLa,
a struggling actress who thinks
she can sing and dance.
- Sorry I'm late.
Traffic was crazy,
the sky was hazy,
my driver was lazy,
pow, jazz!
- Morgan McMichaels
is Beige Swan,
a prima ballerina driven
to perfection and madness.
- [quacking]
Quack!
- She did that.
- Shangela is Actavia,
a maid who's also
a rocket scientist.
- Ain't nobody can make
my famous fudge pies
and put a man on the moon.
[whistle]
- Ladies, don't move.
You are all under arrest.
Now put your legs
behind your head.
[cheers and laughter]
- You're a dirty cop,
and I'm a whistleblower.
- Okay, honey,
launch that rocket.
- And when these divas
let loose,
who knows what drama
will happen?
- How dare you invite
another dancer here!
I deserve to be maid of honor.
Give me that trophy!
- He's dead!
- You killed him!
- Why does this
always happen to me?
- But when
the church organist cancels...
- You gotta be
fucking kidding me!
- Will they make it
down the aisle?
- This is some "How To Get Away
With Murder" shit.
- Quack, quack,
quack, quack, quack.
- If you stay ready,
you ain't got to get ready.
- Pow!
- Girl, you don't need
an organist, you've got us.
- We ate Actavia's pie.
- Hit it!
[playing the "Wedding March"
by passing gas]
[all laugh]
- You guys really are
the best Squirrelfriends.
- So if you loved the poop scene
in "Bridesmaids,"
but also love high brow
award-winning actresses,
then you'll love...
Rated P-U.
[all laugh]
- Good job, girls.
- Thanks, Mother.
- Thank you.
- It's time
for the judges' critiques,
starting with
BeBe Zahara Benet.
- You are a vision.
The headpiece, the makeup,
you look divine.
- Thank you.
- Tonight
in the acting challenge,
you played the Queen,
but you're a drag queen Queen,
so I would have loved
bigger and more ridiculous.
- You were more Helen Mirren,
and I needed Yellin' Mirren.
- It would've been hilarious
if you did a British accent.
- I feel sometimes when
you try to copy some accents,
it can be taken as being rude.
- On this program?
[all laugh]
- Thank you, BeBe.
Up next, Shangela.
- I love your outfit.
I live for moments like this.
- When it started to inflate,
I got a little excited.
I'm single.
[all laugh]
- And if you'll notice
in the acting challenge,
I didn't give you
a lot of direction.
I just sat back
and enjoyed the Shangela show.
- You nailed it, and I think you
did Octavia Spencer very proud.
- Thank you.
- Up next, Trixie Mattel.
- What's your favorite book,
just off the top of your head?
- Oh, my God.
[all laugh]
- This outfit is everything.
- And then
in the acting challenge,
you were so much fun
because every take
you tried something new.
- And that moment
when you used the baby's hand
to wipe your hair, I died.
- You are now
pushing yourself
out of the Trixie Mattel box,
so to speak,
and you're making yourself
do things
that maybe wouldn't be
in your comfort zone.
- Yeah.
- But I think
you taking those risks
is paying off in spades.
- Thank you.
I think so, too.
- Up next,
Kennedy Davenport.
- Tonight, watching you here,
I think fabulous and regal.
- Thank you.
- But I'd lighten up
a little bit
on the highlighter on the nose,
because that's all we're seeing.
- When it came
to the acting challenge,
I thought you were
maybe a little more,
like, Jodie Foster
in "Nell,"
than Emma Stone
in "La La Land."
I was kind of hoping
you'd do more
of the Emma Stone nuances,
you know.
She's very serious
about everything.
- It was kind of one note.
She kept doing the same thing
over and over.
- Pow! Pow!
- And it really
didn't go anymore.
- Up next,
Morgan McMichaels.
- Tonight you're dressed
like Judy Garland
in "Meet Me in St. Louis."
Like, even though your boobs
are hanging right out--
- I was feeling
my Michelle moment.
- There you go.
This is so beautiful.
- I love me
some Morgan McMichaels.
I am so happy to see you back,
but Morgan,
you got to choose the roles
for the acting challenge.
If I were in your heels,
I would have picked
Beige Swan last.
That's a tough role,
because to play crazy,
you either have to play
so over-the-top crazy,
or you have to play that
you're concealing you're crazy.
I worked with you the most,
and I got you to quack.
- Quack, quack, quack.
- I wanted even more.
- Thank you, ladies.
Based on
the judges' critiques,
I've made some decisions.
- Shangela, Trixie Mattel,
con-drag-ulations.
You are the top two All Stars
of the week.
[applause]
- Thank you.
- Word.
- You've each won a $1,000
gift card from Elea's Closet,
and a set of luggage
from Raden luggage.
- This week,
if you're not in the top,
you're in the bottom.
That means BeBe,
Kennedy, Morgan,
you are the bottom three.
Shangela, Trixie,
each of you needs to decide
which of the bottom three
you'll eliminate
if you win the lip sync.
So while you queens
deliberate in the workroom,
the judges and I
will be contacting
our elected representatives.
[telephone rings]
Thank you, ladies.
You may leave the stage.
- Coming up...
- I thought I gave
as much as I could.
- I can't crush
a friend's dream.
- I'm very proud of what I did.
- Who gives a shit, okay?
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Ooh!
- So I'm in the bottom.
And the curse
of the returning queen
is that most of us go home
the episode
after we've returned,
and I do not want that.
I want to break the curse.
- Well, I want to say
congratulations
to Trixie and Shangela.
- Oh, thank you.
- You guys did an amazing job.
- I feel good about what I did.
- Right.
I mean, it's all
strong forces, you know?
But I know for sure
that I didn't do a bad job.
- I thought I gave
as much as I could.
I think the Queen
would have been a lot of fun,
but, I mean, I just didn't
want to do something
that would have
been expected of me.
- Morgan, you know, she got
an opportunity to come back,
and if you only have one chance,
don't try nothing new.
Stick to what you know.
Who gives a shit, okay?
- BeBe, how do you feel?
Because you seem really quiet.
- I personally feel
that if you read the description
of who my character is,
she was very stuffy,
very uptight.
I was trying
to be that character.
I'm very proud of what I did.
When you look at all the girls,
I've been the most consistent.
Yes, there is a top two,
then everybody down there
becomes the bottom.
But I've stayed safe
and I've won challenges.
I should stay.
- If my face
looked like yours right now,
I would never cover it
in my life.
You look so beautiful.
- Thank you.
- You look like Ornacia,
but like--
- Oh! [laughs]
- Who's Ornacia?
I don't know who that is.
- She's fully
never seen "Drag Race."
- Then mannequin head, girl.
- BeBe won "Drag Race,"
and stopped watching it.
- No, no, it's not that.
- You didn't watch
"RuPaul's Drag Race,"
the show
that gave you your career?
Are we all beneath you?
You couldn't watch us on the TV?
Oh, okay, I see.
- Girl, get ready.
They gonna "me-me"
your ass to death, bitch.
- Wait, what is "me-me?"
- You know how they, um--
- Meme.
- Yeah, that.
[all laugh]
- I'm in a nightmare.
BeBe's never seen "Drag Race."
Kennedy doesn't know
what a meme is.
Winning the crown
is the only way out alive.
Would you guys like to sit
on a sofa and possibly cry?
- Yeah, come on, BeBe.
- I'll go first, shit.
- Let's have a sister
conversation.
- Well, shit
- So tell me why you made such
a mess of this whole challenge?
- Oh, honey, I did not make a
mess of this whole challenge,
because when I sit and listen
to what the judges have to say,
I mean, it was like, oh, well,
you were kinda quiet.
I wish you could have
played her over the top.
If those are the critiques
you're giving me right now,
I must have done something
great, and that's the way I am.
- BeBe has, like,
an unshakeable confidence,
which in a lot of ways
is a huge asset.
But on the other hand, girl,
you did get negative critiques,
and you're, like,
fully pretending
like it didn't happen.
I was there.
- You've seen my track record.
You know my work.
If you value what I bring
to the competition,
then I would want to trust
that you would make
the right decision.
- Okay, let me ask you this.
Who would you send to the house?
- Shit.
I didn't win.
- No, bitch.
- [laughs]
- Listen, I'm not
sending Kennedy home.
She's been a rock for me
in this competition as a friend,
and I want to know
what she has to say
because this is really a hard
choice for just one person.
- I was thinking about Morgan,
because she struggled the most.
- In that challenge, yes, ma'am.
- Right.
- But do you think that's enough
to send her to the house?
I know Morgan
didn't do her best,
but I don't want to be the one
to send her to the house
before she's had a chance
to really shine.
This is her second chance,
and, look, I know
about second chances,
and I can't crush
a friend's dream.
- On the other hand,
you have BeBe,
who could have dove in it more.
- But in this challenge,
I don't even think she feels
she did anything wrong.
- Right. I kind of put her
in the place of where Milk was.
- Miss BeBe
is a fantastic queen.
However, when you don't think
you have any flaws,
that's a flaw.
- Either way you go,
you have just cause.
- Uh-huh. Okay.
[telephones ring]
- Ru, Elizabeth Warren
says hi-ee.
- Oh. Tell her
I said, hey, girl, hey.
- Kamala Harris, tell the GOP
to stay out of my uterus.
- Wow. Cory Booker
just retweeted me.
- Ross, did you get through
to the president?
- No. I think my fax paper
is jammed.
- Keep trying.
Who knew it was so easy
to contact your congressman
or congresswoman?
All you gotta do
is go to house.gov
and punch in your zip code.
It's just that easy. Bam!
[telephone rings]
Hello? Maxine?
- I like how you got
this demure look,
but you still found a way
to make it a full hooker.
- Well, you know,
there's something to be said
about talent.
Both Trixie and Shangela
have been in my position.
They've both left
the competition and come back,
so maybe they both have
a little bit more insight
to what is going on in my head,
and I want to get
to the top four.
I just want it so bad.
I haven't been here.
Like, Kennedy and BeBe
have rolled with you guys
from the jump.
So that makes me feel
a little, like,
well, maybe I might be going.
- When I came back
on "Drag Race,"
I felt like everybody
was happy to have me there,
but I did feel
like I wasn't sure
if there was a way
I could possibly stick around,
you know what I mean?
- Like the uneasiness
is unsettling.
- I feel you.
Morgan needed to basically
walk on water yesterday,
and instead she drowned.
- I live for you.
- But I kind of have sympathy
for Morgan.
I know what it's like
to have to get back into it
and get in the same mindset as
people who have been competing.
So I don't know.
- Silence!
Actually, silence equals death,
so keep going on those phones.
Democracy is at stake.
And bring back my girls!
[telephones ring]
[all answering]
- Three great queens,
and as I look at their names,
I want to make sure
I've considered everything.
[exhales]
There's somebody who's been in
the bottom for the first time.
There's somebody
who's making their comeback.
who has won challenges,
but is in the bottom again.
I have to make a decision,
so I'm making a decision.
- I'm really confused
right now.
BeBe, Morgan, BeBe, Morgan,
BeBe, Morgan, I don't know.
[exhales]
Because I care about
both of these queens,
and no matter how this goes,
I might lose a friend over this.
In this moment,
I'm Natalie Imbruglia: "Torn."
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Welcome back, ladies.
Two All Stars stand before me.
Ladies, this is your chance
to impress me,
win $10,000,
and earn the power
to give one of the bottom queens
the chop.
The time has come...
[thunder]
to lip sync...
[echoing] for your legacy.
- I don't have a reputation
here as a lip sync assassin.
That doesn't mean I'm not gonna
give it my whole everything.
- Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
- Good evening, everybody.
I'm so happy
y'all was up in here.
My name
is Miss Valerie Valentine,
and I'll be your hostess
and MC for this evening.
How's everybody doing?
♪ Kiss me like you miss me
♪ Hump me
like you hate me ♪
♪ Shoot a movie on my face
♪ Take another picture
♪ Put it on my Insta
♪ Come on,
give me another taste ♪
♪ Scamming money,
don't make no money ♪
♪ But freaky money do get
the money ♪
♪ 'Cause freaky money
do get the money ♪
♪ 'Cause freaky, freaky
♪ Money, money,
m-m-money, money ♪
♪ Money, money, money, money,
money, money, money, money ♪
♪ Money, money, money,
money, freaky ♪
♪ Money, money, money, money,
money, money, money, money ♪
♪ All up in the club,
I'm making ♪
♪ Money, money, money, money
♪ Walking down the street,
I'm making ♪
♪ Money, money, money, money
♪ When I shake my ass,
I'm making ♪
♪ Money, money, money, money
♪ Even when I sleep,
I'm making money, money ♪
♪ A freaky deek-deek,
la la la la ♪
♪ Ah, get up!
♪ A freaky deek-deek,
la la la la ♪
♪ Ah, get up!
♪ A freaky deek-deek,
la la la la ♪
♪ Ah, get up!
♪ A freaky deek-deek-
deek-deek-deek-d-d-d ♪
♪ Money, money, money, money,
money, money, money, money ♪
- [laughs]
♪ Yeah, yeah
♪ Big Freeda,
better known as Queen Diva ♪
♪ Cute features,
hair long like Mona Lisa ♪
♪ Pockets full,
I don't need to use my Visa ♪
♪ Lotta freaky money
when I'm booking out arenas ♪
♪ Hoes shaking money,
making ass everywhere ♪
♪ Toot it up, bend it over,
go on grab a chair ♪
♪ Make it work, make it twerk,
Imma take you there ♪
♪ If you ballin', throw
your freaky money in the air ♪
♪ Don't give me your love,
I don't want it ♪
don't want your-- ♪
♪ Don't give me your love,
I don't want it ♪
I want your-- ♪
♪ She want that money, money,
she want that money, money ♪
♪ I want that money, money,
money, money, money, money ♪
♪ Money, money, money, money,
[laughter and applause]
- Ladies,
I've made my decision.
It's not over
till the fat lady twerks.
Shangela, you are a winner.
- Yay! Yay!
- Con-drag-ulations.
You've earned a cash tip
of $10,000.
- Thank you.
- Trixie, you are safe.
You may join the other girls.
Will the bottom three
please step forward.
Shangela, which queen
have you chosen to get the chop?
- You know,
Kennedy and BeBe and I
have been here since day one
fighting to get
to this top five,
and Morgan I've known
since I started my drag career
almost seven years ago.
And any one
of these three queens
would be a fantastic All Star,
but unfortunately, I have
to send one home tonight.
It's not something
I want to do,
but it's part of what
the gig is.
The person I'm sending home
is my sister and friend...
Morgan.
- As it is written,
so it shall be done.
Morgan, you are
and will always be an All Star.
Now sashay away.
- Thank you, guys.
Love you much.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't go.
- No, I'm not leaving.
I'm not Fifi, girl.
I hug everybody.
- I love you, Morgan.
- I love you, too.
- I'm not so excited
to be going home,
but I'm at peace with it,
and I would have done
nothing different.
Why blend in
when you can stand out?
I got to be on
"All Stars Season 3,"
so All Star forever.
And I fucking better
get two of these.
Queen of Scotland is out.
- My fierce final four,
con-drag-ulations.
Next week is our All Star
grand finale,
and the race
has never been closer.
So I want to hear from our fans.
Which one of these bitches
deserves a coveted spot
in the Drag Race
Hall of Fame?
Are you Team BeBe,
Team Kennedy,
Team Shangela,
or Team Trixie?
Let your voice be heard
at RuPaul's Drag Race,
#AllStars3,
and tune in in one week
when we crown a winner, baby.
Now, girls, listen closely.
If you can't love yourself,
how in the hell are you
going to love somebody else?
Can I get an amen
up in here?
All: Amen!
- All right.
Now let the music play!
- ♪ Charisma
♪ Uniqueness
♪ Nerve and talent
♪ Let your body tell the truth
- Next time on "All Stars..."
- You'll be writing,
singing, and dancing
in the most ambitious
production number
in "Drag Race" herstory.
Oh, and one last thing.
- Oh, bitch, the gag.
- Someone pulled a muscle
pulling his patch.
- The queen
who has earned her spot
in the "Drag Race"
Hall of Fame is...