- Previously on All Stars...
Blessed be, Kitty Girl.
- What the hell is going on?
- You haven't seen
the last of me.
The day of reckoning is upon us.
- Y'all scaring me.
[screaming]
- How many of my eliminated
girls were you able to capture?
- We think you'll be pleased.
- Show yourselves.
- Morgan of BenDeLaCreme.
- Aja of Bebe Zahara Benet.
- Chi Chi of BenDeLaCreme
and Shangela.
- Wait a minute, just three?
- Sorry we're late.
- Sorry.
- Sorry, sorry, sorry.
- So sorry, oh, my gosh.
- Milk of Kennedy.
- Thorgy of Shangela.
- The time has come
for your revenge.
[cackling]
- Wait...
Did I leave the iron
on in my dressing room?
No, I'm good.
[cackling]
[sighing]
- Good job, girl.
- Good job, bitch.
- You were really fabulous.
"I love you bitches.
Honestly, thank you from
the bottom of my heart."
- [sighs]
It's a bummer.
I think Aja kind of
made us feel motivated
that someone so young
was so good.
- She was such a firecracker.
It was just really, really hard,
but I know she is going
to take everything from here,
and she is going
to be unbeatable.
I made the right decision
when I thought Shangy was
the stronger contender,
but it's also sad
because I know Aja
really wants to be here.
To Aja.
- To Aja.
- Love you Aja-poo.
- Ooh, let me get
all this off.
Help me Lord Jesus.
- So girl, who you pick?
- I also chose Aja.
- Oh, thank you.
- It is obviously you helped me
last week, but besides that,
you had a better track record,
you've done more
with your time on "Drag Race,"
and I believe that next week
you would be doing things
maybe Aja couldn't.
- Well, I'm so happy to be here.
Thank you and thank you.
When both BeBe and Trixie
choose me to stay,
I'm like, honey, the work
has not been in vain.
I do want the validation from
Ru, but I love having it
from my sisters as well.
Them saying, you know what,
you belong in this competition.
I know I belong, but it's nice
to know they think that too.
So we've been basing a lot
of stuff on track records.
Where are we on track
records right now?
BenDeLa has the most.
- I have one win.
- I have one.
- One, one, two, one.
- But then if we go on bottoms,
then how many bottoms?
- One.
- How about you?
- Never.
- I've been in the bottom twice,
but I really do just believe
that the race is not given
to the swift or the strong,
it's the one that endures.
It's not about a track record,
it's about who is there
at that moment,
and that's what
it's about in my opinion.
- It was clear what the criteria
was when it was like all of us,
but now it's getting very,
like, personal viewpoints.
We all have our own
individual scorecards.
Ben has the most wins,
then Shangela, but,
like, Shangela and I have been
the most with "Drag Race."
We probably have
the biggest careers.
That also matters.
Kennedy is a fucking fabulous
competitor,
but she has the worst
track record here,
and BeBe won
"Drag Race" already.
It's like apples and oranges.
We're gonna have to pull
lipsticks we don't wanna pull.
It's bad.
It's bad news, Brenda.
- [RuPaul] The winner of
"RuPaul's Drag Race All Stars"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia
Beverly Hills cosmetics,
a coveted spot in
the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize
of $100,000.
With extra-special guest judges
Adam Lambert and
Baby Spice, Emma Bunton.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race
- ♪ May the best woman
best woman, win ♪
- Hi, everybody.
[vocalizing]
- There is significantly
less of us here.
- It's another day in the
workroom, and baby, I'm here.
[laughing]
Thank God I'm still here.
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Oh my God!
- Hey!
- Ru!
- My top five All Stars.
For this week's maxi challenge,
you'll be auditioning
to be part of
my new super group,
the Kitty Girls.
- Ooh.
- Hashtag #AllStars3.
First, each of you
needs to create
a distinctive Kitty Girl
look and persona,
and then write lyrics
for your solo
on the Kitty Girls
debut single.
- Oh.
- Now, to help you purr-fect
your Kitty Girl look,
you can use fabric
provided by Mood,
and hair provided
by Rock Star Wigs.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman--
wait a minute.
I almost forgot.
- Oh, Lord.
- In addition to you,
my top five All Stars,
I've decided to audition
a few other girls.
[screaming]
- Hey, yo, Sis, I'm back.
- Say hello to Morgan, Thorgy,
Chi Chi, Milk, and Aja.
- Oh, my gosh.
- [Aja] These remaining queens
are acting like
they're not bothered, but
they're clearly bothered.
- The eliminated queens
will be forming their own
competing Kitty Girl group.
- Ahh!
- Work!
- And tomorrow on
the main stage,
the two groups will go head
to head and toe to toe.
Now in the end, one of
the top five All Stars
will get the chop
and be replaced
by one of the
eliminated queens.
- Oh, it's gonna be so good.
a crock of shit.
- I think it's
It's not fair,
and it's not right.
I'd rather one of us leave
and that be that,
not let another bitch come in
and we've been working
five damn episodes and
they done missed all of them.
- In a moment you'll head
to the studio
where you'll be working with
the amazing Adam Lambert.
- Oh!
- All right!
- And tomorrow on the main
stage, we'll be joined
by the legendary Emma Bunton
from the Spice Girls.
- [cheering]
- Oh my God!
- I can't believe
Baby Spice is coming.
I spent a good part of my youth
pretending to be Baby Spice,
and a lot of my adulthood,
so I'm pretty happy.
Oh, my God.
- Now, I know you have a lot
of catching up to do,
so gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best All Star win.
- Oh!
- Oh, bitch.
- I'm so happy to see you.
- Baby, do not be fooled by
the hugs and the kissin'
and the sissin' and the
whatever you wanna call it.
Baby, the shit is
about to hit the fan.
- Great day to have never
drawn a lipstick.
I never won a lipstick,
so I'm like hey, guys.
- So you just wanna
coast through?
- Shangela, I heard you
were really mad
about my lipstick message
that I left.
- To be very honest with you,
I was like not a big deal.
- What did you think
I meant by that?
- Time out.
I'm gonna let you know.
So the lipstick message when
you told me to suck it,
I told everybody in this room,
she must have maybe been
in her feelings.
- Cool.
- Now, the next day, when
I discovered a note
that was left for Trixie
that said,
"Shangela is a fucking
shady fucking bitch",
I was cracked by that.
- She posted that in her area.
- This fucking letter again?
- Posted it?
- Yeah.
- Well, Trixie, did you show
it to her to get her upset?
- No.
- She hung it on the wall.
- She put it on her wall.
- It was obviously
done for a reason.
- This is what transpired,
because I can't have
this conversation again.
- I can. I'd love to have
a conversation about feelings
about me behind my back.
Don't shush me Trixie.
I'm sorry if you don't want
to talk about it anymore,
but guess what, I do.
I'm a little surprised that
like everyone got to see that
and then judged me
while I wasn't here
when it supposed to be
like a joke to her.
- Girl, it was taped
on her wall.
That's what I told Trixie.
I said, that's between
you and your friend.
I would've read the note
and like, girl, she crazy,
and put it in my pocket.
I wouldn't have posted it
where everybody could see.
- I hate that note.
- I never dragged you like that.
It actually hurt my feelings.
- It sounds like you
were really upset, girl.
- No, I was.
Because I had never called
you no shady fucking bitch.
I would not have written
something like that about you.
- No, you wouldn't have.
I was in my feelings.
So moving forward, I had
time to contemplate
why you chose my lipstick.
What the hell was that about?
- I always said I was hoping
to keep strong competitors,
but in the challenge, I felt
like she had more to do--
- And you guys had some
secret, like, shaking hand,
like, oh, no matter what?
- Okay, I'll answer your
second question next, okay?
I felt like she had a
taller order in her challenge.
She was asked to do 15--
- That's not what
you just said that.
- Hold on.
Baby, I ain't done.
Numero uno, I said--
- Girl, I love you.
- Baby, you keep-- don't
start about loving me,
because you keep
cutting me off
while I'm trying
to say my thing.
Either--I'll let you finish,
and then you tell me
when it's my turn.
- All right.
- Luckily the tables
are pretty heavy,
so there was gonna be no
flipping of any sort of table.
- You feel that the only
reason I kept Kennedy
is because we're friends.
That's not true.
I just felt like she had
more to do in the challenge,
therefore, to me,
you were supposed
to up the amount you did
in the challenge.
It was a hard choice to make,
and I just made it.
- And it happened to be me.
- Yes, ma'am.
- So when I come at you like,
I have the right to feel
that way too because
it's how I feel.
- I get it, no tea,
and I hope we can still
be cool after this.
- Let's just move forward.
I also still love Shangela,
but what I wanted
was like closure.
I don't think I should've been
in the bottom two,
however, Shangela didn't
put me there.
- So Ben, what was your
criteria for sending me home?
- We had talked about the
idea of wanting to keep
the girls moving forward
who were performing the best.
- No. We did not come
to no consensus on that.
- No, you didn't.
- And you had said that
you would knock
those girls out of it,
so I was like, okay,
if I make this decision now,
moving forward
we'll all be on
the same page.
It was a hard decision
to make at the time.
- Had you said it--
- But also keep in mind,
if that had been removed,
I still would've thought
that you were
the weakest performance
of the night.
- But in appearance,
in performance, I didn't flub.
If you'd listened to what
the judges said,
there's no way that
I was weaker than her.
But you should know this,
at least I was honest
with everybody up front.
You changed it--
- But I was honest
with you as well.
- No you--
no, you weren't.
Because you sat on
that white couch
saying we're gonna do it
the way the judges want
and we're gonna be sisters,
and then at the last minute
you changed your mind.
You have every right
to do that,
but for me, that makes
you a coward.
- Ooh, oh Miss Morgan is hot.
Bitch, somebody must've
put hot coals down
Miss Morgan's panties, honey,
'cause she is steaming.
- So when you said I'm doing
the best for the girls,
you basically told me
I wasn't part of that,
and that's fine 'cause
you don't know me.
- Well, you decided-- no,
I don't know you at all.
- You sure don't.
- Like I said,
super forthright--
- Right.
- --in saying that you didn't
want to play by the rules
that the community--
- But you understand what
a hypocrite is, right?
- Ooh!
Sister, I don't think
they're gonna find
a bridge over troubled
water, unh-unh.
- [RuPaul] Coming up...
- I thought the least
you could've done was say,
hey, Aja helped me.
- You sat on this couch,
read my drag for feel.
- What?
- I don't owe nobody no apology,
point blank and simple.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- If you were judging the way
that you said you were judging,
I should've still
stayed in the competition,
and that's just flat out.
So at the beginning of
the competition,
DeLa made it seem like she was
going to eliminate the queens
who had the worst critiques
by the judges,
and she didn't do that.
She eliminated me based on
the fact that I was going
to send the strongest girl
in the bottom home.
So now I'm calling
her out basically.
- While I see that it's, like--
- Hypocritical?
- There's, like--
- Yeah.
- I see why there's hypocrisy
in that, which is why I said
as soon as you walked out
the door that I'm trying
my best to make the decision
I think is right
for the competition over all.
- I'm not a fucking idiot.
because DeLa's afraid of
DeLa will not own shit
what the fans think, and
that's just straight up.
- I mean...
- No other way you try
and mince the words,
it's hypocritical.
- I'm tuning out because
it does not help me
to be present for this.
Like I'm not available
to be vented at.
[clears throat]
- Okay, so this is how I feel.
I wasn't mad that
you sent me home.
I was more mad that when
the judges were like,
we love the way you look,
we love your outfit,
and you literally
just said thank you.
And I just thought it was
kind of messed up because
I thought the least
you could've done was say,
"Hey, Aja helped me."
- Really?
Would it have changed anything?
Hey, Judges, oh, she helped
me with part of my body.
Would it have mattered
that nobody really liked
what you have presented
on the runway?
- I also feel like in
the deliberation, like,
you're about to do right now
and cut me off,
I tried to talk to you
and you kind of
just spoke over me
the whole time.
- Okay, great.
I'm happy that you were
able to express that.
First of all, I'm going
to say that your elimination
was one of the toughest
for me and very emotional.
- Here we go, Mother,
hear me out.
I'm like what is with
these introductions.
What are you, the queen of--
shut up, just answer
the question.
- I'm sorry if you feel that
I was talking over you.
I feel like that was a moment
that I could really, really
encourage you, and when
it comes to the runway
everybody knows I don't talk
too much on the runway.
I just don't.
- But everybody on
the runway said who helped.
I just think it's fair
because you're getting praise
for something that it's
a design challenge
and they're up there
thinking that
you made that
from head to toe.
- Aja, what I'm simply
saying is a compliment
was given to me about
my garment, thank you.
- Ah!
Does it take that much
pride to like just take
a step back and say,
"Aja helped me a lot,
thank you so much."
Does that really take that much?
- [Aja] Whatever. I didn't come
here to argue with BeBe.
I came here to continue
my run on the show,
but if BeBe ends up in the
bottom, I will send her home.
That's all I have
to say on that one.
[laughs]
- Since we're talking
about sending girls home
and what the reasoning behind
sending somebody home is...
I don't--
what was your reason?
- You don't get why
I sent you home?
- No.
- I have a lot of reasons.
Okay.
The first reason was during
the Bitchelor
it was like a struggle for you,
and I didn't find
not one moment funny.
So for me, that was
the first X.
Second of all, you sat
on this couch,
read my drag for feel.
That shit hurt my feelings.
Then you would have
chosen me to go home.
- I think I would've
chosen Thorgy to stay.
- That sent a shock through
my brain too, because I'm like,
I thought we were
closer than that.
- And you wanted
to save your friend.
- Huh?
- And you wanted to
save your friend.
- No, that's not it at all.
- That's exactly how it is.
- Well, that's not it at all.
Then you act like
your shit didn't stink.
You didn't even-- and see,
right, you don't even know
what I'm talking about.
I'm tearing up right now
because I just felt
that there was nothing
genuine with you,
and it just seemed
like Milk was only
concerned about herself.
- What?
- Milk just felt
like he was above everybody,
and we all noticed that.
Correct me if I'm wrong girls,
am I the only one?
- No.
- Okay.
- I just don't want
to jump in over anybody.
- [Milk] It's really hard
hearing so many people chime in
and just like subtly
raise their hand.
I mean, they were basically
saying I'm an asshole.
Am I an asshole?
Why didn't you come up
to me and talk--
I mean, you know
I'm approachable.
- Milk, but you have never
even presented yourself
and it was like you kept
running to Trixie,
kept running to Trixie,
and then all of that
just came together,
so you know what?
I'd rather not work
with somebody that is not
gonna be 100 percent
real and helpful.
I don't owe nobody no apology.
I know how I felt,
point blank and simple.
- All right.
This isn't going anywhere.
Let's stop fighting, and let's
send all of the girls
that are still here home
by kicking their asses.
- It ain't no secret.
If we win, these girls
are gonna send the people
home who sent them home.
These girls are out for blood.
- Gather around
cross dressers.
- I think this is an
interesting opportunity to
put forward like
a fierce number,
but also it'd be fun
to put a message through.
Like, we're all eliminated,
we're all, you know,
back for another chance.
- Yeah.
- We have nothing to lose and
everything to fucking gain.
- I want to be Sparkle Kitty.
- Oh, that's cute.
- She's lit up, she's ebullient,
and she's like--
- She's like
the dance team captain.
- Yeah.
- I wanna be Diva Kitty,
very confident, strong.
- We're deciding who's
gonna take what part
of the song and
who's gonna chose
what kind of character
to bring it to life.
- I want to be something,
I want to be like,
[vocalizing].
What would that be?
Like, that would not be diva.
[laughing]
- What about Mother Kitty?
- Don't put her
in that category.
- I'm thinking she has kids
'cause she's old.
Ah!
- Maybe like Jungle Kitty,
but like wild.
- Yeah.
- Right, like Jungle Kitty.
- I love that.
- Because no matter
who we are individually,
I think collectively
we're a fun group, right?
- Yes.
- You're-- right?
I'm like, you're gonna
have fun, right?
- I mean, friends fight.
- You can just tell totally
tell that BenDeLa's rattled.
Her having that conversation
with Morgan shook her.
What are you thinking BenDeLa?
- I don't know yet.
So we've got like puss, diva.
- Yeah.
- Depressed.
- No, you're not depressed.
- After that conversation
I generally am.
I mean, so far this competition
has been about, like,
talent and all of us,
like, bringing it
and being respectful,
and I'm just like really
not here for this drama.
Like, I'm not here for drama.
That's not what
I'm here to do.
- I'm actually glad that Thorgy
was able to clear the air
about how she felt, and
now I think, hopefully,
it's resolved and
we can move on.
You and I talked.
- Yeah.
- We moved on.
- Trying to focus
when you feel like hurt
or attacked is difficult.
I would like--
I'm so shook right now.
- Just shake it off, sis.
- You gotta shake it off,
sister.
This is what you do.
- No, totally.
- You're a performer,
you're a character.
Let that go.
- I'm worried because this
is a group challenge.
One weak link means
that we all fail.
- [RuPaul] Coming up...
- ♪ Raka ta ti ti ta ta
- I rapped in "No, She Better
Don't" on Season Six.
I think it was the most
memorable rap.
♪ Haters there's the door
- I was just bored.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Hey!
- Hi!
- Hi, everybody!
This week's maxi challenge
is to perform
in competing girl groups,
the Kitty Girls, meow.
Right now it's time
to record our Kitty Girl track
with Adam Lambert.
- I'm so excited
to be here today.
I'm here to make you your best.
This is your chance to get
back into the competition,
so we gotta get really good
performances out of you today.
- Our team is
the returning girls,
and we have a fire
under our butts because,
like, there is a chance
for one of us to return back
to the competition.
- I think we should get going.
- Sweet, let's do it.
- Morgan, you're up first.
Kitts, what's her name?
Does she have like--
- Like, Bimbo Kitty.
- All right, let's do it.
- Okay.
- ♪ I'm the kinda girl
that's walking art ♪
♪ So fierce, baby, and
that's just the start ♪
♪ The boys love me
especially ♪
♪ 'Cause I got the same parts
as Miss Tati ♪
- I like the lyrics,
those are cute.
- Fierce.
- I was just bored.
- I think you can do--
- More.
- --a lot more.
- Okay.
- I mean, you can kind of
affect your voice if you want.
Like, you know how dumb girls
are like, "oh, my God."
- Cool, I got it.
I need to nail this.
I need to come in and kick
the shit out of these girls.
This is my chance.
♪ Boys love me especially
♪ 'Cause I got the same parts
as Miss Tati ♪
- That was way better.
Nice work.
Aja, what is your character?
- My character is
Lil' Banjee Kitty.
- Tell me about her.
- She's like the raptress.
- Okay.
- She's a trap queen.
- Got it.
So there's more rap in your
verse than it is singing?
- Yes.
- All right.
- ♪ Go ahead pass me the mic
♪ Let me show you how to
do it right ♪
♪ Let me show you how
to level up your puss ♪
♪ In the middle of
a kitty cat fight ♪
- Aja is a natural
behind the microphone.
She is serving me rap, girl.
- I like it.
I like the flow.
- Ah!
- What's your character?
- My name is Milk, so I'm
just gonna be Milky Kitty.
- Okay.
- Just like ah, lapping it up.
- Abstract, yeah.
- Yeah, that's exactly, art.
- I like it, conceptual.
- Fashion.
- Is it sung or is
it kind of rapping?
- It's rapping.
- I rapped in "Oh No She
Better Don't" on Season Six.
Obviously that didn't
turn out the best for me,
but I think it was
the most memorable rap.
Everybody knows about it.
♪ I am Milky,
So start lapping ♪
♪ Fun with rhymes
They call that rapping ♪
♪ We the Kitty Girls,
hear us roar ♪
♪ Haters, there's the door
[laughs]
- She's a thirsty pussy,
isn't she?
[laughing]
- So I want to hear
how thirsty she is.
- Okay.
- Oh, my God, my pussy.
- Oh, my God.
- I feel great about
my team's chances
at winning this challenge.
We really killed
the recording process.
Girl, we coming to snatch
their edges, bitch.
By the end of
this performance,
the other group's edges
will be on the floor.
- Yah!
- So your song is
"Drag Up Your Life."
We're gonna get it good.
- Yes.
- Up first, BeBe.
- [Speaking foreign language]
Hello, hello.
[Speaking foreign language]
- Is this like a French pussy
that we're doing in this?
- I'm Jungle Kitty.
- Okay.
- She is very wild,
she is ferocious.
[trills]
- Okay.
- Girl, she is very that,
but you know she's
international fish too.
- I'm ready for this.
- I'm very excited about
this challenge because, bitch,
I'm a performer.
- All right, here we go.
[trills]
♪ Raka ta ti ti ta ta
♪ Yeah, I'm pussy, bitch
- What did she say?
- ♪ Ooh, la, la, la, la, la
♪ C'est bon, c'est bon
- That is so crazy.
She's weird as hell, right?
- Oh, she's weird,
but she's, like,
she's living her life, honey.
Yes, honey, I'm going to
bring you the motherland,
and I'm not talking about
coming to America.
I'm talking about going
right to the jungle, okay?
Yes.
- Trixie.
- Okay.
- You ready to rock?
- Yeah, girl.
If you guys have,
like, a note for me,
just like write it down and
then burn it and never say it.
Thank you so much.
- What's your character?
- So I created this
character that's
like a nymphomaniac mathlete.
- Okay, cool.
I'm ready when you area.
- Okay.
Here we go.
♪ Beauty and intelligence
in one combined ♪
♪ Serving body to the fifth
power to the cosine ♪
- I'm not getting
that she's that horny.
I want you to be hornier
if that's what her deal is.
- Okay.
♪ If you want to play
♪ Drag up your life
- Let's get another chorus
where you're singing "drag..."
- I can't hit that note.
- I believe that you could.
- That's really sweet
and misguided.
Let's do it.
♪ It doesn't matter
if your black or white ♪
♪ Any color you can
drag up your life ♪
- It's drag up your life.
- It's the ending note, yeah.
- ♪ Drag up your life
- I'm gonna pick the lower
on that ending one.
- Let's do the high one.
- Okay.
- Trixie can be really dry
and like low energy.
That's her type of humor,
like, ha ha and ahh!
- Ha ha!
- He really doesn't come
across super warm,
and so that can come off
really standoffish
to those who don't know her.
- In hair and a dress maybe
the upper octave
might just
be more appropriate.
Just a thought.
- Oh, yeah.
- Just, you know,
connect the --
- Oh, so you believe in,
like, gender stereotypes.
- I like realism
and believability.
- Oh, you'll love Trixie Mattel.
- Oh, Miss Adam, she not
liking it too much.
- What's your character?
- She's like the depressed
goth girl.
I decided to do this kind of,
like, angry goth punk kitty.
She's definitely I think
a healthy way to channel
some of the feelings
of resentment
and defensiveness
that Morgan's
accusations bring up for me.
- Let's get into it.
- ♪ It's a kind of crappy
world and it sucks ♪
♪ There's bigotry the GOP
and misplaced tucks ♪
- You had your pitches,
you had your words.
The character wasn't there.
- Yeah.
- Like I didn't get
goth girl from that.
- Do you have any thoughts
on how to push blasé big?
- Punch a couple words
with anger,
and then you're trying
to hold the anger back,
'cause goth girls are like,
I'm too cool to be mad, but
I'm fucking pissed, you know?
- Yeah.
♪ So smear your lipstick on
in the shape of a smile ♪
♪ If you hate it, fake it, make
it into something less vile ♪
- I think doing, like,
kind of the nasal thing,
that doesn't trigger
goth girl for me.
- Okay.
- Right now you're
like projecting
and it's kind of
theatrical, so--
- Okay.
♪ It's a kind of crappy world,
and it sucks ♪
- It's better,
but it's too boring.
So find something to change
it up, because if you just
do it like that, it sounds like
you're kind of half assing it.
- It's harder to concentrate
when you're upset,
and I am upset, but
I'm just gonna keep
pushing myself back towards
what I'm here to do.
- Come on BenDeLa.
- ♪ So smear your lipstick on
in the shape of a smile ♪
♪ If you hate it, fake it,
make it into something-- ♪
♪ If you hate it, fake it, make
it into something less vile ♪
- Lord Jesus.
Look, most of us got confronted
by the eliminated queens,
but we've moved on,
and DeLa needs to do the same
because look, bitch,
this is a group number.
And if LaToya and LaTavia
can't hit the notes then
ain't nobody getting the Grammy
in Destiny's Child, okay?
So she's gotta
pull it together.
- Coming up...
- If I feel you
this certain way,
then I'm just gonna shut down.
- I feel sort of like
shafted that I was let
to walk around
like a douche bag.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Okay, sis.
So now it's time for us
to get up in the gig
for our Kitty Girl
performances for the judges.
Now the real tea is that
today someone is going home,
and one of these eliminated
queens comes back.
- I'm happy for someone
coming back,
because I've been that girl.
But this top five has gotten
so tight
that like it seems impossible
that one of us goes next,
but that's All Stars.
- Did you and Morgan have
a chance to talk today?
- We didn't.
I mean,
we haven't followed up.
I just feel like, you know,
the ball's in her court.
- Right.
- I'm just focusing
on what I'm doing.
Like, I'm not ignoring her,
but I'm just trying to keep
my eyes on the prize.
This one thing with Morgan
has brought up
this feeling of am
I compromising, like,
my personal ideals,
ideals about, like, not
wanting to be a part of,
like, unnecessary conflict.
That kind of has been gnawing
at me since even before
I came here,
and the fact that I need
to eliminate somebody
every time I win,
I don't care about it.
It doesn't, like,
resonate with me.
Competition itself has not
ever been something
that I like got into
this game to be a part of.
I'm competitive with myself.
- See, I know her really well,
and I don't think she comes
from like a mean-spirited place.
- Yeah.
- And I think that maybe
you should pull her aside.
Look, nothing's gonna
get resolved by you
sitting over here and
her sitting over there.
We don't know what's
gonna happen tonight.
You may never have
this opportunity
to clear the air
with her again.
Sometimes you just gotta
pull the Band-Aid off.
- I just want you to know that
I don't-- I don't know--
like, I don't know
what to say to, like,
make anything feel better, but
I just want you to know--
- You don't have
to say anything.
- Okay.
- I'm not mad at your decision,
I was confused by it.
I was like, but that's
not what she said.
- Yeah.
- And I felt like--
I felt, like, dumbfounded
a little bit.
And then yesterday I needed
to say what I needed to say
right then and there or
it was never coming out,
and it just kind of
verbal diarrhea'd, you know.
And when I questioned you about
it, you were just kind of like,
well, that's, you know,
and I was like,
is this bitch being smug
right now?
- I just kind of glaze over
in those moments,
and I don't always know
how people interpret that
or if it feels like you
were saying, I seemed smug.
Like, I just-- I'm like,
power down, can't deal.
- I felt terrible the whole day
because I was like, bitch,
I just came for her
too much without giving her
a chance to even respond,
so I have to say I'm sorry.
I'm confrontational.
She's so anti-confrontational.
Maybe had I come in a little
softer or less pointed,
she would've responded
to me a lot different.
Truce and peace and all
that kinda shit, yeah.
- Yeah.
No, I feel the same way.
I really respect your work.
- Honey, you fuck with me,
you're stuck with me.
I'm not going fucking anywhere.
- I'm pleasantly surprised by
this interaction with Morgan.
Yesterday I saw a very specific
side of her that I think
is really easy to pigeonhole
and today I'm seeing that,
like, no, Morgan is like
a fully fleshed human being,
and I'm so glad that
I was really hanging onto
the idea of giving her
the benefit of the doubt.
- I don't want
to hold grudges.
I don't want to hold
regrets with Kennedy.
Whatever I did hurt her,
and so I'm gonna go about
trying to reconcile it.
I don't want us to be,
like, angry at each other.
- Yeah.
I can say that I was probably
wrong for not at least
making an attempt
to talk to you about it.
- Yeah.
I feel sort of like
shafted in a way that
I was let to walk around
like a douche bag.
- Here we go again.
The fact of the matter is
Milk has a bit of an ego.
Everybody praises him
for being a hot guy,
and I think he kinda thinks
that translated
into being a hot Milk,
but it doesn't.
I mean...
- Yeah, it would suck to hear,
but it sucks to hear it--
- After the fact.
- --hardcore after the fact.
- Yeah.
- They've been allowing me to
just do this without ever, like,
talking to me about it,
like, what is that about?
I feel like Alexis Michelle,
when she's just like,
guys, why did you let me
walk out on the runway
in this blue dress and
this hideous fur?
- But at that time I didn't
see anything genuine from you.
I feel like if we had
that conversation then,
I wouldn't have believed it,
and I would've felt
like it was fake.
- That's sort of, like,
painful that you would
think my reaction would've
been disingenuous.
- If I feel like you
this certain way,
and I feel a sense of rejection,
then I'm just gonna shut down.
- Yeah.
- You know?
And sometimes that's just--
maybe that's just a
bad quality that I have.
My reaction, it comes
from wanting to be accepted,
very much so as a kid,
like, wanting to be
in the in group and
not being accepted.
I just leave it alone,
and I just stop trying.
- I understand where
you're coming from.
It's definitely something
I've been trying
to think about because, I mean,
I would hope that no one else
in the real world
feels this way
and hasn't talked
to me about it.
- Right.
I mean, now I know, if I feel
a certain type of way
then I know I can
come to you now.
- Talking with Kennedy
is helping me, like,
look inward and figure out
the way I act
and react towards people.
So maybe it's all
a good thing.
I love you.
- I love you too, honey.
- Coming up...
- The look is straight out
Baby Spice's wardrobe.
- You nailed it.
I was blown away.
- The hair is a little
Newark realtor for me.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- ♪ Cover girl, put the
bass in your walk ♪
♪ Cover girl, put the bass
in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe, let your
whole body talk ♪
♪ Cover girl
- Welcome to the main stage of
"RuPaul's Drag Race All Stars."
Michelle Visage, now, is
there any truth to the rumor
that your girl group
Seduction is reuniting?
- Yes, they are, only without me
and it's called Reduction.
- Style superstar
Carson Kressley.
- Hi, Ru, do you
my Meowch fit?
- [meows]
- Thanks.
- Adam Lambert, thank
for coaching my Kitty Girls.
- I've never been around
that much pussy at once.
- Glad we could help.
And Emma Bunton,
are you ready for my girls
to spice up your life?
- I sure am.
Bring it on.
- This week we challenged
our All Stars to audition
for my new super group,
the Kitty Girls,
and now they're ready
to step their pussies up.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best All Star win.
First up, the Eliminated Queens,
and they're
"Sitting on a Secret. Oh!
- ♪ Kitty power
- ♪ Back in your stereo
- ♪ Meow bitch
- ♪ Let's do this, girls
- ♪ Sitting on a secret
- ♪ Oh, you didn't know
it hangs to the floor ♪
♪ Got it snatched back tight
so you can't see it ♪
♪ It's a big ol' thang,
you know what I mean ♪
♪ Gaggin' all the kids
with my secret ♪
- ♪ I'm a certain kind of girl
that's walking art ♪
♪ I'm so fierce, baby, and
that's just the start ♪
♪ Boys love me especially
♪ 'cause I got the same
parts as Miss Tati ♪
♪ Girls like me on
All Stars 3 ♪
♪ No innuendo here,
it's what you see ♪
♪ I make my own choices
and love to be free ♪
♪ I choose both bathrooms
when I gotta go pee ♪
- ♪ And it's one, two,
three, four ♪
♪ Sitting on a secret
♪ Promise that we'll keep it
♪ And we won't tell no one
- ♪ Go ahead pass me the mic
♪ Let me show you how
to do it right ♪
to level up your puss ♪
♪ In the middle of
a kitty cat fight ♪
♪ Got a secret bigger
than Alyssa's ♪
♪ Wanna pet my little kitty
and kiss her ♪
♪ Banjee queen got
my baby hair slick ♪
♪ Don't gotta say shit
just lick my secret ♪
- ♪ Move the body,
work up a sweat ♪
♪ I got a workout
that you will not regret ♪
♪ Lunge down low, come on, Ru
♪ Squeeze that tush and whoo!
♪ You want more
♪ If you really, really want
to work out your core ♪
♪ Take the secret,
put it on the floor ♪
♪ Disappear in
one, two, three ♪
- ♪ Sitting on a secret
♪ Promise that we'll keep it
♪ And we won't tell no one
- ♪ If you say you're
super smart, you're not ♪
- ♪ Not
- ♪ If you say your drag
is art, it's not ♪
- ♪ Not
- ♪ If you say you
didn't fart, you did ♪
♪ I'm not joking, kid
♪ I am Milky,
so start lapping ♪
♪ Fun with rhymes,
they call that rapping ♪
♪ We the Kitty Girls
here us roar ♪
♪ Honey, there's the door
♪ Out
- ♪ Sitting on a secret
♪ Promise that
we'll keep it ♪
♪ And we won't tell no one
♪ Sitting on a secret
[laughing]
And now it's
the top five All Stars,
and it's time to
"Drag Up Your Life."
- ♪ Drag up, drag up your life
♪ Drag up, drag up your life
- ♪ Beauty and intelligence
in one combined ♪
♪ Serving body to the fifth
power to the cosine ♪
♪ Maybe I can tutor you
♪ Just read my text
♪ You can meet after class
♪ Baby, we can solve for X
- ♪ Say yes to drag
♪ Yes, ma'am to drag
♪ It slays
It pays ♪
♪ Unleash the diva that lives
deep inside your mind ♪
♪ If you want to play
- ♪ Drag up your life
- ♪ Super duper
- ♪ Doesn't matter if
you're black or white ♪
♪ Any color you can
drag up your life ♪
♪ Drag up your life
- ♪ Precisely
- ♪ Doesn't matter
if you're black or white ♪
♪ Any color you can
drag up your life ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four
- ♪ It's a kinda crappy world
♪ And it sucks
♪ There's bigotry, the GOP,
and misplaced tucks ♪
♪ So smear your lipstick
on in the shape of a smile ♪
♪ If you hate, fake it, make
it into something less vile ♪
- ♪ Oh, girl,
just add some sparkle ♪
♪ It feels so sexy and free
♪ And you'll see,
yes, you will ♪
♪ What the glitz and glamour
♪ Be flashy for the cameras
♪ So gay, gay, gay
♪ Bitch, if you want to play
- ♪ Drag up your life
- ♪ Fine
- ♪ Doesn't matter
if you're black or white ♪
♪ Any color you can
drag up your life ♪
- ♪ Drag up your life
- ♪ Okay
- ♪ Doesn't matter
if you're black or white ♪
♪ Any color you
can drag up your life ♪
[trills]
♪ Raka ta ti ti ta ta
♪ Yeah, I'm pussy, bitch
♪ Ooh, la la la la la la
♪ C'est bon, c'est bon
♪ Do ko cho cho
la te la ♪
♪ You can take my snatch
♪ Dragging it up
Wheel it up ♪
♪ Give me more,
bring it to the ball ♪
- ♪ Drag up your life
- ♪ C'est la vie
- ♪ Doesn't matter
if you're black or white ♪
♪ Any color you can
drag up your life ♪
♪ Drag up your life
- Brava.
- Whoo!
- Coming up...
- I was blown away.
- She's killing it, she's out
there, she's living it.
- You have not made this easy.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Welcome, All Stars.
Wow, you have
not made this easy.
Based on your
Kitty Girl presentations,
I've made my decision.
My top five All Stars,
condragulations,
you're the winning team.
- Ah!
- Yay!
[trills]
- Now it's time for
the judges to determine
the top two All Stars
of the week.
And later, the top two will
lip sync for their legacy.
The winner will get the power
to bring back
one of the eliminated queens
and to give one of
her teammates the chop.
Eliminated queens, you may
step to the back of the stage.
- Now it's time for
the judges' critiques.
First up, Trixie Mattel.
- IQ Kitty.
I think you are
as cute as a button.
The look is straight out of
Baby Spice's wardrobe.
I loved it.
- One thing that threw me
off was the hair,
'cause I felt like it
wasn't really nerdy hair.
- I actually love the hair,
and then the quality
of your lyrics really
sold the nerd to me.
It's just all smart
and well done.
- But yesterday I was trying
to work with you to just try
to experiment,
and I gotta be honest,
it felt like you were, like,
over me being there.
Yeah.
I kind of got like
a standoffish vibe,
like you were kind of like,
yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
For the future, like,
be, you know,
open and just collaborate.
- Up next, Diva Kitty,
Kennedy Davenport.
- I love the body suit and
I love the thigh high.
I think it's got loads
of girl power in there.
- But the hair's a little
Newark realtor for me.
Like, it could be a little
more glamorous.
- I love your high kicks though,
and I loved your splits.
I was missing the diva
a little bit though.
I mean, diva to me
is she's killing it,
she's out there,
she's living it.
I wanted to see much more.
- Up next, Goth Kitty,
BenDeLaCreme.
- The makeup, I love it.
It's goth but it's also 1920s.
I actually like
this whole look on you.
- This is actually my
Julie Andrews outfit.
- All right.
Recycle Kitty.
- Yes.
- Yesterday I was worried.
You worked well with me,
you weren't standoffish,
but it was literally tough.
Today, the minute you hit
the stage, you nailed it.
I was blown away.
- I did see you have a
little trip on the heels,
and I know how hard it is
to dance in those wedges
because I've actually broken
my ankle a few times in those.
- Well, I was very angsty,
so I guess it was method?
- Why were you angsty?
- The eliminated girls
came back
and there were a lot of
emotions about who had left.
I was having
a terrible day yesterday,
and this was a place
to channel it.
- Thank you, DeLa.
- Thank you.
- Sparkle Kitty, Shangela.
- Hey!
- This look is flawless.
It's detailed,
the shoe is fantastic.
Everything is perfection.
- And I'm also getting into
this new
Shangela padding
that we're seeing.
- Just a little extra shape.
- Girl, she got some
thunder thighs,
and it's very, very womana.
- But you are such a show woman,
the thing that I noticed
most during your performance
was that it just felt
a little bit more tentative
than it normally is.
- I totally disagree.
I could not take
my eyes off you,
and I kinda like that it was
just a bit downplayed,
a bit sexy.
I really enjoyed
your performance.
- That means a lot
coming from you.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- And if y'all
ever do a reunion
and you need a number six,
you can call me, okay?
- I think you should come
and join us anytime.
- Thank you.
- Up next, Jungle Kitty,
BeBe Zahara Benet.
- Hi, Mother.
- I, of course, love the
leopard print cat suit
because I hope that
Scary Spice was a bit
of an influence on that.
- All I have to say
is "raka tiki ta ta".
Did I say that right?
What does that mean?
- Honey, it is just
speaking in any language
you're feeling at the moment.
It's an emotion,
"raka ta ti ti ta ta".
[laughter]
- You cracked me up every
take yesterday
because you were just
bizarre and hilarious,
and today I was blown away
by how brilliant
you were delivering it.
- When you come out, there's
a presence that comes with you.
There's a reason why
you won Season One.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, ladies.
Based on the judges critiques,
I've made some decisions.
BenDeLaCreme,
BeBe Zahara Benet...
you are the top two
All Stars of the week.
Condragulations.
You've each won a $1,000 gift
card to Spa on Rodeo,
and a $1,000 gift card
from MuLondon.
In a moment, you will
lip sync for your legacy.
The winner of that lip sync
will have the power
to bring back one of
the eliminated queens,
and to give one of
your teammates the chop.
While you queens deliberate
in the workroom,
the judges will be
giving me a sponge bath.
[laughs]
- Thank you, Adam,
I'll be here all week.
[laughing]
- Coming up...
- It hurts like hell because
I don't feel I didn't do bad.
- I can't send her home.
- As an artist, like
I have so much to give.
- I want it so bad.
- I want to show more.
- There will be a lot
of broken hearts.
How do you win?
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Oh, my God.
- I feel for BeBe and DeLa
because not only do they have
to bring back one of us girls,
they have to send somebody
home from their group.
Tough decision,
tough decision.
- So I have a question for
Trixie, Kennedy, and Shangela.
Knowing that you
killed the challenge,
and to be told
that that was great,
but you might be going home,
what does that feel like?
- I'm like all over the place.
Being that we have to go by
the rules, you know,
I understand that's
what it has to be,
but it hurts like hell
because I didn't do bad.
It just sucks ass.
It don't feel good.
- Kennedy's upset because she
has the worst track record here
and had
the harshest critiques,
so I think she's feeling
like it could be her day.
- Can we get, like, real?
Is this hard for
you guys to consider?
- It's-- um...
I-- it's always hard,
but I have less of a concept
than I ever have of why
anyone should go home.
I'm trying to pick through
what the reasoning
would be to send anybody home.
I'd love to talk to all three
of the rest of the five.
- Same here.
- Come with me.
- But it just--
it doesn't make sense to me.
How do you-- how-- what do--
- What are you gonna pick?
Oh, I know.
- What do you do?
Like, how do you even
think about this?
I mean, like, how am I supposed
to even consider this?
I don't have any clue.
- I would just not pick me.
- Okay, that's fair.
- No.
I mean, Shangela
has more wins than me.
I have a better track
record than Kennedy,
and I got better
critiques today.
- Yeah.
- I know we're at the point
where everyone's fierce,
but I felt exceptionally
fierce in what I did.
- Yeah.
You-- yeah, got
your groove back.
Trixie has only had two weeks
to start to prove herself.
She deserves more time here.
I can't send her home.
- How are you feeling?
- I'm not ready to go home,
that's all I can say.
I'm not ready to go home.
- In order to make a
really fair decision,
I'm looking at the whole
entire body of work
and if they still have
the fire to go on
to the very last end,
because at this point, to me,
that's what would really
differentiate everybody.
- You know that
I'm 100 percent in this thing,
but it comes down to you.
- Right.
- And your decision.
I need to go to the end,
point blank and simple.
I need to go to the end.
Just know in your heart who
you really want to be here,
'cause that's
what it boils down to.
- I'm wrecked, girl.
I'm rattled, bitch.
- Are you?
- I mean, I'm just so cracked
that you guys have
to make a choice
out of the top five.
Bitch, I'm nervous.
It's just a toss-up
at this point.
I just want to say to you,
I'm proud of you
and the work that you've done,
regardless of
this whole competition.
- I have always been
so impressed by your work.
I've been impressed by
the way that you bounced back
from being booted out of this
room over and over again.
- Over and over.
- Shangela is a rock star.
She has an incredible track
record in this competition
so far, and she-- I--
she belongs in the top
for this competition.
It would be, like, kind of
insane to send Shangela home.
- Bitch, you were in this
same place last week, honey.
- I know.
- How you feeling? Like...
- I feel great.
- Calm.
- Right.
Pleased, happy.
- Mm-hmm.
- They got my character,
they thought it was funny.
The look worked for them.
I feel proud of what I did.
- Yeah.
- So like, you know,
if it comes down to,
we would've like you
in different hair,
I'm like, well, that's
the point we're at.
- There's a sense of calm.
There's a sense of resolution.
It's almost like she is ready
either way, but I love Trixie.
Look at us trying to, like,
hug, and it's like--
I feel Trixie is talented.
I mean, it's top five, how do
you choose who's gonna go home?
- Hey, again.
- I mean, I wouldn't want
to be in your position.
- Neither of us are
in great positions.
- Well, you, at least you in
the position to stay, you know.
But bitch, I'm definitely
not ready to go home.
I don't know what else to say.
I just don't.
- Kennedy is the lowest
ranking right now,
but she keeps bouncing back.
She's so consistent
in her temperament,
which is so valuable.
I can't send her home.
It just doesn't feel fair
to send any of these girls home,
and this idea just makes
zero sense to me.
- Hey, ladies.
- Hey, sis.
- Hi.
- So it's turn to talk
to Ben and BeBe.
We've got to plead our cases.
- I really broke down
the episode I went home.
It just-- the pressure
really hits me
because I expect
so much from myself.
I didn't think I was ready
to go then,
and I'm ready
to come back now.
As an artist, like,
I have so much to give.
- Obviously I want to be here
just as much as anybody else.
I want to show more,
but if that's not
what's in the cards
for me, that's cool.
If I went home tonight,
I could raise my head up high
and say, you know what,
fucking rock on, bitches.
- The only reason I can say
is because I want it.
I want it so bad.
I will jump off of
this building for it.
- I saw you do it
in the talent show.
- I was doing so well,
and I want to come back.
This just means so much to
me because I've already been
kind of like going on such
a better run than my season,
so I want to continue it.
I just want to be in the top.
- Girl, this an easy one
for you with me, honey,
'cause I feel like I got
a little bit more work to do.
So bringing me back would
kind of be like
beating a dead horse basically,
you know what I mean?
Like, girl,
the horse dead already.
I don't want to be
the Roxxxy of All Stars 3,
you know what I mean?
I realize when it's my time.
You just gotta know
when it's time to go.
- I know I don't need this
to prove myself
because I've proved myself
in the outside world,
but I feel I really grew
a lot and I learned a lot
from my first experience,
and so I want to be able
to have more experience
to grow even, like, bigger.
I really fucking want this.
I want to be brought back.
I feel very deserving
to be brought back.
- Thank you, ladies,
I love you all.
There's just so many emotions
going on at the same time.
All of these girls are
deserving of a second chance.
I don't know how
I'm going to choose.
- I think that there is
one queen in particular
who has more to show here,
and I want to give her
the second chance.
- Now, when my fans receive
one of my limited edition
collectibles from Tweeterhead,
they must be spotless.
Emma, let's take a look.
- Okay, here we go.
How's that?
- Oh, Emma, it's filthy!
I'm not mad at you,
I'm mad at the dirt.
Silence!
Bring back my dirty girls.
Emma!
- There's been four other
times that I've been standing up
here in this position
deciding somebody's fate,
and it is always a
really difficult decision.
It's always really
hard to be here.
What would you do?
- When I'm looking at the box,
it's coming to life
who I'm thinking would
be deserving to come back,
but when it comes
to the top five girls,
this is a very hard
decision to make.
And no matter what I do, there
will be a lot of broken hearts.
How do you win?
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Welcome back, ladies.
Two All Stars stand before me.
Ladies, this is your chance
to impress me,
win $10,000,
earn the power to bring back
one of the eliminated queens,
and to give one of your
All Star teammates the chop.
The time has come
to lip sync
for your legacy.
- I have made my choices.
I feel strong in my conviction
about these choices.
I have to win this lip sync.
- Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
- ♪ All my life
♪ On a search to find
♪ The love who'll
stay for eternity ♪
♪ The heaven sent
to fulfill my needs ♪
♪ But when I turned around
♪ Again love
has knocked me down ♪
♪ My heart got broken
♪ Oh it hurt so bad
♪ I'm sad to say
love wins again ♪
♪ So I place my heart
under lock and key ♪
♪ To take some time
and take care of me ♪
♪ But I turn around
and you're standing here ♪
♪ How did you get here
♪ Nobody's supposed
to be here ♪
♪ But I turn around and
you're standing here ♪
♪ How did you
♪ How did you get here
♪ No nobody, no, no,
no, no, no, no. ♪
♪ Nobody's supposed
to be here ♪
♪ No, no, no
♪ Ah
♪ How did you get here
- BeBe has taken her wig off,
and I'm like, girl,
I don't see no flowers,
I don't see no glitter,
I don't see no gag.
You ain't no Sasha Velour,
bitch, keep your wig on.
- ♪ My heart says no, no
♪ Nobody's supposed to be here
Nobody's supposed to be here ♪
♪ But you came along
and changed my mind ♪
♪ Ah
- Yay!
[applause]
- Yes!
- Ladies, I have
made my decision.
BenDeLaCreme,
you're a winner, baby.
Condragulations, you've won
a cash tip of $10,000.
- Thank you so much.
- BeBe Zahara Benet,
you are safe.
Now, will the eliminated queens
please step forward.
DeLa, which queen have
you chosen to bring back
to the competition?
- I think that everyone here
is deserving of getting to be
a part of this, and of getting
to show their talent
to the world, and there's
one queen who didn't have
as much of an opportunity.
So Morgan, get in here
and make me proud.
- Condragulations, Morgan,
you are back in the game.
- I don't like emotion.
- Will the four
eliminated queens
step to the back of the stage.
Will the bottom three All Stars
please step forward?
DeLa, which of your All Star
teammates have you chosen
to get the chop?
- This is the easiest choice
I have had to make
this entire season.
I'm going home.
- What?
- What did she just say?
Did she just say her own name?
- I am so, so grateful
for my time here,
both on the last season
and this season.
I scribbled out a different
one and I wrote this one
in whiteout, and let
me tell you why.
I hope that you don't see
this as a sign of disrespect,
because I see myself as such
a Drag Race success story.
I had such a difficult
time on my season,
even though I did well.
I wanted this opportunity
to come back, to fight hard,
to show myself what I can do.
I have accomplished that.
I feel like a winner.
I love these girls.
I think they all deserve
a shot to win, and I--
I'm incredibly grateful.
I hope that you all
can see that.
- I'm-- actually,
I don't know how...
how to take this.
- I feel so good.
I feel like I'm going
home winning.
- As it written,
so it shall be done.
DeLa, you are and will
always be an All Star.
Now, sashay away.
- I love you guys.
I love you so much.
- Ben wanted to leave on her
own terms, and good for her,
but it's still kind
of like fuck girl.
We're just kind of like
over it
because she's like
being omnipotent.
- You guys win. I won.
I love you.
- It just seems so like--
- Thank you all.
- What the fuck
is happening.
Not BenDeLaChrist, savior
of Morgan and the drag queens.
But I don't know if that's
gonna look good or bad.
Honestly.
- Thanks for letting me be
my kind of winner.
I had a real good time.
I was looking over
those lipsticks,
and none of those answers
felt right to me,
so I made my own rules,
and I feel great about it.
It's like I proved
everything I have to prove.
After five out of six wins,
what more can I want?
This in gold?
I have spray paint at home.
I know the queens
in the top five have
had their struggles and
I'm delighted to get
to give them the opportunity
to live another week.
I think the actual title
is more important to them
than it is to me.
- Well, condragulations,
and ladies,
no more white out!
And remember, if you
can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
- Amen.
- All right.
Now let the music play!
- ♪ Charisma, Uniqueness
♪ Nerve and Talent
♪ Let your body
tell the truth ♪
- Next time on All Stars...
- You'll be starring in
"My Best Squirrelfriend's
Dragsmaids Wedding Trip."
- Yeah, that's all you've
got, lady, big feet
and ugly fucking pumps.
[laughs]
- Wow! Jazz!
- I don't get it.
- I live for moments
like this, where you just
ask yourself how
did she do that.
- I got a little excited.
I'm single.
- You need to be bigger
and more ridiculous.
- Girl, what the fuck?
- Nothing is getting in my way.
- I'm Natalie Imbruglia, Torn.
- You're not friendly enough
for someone
to think you're a jerk.
- Who gives a shit, okay?