I think it's brilliant.
It's not even
a good clown makeup.
It's a beautiful,
beautiful design.
Thank you.
Previously, on Face Off,
the judges fell in love
with Emily's queen of hearts,
but Daniel was eliminated,
leaving only three artists
on Team Anthony.
Now, 12 artists remain,
and tonight,
their stamina is tested
with two intense challenges.
It's relay race time.
I'm a makeup artist,
not an athlete.
Ahh!
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm freaking out.
Is he a good guy
or is he a bad guy?
There's a lot of blank stares.
We do have business
to attend to.
- What?
- What is going on?
You did an amazing job.
In the end, only one will win
a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand new 2015 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
This is Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- Okay.
- So we walk into the lab,
and I see that there are
these four makeup stations
that look like lanes.
What is this?
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
So life on a Hollywood set
can be pure chaos,
and sometimes, that means
having to hand off your work
to someone else
to finish the job,
and that's exactly
what you'll be doing today.
- It's relay race time.
- Oh, yeah.
I don't feel
to good about this,
'cause I'm a makeup artist,
not an athlete.
You'll be working
in teams of three,
and each team member will get
two 20 minute turns.
When I call, "Switch,"
at the end of your first turn,
you need to grab
a new prosthetic
and hand it off
to your teammate.
That new piece
must be incorporated
into your team's
overall design.
Oh, my God.
While you're working,
you will not be able
to communicate
with your team at all.
So you'll find out
what you're dealing with
when you come
around the back side
of one of these
makeup stations.
Now, you're going to need
a little inspiration
for your makeups.
Oh.
From Freddy Krueger
in Nightmare On Elm Street
to Edward Scissorhands,
claws have played
a significant role
in defining
iconic movie characters.
So you will use
your model's claws
as inspiration
for an original character.
The winner of today's challenge
will earn immunity...
Ooh.
...and cannot be eliminated
in this week's
spotlight challenge.
I want that immunity
because I've been
in the bottom twice,
and I know I'm better
than what I've been able
to accomplish so far.
Your guest judge this week
is the co-host
of ABC's hit show Wipeout,
and one of the stars
of MTV's Teen Wolf.
Please give a warm welcome
to Jill Wagner.
It's really cool
to have Jill Wagner here
because she knows how it feels
to be in prosthetics
and understands
the importance of makeup
in creating
a cohesive character.
So Jill, you have
some claws of your own.
You're a were-jaguar.
I do-- Which are
totally different claws,
by the way, than a werewolf.
Exactly.
Good point.
So what are you gonna be
looking for today?
Everything has to flow.
It's got to look like
your claw belongs
with the rest of the character,
but the most important thing
for me
is the detailing in the makeup,
particularly the mouth.
All right, everybody,
your teams and stations
have been randomly assigned.
Head back to the starting lines
and stand with your teammates.
On your mark, get set,
- go!
- Ahh!
Oh, geez.
What's up, man? I'm Logan.
I can't shake your hand.
You have stuff all over it.
Our claws have a lot
of colorful, mechanical parts,
and I think,
"Toy factory, cyborg."
- Yeah.
- Tip your head back.
So I apply a bald cap...
Ready for this?
...and lay down a gear prosthetic
right on the forehead.
This is exciting.
I see these amazing,
bedazzled out in gold cat claws,
so I think,
"Egyptian cat goddess."
Let me see those claws.
We've got these
Freddy Krueger-looking claws,
so the first thing
I could think of is
maybe he's cutting himself.
I find a prosthetic,
and it's got all these cracks,
and I start applying it
to his face.
It makes scars
and some open wounds.
So I'm just setting
a foundation for my team.
I have no idea what's going on,
and it's excruciating,
knowing I'm up next.
We get these sparkly,
icy fingers,
so I first think, "Ice queen,"
and I'm gonna have
this really pointy, evil brow,
and I need to also grab
the next appliance for Adam.
Switch!
What the hell is it?
I look at the prosthetic
Logan hands me,
and it's a set of teeth
with, like,
more mechanical stuff
underneath it,
and I see gears
on our model's head,
and it triggers cyborg for me.
That's pretty cool.
_
It is, but you have
a nose piece in your brow.
I remember Jill's comment
about details around the mouth,
and I just create
a little chin piece out of it.
Oh, I get it.
Ben gave me
a set of eye bag prosthetics,
but I decide to use
these as blender pieces
to cover up some of the edges,
and I notice that there's
some really thick edges
along his brow area,
so I find a piece
that will cover that
for Emily to apply.
I can tell that Anthony's going
for some kind of Egyptian style,
so I start gluing down
the horns on the chin
to add some kind of silhouette.
It's getting down to the end
of my turn,
and my concept
is an alien diva,
but I don't know
how to tell Rob,
so I grab some blues,
whites, and silvers,
and I hope rob gets
the message.
Then I grab a set of horns.
Perfect.
Switch!
- Hi.
I hope she doesn't take
what I gave her too literally.
Stephanie has handed me
a full face,
and I kind of know
where they're going with it.
Somebody's been torn up.
So I'm like, "Okay,
I got to Frankenstein this."
What is he supposed to be?
I have
a little nose prosthetic.
I think Darla wants me
to cover up the edges
around the eyes...
Perfect.
So I apply the nose piece
very quickly,
and I just start painting.
I see Adam grab the paints,
and I start laying down
Kryolan Aquacolor.
Switch!
You are looking
like a beast, man.
At this point, this is obviously
a wounded character,
so we're just gonna burn him up.
Switch!
Hi.
What do we got?
What do we got? What do we got?
Oh, shit.
What in the--
Switch!
Time, guys!
That's it, brushes down!
Tell us about the concept
that you created with the claws you got.
First thing
that I could think of was,
"He's always picking
at himself,"
so I found something
that looked like
it had already been cut.
- And then, we all added...
- Yeah.
layers of paint to it to create
extra depth within the piece.
Overall, it's great.
The cracks and everything,
they're really good,
but I just would like to see
just a little more originality,
but he looks like his claws.
- It matches.
- Thanks.
I immediately thought doing
an Egyptian cat goddess.
What made you put
the horns right there?
I could just tell
that Anthony wanted the bangs
to be flowing down, and
I didn't want to interrupt that,
so I thought the chin would be
the place to put them.
I love the coloring,
love her lips,
but where the horn comes out
needs to be blended
a little bit better.
This is Ivan, he was involved
in a toy factory explosion.
All the bits were seared
into his face.
I love the whole story
of this one.
He looks scary.
He would have terrified
the hell out of me.
Thank you.
She's Princess Meg,
and she's a hostess
for an intergalactic
music video show.
I have to say, the wig was
a pretty bold choice.
Who made that decision?
When I saw how he went
with blue,
I walked back there, and
I was like, "That's the one."
I love the coloring.
This is really cohesive.
- Yeah.
- Thank you so much.
So Jill, how did they do today?
They did amazing.
I love the characters
and originality.
- Great job.
- All right, who created
your favorite looks?
Kelly, Adam, and Rob,
'cause I love the way you guys
made her beautiful
instead of scary.
- She's uber-cool.
- Thank you.
My other favorite was from
Logan, Stephanie, and Jamie.
It was very cohesive
and creepy and scary.
Thank you.
All right, Jill,
so who has won immunity?
The winner is...
Adam.
The wig totally made
the character,
and this little chin piece
was so unexpected,
so congratulations, Adam.
Thank you so much.
I'm stoked,
because having immunity
is gonna give me a chance
to do some things that
I don't typically do without,
you know, the consequences.
Jill, thank you so much
for being here.
- Thank you so much.
- It was such a pleasure
to have you.
Bye.
All right,
before I send you home,
we do have a little bit
of business to attend to.
What is going on?
Rayce?
- Hey, guys.
- What?
Oh, man,
what's Rayce doing here?
So why don't you fill them in?
I have a big client that I have
some prior commitments with,
and I will not be able to attend
this spotlight challenge.
But I've got
a Face Off rock star
that is gonna come
help you guys out.
Hey.
Hey, guys.
- Ah.
- You look great.
So good to see you.
Thank you.
It's awesome to be here.
All right, well,
you guys all remember RJ.
So Rayce, how do you feel
about this guy
stepping in while you're gone?
Oh, I'm really excited.
He's got an insane amount
of knowledge
to help execute your makeups.
All right, guys,
RJ will be in the lab
with Anthony and Laura
in the morning,
so we'll see you tomorrow for
your next spotlight challenge.
It's gonna be really weird
not having Rayce around,
but RJ's an amazing artist,
so I'm really excited
to be working with him.
We arrive at Fox Studios.
I can just feel the history,
walking down these streets.
It's so amazing.
Welcome to the historic Newman
scoring stage at Fox Studios.
Now, some of the most memorable
motion picture music ever
was recorded right here
in this room.
And this, of course, leads us to
your next spotlight challenge,
which taps into an essential
element of movie magic,
sound.
Sound designers are often
involved
before a creature
is even designed,
meaning the sound
inspires the final creation.
Your spotlight challenge
is to create a character
inspired
by a unique sound effect.
Ooh.
I think that's awesome.
This challenge is gonna
really show
everyone's imagination
and what they can do.
Now, you'll be working
together in teams of two,
so go ahead and pair up.
I'd like to introduce
a very special guest.
He's earned five
Primetime Emmy nominations
and two Academy Award
nominations
for his sound design work.
Please give a warm welcome
to sound designer Erik Aadahl.
Thank you so much
for joining us today.
Oh, my pleasure.
It's great to be here.
Well, I mean, you have built
quite an impressive resume.
How do you find inspiration?
When you're giving voice
to something,
you're giving it its soul.
So the job of the sound designer
is to illuminate that soul.
So try to find the personality,
the environment, the genre,
and play off of that.
You will have
the unique pleasure
of using original sounds
that Eric has created
to inspire your designs
this week.
That's real cool.
They've been randomly assigned
and preloaded onto your tablets.
This guy is a genius,
and the fact that he is making
our sounds, that's awesome.
- Thank you so much again.
- My pleasure.
All right, guys,
your sound effects
will play back
alongside your characters
on the reveal stage
for the judges.
So grab your tablets
and headphones
and start conceptualizing
your creations.
I think we should both
individually
listen to the sound twice.
Rob and I get this rumbly,
roaring character
that sounds like t-rex
with a cold.
We want a large bog creature,
bigger than life.
We want to make it
a head-to-toe piece.
It's this big, snarling,
snotty beast
with a few different
nostril sets.
It's gonna be a lot of fun.
We hear, like,
these clicking noises,
and then rustling and water.
I'm thinking
very dinosaur-like.
Mm-hmm.
Our concept for our character
is a prehistoric,
bird-like creature.
It lives in the jungle,
and it defends itself
by its quills.
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking
similar to full robot.
We have something that
the other sounds don't have,
which is words.
Activated.
Weapon system armed.
I don't want to do a robot.
I think that it's too obvious.
This is speaking to me, though.
One-armed robot?
That's been done before.
Armed.
It sounds horror.
Yeah,
that's a terrifying sound.
There's women screaming
and hollow ghost sounds
and men groaning, and I'm like,
"What the actual hell?"
What if we did some form
of, like, demon banshee?
The first thing that pops
into my head is Satan's servant.
He's able to grasp
onto their souls
and drag them down into Hell.
The character's face
is definitely gonna be demonic,
but then, all down his chest,
we're gonna have
these sort of ghostly figures.
It sounds like multiple things
happening at the same time.
So basically, Anthony and I
are gonna make Hell.
All right, everybody,
let's go back to the lab.
Like the clockmaker's wife
or something,
and she died or something
so he put her back together.
Ticking is really prominent
in our sound,
and we decide that we're not
gonna do the clockmaker,
but do the clockmaker's wife.
She dies and he ends up making
a porcelain clockwork doll
that looks like her.
But maybe we can make her,
like, '50s housewife.
I'm digging this.
I really, really want to focus
on the detail on this guy.
I'm gonna get this molded today
- when it's done.
- Okay.
We have kind of bits
and pieces of an idea,
but we don't have
a concept right now.
This sound is really tough.
It just sounds like breathing.
We just start adding clay
on there,
and hoping maybe a concept
will appear to us
as we're sculpting.
- Do you a back story in mind?
- I don't.
- How are you?
- Good to meet you, man.
We're Team Rayce.
That's why I called you over.
- Hey, guys, how are you?
- Rob, how are you?
I am so excited to be back
this season,
- coaching Team Rayce.
- As you can see,
- I've started on a face on--
- That's a big head.
These two guys are planning
to build
a creature suit
from head to toe.
The sound really works
with this design,
and I'm gonna make sure that Rob
and Logan get things done today,
because that clock
is always ticking.
You got to move.
Is he a warrior?
Where-- you know,
what period does he come from,
like, time frame?
Laura and I see they are
struggling with their concept.
Is he a good guy
or is he a bad guy?
- Frankenstein character...
- Yeah.
- Orc character...
- Is he science fiction?
- Grotesque character?
- Is he horror?
What genre is he?
There aren't a lot of answers.
There's a lot of blank stares.
Take a few minutes and
figure it out a little bit more.
Maybe draw a few more pictures.
So I'm sculpting
the chest piece
with all the different faces,
and Darla is working
on the facial sculpt,
and I realize
we have all of the models'
silicone life casts.
So I grab white clay,
and I press it in,
take the imprint
of the models' faces,
and then slap it right on
and have
a form that I can just
work with.
Actually use a chest,
so that you can see the lines.
You don't want edge problems.
That's really clever.
It looks really good too.
Thank you.
I hear gears.
I hear heavy breathing,
and I hear a knife
or some kind of blade at the end.
After two long miserable hours,
we finally come
to some sort of concept.
It sounds like something's
coming towards me.
At the last second,
when I finally see it,
- that's when he-- "ching."
- Yeah.
Our concept is
a demon executioner
that wears the faces
of people that he kills.
I'm a little nervous.
It seems like
the only other people
that haven't gotten started yet
are Adam and Regina.
I'm thinking, like,
almost, like, organic-ness.
Like, bio-organic
- is the style?
- No, no, no, no, no, hold on.
Adam wants to go robotic.
That takes
a lot more fabrication,
which is not
one of my strong points.
I have to do
a really good job at this,
because Adam has immunity.
I'm freaking out
because we're lost.
It's the first day
of our sound design challenge,
and the entire room has
at least one sculpture,
but Adam and I
don't have anything.
I'm just getting frustrated
at this point.
They're kind of lost,
so I'm gonna go over
and hang out with them.
I really like the face.
So after sketching
back and forth,
I'm thinking robot,
but Regina has
this idea
of this alien super soldier.
Activated.
I want to stick
to Regina's design
'cause I do have immunity.
You got to get
some clay in your hand.
If I don't see some clay
on this face,
I'm gon' bust some humps.
We got to get something
on that positive now.
You got-- You grabbed it
for a reason.
Time's up, everybody.
Adam and I are really behind
for such a big concept,
but it's definitely
something different
than anybody else is doing
in the room.
It's day two in the lab.
We got 9 1/2 hours.
We're gonna make the doll
look like she's withering away.
I'm trying to think of where
I want to put the cracks on her.
She's gonna have cracks,
but underneath all of that,
she's still
perfect and pristine.
To unify these pieces,
to get hers a little more
like yours, or make yours have
a little bit more going on.
Okay.
Our sound is so cool.
I started fabricating the cowl.
It needs to look
more bird-like,
so I used latex and paper towels
to create a shell,
and then put in all the quills.
I'm getting very frustrated
because the cowl is taking
a lot longer than I expected.
I need to finish the chest,
and then fabricate
arms, legs, and hands,
and somehow get it done today.
I mean, is he wearing anything?
No.
It's full fabrication.
It looks like there's
a lot left to do on this,
and I'm not seeing
all the pieces
that I should be seeing.
I'll get it done.
I finish the sculpture
for the helmet,
so RJ helps me
with the vacuform piece.
Ooh, that's cool.
All right, guys, good luck.
- Uh.
- Got this.
- See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
Good luck, guys.
Now I need to finish
the cowl and the face.
- What's going on with him?
- I don't know.
The clock's ticking,
and we're at the point where
we won't have time
to mold everything,
so I help Regina finish the face
so she can finish the cowl,
and then, we finally get
into molding.
I've never done
this amount of molding
in this amount of time.
That's time, everybody.
Go, go, go, go, go.
It's application day.
We've got four hours in the lab
and one our at last looks.
Yeah, if you put reds
on first...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...and then you dry brush
the black over it, that'll be
- a good transition.
- All right.
Dude, this came out
pretty nice.
Oh, that's sweet.
Kelly and I want to give
our character a prop,
so I do a quick drawing
of the husband
and our character.
So we're gonna just take
some tea, stain it,
and it looks
like an old photograph.
I got another big cowl for you.
And you're just, like, kind of
looking-- like, looking down.
We're not gonna put this on
you until we get to last looks.
This is such a big costume,
we don't want to make
the model uncomfortable.
If you could put this on,
'cause I just need
to size up some pieces.
I have to basically
refit the whole suit itself
to make sure it fits
our model perfectly,
and then, Logan pre-paints
the face,
so we have a lot on our plate
and no room for error
on this one.
_
We've got a lot to do.
Adam still has to make
arm pieces.
Since Adam's gonna be
fabricating these arms,
I'm gonna be
the one that's applying,
and I'm not sure if we're gonna
be able to get it all done.
_
The most important thing
is getting those pieces down.
Once I get the face down,
Anthony comes over
and we sort of tag team
gluing down the chest piece.
I think we do have
a really cool concept.
I personally would love a win.
So while I'm applying
the bald cap and the face,
Stephanie is pre-painting
this cowl,
and anything that's not smooth,
we're gonna have to make
look like cracks.
The back piece
and the front piece
they haven't even put on yet.
They need to motor
on this stuff.
Are you almost good with that?
Yeah, we're at 1:53.
I'm just letting you know.
I'm wrapping up.
One thing about Face Off is that
you got to figure out
what shortcuts are gonna work
so that you can get these things
done in time.
Try and lay that one hard edge
right up against the other one,
and then that way, you don't
have to hide two hard edges.
- Do too much.
- You know what I mean?
Yeah.
_
_ _
Jamie's applying this face,
and it's taking her
a little bit longer
because we have to overlap
the face onto the cowl
and then do
a full body paint job.
We just have so much to do
still, so I'm nervous.
It's 15 minutes, everybody.
This is a huge risk
because we need to put
everything on this model
in last looks.
That's time, everybody.
Whoo.
Everything is at stake,
because if anything goes wrong
at this point,
it's gonna completely ruin
everything.
It's last looks.
Kelly and I have one hour.
We got to get her contacts in,
we got to do her beauty makeup,
we have to gloss her down, and
then we have to dirty her up.
Nice.
We've still got to glue down
the face.
We have to stretch
the prosthetic a little bit
in order to fit the cowl,
and it's kind of pulling
on our model's eyes,
so it's making me
a little worried.
_
Luckily, he's 6'4,
and the judges can't see
down into his mouth,
but it's not gonna be
the top look.
I'm gonna have to get
more glue in there.
Still got to paint
the helmet green.
Yeah, just do it.
This helmet that we have
has to match
all the other armor,
and I can't find
the color we need.
I find something close,
and I end up just spattering
color onto the helmet.
Ten minutes.
That's time, everybody.
There's a lot of missteps
that happened during last looks.
Now, I'm super nervous.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
As you know, one of you
will be going home tonight,
but before we see
your creations,
let's say hello to our
illustrious series judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve
Makeup Effects Studio,
- Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
Good evening.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
- Hi, everybody.
- Hey, Ve.
And creature and concept
designer, Neville Page.
- Hello.
And welcome back, Rayce.
Thank you.
It's good to be back.
I'm excited to see
what they've come up with.
Well, guess what?
The wait's over.
- Yes!
- Yeah.
All right, guys, this week,
your spotlight challenge
was to create a character
inspired
by one of the unique sounds
created
by Academy Award-nominated
sound designer Erik Aadahl.
So let's take a look
at your creations.
I feel like we really were able
to capture the sound
in our makeup.
I love it, and I'm proud of it.
He's really bigger than life,
but I'm kind of worried.
Did we do enough, makeup-wise?
At this point,
it's either go big or go home.
They made a full fucking suit?
Mm-hmm.
She rocks it.
Oh, my gosh, Stephanie and I
are just on Cloud Nine.
Our demon's looking
scary and badass,
and I'm so excited,
and I think our execution
is near perfect.
Activated.
Weapon system armed.
I'm really disappointed
with the paint job.
It looks washed out
and kind of clownish.
I'm really scared
that I'm gonna be going home.
Jamie and I are feeling
really good.
It's an overall character,
and I feel like it
really matches our sound.
All right, judges, why
don't you take a closer look?
You know, for having to do
so many heads,
they're pretty well rendered
in terms of sculpture.
I just don't understand
this jaw line,
and the way that it comes
down into the chin.
Wow, they did
a lot on this guy.
It's too bad though that...
_
Turn all the way around for us.
I'm really worried
about the back
because a lot of that
didn't get done.
It was just kind of thrown
together last minute.
I'm just hoping
nothing's falling off.
It's just a mess.
Tell us who made your favorite
sound-inspired creation
on Twitter, using #FaceOff.
Yeah, that's a waste of time.
It's just too much.
I'm just hoping
that nothing's coming apart
and they really like our idea.
It's busy,
but it's still kind of cool.
Thank you.
Look at her earrings,
they're little screws.
- Yeah.
- It's cute.
Look at that beautiful profile.
They did a great job retaining
the female facial form.
Open as wide as you can and
just see what that mouth does.
You know what?
That's not as bad as
- what I feared.
- Yeah, I didn't think
it was gonna move.
There's just nothing
around his lips.
It really doesn't blend.
It's just the hole
for his mouth.
Can you turn around, Megan?
- Wow.
- Amazing.
Amazing profile.
Thank you.
Okay, the judges have
scored your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Emily and Jamie...
Logan and Rob...
Congratulations,
because you are all safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
The rest of you were the best
and the worst this week,
and the judges
would like to find out
more about your work.
Stephanie and Kelly,
if you'd please step up.
Tell me how you used the sound
to inspire your design.
There's a clockmaker
and his wife,
and she ends up dying.
He can't live without her,
so he makes a doll
that looks just like his wife.
You could not have done
a better job
of integrating the sound cue.
And your story motivated
the decision, sculpturally,
to put some of these cracks
and things,
which created opportunity
to put those nice brown,
eroded colors in,
and that makes
all the difference in the world.
Thank you.
I think you both did
an amazing job, and of course,
the little portrait of her
and her husband, adorable.
Who drew that portrait?
- That was me, yeah.
- You did?
Good job.
Thank you.
It's beautiful, graphically.
Who sketched out
the overall idea?
I came up with--
instead of doing
a steampunky, grungy character,
I was like,
"Well, why don't we make it look
like a '40s, '50s housewife?"
It really is rendered
and sculpted quite well.
- Thank you.
- Thanks so much.
Kelly and Stephanie,
please step back.
- Yes.
- Good job.
Adam and Regina.
Please tell me how
your sound influenced
the design of your character.
We got a pretty direct
robotic sound,
and there was an animalistic,
techno sound in it,
so we went half organic,
half mechanical with it.
And who is responsible
for what on this character?
The idea came from Regina.
I sculpted
the chest and the back.
And I sculpted the cowl,
the face, and the dome.
I don't feel that this is
a very successful makeup.
The face sculpt underneath
is very, very rough.
He almost looks like
an old man without teeth,
and his mouth
sucked up on itself.
The body pieces are a lot more
successful than the face,
which is what your center
of attention should be.
Okay.
- The visor you sculpted...
- Mm-hmm.
...is gorgeous,
but the face is an abomination,
and I know you're better
than that.
Adam and Regina,
please step back.
Thanks, man.
Julian and Ben, you're up.
Tell us about your character
and how the sound
influenced its design.
The heavy breathing
really stood out as demonic,
and so we went for a demon
that kills
anything and everything,
and then rips their face off,
and en wears it himself.
Face off demon.
I did the cowl,
and then Julian did the face.
I think you hit it
out of the park.
I think the sculpting
is done really well.
The proportions
are done really well.
I love the changes,
graphically,
from black to red
to the pale face.
- Thank you.
Getting that nice,
light tone in the face
and then fading
into the darker colors
just presents
extraordinarily well.
- Thank you.
- He's very scary,
and I think you did
a great job this week.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
You can please step back.
Thank you.
Darla and Anthony,
please step forward.
Tell me how your sound
inspired your design tonight.
We noticed that it was
a very ghostly sound
that had
a lot of different voices,
so we created Satan's servant,
who absorbs souls
and drags them down into Hell.
I primarily sculpted the face,
and Anthony did the chest.
It feels a bit directionless,
I'm afraid.
The paint job-- it feels like
you didn't leave yourself
enough time to color it,
and the dark tones
in the lower half of his face
muddle his head into his chest.
From here, it looks like
he as whiskers,
and the facial structure
is much too big for the size
of his face and his body.
You're trying to animate
this chest
in a way that doesn't work
as a practical makeup,
so it feels silly as a result.
All right, thank you very much.
Please step back.
All right,
I'd like to offer our coaches
the opportunity to speak
on behalf of their team members
before the judges
make their decisions.
I feel like I need
to speak up for Darla.
She has done amazing top looks,
and I would love to see
more of her work,
and I hope we get to.
Regina, she's had
some really successful makeups
up to this point, and I think
the sculpture did get
away from you a little bit,
but I know you can sculpt,
so I think it was just
kind of a bad day.
Something I thought was
really clever
on Anthony's part was to take
the silicon face casts
of the actors and press
the wet clay into their faces
and use those
in the chest piece.
Yeah.
Innovative thought,
I think it's really important.
All right, thank you, guys.
If you'd please
head back to the makeup room
while the judges deliberate.
Alright, judges, let's start
with your favorite looks
tonight.
How about Stephanie and Kelly?
Oh, I love that makeup.
Really nice touches, right down
to their little earrings.
Stephanie drew
that family picture
that she was carrying
around with her.
That's a detail that you often
don't have time to do
and have it actually look
as competent as it did.
All right, should we talk
about Ben and Julian?
I think it was
so well executed.
They made really great use
of the model as well.
They didn't have to take
a whole, big, phony chest piece.
They just sculpted it down
as far as they had to.
I think this is the second
time we've also seen
this idea of a face
going onto a cowl,
and it's almost a separate
element within the design,
which I like.
It's a quality makeup.
All right,
let's move on to the makeups
that didn't quite work
for you guys.
Regina and Adam.
I liked the cowl,
the chest, and the back,
and the face was
horribly painted,
and it was horribly sculpted.
He went into this challenge
knowing that he had immunity,
but the one thing
that does work
are the elements
that he contributed.
She needed to make the decision
of bailing on that makeup
and showcasing what she did
a gorgeous job on,
and that is this visor.
All right, let's move on
to Anthony and Darla.
What a confused concept.
That face was bad.
There was no sense
of understanding of anatomy.
Yeah, I don't know
what she was thinking of
when she sculpted that brow,
because it really did look
like big, giant, bushy
eyebrows.
The bottom of the face merges
into the top of the chest
and it makes it worse,
not better.
I'm want to give higher marks,
though, for Anthony
in using clay presses
- as the faces on the body.
- Yeah.
And I'm glad RJ
brought that up,
because that was
a smart process.
All right, judges,
is everything settled, then?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Yeah.
- It is.
- All right,
let's bring them back out.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about tonight's top teams.
Stephanie and Kelly,
your crystal-clear concept
paid off big time
with a unique character
that paired brilliantly
with your sound.
Julian and Ben. The precise
forms and quality sculpting
really made him shine.
So which team came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Stephanie and Kelly.
Yes.
Your character was
the best tonight
in terms of matching up
to the sound effect.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Stephanie and Kelly,
congratulations,
but as you know,
we can only have one winner.
Glenn?
Tonight's winner is...
Stephanie.
You were more responsible
for the concept,
which is exactly what
sealed the deal here tonight.
It feels so awesome,
winning a spotlight challenge.
It, like, rejuvenates
my confidence in myself.
Stephanie, congratulations.
You, Kelly, Julian,
and Ben are all safe,
and Adam,
since you have immunity,
you are also safe, and can head
back to the makeup room
along with the coaches.
All right, guys, the rest of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be going home.
If you'd please step forward.
Glenn, tell us about tonight's
bottom looks.
Regina, you and Adam
actually had a cool concept,
but a lot of your
sculptural choices
resulted
in a confused character.
Darla and Anthony,
the face and the body
ended up really disconnected
in both shape and color palette.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Regina.
We know that you're
a talented makeup artist,
but we just couldn't get past
the poor face sculpture
this week.
Regina, I am so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
That means Darla and Anthony,
you're safe this week and can
head back to the makeup room.
Regina, you have
so much more to offer,
and I'm truly looking forward
to seeing it in a professional world.
Thank you.
Regina, it's been really great
having you here with us.
But if you please head
backstage and pack-up your kit.
- Good luck.
- Good luck, Regina.
I think the hardest part
is knowing how you do better.
I'm really happy that
I got to this point.
I really, really am.
This is a great job, okay?
I found my voice,
I found my heart,
I found what I love to do,
and I found myself again.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net