I think you hit it
out of the park.
I don't feel this is
a very successful makeup.
You could not have
done a better job.
Previously on Face Off...
Stephanie and Kelly's
mechanical housewife
brought Stephanie her first win,
but Regina stumbled
and was the first on Team Rayce
to be sent home.
Now 11 artists remain,
and tonight they'll dive
into the world of fantasy...
- Oh, my gosh.
- How much do we have?
- Not much time.
- Damn it, damn it, damn it.
I am worried for Kelly
on this one.
And witness the genius
of Hollywood's
greatest creature actor.
Hello.
This is amazing.
Doug Jones is one-of-a-kind.
This is something I would be
proud to wear myself on film.
In the end, only one
will win a VIP trip from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand new 2015 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
This is Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
What do you guys want?
Bacon sounds delicious.
Two bottom looks in a row.
I'm frigging determined
at this point.
I'm the only person
in the house, other than Adam,
who's had two bottom looks.
Yeah, that sucks.
I cannot afford
to be in bottom this week.
I'm sick of being on bottom.
I want to be on top again.
I need to show showcase
what I can do.
I have a lot
to prove at this point.
I'm just gonna
do what I want to do,
what I think is gonna look good.
I'm gonna make it to the finale.
- Yes!
- Look at that bridge.
Ooh, wonderful!
We're walking
down the LA River...
This is exciting.
...and all I can think is,
"So many movies have shot here."
It's amazing.
This place is awesome.
However, I actually have no clue
what we're gonna be doing.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi!
It's here, underneath
these iconic bridges
at the LA River,
that the Terminator himself
hopped on his Harley
and outran a T-1000 in James
Cameron's classic chase scene
from Terminator 2.
Hell yeah.
We might also recognize it
from movies like Grease,
Chinatown, and Escape From LA.
Yeah.
Bridges are a functional
necessity of everyday life,
but they can also
be design marvels,
becoming beautiful testaments
to mankind's engineering
achievements.
However, in the world
of fantasy and fairy tales,
they're also home to a classic
mythological character...
Oh, my gosh.
Trolls.
Yay!
Trolls!
I can't describe
how excited I am.
According to myth,
these oafish but devious trolls
lurk underneath bridges,
devouring those
who dare to pass.
So, your spotlight challenge
is to select one
of these incredible bridges
and create the troll
that lives beneath it.
Oh, that's awesome.
Knowing that it's
a troll challenge,
it, like, clicks in my mind.
"Okay, this is awesome.
I can do this."
I love all things fantasy.
The choices are the Golden
Gate Bridge in San Francisco,
Tower Bridge in London,
Corvin Castle Bridge
in Transylvania,
Dragon Bridge at the Monkey
Forest Sanctuary in Bali,
Helix Bridge in Singapore,
and Python Bridge in Amsterdam.
Adam, you're up first.
Select your bridge.
Now, before you start
working on your designs,
I've got a big surprise for you.
The character and the movement
of a troll is key
to how they express themselves,
and I really want to make sure
that your models
understand that,
so on application day,
I'm bringing in a secret weapon
to help them out.
He happens to be
Hollywood's most sought-after
creature actor.
You've seen his incredible work
in Pan's Labyrinth, Hellboy,
and Fantastic Four
Rise Of The Silver Surfer.
- Hellboy!
- You're kidding me.
Doug Jones.
- Whoo!
- Oh!
That's going to be exciting
to have Doug Jones here.
He's behind all these amazing
characters and their movements.
I can't wait
to actually meet him
and hear what he has
to say to our models.
All right, it's time
to get started, guys.
Now, make sure you keep in mind
not only the architectural
design, but also the location
and cultural setting
of the bridge
when creating your trolls.
Good luck, guys.
See you!
I got the Helix Bridge
in Singapore.
Singapore used to be
a rain forest,
so my idea is that my troll
fell asleep in this rain forest,
and wakes up
in this crazy modern society,
and he starts to genetically
modify himself to be able
to blend into the Helix Bridge.
I'm glad we finally
have a fantasy challenge.
I dig it.
That's my style.
Corvin Castle in Transylvania
was the inspiration
for Dracula's castle,
so I'm thinking that this troll
is a servant to Dracula.
He's going
to be very stone-colored,
matching the color
of the bridge itself.
I got the Corvin Castle Bridge.
My Transylvanian troll blends
into the willow trees
and attacks people
that Dracula doesn't approve of.
I'm gonna try and stick
with a gloomy, scary troll.
It's gonna be awesome.
The history
of the Dragon Bridge in Bali
is that the two statues
guarded the healing waters
that are beyond it,
so I decide that the troll
is camouflaged
by the trees and the moss,
and that he protects
the stone-like guardians.
I chose the Dragon Bridge
at the Monkey Sanctuary in Bali,
and my troll is a fallen warrior
that was given new life,
but his new life is the curse
of being a troll
and protecting the bridge.
The vines
create this hunched silhouette,
and the rest
of it will be brought to life
through costuming
and fabrications.
All right everybody,
let's go back to the lab.
Excited!
We get back to the lab,
and we pick our models,
and we have 5 1/2 hours
to work today.
Amsterdam originated
as a fishing village,
and so I'm making
a water-dwelling troll
who is tormenting the fishermen,
but I'm still not really
sold on anything right now,
so I have a lot
of work ahead of me.
Hi!
Come.
Rayce comes in, and he pulls
us together for a team meeting.
When it comes
to the conceptual stuff,
you guys have to think
where no one's thinking.
Reinvent trolls.
I want to make sure that no one
is doing
the traditional big nose.
If we've seen
those trolls before,
it's not gonna go well.
I have four people left,
and I really want to keep them,
so I'm really
pushing these guys.
- Okay?
- All right.
It's time to move, gentlemen.
All right.
Word up.
My bridge
is the Tower Bridge in London,
so I want to keep
the regal aspect of it.
My backstory is a prince
that fell in love
with a princess,
but the king's not too happy
about their courtship,
so he turns him into the troll.
I'm really taking Rayce's
advice on this one,
and I'm not going with
the traditional large forehead.
I'm extending the back
of the head,
and I want to add horns
to the top.
So hopefully I can make
it stand out.
I'm really excited
about this piece.
I'm gonna
incorporate the cliff texture
into doing a
shoulder-chest-back, one piece.
My concept is a girl jumped
off the Golden Gate Bridge
during sunset.
Her body washed ashore
to the little island,
and became one of the rocks,
and she climbs up the bridge
during sunrise and sunset
to drag people down.
- Like, that kind of sunset...
- Yeah.
- ...fuse colors?
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Ooh, so more of a spritely
kind of character, I like it.
I want something
very lean, very feminine.
My coach, Laura,
is on board with it,
so I'm gonna run with that.
I think you're in a good place.
- Hi, everybody!
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Hello.
I'm gonna troll over here
and see what you're doing.
So, what bridge did you get?
So, I have the Python Bridge
in Amsterdam.
During the summertime,
children will play on the bridge
and jump into the water.
It'll actually look
like a regular girl,
but when she turns around,
she's this hideous troll.
I've changed this probably
five times.
I think you've got
a great direction going.
You need more bulk,
though, in the face.
You need to bring up the fantasy
and the character in it.
Right.
My bridge
is the Tower Bridge in London,
and my troll is this mother
whose child died on the bridge,
so she will forever haunt
this bridge in revenge.
Your technique
for your sculpture is great,
but I think you need to pull
a little bit more troll into it.
Give her some more lower lip.
This could have
more weight to it.
It could even be
a little bulbous,
as opposed
to trying to make it narrow.
Awesome. Thank you so much.
I got the Golden Gate Bridge.
San Francisco burned
to the ground in the mid-1800s,
so I'm giving the toll
a burned look,
and he's wearing a mask
to worship the crows
of San Francisco.
I think your
sculpture looks great.
You can paint this,
and get black down into
those crevices and everything,
and then dry brush,
or with a sponge,
going over the top of it
and picking up highlights.
You want it to be
able to pop out.
Thanks very much.
I have the Python Bridge
in Amsterdam.
I would go
a little bit more traditional
with the troll nose.
- This is a fantasy character...
- Right.
...and so you can add
some depth to that.
- Yeah.
- Good luck.
All right.
Thank you so much.
I have the Dragon Bridge.
Oh, and you have it right here.
I just want to incorporate
a lot of the moss,
and a lot of the greenery
in there.
Don't cover it
with so much vegetation
that you can't see it at all.
When you apply it,
there should be some thought
of how this is, like,
the branches of the tree.
- Mm-hmm. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Bye, everybody.
- Bye.
See you under the bridge.
After Mr. Westmore leaves,
I start to bulk out the nose,
'cause that was one
of his first suggestions,
and I get kind of stuck.
This is totally throwing
me right now.
I talked to Laura about it...
Bring the nostrils in.
I'm liking her ideas,
but at the same time,
I'm not seeing them
in my finished product,
so now I'm kind of at this wall.
_
I just hate it.
I can't figure this shit out.
This could be the challenge
that puts me on the bottom
and sends me home.
I don't know.
It's day
one of the troll challenge,
and I'm at this wall.
I can't figure this shit out.
I just hate it.
I decided the best thing to do
is start blocking out the cowl.
I've wasted five hours
of this challenge,
so I'm just really nervous,
and stressed, and frustrated.
I don't know how much texture
I'm thinking about.
If I can figure out
the shapes of the cowl,
then the face
might work itself out.
It's time
for us coaches to leave,
and I am most
worried about Darla.
I hope she's able to get
past this funk.
- Relax.
- Yeah.
- Tomorrow will be a better day.
- Exactly.
- Keep rolling on it.
- Thanks, man.
I appreciate it.
Great job today.
Logan, how much time
do we have left?
30 minutes.
Rayce says not to do
what's expected,
so I'm making
one side very rocky,
but then what I'm having
is the rocks start to fade off
into these very smooth,
angular shapes,
because they have
such a modern society
that he's trying to fit in.
Hopefully the judges
are going to understand
what I'm trying to do.
That's time, everybody.
I just feel like
they're not gonna be able
to look at it and just get it.
I'm thinking, "Am I
doing something wrong?"
I am so nervous for tomorrow.
And so it begins.
So, it's day two
of our bridge troll challenge.
We have 9 1/2 hours in the lab.
- Good morning!
- Hello.
There are a lot of trees
around the bridge,
so I want to incorporate the
wood texture into the sculpt.
I have done wood texture before.
It's really difficult, but I
can't play it safe anymore.
I like it a lot.
I like it too.
I want to try
to bring it back a little bit,
just so you have
a good edge there.
With only three people
left in the competition,
I really don't want
to go down to two.
Luckily, Ben, Kelly,
and Jamie are very talented,
so I'm confident in my team.
This is your
best sculpture yet.
Yeah, I'm really happy
with the forms
that are happening on this face.
I'm feeling better
about my sculpture.
It's a big risk
not going with, like,
the very traditional troll,
but I'm staying positive,
and I'm staying confident,
and I'm just going to keep going
and hope for the best.
Looking at the reference photo
of the Golden Gate,
there's a little island that has
more of a rocky style to it,
so I decided to use rock texture
on my sculpts.
It's definitely
gonna be different,
but I am happy with my sculpt,
so I'm gonna run
into the mold room
and start molding everything.
It's not my favorite,
but it's all right.
I'll get pieces done,
and I'll do a killer paint job,
and it'll be all fine.
I'm working hard
on these sculpts,
and I'm still not in love
with either one of them,
but at this point I know I don't
have time to change my mind.
I just need to get these
into the mold room
so that I have pieces
on application day.
Trolls usually
tend to be a nasty creature,
but I'm trying
to incorporate playfulness,
so I want her to have
a big beer-belly on her.
When I come in tomorrow,
I'll cut open the swimsuit
and expose some of the sculpt
that I've done.
Hopefully this complete change
will show the judges
that I'm able to create
something that's fun.
This is a very big cowl.
I'm extending the back
of the head a little bit,
and I want to add horns
to the top.
I'm a little worried
that it looks kind of alien-ish.
I'm not going
too troll on this one.
But it's kind of too late
to change my idea.
I've got to go with this.
I kind of
like the head shape, Rob.
Yeah?
Rayce is liking the sculpt.
He kind of likes
the elongated head.
I'm going with his instinct,
and I'm rolling ahead with it.
Just keep cracking on it,
and keep watching that clock
to make sure you're getting
in there when you need to.
- Good luck!
- Yes, thank you.
- Bye, guys.
I build the back piece
on a mannequin
for the character's silhouette,
and the first thing I do
is I grab a block of foam
and begin to shape it
like a hump.
Because the troll lives
under the Dragon Bridge in Bali,
the back piece is going
to be consisted of large vines,
and hemp, and leaves,
and some snake textures,
so that it looks
like one cohesive design.
I took my face to open it,
and my mold doesn't go anywhere.
Oh my God, it's locked.
If this doesn't open up,
I don't have a face.
I leave it aside because I
don't want to think about it,
I want to work
on something else,
so I start to open
the chest mold...
If you can just
press down on that.
Logan helps me get it out.
Oh, shit.
Okay, you definitely
have a crack.
Great, it's cracking.
Oh my God.
I don't have time to fix this.
I don't think I'm gonna
have my molds done.
Shit.
I'm just feeling
so afraid right now,
because I won't have
any pieces tomorrow.
I don't know what to do.
It's day two of our
troll challenge.
My face mold's locked,
and my torso mold is cracked.
Shit.
This is such a train wreck.
I need to get the face out
no matter what.
Ben takes the chisel
and starts hammering it,
but it's still not opening up.
Finally, somehow, it pops open.
Thank you so much.
I feel so much better,
but now I don't have time
to fix my torso mold.
I take it to the pressure
washer, clean it out,
and put it back together,
but because the mold
is so beaten-up,
the foam latex
is gonna be a mess,
and trimming and patching
is gonna be very difficult
and time-consuming.
All right, everybody.
That's time.
I'm so flustered
and just disappointed.
Application day is a disaster.
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab
and one hour for last looks.
Doug Jones is going to be
interacting with our models
to get them more
into this troll character,
and I can't wait.
- What's up, man?
- Bam!
Oh, gosh.
I look at my foam, and...
This is not good.
I've never seen foam this thick.
My edges are horrific.
Yeah.
It'll take a little time.
I have to make it work.
- Hi!
- It's so good to see you!
This is gonna be so much fun.
My confidence level
today is way up here.
This is really important
for me to show the judges
that I can not only sculpt,
but I can also paint too.
It's gonna be much better
to lay in your light colors
over the top.
I'm not doing
the traditional green troll.
I want to make it different.
Team Rayce getting
their paint on.
I want to incorporate
a lot of that tan look
that you see in the trees,
and the roots,
and the dark crevices,
and I want him to be able
to camouflage into the setting.
_
I blended the edges somewhat,
but it's taking forever.
Start painting
in the next half an hour.
I'm sweating bullets,
because I'm so far behind.
So I just start paining
as fast as I can.
Hello!
Hey, hey!
This is amazing.
Here he is, Doug Jones.
- Hi, everybody.
- Hi.
Can we just see what you're
all coming up with today.
He's one of a kind.
He can bring a simple
character to life
in just a matter of movements,
and now he's directing
our models
on how to become our trolls.
It's really an honor.
What happened here?
You poor thing.
He's a prince
that's been cursed.
The live-in stance
would be the regal posture,
but what's gonna sell the shame
might be in the head itself.
Like, if the head
hangs from time to time,
while you're keeping
the proud chest, you know?
Like you're walking
into the court room,
but then you remember,
"Oh, right.
I'm a troll now."
I wouldn't rock so much.
Make your movement
very definite.
You know what I'm saying?
Right?
Argh!
That's what I'm talking about.
If this was a remnant
of my son that I lost,
it would be a clutch
and a love for this.
- That is so cool.
- That is awesome.
- Oh.
- Get fluid in the arms.
That's beautiful.
It's more tree-branchy.
It seems like that might even
be a more jittery motion.
You know, when I did
Pan's Labyrinth, for instance,
the faun was part tree,
so there was a sort
of a ricketiness to him.
So you're gonna help sell this
with that climbing
instinct, right?
Like, if you wanted
to come up like this,
and sort of use the air
as something to climb on...
- Oh, I like that!
- ...while you're facing us.
My model is practically
screaming.
She's so excited.
It's really nice
having his input.
See? Okay.
You knock 'em alive, okay?
There's many, many combinations
of posture we can do.
You can-- We have shoulders,
we have the back,
we have the lower back,
upper back,
we got the neck, neck, neck.
If you're coming out
with a reveal, give us a "Ugh."
You know what I mean? Ugh.
I would be proud
of this for sure, right?
Look at it,
look at us, show it off.
This way, this way, this way,
that way, that way, that way.
And then maybe
back down again, right?
Find the child in you,
'cause you want
to fit in with the kids.
One of these kind of things
is gonna help sell the whole--
Yeah, there you go.
Sassy, sassy, playful, playful.
Whee, whee, whee!
All right everybody,
thank you so much.
- We'll see you soon.
- Thank you.
Okay, bye.
Your transitions
are looking good.
- You like it?
- Yeah.
I definitely want to be able
to show that my troll
is changing
into this Helix Bridge,
so I'm using the dark
bluish-grey on the rock side,
and I'm using the lightish grey
on the metal side
to show that he
is genetically altering himself.
Look that way for me.
I take a step back
and look at my paint job,
and I see
the transition happening.
Sick.
For the paint, I want
to make it look like flesh
and match the model's skin.
My troll
is definitely different.
I'm not sure if I went
in the right direction or not,
but I like
what I've created so far.
Everybody, ten minutes!
At the end of the day,
I'm coming in
with my layer of pax--
definitely getting
some really sweet tones--
and then...
It's looking kind of muddy.
Great.
All of the sweet
colors that I chose
bleed into one solid brown mess.
You don't know where
the costume ends and she starts.
Now I have to go
in a completely different
direction with my paint.
- How much do we have?
- Not much time.
Damn it, damn it, damn it.
I am worried for Kelly
on this one,
and I do not want to lose
another person this week.
She still has
a lot of work to do.
That's time, everybody.
Holy crap, I am going to have
to fix this hot mess
in last looks.
I'm screwed.
So it's last looks,
we have one hour left,
and I got to get
those contacts in,
and I have to
finish the paint job,
and it's definitely going
to be eating up my entire hour.
Open your eyes.
I have to finish
painting the face,
finish painting the body,
and I'm just slopping
on color as fast as I can.
Moss everywhere!
I'm grabbing moss
and just throwing it on,
because without the moss,
he doesn't camouflage into the
setting of the Dragon Bridge.
Anything else I'm missing?
I just want to dirty
up her arms,
and make her as nasty
as possible
to change up my colors.
Ten minutes, everybody!
That's time, everybody!
I'm noticing that mine
looks like no one else's.
It's really starting to sink in
that I really
could be going home.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Now, as you know, one of you
will be going home tonight,
but before we see
your creations,
let's say hello
to our series judges.
Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
Ve Neill.
- Howdy.
- How are you?
- And Neville Page.
- Hello.
Hello.
And of course,
we have the very special guest
that I mentioned to you
a couple days ago.
He's a fantastically
talented actor
and one of Hollywood's
most in-demand creature actors.
Please welcome
the phenomenal Doug Jones.
Thank you. Hi.
That's a tough intro
to live up to, but thank you.
It's so great
to have you back on this show.
Thank you for being here.
Boy, it's great to be back.
Thank you for having me.
Now, how did your time
go with the models today?
Oh, goodness.
A great time with the models.
It was really exciting to see
the love they have
for putting on these creatures
to make your creations
come to life.
All right, well you
saw the makeups in progress...
I did, I did.
So let's see
how they turned out.
Seeing Megan with
that backdrop makes it work.
I'm proud of what's onstage.
I'm definitely not happy
with how the face turned out,
so I'm just hoping for the best,
and we'll see
what the judges say.
He matches the culture
and the history of Singapore,
and that's what I set out to do,
and that's what I accomplished.
It looks pretty cool.
The silhouette's there--
I'm happy with it.
It's a little bit rough,
but I did execute the vision.
I'm at least proud that I was
able to get this much work done.
Mine looks like no one else's.
I really thought
outside the box,
and I'm just hoping that the
judges are with me on this one.
I'm not 100% happy
with the sculpt,
but I'm really happy
with the paint job.
I think he's really
looking good.
Doug Jones brought my character
to a whole other level.
She looks creepy, crawly,
and I love it.
I don't know where I stand,
because mine doesn't look
anything like anybody else's.
I could either be on top,
or I could be on the bottom.
I feel like my model could be
moving a little bit more,
but I really like her.
I think she could be a top look.
I think it looks fantastic.
She sells it very well,
and I'm totally sold
on my own character.
I'm sorry, I love it.
Okay, judges,
it's time for a closer look.
There's these hard edges
that don't even, shape-wise,
go into the anatomy;
that's a big problem.
It's also not sculpted
literal enough to tell us
that it is rock.
Yeah, I think you're right.
Can you turn to the side?
It's the round, spherical shape
that I struggle with,
and I'm not sure
how that communicates troll.
Yeah.
I have no idea what
the judges are thinking.
I know the sculpts
don't look good,
but I hope they
don't hate them too much,
because I don't want to go home.
Tell us who made your favorite
fantasy troll tonight
on Twitter, using #FaceOff.
I'm not sure
how that spherical shape
communicates troll.
I'm just not a fan of
the sculpts that I did,
and that makes me
a little bit worried.
My favorite part about
this whole makeup is the color.
- I agree.
- Good job selling it.
I just don't even understand
what's going on.
It's morphing.
But there's no line
of demarcation with colors;
you can't tell
that it's morphing.
Yeah, it's pretty rough.
I think it's
a gorgeous sculpture.
It looks like a caricature
drawing to me.
From the boardwalk, yeah.
- Yeah, from the boardwalk.
- Totally, totally, yeah.
There's some really rough forms
covered by some
really good paint.
And that head shape
is not even remotely troll-like.
There's some
really beautiful color.
Lovely job.
I love this hybrid of, like,
woodsy-barky-dragony together.
Love that chest.
It's beautiful.
To the right, please.
It doesn't seem appropriate
for a troll to me.
It's very bizarre
that this is so bright red.
Thank you.
It's great.
Okay, the judges
have scored your creations.
Let's find out
what they thought.
Adam,
Darla,
Stephanie,
Logan,
Julian,
you are all safe and can head
back to the makeup room.
Nice work this week.
Thanks.
Good job.
Now the rest of you
were the best
and the worst this week,
and the judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Kelly, could you please step up?
Explain how your bridge
inspired your design this week.
Her child
was working on the bridge,
and he falls to his death,
and it drove her completely mad,
and so she's just
forever cursing this bridge.
I think you did
an astounding job.
Thank you.
You've made proficient use
of your model's features.
I really like
what you did this week.
Thank you so much.
It's very monotone,
which is absolutely okay,
because she just seems
like she's become
at one with this bridge.
- Nice job.
- Thank you so much.
It doesn't feel troll-like,
but I do like how you've
completed this as a character.
- It's pretty solid.
- Thank you.
Nayeli, your performance
is absolutely perfect.
- Beautiful job, both of you.
- Thank you.
Kelly,
if you'd please step back.
_
- Good job, Kelly.
- Thank you.
Anthony.
Tell me how the Helix Bridge
inspired your character.
My character was a troll who
used to live in the rainforest,
but he fell asleep, and woke up
in this crazy modern society,
so he started to genetically
alter his features
in order to hide
under the new bridge.
This guy doesn't look like he
belongs with that bridge at all.
I couldn't figure out if he was
supposed to be metal or rock.
- I just don't get it.
- Okay.
This transition
is the biggest problem.
It's just all one grey
textural thing.
I see a little bit
of confusion in the sculpt,
and I think it's
because of a lack
of a clearly-identified
goal for yourself.
Anthony, please step down.
All right, let's talk to Ben.
Tell us how your bridge
inspired this troll.
During the summertime,
kids will actually come
and play on the bridge.
She's a fun troll,
and I wanted to do something
a little more fun and whimsical.
Excellent, 'cause
that's why I love this.
Thank you.
I really applaud
the courage to do something
that may not work.
Love it, and I love
how you're thinking.
Thank you.
I love the whimsy,
I love the laughter of it all,
and Alexandria,
you have brought such playful,
childlike attitude to this.
As an actor, I would love
to work on film with you.
I think it's the best work
I've seen you do.
Super strong decisions
in terms of detail.
Everything on that face
is working for me.
Thank you.
Ben, please step back.
Emily, please come forward.
Talk to me
about the Golden Gate Bridge
influencing this troll.
The story is that she
jumped off the bridge,
and her body washed ashore
to one of the little islands,
and she transformed
into that rock texture.
I would rather not see the
skin-to-prosthetic transitions,
but the paint job
I think is gorgeous.
Your choice of colors
and complimentary colors
is beautiful.
I get that you
took huge risks this week,
but they didn't pay off.
I'm bumping on the abrupt
transitions really hard.
This doesn't fit
into the troll thing for me.
It's a beautiful character,
it's just not a beautiful
character for this challenge.
I agree.
Emily, you can head back.
Rob, please step up.
Please give us the backstory
to your bridge-inspired troll.
This is a prince that fell
in love with a princess,
but her father didn't like the
courtship that they were having,
so he put a curse on him.
The underlying form
is extraordinarily flawed.
I actually love your paint job,
but unfortunately,
there's not a whole lot
happening here anatomically
to tell me it's a troll,
or more importantly,
to communicate
a successful makeup effect.
It looks like a pullover mask.
It's got too much
going on back here,
when it should've been
going on up here.
It just missed for me
this week, Rob.
Okay.
Rob, please step down.
_
Jamie, please come forward.
Tell us how the Dragon Bridge
in Bali inspired your character.
There are statues
of good and evil
that protect the bridge.
This is actually the protector
of those guardians.
I think it's really well done.
Your paint job
is really beautiful.
Thank you.
I think that you've achieved
a plausible wood sculpt,
and that's not easy to do.
Thank you.
This is something I would be
proud to wear, myself, on film.
The sculpt is
so incredibly detailed
and gorgeous to look at.
You did a great job.
Beautiful.
Thank you.
Jamie, please step back.
All right, coaches,
do you have anything
to say to the judges before
they make their decisions?
I apologize, guys--
Anthony and Rob.
I told my team the last thing
that I wanted them to do
is go in the direction
of the big noses
and the big chins,
so I'm realizing now
that that was the wrong route.
A lot of those choices
were from my pushing.
Okay.
Please head back
to the makeup room
while the judges deliberate.
All right, judges,
why don't we talk
about your favorites this week?
- Let's start with Kelly.
- I love the pallet.
It had that real
washed-out look.
It was fabulous.
To pay that much
attention, head to toe,
I'm a big fan of hers.
All right,
let's move on to Ben.
I loved the whimsy.
I love that she wants
to fit in with the kids.
Creating those big,
fantastical proportions
and making them work
is extremely difficult.
Okay, what about Jamie?
She did an amazing job
bringing in the surroundings.
Beautiful paint job.
I loved the makeup.
Also the decision
to use a wood-carved sculpture.
Huge risk, great reward.
All right,
so let's move on to the makeups
that didn't work for you.
Let's start with Anthony.
I think the paint job
is what was lacking for me.
If he would've
changed the color,
you would have realized it was
some sort of a transformation.
All right,
let's move on to Emily.
Hard ledges
that don't fit the anatomy,
and they have no blending edge
on them whatsoever.
There's no evidence
visually of troll.
- None.
All right,
let's move on to Rob.
The thing I struggled the most
with was the overall form,
in side view in particular.
Rayce really did trip him up.
It looked too masky for me,
like it was slipped over,
and painted some dark eyes
on it, you know?
All right judges,
have you made up your minds?
- We have.
- Okay.
Let's bring 'em back out.
All right, Glenn,
tell us about the top looks.
Kelly,
I thought you did
a really convincing job
with your painting,
and your character
as a whole was
creepy and compelling.
Ben,
what a bold choice,
to fully embrace the fantasy
aspect of this challenge
in such an exaggerated
and fun way.
And Jamie,
we love the wood texture
of your character.
We also thought you did a great
job embracing the culture
and the history of your bridge.
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of this challenge is...
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of this challenge is...
Jamie.
This was hands-down
your best work so far.
Whatever you did
to find your focus
and put your best foot forward,
you must keep it up.
Okay.
To be on top and to win,
it's a great feeling,
but at the same time,
it's humbling,
because I need to work harder,
and keep that up.
There's just one more
congratulations that we owe,
and that is to you, Anthony.
All three of the top looks
tonight were from your team.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
All right, Jamie.
You, Kelly, and Ben
can all head back
to the makeup room,
along with the coaches.
Thanks, guys.
The rest of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be going home.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Anthony, we thought
that there was some nice
sculpting moments in your work,
but your vision
was not communicated
in the final character.
Emily, we appreciate
your creative thinking,
but this one got away from you,
and the troll aspect
of the challenge
was lost in the mix.
Rob, your paint choices
and your techniques were good,
but your makeup suffered
from anatomical flaws
that rendered it
more alien than troll.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going
home tonight is...
Anthony.
Unfortunately, the visual
language of your character
was indiscernible as troll.
Anthony, I'm so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
Emily and Rob,
you are both safe this week.
You can head back
to the makeup room.
We've been so impressed
with your passion for makeup,
and we understand
that you really
belong doing this for a living.
This is just the first
step on that journey.
It's just been an absolutely
amazing experience.
Thank you.
Anthony, it's really been
great having you here with us,
but if you would please head
back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you.
- Good luck.
- Good luck, babe.
This experience has been
absolutely life-changing for me.
It's me.
This is just the beginning,
and I've grown so much.
I'm now a better person,
and I'm more confident
in my abilities.
The world is open to me,
and I can't wait
for what's next.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net