You were incredibly successful.
One of the prettiest paint jobs
I've seen on the show.
You've created these dimensions.
It's very smart.
Thank you very much.
Previously on Face Off...
Logan's beautiful body paint
carried him to victory,
and Rob became Team Rayce's
third straight artist
to be sent home.
Now nine artists remain,
and tonight they will tackle
a terrifying challenge
for a movie legend,
Clive Barker.
Hello, Face Off contestants.
Oh, shit.
My mold's cracked.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
How did this happen?
My face is a frickin' disaster.
I do not know
what I'm looking at.
In the end, only
one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand-new 2015 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
This is Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- Congrats on that win.
- Thanks.
I got to celebrate
for about five minutes,
until I found out
Rob was going home.
Adam and I are the only ones
left on Team Rayce,
so it's time for other teams
to start losing people.
All right.
I hope I can keep bringing it,
but it's gonna be tough.
Whiskey A Go Go.
That's cool.
This place is legendary.
All right.
So I'm pretty excited for this.
_
Hey, guys.
Welcome to the most legendary
music venue on the Sunset Strip,
the world-famous Whisky A Go Go.
Since 1964, this stage has
featured incredible performances
from iconic bands
like The Doors,
Led Zeppelin, The Ramones,
and The Sex Pistols.
Wow.
Are you guys ready to rock?
Yes!
Good, because this week's
Spotlight Challenge
is inspired by a true master
of the macabre.
He has spawned some of the most
terrifying characters
in the history of horror films,
including Candyman
and Hellraiser's Pinhead.
Clive Barker.
Wow.
Not only am I
a huge horror fan.
I am a massive Hellraiser fan.
So I'm pumped.
So in the 1980s,
Freddy Krueger, Jason Voorhees
and Michael Myers
terrified audiences
as silent killers
hell-bent on destruction.
However, in Clive's
now-classic film Hellraiser,
he essentially redefined
the cinematic villain
by making Pinhead
intelligent, eloquent,
and, best of all, stylish.
Perhaps it's best if you hear it
from Clive himself.
Hello, Face Off contestants.
I'm Clive Barker,
and I'm very excited
about this challenge.
When I was making demons
for a new age,
it was the punk clubs I went to
where I looked
for fresh inspiration,
fresh blood if you will.
I would love to see you
create something new.
go to the very cutting edge
of current fashion,
and marry that with images that
are startling and terrifying.
Have fun.
So for this week's challenge,
like Clive,
you'll find your inspiration
from today's
futuristic fashions.
Oh, this is so cool.
Your Spotlight Challenge
is to choose
one of these stunning
avant-garde outfits
and use it as an inspiration
for your very own
stylish and intelligent
horror villain.
Your villains will be wearing
these outfits
on the reveal stage.
And by choosing the outfit,
you're also choosing your model
for this week's challenge.
Jamie, you're up first.
Megan.
Matt.
Sarah.
Elena.
Alex.
Naele.
Augustine.
Kerstin.
Come on, Kodi.
All right, guys,
in true muse fashion,
your models will stay with you
while you work on your designs.
Good luck.
Bye.
Turn around.
I'm looking at Kodi's outfit,
and I find a shape
that is just different,
and I want to run with it.
So my concept is a fallen angel
who is cursed with a cage
around his head.
So your head will be,
like, right there,
and this is gonna go over it.
It's almost spider-like.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know?
So I was thinking
we can go black widow-ish.
Yeah.
My concept is a female
who has been scorned by men,
so she attracts them
through her beauty
and then kills them.
I'm so excited.
Such a weird combination,
old relic necklace
and the futuristic jacket.
This character
needs to be intelligent,
but also scary and creepy.
So my concept is a demon
that goes after people
that wear this amulet
and kills them.
His whole head
is one giant mouth
with finger-like appendages
that rip the souls
out of its victims.
_
Yeah.
Look at me.
Ooh, that's cool.
My character is very vain,
very obsessed
with plastic surgery.
Then she starts going
under her own knife.
I also want to give her a mask.
So she appears to be
super sleek and stylish,
then she takes off the mask
to reveal the ultra,
ultra nastiness.
With how fierce you are, girl,
it's gonna be so rad.
All right, thanks a lot.
- I'll see you soon.
- Yep.
We get to the lab.
We have 5 1/2 hours today.
And I really want
to sculpt to finish the face
and block out that extreme cowl,
because if it doesn't
look good in clay,
I want to have enough time
to scrap it
and create something else.
Clive Barker said, "We want
to see something different."
So I'm gonna try
something different.
- Ooh, hey.
- Hello, guys.
That's a cool costume.
Right now I don't have
a solid concept.
I'm feeling like
there's not a whole lot
that I can do with this
without going too obvious.
So I'm getting
a little frustrated.
So that's what I'm stuck with.
No, it's not "stuck with."
You've been given an opportunity
to expand on it.
Stephanie is having some
serious conceptual problems,
and I implore her
just to take some time
and think about it
before starting to sculpt.
I kind of want to just start
throwing clay down and playing.
I think this
is a cool challenge,
to kind of create things
that are just bizarre.
Mine has this big silver tutu,
so I come up
with this metal-like surface
that is encapsulating
the back of her head,
which is gonna be
this leather-bound skull cap.
And I'm feeling
pretty good about it.
I think I've landed
on a theme of poisons.
My character's going to be
a snake charmer
who has turned killer
and has developed
an immunity to venom.
He's going to look sickly
and anemic and have boils.
And to suggest his intelligence,
I've actually come up
with this grid-like pattern
down both sides of the arms.
It's a means of cataloging
all the different poisons
that he creates.
The one thing I'd suggest
is making bigger grids...
Yeah.
Just so from afar it doesn't
read like a busy
mess kind of a thing.
Does that make sense?
Yeah, good point.
I picked the costume
that screams "post-apocalyptic."
And I'm doing a demon character.
But I want to make sure visually
he looks completely different
than what you would
necessarily expect of a demon.
Hi, everybody.
- Hey.
- Hi.
So it looks very interesting.
She's pretty much
a South American goddess
that was resurrected,
and she kills people
by turning them to gold.
Are you meaning this as a hat?
Some kind of headdress,
but it's also a part of her.
I would blend this off
onto her nose,
and then it actually
becomes her.
Okay.
She comes out kind of seeming
all nice and pretty
and beautiful...
Right.
Then reveal this
nasty, nasty mouth.
You could even
put a little blood there
and shoot a little water,
and it'll just kind of drip.
Then it really looks horror
when that piece comes off.
What are you pounding on?
- A cowl.
I've been battling
the concept all day.
Let's see what
you're doing there.
Right now you've got
a head piece
with nothing going on here.
An interesting
thing to do would be
put little hooks
on the ends of these things
so it looks like it's hooked
into her skin
all the way around.
Yeah, that's an idea.
- Go for it.
- Ehh...
Go for it, you know.
Listen.
You're on the way;
you're on the way.
The idea is, put one big hole
in the back of his head.
It's almost like
he has these appendages
that sucks the souls
through this hole.
Mm-hmm.
I think
you need to think somewhere
of having something into it
that is either pulling skin
or something that is going
to read as horror.
Mm-hmm.
Thanks, everybody.
- See ya.
- Thank you.
Bye, thank you.
I'm really embarrassed
that Mr. Westmore came through
and I didn't have anything
to show him.
_
It's frustrating because I feel
like this should be my element.
I'm a haunter.
I do scary all the time.
This shouldn't be that hard.
I can't not make anything.
I can't say, "Oh, give me
another day to think about it."
Stupid.
And at this point
in the competition,
if you don't make something
really cool,
you could be going home.
So, it's day one
of our Clive Barker challenge,
and I'm having trouble,
like, nailing down
a solid concept.
And I'm just super frustrated.
What parts of that do you like?
I'm definitely
worried about Stephanie.
She's such a good
concept person,
and for her to struggle,
it just breaks my heart.
I decide to just
keep concepting
for the rest of day one.
No more sculpting.
I have 9 1/2 hours tomorrow.
And hopefully I'll get it done.
Do something like this,
not just-- boom-- into it.
It's just that subtle
change of form.
Jamie is having some
trouble refining the face,
so I keep pointing out
some things just to clean up.
Maybe you want to
get a little bit more.
Oh, yeah, down--
- In here.
- Uh-huh.
And we talk about incorporating
elements of the spider
to be a little bit more
into the Clive Barker universe.
We'll see.
Just keep refining;
get all the details.
- I got to get going.
- Okay.
And have fun, most importantly.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
It's time for the coaches
to leave,
and I'm pretty confident
with what both Adam and Logan
have done today.
But at the same time,
I only have two artists
left on my team,
so I'm really not feeling
relaxed in this stage.
Just win, okay?
- Yeah, Yeah.
- Just win.
Have fun.
How you feeling about it?
Pretty good.
Struggling a little bit.
Think I'm headed
in the right direction, though.
I decide to follow
Mr. Westmore's advice
and work on making the face
look a little less human--
a lot less human.
Have to do a lot more
detail sculpting,
but I feel really good
about this concept,
and I think I have
a good chance.
I'd really like
to win this one.
Yeah, same.
30 minutes, everybody.
That's time, everybody.
It's day two, and I'm feeling
a little better than day one.
I know what I'm gonna do now.
Basically it's gonna be
gross skin,
like, peeling up
and being, like, hooked forward.
Ooh, okay.
My concept for this character
is some sort of seer,
and then the way she kills
is that she tells people
their futures
and how they're gonna die,
and if they try to avoid it,
then she ends up
killing them herself.
The only advice I'd give
is to try to keep her
somewhat beautiful.
Pretty, yeah.
I have to have something
sculpted, molded,
and ready for foam today.
So I decide to just go
with a cowl
that's manageable for me
in one day.
Today I've got a lot to do.
I have to get the face done.
I also have to get
these arm pieces done.
These are gonna be, like,
the different poisons
that he injects...
Mm-hmm.
And the different things
it causes?
Yeah.
I'm sculpting with monster clay,
which is a wax-based clay,
and it's great for fine detail.
You can melt it
with a heat gun or torch,
and you can get certain effects
that I think will really help
with the character design
that I've come up with.
I like what you're doing here.
I think it's cool.
I'd start working
on the face, you know?
Well, I was gonna mold this
and then go work on the face.
So I've got my cowl sculpted.
Now I need to get it molded
as soon as possible,
because I still need
to make a face piece.
The overall design for
Ben's cowl is really awesome.
Hopefully the face
looks equally cool.
No, the string
isn't long enough.
For the cowl,
I want to fabricate a cage
that interlocks with the face.
And I'm really inspired
by string art.
One thing that
was really important
is, like, make sure
it's something
that Clive hasn't seen before.
- Yeah.
- So, I just--
I haven't seen
anything like this before.
It's going to have a wonderful
profile and silhouette.
Sweet.
I finish my cowl,
and I'm actually
really pleased with it.
Now I have to get it molded
and out the door.
So it's really important
that I take my time,
because it's gonna be
a two-part mold,
and if one half
is slightly overlapping,
it'll lock my mold.
It doesn't look like this
is all stretched skin.
Mm-hmm.
Darla is still kind of
struggling with her cowl.
She's sculpting
the stretched skin idea,
but, for whatever reason,
it doesn't seem
to be translating.
So I just grab a head
and I start sculpting on it
to show her how
to sculpt wrinkles.
These wrinkles,
they go all the way.
Yeah.
We're leaving.
All righty.
Cool, good luck.
- Awesome.
- Okay?
Sweet, thank you.
Leaving day two,
I think everybody
seems to be in a good place,
but I'm still worried
about Jamie.
Her face has to look beautiful
in order for this character
to work,
and right now she still has
a long way to go on it.
- Bye, guys.
- Keep kicking ass.
Good luck.
I get my cowl molded,
and I start to open it.
Oh, shit.
I notice that my mold's cracked.
And I'm like, shit.
I'm trying not to freak out.
I'm looking at the crack
in the mold,
and it's a pretty big crack.
I mean, I've seen
some big cracks.
This is the biggest crack
I've seen.
This is my only piece,
and if I mess this up,
I'm gonna go out on stage
with nothing.
So this needs to get fixed.
Mold cracked in half.
It's day two
of our horror villain challenge,
and my mold's cracked.
I'm freaking out
because it's just all I got.
This is my only piece.
You got to be fucking
kidding me.
I grab a plumber's epoxy
and use it to seal the crack.
I got it fixed, but I'm worried
I'm gonna have
a lot of patchwork
on application day.
Man, you need to start molding.
I know.
Last time I was
in an individual challenge,
I sacrificed sculpting detail
in order to get
the molds done on time.
It was a really bad idea.
I don't want to do that again.
So I don't see how
you're not freaking out.
What's the worst
that could happen?
You're not gonna get
your cowl out.
Ben's looking over at me
and thinks that I'm crazy,
but I'd rather risk it.
I just want to make sure
I put out something good.
So now it's time to work on my
futuristic surgical fetish mask.
It needs to be smooth,
sleek, and sharp
to reveal the nastiness
underneath.
The mask is gonna work
with my wardrobe
to add that Clive Barker element
to my character.
Looking pretty freaking cool
right now.
That's time, everybody.
I'm feeling okay.
I've got a general idea
of what the character is
and what it's going
to look like.
I just have to attack it
for application day.
- Nice shirt.
- You too.
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab,
one hour for Last Looks.
Oh, my God.
My face is a frickin' disaster.
How did this happen?
I don't know, just could be
one of those things.
It has the worst
second skinning
I have ever encountered.
So you can...
Oh, my God,
that's so--
...work it in.
Kelly's face is mutilated.
but to be honest,
I think it could help it.
with the type of character
she's doing,
That could be a happy accident,
because if someone's
continuously cutting themselves,
it wouldn't be
in such perfect symmetry.
It would be a little bit more
sporadic and spontaneous.
But, you know...
It's okay; it's okay.
I can work with it.
- She's mutilated.
- Yeah, she's mutilated.
Got some of those cuts,
work it, part of your story.
It might make it
more in the horror realm
than the alien realm.
Yeah.
'Sup?
- How you doing?
- Hey.
So you have, like,
the back of your head too.
Oh, it looks
like a spider body.
Yep.
These are all test samples of
poisons on your arm.
Ohh.
Today I'm starting
with the arms.
I know that I have to be
very delicate,
otherwise I'm gonna be
tearing my prosthetics apart.
Rotate in just a little bit.
Thank you.
So one arm at a time,
I lay it down very carefully.
They're fragile,
especially where
the joint bends,
so don't do any
excessive movements.
I just hope they're able
to hold up
between now
and the reveal stage.
I'm cooling down the black mesh
into the eye area
of the face prosthetic.
Hopefully it will block out
my model's eyes completely
and he'll still be able
to see through it perfectly.
_
It came out pretty good.
I am super relieved,
because the crack I was
trying to fix on the cowl mold
didn't even show up
in the piece.
So, as far as these eyes,
push them out
and then cut them?
This is what I'd do.
Right now we're
just making sure
the eye slits are big enough.
I'll come in, and then
I'll kind of ride the line.
See what I'm doing there?
Yeah.
Come under your nose.
I'm bouncing back and forth
between sponging, airbrushing,
and flicking just to break up
all of the solid colors.
All right,
tilt your head up for me.
I'm having to spend
a little more time
on the area where the cowl
comes over the eye,
because certain parts
are lifting
and I have to glue it
back down.
Stupid things.
It's looking a little rough,
but I can't let myself
get frustrated.
Are you gonna paint
this whole thing black?
Well, I was thinking of doing,
like, black under there
and then a lighter tone
on the top.
The paint scheme
I'm gonna go with is,
dark colors come in
across the cowl piece
all the way to the front
of the face
and keep the front very light,
because I don't want
to take away
from the skin color aspect
of it.
And then here on the face,
this his gonna be fun.
I'm a little worried
about her pieces
looking like
realistic skin texture,
but hopefully
she can pull it off.
Keep it scary but pretty.
Yeah, I like that.
Oh, gosh.
I'm fumbling
with the webbing part
of my cage
that's on top of the cowl.
And the left side
starts falling.
So now the string
is falling off,
and it looks disastrous.
I'm going home for this,
I'm telling you.
This is atrocious.
I look at the clock.
I do not have time
to fumble with this.
So I scrap it, and I decide
to throw feathers into it
and just leave it.
And I'll work
with the feathers later.
Ten minutes.
We're running out of time,
and I'm so far behind on paint,
I'm worried
that I won't be able
to actually complete
the full beauty makeup.
It's gonna crack.
You think it's gonna crack?
I'm trying to do it
as fast as I can,
'cause there's a lot to cover
on this thing.
That's time, everybody.
A big part of my concept
is the beauty aspect of it,
so it's really important
to get that down.
But now I've got to wait
until Last Looks,
and now I'm worried.
Come over here.
Get out of the way.
Let's get this done.
It's Last Looks;
I have one hour left.
And I have to finish
my paint job.
The highlights and shadowing
aren't working.
The skin tones aren't matching.
I'm just struggling.
Oh, God, all this disease
that I got to paint.
I got to do your eyes.
I'm rushing around
like a madhouse,
trying to get
this beauty makeup done.
Close.
It's not gonna work.
These teeth are not fitting.
All I can do right now
is make that mouth look nasty.
30 minutes.
All right, time, everybody.
Thanks, Kodi, good luck.
I'm really worried,
because it's not as finished
as I wanted it to be.
So I'm just hoping
that I'm at least safe.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
As you know, one of you
will be going home tonight.
But before we see
your creations,
say hello to our series judges.
Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening.
Hello.
Ve Neill.
Hello, everybody.
Hello, Ve.
And Neville Page.
Hi, guys.
Hello.
And joining us tonight
is a very special guest.
He's the co-head
of Clive Barker's
production company,
Seraphim Films.
Please give a warm welcome
to Mark Alan Miller.
Pleasure to be here.
Thank you so much
for being here.
Thank you for having me.
I'm extremely excited.
He is Clive Barker's
right-hand man,
so to hear what mark has to say
is gonna be really interesting.
All right, guys, this week
your Spotlight Challenge
was to choose
an avant-garde outfit
to inspire a stylish
and intelligent horror villain
in the vein
of Hellraiser's Pinhead.
So let's take a look
at your creations.
I'm nervous.
It looks a lot different
than everything else,
which could be a bad thing
or a good thing.
I definitely could have
done way better
on this challenge.
I know I'm on the bottom.
I am a little bit worried
that maybe the character
is not scary enough.
But I am happy
with the way it looks,
and hopefully
the judges like it.
It is the best thing I
could picture in that outfit,
so I'm like, "All right, cool,
mission accomplished."
From far away,
I like the paint job.
but up close,
it's really rough.
They're gonna see
all the mistakes in there.
Even from a distance, I can see
how much he's able
to emote with his face.
just giving
this really creepy vibe.
And I'm hoping the judges agree.
She's got this
creepy vibe to her.
I see the white face
with the silver tips.
And overall I'm pretty happy.
I don't know
whether or not to think
I am unique in the way it looks
or if I'm completely off.
I don't really know.
She looks nasty!
And I'm like, "You know,
you're pretty fucked up, Kelly.
Did all right."
All right, judges,
why don't you
take a closer look?
There's no texture
in the prosthetic piece.
It's not so much monstrous.
It's more sympathetic.
What is going on here?
I don't know, but it's cool.
It's beautiful coloring on it.
Yeah, I love the paint job.
This feels
like an alien character.
I was gonna say the same thing.
Yeah.
I do love the originality
of this in sculpting.
I would have liked to have
seen a lot more of this gold
being brought down onto
all these highlighted areas.
Oh, jeez.
This does not even
resemble skin.
This chin and nose and forehead
don't say, "Clive Barker."
I'm mainly worried
about the paint work.
It's too flat.
This could be a disaster.
Tell us who made
your favorite horror villain
tonight on Twitter
using #FaceOff
This does not
even resemble skin.
I am freaking out.
The paint work is too flat.
The quality of it
isn't where it needs to be.
This is even better close
than it was far away.
Yeah.
This is the first time
I'm scared today.
And that's good.
I love these weird
asymmetrical shapes.
All of these notes
tie into the wardrobe,
and it's the only makeup
that addresses that
so completely.
Oh, yeah.
Gets a little soft and full
through here,
but up in here,
that's really well-handled.
Oh, the eyes, it's creepy.
She is creepy.
We have pain.
We have disgusting and sexy.
I love it.
Oh.
Okay, the judges
have scored your creations.
Let's find out
what they thought.
Adam...
Logan...
Darla...
Congratulations,
because you are all safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
The rest of you were the best
and the worst this week.
and the judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Julian, you're up.
Give us the
backstory of this character
and how Clive's work
inspired you to design this.
Well, the first thing I noticed
when I chose the costume
was the amulet,
and I figured that that was
some sort of cursed object,
and whoever wears it,
he comes after them.
And his whole head
is a second mouth
that rips the souls
out of his victims.
I am absolutely thrilled
with what you did this week.
I am a huge Clive Barker fan,
and I think you did
an amazing job
of working within his world.
You're obviously a Clive fan,
and you know your stuff.
Well done.
Thank you.
On a scale of one to ten
in the creepiness,
he is a 15 1/2.
I love the paint job.
I think this character
was very successful.
Thank you.
I don't think
it's that creative.
I think it's a very good
"now" design.
I don't think it's
a very next-gen version
of Clive Barker world.
He's definitely scary.
I do love the idea
of the mouth.
I love the jaw line.
He's very cool.
Thank you.
Julian, if you'd please
step back.
Thanks.
Emily, please step up.
Would you please tell us
how your avant-garde wardrobe
inspired your character?
I had the crow feather
and the chain mail skirt.
So I decided to go
with a fallen angel.
This is a great makeup.
Thanks.
I absolutely
love the paint job,
and the silhouette
on this character is phenomenal.
Oh, thanks.
What you've achieved is
something that's iconic
and extraordinarily memorable.
I think this is beautiful.
Thank you.
I'm not quite sure it falls
into the Clive Barker world,
but I do think it is
something extraordinary.
Thank you.
Emily, you can step back.
All right,
let's talk to Stephanie.
Okay.
So tell us about
your Clive Barker character
and how the fashion motivated
some of your choices.
She's basically, like, a seer,
but she was cursed
into, like--
I don't know, it just was
a much more twisted form
than she had
originally intended.
I don't think you know
what it is that you were
trying to execute.
It's so nonspecific
in terms of sculptural form
that I simply do not know
what I'm looking at.
Yeah.
Another huge problem with this
is, it is not conducive
to your model's facial features.
You've weakened her chin,
which evokes sympathy,
and it does not use
her jaw line or her nose
to convey any of the things
that we were looking for.
Stephanie, please step back.
Kelly, you're next.
Could you tell me a little
about your character?
She was obsessed
with plastic surgery,
so she is just continuously
under her own knife.
Well, I'd like to applaud you
for marrying sex and violence.
That's definitely a
big part of what we do.
We have a new Hellraiser
anthology comic book
coming out,
and I could very easily
see this character
in one of those stories.
Oh.
The integration
of your wardrobe
through that vacu-form thing
is an astounding touch.
It brings the avant-garde
into the Clive Barker world.
Thank you so much.
That green dress
and the red hair
are phenomenal together.
She is the most disturbing thing
I have seen in ages.
Kelly, thank you.
You can step back.
Yeah, girl.
Jamie, please step forward.
Please tell us
how your wardrobe
inspired this
Clive Barker character.
I thought black widow lady
who attracts people
through her beauty.
The legs are coming out,
grabbing the rest of her face.
I am not thrilled
with this makeup.
The spider growing out
of the back of her head
and grabbing her skin,
it just feels alien/monster-y
in a way that's not part
of the Clive Barker mythology.
That's okay.
This paint job
is completely flat.
It doesn't look like skin.
This is a failure this week.
Okay.
There's stuff on it that says
it's a Klingon, it's a Borg,
not at all in the world
of Clive Barker.
It's very problematic.
Jamie, please step down.
Ben.
Would you please give us
a little backstory on her?
She was a fetish model,
always worried about her looks,
and now she reaps the souls
of other people who are vain.
She is really quite exquisite
when you get up close.
I love how you use the
inspiration from her bodice here
and put that in her cowl
as well as her neck.
You brought the fashion
into the makeup,
which is really a great idea.
Thank you.
I love the story.
I love the corrupted
porcelain doll look.
And I know Clive said
to go to the avant-garde,
and you, perhaps more
than any other, have done that.
Thank you.
I absolutely love
the back of the head.
It's so cool.
And I appreciate
how smooth that is
and the detail
that you put into it.
I think it's a brilliant
and daring combination
of all the different things
in what is an extraordinarily
complex challenge.
Thank you.
Ben, please step back.
All right, thank you, guys.
If you'd please head
back to the makeup room
while the judges deliberate.
All right, judges,
let's start with the looks
you liked the most tonight.
How about Julian's work?
He hit all the
right notes for me.
It's the one
that is the most standout
in the Clive Barker world.
Up close, definitely one
of the most terrifying
of the bunch.
All right, let's move on
to Emily.
The silhouette
of that character
is just unbelievable.
It's freaky.
I mean, she's amazing, this kid.
it's an incredible makeup,
but it's nowhere near
the Barker universe.
All right,
let's move on to Kelly.
Talk about a makeup that feels
so perfectly suited
for this challenge.
It was scary.
It was sexy.
The story behind it was maybe
my favorite of the night.
I agree.
All right, judges,
let's move on to Ben.
I think that it is
the most astute treatment
of bringing fashion
into the makeup.
It's got pleasure and pain.
It's got grace and grotesquerie.
And that's all
that we can ask for.
All right, judges,
let's move on to the looks
that didn't quite work
for you this week.
How about Stephanie?
It is not avant-garde.
It sure as hell
isn't Clive Barker.
And it's not scary.
I don't think she has any idea
where she as going with it.
I don't think it was executed
particularly well.
All right,
let's move on to Jamie.
The paint job was atrocious.
It did not look like skin.
And the black widow wasn't even
painted properly.
It had nothing to do
with Clive's world at all,
even on a technical level.
The chin and the nose
look like melted wax.
All right, judges,
have you made up your minds?
Easy.
Okay, let's bring them
back out.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about tonight's top looks.
Julian, you gave us
a sophisticated
and intelligent horror villain
that definitely felt like it was
in the world of Clive Barker.
And Kelly, your character
and concept told a great story,
and you did a fantastic job
tapping into Barker imagery.
And Ben, we were thrilled
by your high-concept thinking
and loved the way that you
integrated your costume
into the back of the head.
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner of tonight's
challenge is...
All right, who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
Ben.
While some of the characters
may have better captured
the classic
Clive Barker aesthetic,
you gave us a glimpse
into the future.
Great job.
Thank you.
Second win for me.
It's extremely cool,
especially since this
is a Clive Barker challenge.
I'm sure that he's
gonna see this creature,
which feels awesome.
Ben, congratulations.
You, Julian, Emily, and Kelly
are all safe
and can head back to the makeup
room along with the coaches.
All right,
that means the two of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be going home.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Stephanie,
the prophet seer concept
could have been
very interesting,
but you let your indecision
compromise many of the aspects
of your final makeup.
And Jamie,
we get wanting to draw
on the spider vibe
of the outfit,
but that concept
was heavily undermined
by all the technical issues
with your makeup.
So who is going home
tonight, Glenn?
The person going
home tonight is...
Jamie.
Despite all your best efforts,
it seems like you just couldn't
pull all of your ideas together
to deliver a clean makeup
this week.
Jamie, I'm so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
Stephanie,
you are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Jamie, I personally feel
that we're quite fortunate
to have experienced your talents
on Face Off.
And I know that this week
it got a little away from you,
but I know that you've also got
a tremendous amount left in you.
Thank you.
Jamie, it's been so great
having you here with us,
but if you'd please
head back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you, guys.
- Good luck, Jamie.
Thank you.
I'm really surprised
that I'm going home.
I feel that I have
a lot more to show.
Jamie?
I've met some amazing people,
and my coach is amazing.
You've shown you can
do great makeups.
You know, you've progressed
throughout the season.
So continue growing
as an artist.
I came out here to push myself
and break out of my shell.
I'm upset,
but at the same time,
I'm excited to look ahead.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net