Previously on Face Off...
This is insane.
An all-new season kicked off
with a shocking twist.
Please welcome
your new champion coaches.
I can't wait.
Deep breath.
The champion-led teams were
tasked with creating two aliens
for a movie legend...
Seven-time Academy Award winner
Rick Baker.
Yeah!
I'm ecstatic.
But that was only
the beginning.
Can you see the sweat
on my forehead?
It's all over the place.
- Okay.
- Needs a lot more work.
Oh, my God.
I have another big surprise
for you.
You'll be making
a third character.
- Oh, no.
- Oh.
Things are about to get real.
In the end, only one
will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand-new 2015 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Find out
what happens right now.
This is Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
I have another big surprise
for you.
There's a huge piece
of information
that I didn't share
with you yesterday.
What now?
There's something going on,
and I don't know what it is,
but things
are about to get real.
Your spacecraft
didn't crash-land on Earth.
- Oh, no.
- Oh.
It crash-landed on a planet
controlled by primates
who are not happy
to see your alien invaders.
So you'll each be choosing
one of these simians
as inspiration for
a third character.
We had a plan,
and now that's out the door.
That's right.
You'll be making a tyrannical
primate ruler
who has no interest
in making your alien intruders
feel at home.
Keep in mind, Rick is the one
who created
those incredible makeups
in Tim Burton's
Planet Of The Apes,
and he won an Academy Award
for his work
in Harry And The Hendersons,
so this is not going to be easy.
And I want you guys
to have every opportunity
to impress Rick Baker,
so I'm going to give you
an extra day for this challenge.
Yes. Yes.
Oh, thank God.
We have this extra day to do
some type of monkey makeup.
This should be interesting.
Now that we have
all that nasty monkey business
out of the way,
let's pick your primates.
Your options are
squirrel monkey, brown lemur,
white-faced capuchin, mandrill,
and we have the olive baboon.
Team Laura, you get first pick.
Yes.
That one's adorable.
That face
is really expressive too,
so I think we could do that.
I agree.
We're gonna pick
the squirrel monkey.
- Okay, Team Anthony?
- All right.
- We're gonna pick the mandrill.
- And Rayce?
We're going to go
with the white-faced capuchin.
All right, guys,
why don't you take some time
to work on your new designs
while we have these amazing
monkeys right here in the lab?
- Good luck.
- Bye.
I like this profile.
- We're gonna make him a--
- Ruler.
- Tyrant.
- Like a tyrant.
That's what I was thinking,
like,
the scars
would come in to play at.
'Cause a tyrant
is not a pretty person.
Our original story
was two aliens from a cooler,
aquatic planet,
and one is older than the other.
And now, our monkey,
he's a tyrannical monkey
that hunts aliens
because they just drop a lot
of their cargo on his planet.
So, our team
chooses the mandrill monkey.
Oh, and his butt.
Let's give him a pink butt.
In our original idea,
the smaller alien is the pilot,
and the larger alien
is the protector.
So our concept for the third
character is pretty basic.
He's gonna be the ruler
of this planet
that is strictly just a monkey.
He's not supposed
to be some hybrid.
Think you want to stay
with the tribal theme?
My team opts to go
with the white-faced capuchin.
This particular monkey
is 25 years old,
and she looks it,
so we're going to run with that.
I think we should tie them
together somehow, like,
the apes are the higher thing,
and then, the arachnid are--
are their slaves.
It's gonna be the warriors,
the beasts, the slaves?
I like that.
Our original concept was,
this higher intelligence
alien crashes on this planet
where arachnid
is the native species.
So our monkey is the ruler
of this planet,
and she's enslaved the arachnid.
And she's an old character.
She was born into royalty.
I'm liking this though.
This-- what you have here.
Okay,
then we can start working.
I think my team is very
excited about this twist.
Alan gets to step up
from the fabrication
and start doing
some more sculpting.
I'm trying to make sure
that I keep in line
with his nose like this.
Yeah, I agree.
I have a pretty good knowledge
of animal anatomy,
including monkeys,
but I know Rick Baker
is gonna look
at that face extra close.
I'm sure Rick Baker
will be looking for details.
First thing I need to do
is finish detailing
this alien warrior face.
These holes-- are they plugged?
- Or they go all the way back?
- They go all the way back.
You might want to put
a little bit of clay in there,
'cause otherwise, if the plaster
goes all the way through and--
- It might lock.
- It might lock, yeah.
I know that I should've been
finished and in the mold room
yesterday, so right now,
I am just thinking,
"I need to get that face done."
We have to,
like, bang these out
and get you guys
into the molding room.
I want my team
to continue with the aliens
as much as possible while
Gregory begins on the monkey.
- The monkey face.
- Yeah.
I have my own special effects
makeup shop in North Carolina,
and so I feel comfortable
taking a leadership role.
So I volunteered to sculpt
the face for the monkey.
I'm a little concerned
about having a squirrel monkey
and changing it into a menacing,
tyrannical leader,
because it's sculpting something
mean from something cute.
That can be a little difficult.
Sometimes, big works,
and then other times,
it can bite you in the anus.
I spent ten years
in the Air National Guard,
but I've always had a passion
for doing effects.
I feel like this is my chance
to prove myself,
so I volunteered
to sculpt the monkey face.
It's going to be the only
prosthetic on this character,
and it's Rick Baker
that is judging it.
This is a big responsibility.
We got lots to do.
Okay, Regina.
What's your goal?
Another half an hour?
I'm a little worried
about Regina right now,
because she's spending a lot
of time on the arachnid's face.
I think
the sculpt's looking great,
but it's just taking
a long time.
I just have to get her
moving a little bit quicker.
Hi, everybody.
- I'm back!
- Hello. - Hi.
This is our mandrill king,
and he's really an overlord
for this place.
What are you gonna do
with the fur?
We're gonna use
four-way stretch fabric fur,
so that way, it actually
moves real organically.
Are you gonna have
to hand lay anything?
- Certain bits.
- I would hand lay the edges.
And again,
your paint structure--
paint colors underneath, if you
break them up a little bit,
that actually shows
through your hand laying.
Mm-hmm.
So for this creature,
we decided
to scrap the old idea.
Good idea.
Yesterday,
when Mr. Westmore came in,
he didn't like my face sculpture
for the high intelligence alien,
so I tore that off
and started over.
We're playing with more organic
shapes and everything.
Mm-hmm.
I think it's great.
You've done a great job.
Let's see the next one.
This is your little bit
of a twist?
Just started on the monkey.
She's aged.
She's stern.
In the face here too, you know,
you can give yourself
a little bit more power here.
Actually, just getting
possibly more of a muzzle,
less human.
- So bring it out further?
- Yeah.
We wanted to keep the pattern
of the fur,
'cause he does have such
a cute face.
We wanted to make, like,
the widow's peak
on the fur to, like,
help give him
more of a menacing look.
Are you actually gonna do
fur on the face too like this,
or are you gonna be painting?
I'm gonna ventilate
hair pieces for it.
How long will that take you?
Maybe like an hour an half,
two hours.
What?
Took me six hours to do
my first and last mustache.
Nobody ever wore it, thank God.
I'm gonna say good-bye.
Everything's really
looking great.
You've really stepped up.
Good luck.
- We'll see you later.
- Thank you.
I know that I need
to get this alien molded,
so I go back into the mold room,
and I get to work.
Are you just doing
the splash coat?
Yeah.
I'm mixing a bunch of plaster,
but I'm rushing it,
so I made it a little too thick,
and it's almost setting.
I'm worried that I won't be able
to stick burlap into it,
which means when it's time
to open it, it's going to crack.
Are you putting burlap in it?
No, not yet,
'cause it's setting too fast.
It does--
That's not an option.
Kelly is making
some big mistakes right now,
so I can't really
be Mr. Nice Guy.
It needs three layers of burlap.
You don't have enough plaster
or bandage to even do the job.
If I mess up my mold,
then everything's ruined.
Start cutting burlap.
Or you don't have to.
I don't give a shit.
Don't be giving me attitude.
Are you putting burlap in it?
No, not yet,
'cause it's setting too fast.
It does--
That's not an option.
It's day two of our first
spotlight challenge.
I'm making my mold
for my alien warrior face,
and I'm rushing it,
so I made it a little too thick.
Start cutting burlap.
Or you don't have to.
I don't give a shit.
I remind myself,
"It's still gonna work.
I just need to add
another coat."
Don't be giving me attitude.
It's gonna be okay, Kelly.
It's gonna be okay.
All right, guys, good luck.
Have fun.
It's time
for us coaches to leave.
- Good job, guys.
- Thank you, sir.
My biggest concern
is Gregory's facial sculpt
for the monkey, but overall,
I think they're in a good place.
- We'll see you, guys.
- Bye.
- Make sure it doesn't tip towards me.
- Oh, yeah.
My team is molding
four or five different pieces
for our two aliens.
I know that I'm a fast molder,
so even though I'm still
sculpting the monkey face,
I agree to take the lead.
Everybody's in the mold room
at the same time.
The clock is ticking,
and there's clay everywhere.
It's pandemonium.
Nobody wants to fall
behind schedule,
'cause it's Rick Baker.
- Hey, everybody, time's up.
- Whoo.
It's the end of the day,
and I'm a little worried.
All of our molds are done,
but I'm behind on the face
for the monkey,
and I know the face can either
make or break a makeup.
So I'm not feeling
really confident
at this particular time.
We are all exhausted,
and we come into the house,
and we just kind of collapse.
And then we hear a knock
at the door.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- How you guys doing?
- How are you guys?
We're just here to hang out.
A little barbecue.
All right.
How is it going?
I get to sit down,
hang out with my team,
and I'm getting to
know these guys now, you know.
And that's important.
There's a lot on the line,
but it's also like one of the best
opportunities of your life.
Me being a father of three,
I know you are a father,
you are a father,
I wonder how hard was it for you
to cope with being away
from your kids and your family.
You can use them as motivation,
"What would they want
to see me do right now?".
It's nice to sit down with
Rayce and talk about family,
because I know
he left his family behind.
I left my family behind.
Everything is flaming up
back there...
That's not a phrase
you hear every day.
It's really nice to hang out
with Laura outside of the lab
and get to know
more about her as well.
What's everybody's
favorite movie?
That's like you're choosing
your favorite children.
-  The Thing.
-  The Thing?
-  Legend.
- That's-- Ah, Legend.
That's one of the movies
that screwed me up as a kid.
I can't count--
Made me get into this field.
It's great, especially
in a competition like this,
to just get your mind
off of things--
just to kind of step away
from the stress a little bit
and try to come fresh
the next day.
Yeah.
Whoo-whoo!
Hi.
It's day three
of our alien-monkey challenge,
and we have ten hours
in the lab today.
So much.
What we've got to do is open
the molds for our two aliens,
clean them out,
finish the monkey,
all our fabrication--
there's a lot of work to do.
This is so awesome.
I run to my station,
look at the foam pieces...
Look at them edges.
"What edges?" I know.
The foam's looking good.
We're in a good spot,
and I know
that we can get
these two aliens
prepainted today.
So we're going with a taupe,
right?
Mm-hmm.
I'm actually
gonna make a whole suit.
Okay.
I still have so much
to do for the arachnid,
so I take L200 foam
and make plate armor to wear.
It's like the underbelly
of a scorpion.
It really looks good.
It's really coming
together nicely.
How much longer you think
you got on this guy?
Just a few little touch-ups
here and there.
I'm gonna look it over and make
sure everything's sealed up.
Thanks, Rob.
So, Alan and Daniel
cast Alan's hands in alginate
so we can use them
as a positive.
Okay.
We get them pulled
out of the alginate,
and I start sculpting hands
that will be gloves
for this alien creature.
Here, let me give you a hand.
I volunteered to make
the crown for the monkey,
but I've never really
fabricated anything.
I start drawing out
my interpretation of this crown
onto the foam.
I get a dremel to the top of it
and start moving it around
and getting chunks out of it.
I'm ecstatic
about how this is turning out.
I'm stoked.
I like this.
There you go.
How's it going?
Ah, we doing good.
I look at Gregory's
facial sculpt for the monkey,
and it's look--
it needs, um...
a lot of work.
I feel like you lose
the monkey aspect of it
if you make it too mangled.
I wouldn't do anything
to the nose,
and if you're gonna do accents,
just on the chin
and on the eye and--
You got to make sure
anatomy-wise the creature
looks like a monkey.
I'm extremely worried.
The face is so crucial.
It has to be just right.
Well, Laura does not like it,
and that's a bad feeling.
I don't want to go home
for this makeup,
but I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
You got to make sure
anatomy-wise that the creature
looks like a monkey.
It's day three
of the alien challenge,
and Laura says my face sculpt
doesn't look like a monkey.
Usually, wrinkles wouldn't
flow like that around eyes.
They typically go like that.
I'm just telling him how crucial
it is that the anatomy
is perfect, and I don't think
he's really getting it,
but I guess we'll have
to wait and see.
It's almost time
for the coaches to leave,
so I meet with my team
to make sure
that we're all getting things
ready for application day.
Do whatever it takes so that
tomorrow we're just applying
and painting, okay?
And we know our colors
and everything.
If we do that,
then we'll be set.
Okay? You're doing awesome.
If my team can stay on schedule,
then I think
we're gonna be okay.
- Bye, guys. Have fun.
- Bye.
- Wow, it's bright out here.
So to prepare the hair
for the monkey,
I grab synthetic hair,
yak hair, scrap wig hair,
and then I just use the hackle
and start mixing.
I'm gonna ventilate hair pieces
for our character.
So you're gonna hand tie
each and every hair?
Yep.
- Or bunch of hairs?
- Mm-hmm.
Ventilating hair is
when you hand tie hair
into this piece of lace.
It's one of the most realistic
techniques to make hair.
This is so tedious.
***
We have ten minutes left,
and I still need
to open the hand molds.
The top comes off just fine,
and I start pulling clay.
_
And I notice there's no fingers
on them.
So now I've got two hands,
all missing fingers,
and we've only got
a couple minutes left.
I'm not running these things
in foam today.
I'm gonna have to jam them together
with *** epoxy and some sticks.
*** run polyfoam tomorrow.
Okay, that's time, guys!
This is one of the ***.
So, if I can't run it tomorrow,
I could go home before anyone.
*** see what I can create.
- Ooh, wow, that's pretty.
- It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab,
one hour at last look.
We walk into the lab,
and I find my arachnid cowl,
and it's kind of rough.
That one's all jacked up.
I have no time for this,
but now have to fix this thing.
For the first challenge,
to have to experience
fixing a cowl like this--
Logan's going
to learn a lot right now.
First thing I have to do
is get these alien hands made.
I don't have time
to grind down the hands,
but I got to make them fit.
And I'm worried
that this isn't gonna work.
- Hello.
- Good morning.
Hi.
I'm Jamie.
The plan of attack
is that Darla and Emily
are handling the younger alien,
Stephanie and Julian
are handling the older alien,
and Gregory
is handling the monkey.
And then Emily
will apply the hair.
Daniel is putting on the cowl
while I'm taking the face
and blending that,
but I'm noticing
it doesn't fit the model properly.
I'm having a little issue
with the chin.
I don't think it's gonna fit,
because this is pretty high up.
I'm really frustrated, because
I'm spending so much time
trying to get it on my model.
- Seem good?
- Yeah.
Okay.
You guys doing all right?
I'd give us a four
out of ten right now.
Having a lot of fixing to do
creates this insane pressure
for every one
of my team members,
but they got to move.
They got to get going.
As important as this is,
it's not as important
as getting those faces on.
Can I have you help Anthony?
And Adam,
can I have you help Logan?
No problem.
How long do you think
this'll take you guys?
Keep working
as I'm talking to you,
but I'm worried about time.
Check that seam around the head.
There's also this section
up here.
I like it.
My biggest concern
for my team for application day
is the paint job.
The goal is for it
to be so translucent
that it just layers up
really nice.
The painting is very important
in this competition.
Since the coaches won't be
with their teams in last looks,
I'm hoping to guide them
through the paint jobs
so that they can get
these things finished.
Keep it a little more cohesive
so it's-- if you look here.
You're gonna get
a nice breakup of color.
This could be, like, broken up
a little bit more. Here.
The pressure's on now,
because there's not much time
left on the clock, and I'm the
only one working on the monkey.
Painting is taking
a lot more time
than I thought it would.
This is stressing me out a lot,
because it's just--
it's a mess.
You do only have 44 minutes
though.
If you need to finish the face,
I'll help you out a little bit.
You-- put your hand down.
There you go.
This is the brown.
This is the dark brown,
like the base.
And then
it goes up into this yellow.
Those are to set out
the basic shapes and forms.
I've been behind all morning
working on this cowl,
and then I realized
that we're actually caught up.
Are we gonna
paint the eyeballs too?
Yes.
And I think
it looks pretty good.
15 minutes, everybody.
I spent
all morning making hands,
and they aren't looking good.
Time.
I'm potentially
the odd man out,
because I don't have anything
to really attach my name to.
So I might be going home
tonight.
Other side.
Okay.
The first thing we want to do
is attack those ears.
We have a hour at last looks.
It is crazy in here.
I'm trying to put
the final touches on this one.
Okay, Emily, you really
need to get on the hair work.
Just let them do the painting.
We have a lot to do.
I'm popping in teeth.
I'm popping in eyes.
Give me a snarl.
I realize
that I don't have time to do
what I originally
wanted to do with my paint job.
Teeth?
Your plastic thing's
coming out of them.
- Really?
- In all honesty,
it's probably not gonna stick.
This creature
needs to have nasty fangs.
It don't need to have nice
pearly whites.
So we tell the model,
"Don't show your teeth."
You're almost done looking
like the coolest thing ever.
Ten minutes.
Wiggle your fingers
inside those little holes.
The hands aren't even
on the models yet.
They're ripping up the sides,
and they're not holding
in place.
You got bobby pins?
So I grab burlap rolls, and
I start wrapping them around.
Just trying to make sure
they look like hands
and not some messed up gloves.
That's time, everyone.
Rick Baker
is gonna be like, "What on Earth
is on this guy's face?"
The monkey's
in a really bad position,
and the more and more I look at
it, it just looks like a mess.
I can't.
It's really disappointing,
and I'm just thinking,
"This is what Rick Baker's
gonna remember me for."
Welcome to
the Face Off reveal stage.
As you know, one of you
will be going home tonight.
But before we see
your creations,
let me introduce you
to our judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve
Makeup Effects Studio,
Mr. Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
- Hey.
Three-time Academy Award
winning makeup artist
Ms. Ve Neill.
Hello again, everyone.
- Hey, Ve.
- Hey.
Creature and concept design
expert Neville Page.
- Hello, everyone.
- Hey, Neville.
And of course, we are
very lucky to have
seven-time Academy Award winning
makeup artist Rick Baker.
Hi, guys.
Rick Baker's my idol.
I still can't believe he's here.
This is just an experience
of a lifetime
that I would never think
I'd ever get in a million years.
All right, well, you ready
to take a look at some makeups?
- I'm ready.
- Okay, let's do this.
Your first spotlight challenge
was to create two aliens
that emerged from a unique
extraterrestrial crash site.
Then you had to create
a primate ruler of the planet
your aliens had crashed on.
Team Anthony, you're first.
When my team's characters
walk out on stage,
I really don't know
what to expect.
I'm just excited
to see what they were able
to pull together in my absence.
I'm really proud of my team.
The monkey looks very powerful
up there.
But at the same time, you know,
I do feel that there's
still more work to do.
I'm feeling kind of
disappointed
with our two aliens.
Now it's time to,
you know, pay the piper.
I'm really happy
with the mandrill,
but I am not sure
about the other aliens.
So we'll see what happens.
I'm really proud of the team
right now,
and I'm really happy
with the work
they did in that last hour.
Our pieces look like they
stepped out of another world.
They're fantastic.
We did have some setbacks,
but we pulled together
as a team,
and we made it happen.
I love the anatomy
of the monkey.
This definitely looks like
a regal, queen-like character.
I'm a little nervous, 'cause
I'm seeing a few things that,
in the past,
the judges have not liked.
But overall,
I'm still extremely proud.
My alien is definitely
what I wanted.
I'm looking at the judges,
and I'm like,
"It looks great, right?
Right?"
I'm just at awe
at how real they look.
I love the aliens,
but I'm a little concerned
about the monkey.
All right, judges,
why don't you take
a closer look
at tonight's makeups.
Got some problems going on
with the mouth there,
don't they?
Can you do anything
with your brows at all?
No.
Thank you.
They made a massive investment
in fabricating wardrobe
to the detriment of the sculpt.
I think that they should've
spent more time on his head.
I don't think this read well
from a distance.
- Yeah.
- This is beyond intense.
We've got Rick Baker, you know,
face-to-face with our aliens,
and I am not happy
with this paint job at all.
This paint looks very matte
compared to the other one.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
I am freaking out.
This paint looks very matte
compared to the other one.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
This is beyond intense.
I am not happy
with this paint job at all,
and I am freaking out.
This is all pretty
great-looking.
One thing that's really
that's really working on this
though is just
the general massing of the head.
Yeah, no,
I think the whole thing
works pretty well together.
Someone made an attempt
to address the entire character.
What happens
if you push your tongue
against your upper lip like,
"t-t-t-t-t"?
Yeah, that's cool.
Ew, creepy.
All right, thank you.
This looks like it's a mistake.
It looks like it's on crooked,
doesn't it?
- Yeah, definitely.
- Thank you.
- It's actually pretty darn cute.
- Yeah, I like this.
This is pretty great.
This all works really well,
considering it's all one piece.
Yeah.
Wow,
there is some super cool color
going on that I did not see
from far away.
- Try to smile.
- That's even freakier.
Yeah, it is.
Thank you.
Can you tilt your head
all the way down?
I like the transition.
I think it's pretty cool.
Mm-hmm.
I've never seen that shape
before.
Yeah, and the forms
work better close up,
which is weird, you know?
He's beat up, this guy.
The lip is so deep in here
that the profile
doesn't feel like a primate.
Okay, thank you.
Okay, the judges
have checked out your creations
but now would like to talk
to their top and bottom looks.
Logan, Regina, Rob, and Adam
from Team Rayce,
we're gonna start with you.
Tell us your character's
backstory
and how it fits into
your cryochamber crash scene.
This is the native creature.
We opted to go
with an insect-like alien.
Sort of like
the desert environment.
I think this is extremely
well-managed piece of work.
Thanks very much.
I'm thrilled that you chose
to predicate your design
on an insect.
I think that's very right
thinking in alien design, so...
You guys
really brought it to life.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
Who did what?
I sculpted
and painted the cowl.
I sculpted the face.
I developed
the overall concept.
I fabricated the arms,
chest piece, hands,
and then the weapon.
I think you did a great job
with your attention to detail.
You've put all these different
little paint schemes
up on the head.
You even have
those little hair things
coming out of his shoulder.
That is so cool.
- Thanks very much.
- Thank you so much.
I'm really impressed
with the sculpt.
There's some really beautiful
forms happening in it.
- It looks really confident.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
It almost looks to me
as if the body blends
with the costume
a little too much.
I think if some of that earth
tone went down into the chest
a little bit,
it would pop a little bit more,
but overall, I'm very impressed
with what you did.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Awesome.
- Thank you very much.
You can step back.
Kelly, Daniel, Alan, and Ben
from Team Anthony, you're up.
Would you please
describe your character
and how it fits
into your crash site?
Well, they come to mine gold
to power their ships.
They are more technologically
advanced and more militant.
I sculpted the face,
Daniel sculpted the cowl,
Alan did the armor,
and Ben did the hands.
I got to tell you guys,
I'm not really excited
about this character.
I'm not real hot on the design
of him or the paint job.
I don't think
that this is the character
that you say is a miner
or whatever he's supposed to be.
- Who made the hands?
- I made the hands.
I think I would've taken those
off and just painted the hands.
I think they would've
been more functional,
less distracting.
I do have a certain disdain
for the flatness
of this sculpture.
It doesn't make
anatomical sense.
There's also
a severe lack of detail.
Thank you, guys.
If you'd please step back.
All right, Stephanie,
Julian, and Gregory
from Team Laura, if you
please step forward.
So tell us a little bit more
about this character
and how the crash site
inspired the design.
The creatures are used
to a very moist climate,
but since the ship dropped them
on this really dry desert sand,
they're starting to crack some.
I sculpted the back.
I sculpted the cowl.
And then I sculpted the face
and painted the front
and top of the cowl.
I really like a lot
about this particular character.
There's some really beautiful
sculpture happening in the face.
For me, when I see it
as a head-to-toe piece,
the face and the cowl and
the paint work are quite lovely.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
I like the paint job
and the kind of abruptness of
the changes of the two colors.
Overall, I think
these were very successful.
- Thank you.
I think you did an amazing job,
and I love
that luminescent quality.
And it does really read
like an aquatic reptilian race,
which is kind of neat.
- Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
You can head back.
All right,
Logan, Anthony, Regina,
and Rob from Team Rayce,
if you'd please step forward.
Please tell us
about your simian character
that goes with this planet.
She is an empress.
She looks weathered and tired,
but she's also supposed
to be strong and wise.
Who did what on this character?
I sculpted the face.
I painted the face, the hands,
and fabricated the crown.
I dremeled down the teeth
and sculpted them,
and I also hand laid the hair.
I sculpted the chest piece,
vacuformed it,
and then L200--
the rest of the bottom
and the shoulder pieces.
Well, I think
she's pretty damn fabulous.
I even like the paint job.
She does look aged.
She has frailty about her.
I think she's a beautiful
character, and congratulations.
- Thanks very much.
- I think this works very well.
I like the color choice.
I like the dark hair
with the light streaks.
I also did that on Michael
Jackson's were-cat monster,
where I--
I'll do that very often,
have white highlights
to show off certain parts.
- I congratulate you.
- Huge honor. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
Little things, like the fact
that the tear duct
is sculpted into the prosthetic,
allowing you to transition
into the eye
without having to deal
with an edge right there--
great choices combined
into a very successful makeup.
Thank you very much.
All right, you can step back.
All right, Gregory
and Emily from Team Laura,
if you'd please
head to the circle.
Give me a background
on this character please.
He's a warrior--
like, a tyrant.
He has been
through many battles.
He's got battle scars
to show for it.
I sculpted the face
and painted the face.
I ventilated the front
of the ape's wig,
and I laid the hair.
Unfortunately,
I feel that it is somewhat
conceptually inarticulate.
I think it's suffering pretty
severely, anatomically speaking.
None of it feels
like a monkey-man combination.
I think this looks
like a turtle in the muzzle.
It probably would've added to
him looking more like a warrior
if he had
more ferocious-looking teeth.
I'm afraid this makeup
doesn't work really well for me.
That whole muzzle feature
feels completely wrong.
Around the mouth
on most primates,
it's kind of a continuous line.
It doesn't sink in
and kick back out.
That's my biggest beef
with this.
Thank you both.
If you'd please step back.
All right,
if you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while the judges deliberate.
All right, judges, let's start
with some of your favorites,
which was Team Rayce's
arachnid alien.
That was made by Logan,
Regina, Rob, and Adam.
I was really impressed
with the arachnid face.
They put so much energy into
all the little details on it.
It just worked in
that insect type of a character.
Yeah, I thought it was
nicely fabricated actually.
- It was really well done.
- All right.
Let's move on
to Laura's older alien.
It was made by Stephanie,
Julian, and Gregory.
Love the coloring.
I absolutely loved
the transition
between the front and the back.
It looked sun-bleached
and weathered.
I haven't seen
that forehead shape before.
That, to me, is something.
All right, let's move on
to Team Rayce's primate,
which was made by Logan, Regina,
Rob, and Anthony.
Yeah, I liked everything
about this makeup.
I thought it was
such a cohesive design.
And those Aztec-like jewels
were an interesting touch.
I think the sculpture of
that face
is so beautifully executed.
It read easily enough as simian,
but it still had
an alien characteristic
that made it unique,
and it stood out
from the other characters.
All right, judges,
let's move on to the looks
that you weren't so crazy
about tonight.
Team Anthony's male alien,
which was done by Kelly, Alan,
Daniel, and Ben.
It was just too complicated
visually.
None of it makes any sense.
It very much feels like someone
just kind of pushing clay around
and going, "Done."
That was all Kelly.
What worked the least
were Ben's massive mitts
for hands.
I would rather see
a really good, clean makeup.
Don't add too much stuff to it.
And that's
exactly what they did.
Al right, let's move on
to Team Laura's primate,
which was done
by Gregory and Emily.
For me,
that one just didn't work.
Sorry to say, I think
they made a lot of mistakes.
It's not a good facial
sculpture.
And Gregory was at the helm
of this makeup.
Yeah, he applied it
and painted it.
Okay, that's everyone.
Have you guys
made up your minds?
- I think so.
- Mm-hmm.
Then let's crown a winner.
Glenn, why don't you tell us
which champion's team
came out on top tonight?
The top team tonight is...
Glenn, why don't you tell us
which champion's team
came out on top tonight?
The top team tonight is...
Team Rayce.
Good job, guys.
Your team had two of
our favorite characters tonight,
both of which were
absolute standouts.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
Appreciate it, guys.
I'm more excited about the team.
There's more of a reward
knowing that all five
of these guys
are growing and getting better,
and they learned to bring it.
Congratulations, Team Rayce.
Nice way to kick off
the competition.
Thank you.
However, we can only have
one winner.
So, Glenn, who is the winner of
our first spotlight challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
Logan.
The sculpture
of the primate ruler is great,
but you were also responsible
for the cowl
on the arachnid alien,
and that's what pushed you
over the top tonight.
- Thank you.
- Congrats.
I'm very excited to win.
It feels great to have
Rick Baker compliment my work,
especially being self-taught.
I'm elated right now.
Unfortunately,
Kelly, Gregory, and Ben,
you are on the bottom, and
one of you will be eliminated.
The rest of you are safe
and you can head back
to the makeup room.
It's time for you guys
to step to the center circle.
All right, Glenn,
tell us about the bottom looks.
Kelly, we definitely appreciate
how big you went
from a design standpoint,
but your flat-faced alien
just didn't work for us.
Gregory, your character
lacked specific primate anatomy,
and your paint job, particularly
on the muzzle, was very muddy.
Ben, while we appreciated
your work on the female cowl,
I'm afraid the hands for both
aliens ended up quite rough.
Who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Gregory.
Unfortunately, it seems that
none of the parts of your makeup
quite came together,
and we just weren't seeing the
concept in the final character.
Gregory, I'm so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
That means, Kelly and Ben,
you are both safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
When I was 15 years old,
I went to the makeup union,
and a business rep with
the union told me to give up
and that I was never
gonna be a makeup artist.
So they were wrong.
So don't let this
discourage you.
Thank you, guys.
It's been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please
head back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you.
- Good luck, Greg.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
- Bye-bye.
Thank you.
This was a risk that I took,
and it did not pay off,
so I'm going home.
It's me, guys.
- Aw.
- What?
- Yeah.
I have no regrets.
I'm happy that I was a part
of the competition.
My goal now is just to go back
to doing what I do.
I love special effects make-up.
I like teaching it.
And I'm happy.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net