You've really done a great job.
I'm just very disappointed.
It's incredibly impressive.
Thank you very much.
Previously on Face Off...
Logan's self-applied superhero
slayed the competition.
And Team Laura finally lost
another member
when Stephanie was sent home.
Now six artists remain.
And tonight there's
no more playing around
as the competition
gets very real.
Nothing compares
to the imagination
of a child.
This can be very fun,
or it can be a total nightmare.
It's going awful.
The fur needs to get done here,
man.
Ben bit off more
than he can chew.
You okay?
It's getting worse.
It just sucks.
When Barney has nightmares,
this is what it looks like.
In the end, only
one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan Professional
Make-Up
to one of their 85 international
locations,
a brand-new 2015 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
This is Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
This is a pretty low point
for me in the competition.
I'm away from my family,
and I miss them so much.
It's starting to take a toll.
Being on the bottom
doesn't feel good.
But to win--
because we've made it
to the final six,
which is really awesome.
At this point, half of us will
be competing in the finale.
I just want to make it there
so bad.
Whatever challenge
comes up next,
I want to push myself.
If it's easy,
then it's not worth $100,000.
It's a nice day at the park.
This place is really cool.
It's a gorgeous day, and
there's kids running around
and a huge playground,
and we're not really sure
exactly what we're doing here,
but I don't think it's just to
go play on the swing set.
This is cool.
Welcome to Brookside Park
in Pasadena.
Every year, movie studios spend
millions of dollars
on Hollywood's top writers,
producers, and directors
to conjure mind-blowing
action sequences,
spectacular fantasy worlds,
and over-the-top characters
to entertain people
all over the globe.
Now, while these incredible
individuals
are some of
the world's most creative minds,
nothing compares
to the innocent originality
and raw imagination of a child.
- Oh, my God.
- I love it.
Hey, guys.
Come on over.
- Kids.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, man.
Come on in here.
There you go.
How are you guys doing?
Good!
You ready to have some fun
today?
Yes!
All right, so
as you may have guessed,
you'll be working
with these amazing kids today.
I love kids, but I
have no idea what's coming.
This can be very fun,
or it can be a total nightmare.
Sometimes, a child's
imagination can be so powerful
that they can see
and hear things
that you and I just can't.
So in this Spotlight Challenge,
you're going to work with one
of these creative visionaries
and bring their imaginary
friends to life
as a whimsical character.
Yes!
I am super excited about this.
Kids-- they don't have
boundaries.
This is creativity
at its rawest form.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, and one more thing.
These guys are gonna be coming
to the reveal stage this week
to see how you've brought
their special friends to life.
So no pressure.
Oh, gosh.
Okay, kids, when I say "Go,"
I want you to run over
and pick a contestant.
You got it?
Yeah!
All right, go get a contestant!
How are you?
What's up?
- Adam.
- Lance.
- Why don't we go over there?
- Okay.
Let's go draw something.
You ready?
- Yeah.
- Come on, buddy.
Holy cow.
We're both gonna draw it.
Oh.
Alexandra is an
adorable little blonde girl.
And I'm wanting to do
a monster.
So I'm looking at her
with hopeful eyes, like,
"What do you want,
Alexandra?"
My imaginary thing
is a mermaid.
A mermaid.
Shit.
Hm.
Of course.
Mermaid.
She has a pink tail.
Alexandra's mermaid
has a very pink tail
with scales
that are glowing hearts
and a heart-shaped bracelet.
That's, like, kind of pink.
Or there's a pink here...
I've never had the color pink
in my airbrush,
but when a little girl
asks you to do a mermaid,
you do a mermaid.
Oh, I know another
thing we can do to her--
her pet dolphin.
Do you know how many
days I have to do this?
- Nevermind.
- No pet dolphins.
Crazy.
- Its name's Lulu.
- Lulu?
I love that name.
It can be a bunny,
and it's super cute.
Maya is adorable.
I love everything about Maya.
She's my best friend.
My concept for
Maya's imaginary friend Lulu
is a stuffed animal
that helps inspire creativity.
I can't wait to start on this.
It's gonna be so much fun.
You're awesome, Maya.
Thanks.
You are too.
All right,
so he's got horns, right?
Yeah, he's kind of
like a giant alligator.
And he just has two legs,
and he breathes out fire,
and he has lasers
all over his eyes.
Also, it has wings,
like a dragon wings.
Lance has a long list
of everything he wants
in a monster,
but I know
I can't make everything.
And the monster's name is Laser
or Godzilla.
Or Godzilla.
Okay, so what if we spell it
like "La-zor."
Great.
I envision Lazor as
a creature responsible
for missing toys.
So for this character,
I'm going to fabricate
a lower jaw
coming from the model's chest
and then do a whole upper jaw
and a head.
This isn't
a heavy makeup character.
And it's gonna involve
a lot of suit fabrication,
so I'm worried about,
it may put me on the bottom.
You gonna be a designer
when you grow up?
I was more thinking of a model.
Oh, well, that's always--
A muscleman model.
That's cool.
So her head's,
like, a big real diamond.
Okay.
Because her skin,
it looks like sparkles.
And she lives underground.
Okay.
She has a purse that
she always takes with her.
- Her shoes are like high heels.
- Mm-hmm.
Jordyn tells me a lot
of information very quickly,
so I just started writing a list
as fast as I can.
Now, you said
she has a diamond head.
Yeah.
Jordyn's imaginary
friend has curly hair,
black buttons for eyes,
wears a sparkly pink dress,
but the thing that's making me
the most nervous right now
is this sparkly blue
diamond face.
Diamonds are translucent,
and you can't make
a person see-through.
It looks like a diamond.
Nice and sparkly too.
Perfect.
Ben, you have
to make it like me.
Look at mine.
See how mine are shaped?
Blayne has the biggest
imagination ever
and wants everything
on this creature.
How many heads does he have?
- Three.
- Three heads?
- Yep.
- Big heads?
The size of your head.
Oh, and one has horns.
He wants three heads,
wings on the head.
One of them has horns,
and the other one has one eye.
He wants it to have a tail,
no legs,
and walks around on its arms.
I have to kind of remind him
that I got to put a person
inside this thing.
It has to fly!
Fly?
We have to see him walk out
on the stage.
Nope.
This is a tall order,
and I'm not sure
how I'm gonna get away with it.
I'm not done.
Andrew is a wild kid.
He's doing backflips, and
I can't even keep up with him.
He's like a B-boy,
but he's half zombie.
The rest of the face is, like,
all ripped up.
Okay. Awesome.
I like where this is going.
What's B-boy?
It's like a type of dancing,
but...
Like break dancing?
Yeah, break dancing,
but they call it B-boying.
Okay.
Andrew's imaginary friend
B-boy Z
is half-zombie, half-human.
He wants him to be bloody,
with his heart exposed,
and have a mohawk.
I really dig
his imaginary friend.
That's my style.
Cool.
We done?
I think we're good.
Bye!
That was so much fun.
I love the energy from the park,
and ready to get into the lab
and try new things.
Can't wait to grab another wig.
I'm sure they're
gonna love that.
From what the judges
have said in the past,
I need to start
breaking up my makeups
so they don't look the same.
So I'm gonna use a wig.
I just have to get more subtle.
This is the one.
And I come up with the idea
to flock my rabbit.
This is all flocking?
Yes.
Flocking is basically
tiny bits of fabric.
I want to glue it on my pieces
so when you touch it,
it's velvet.
But before I start
sculpting anything,
I want to test out my idea.
So I grab just a random
foam latex prosthetic,
and I paint it with Pros-Aide,
I cover it with the flocking,
and then brush it away.
And it has that velvet texture.
Hey, what's up?
Good afternoon, guys.
Hey.
Hey, it's getting quiet in here.
What kid did you get?
I got this kid named Andrew.
He wants B-boy Z.
It stands for
B-boy Zombie.
But he wanted,
like, Walking Dead zombie.
I'm all for it, but...
Um...
I'm instantly worried.
Uh, let's see here.
The heartbeat is exposed
and bleeding?
That's what he was saying.
I love gory characters too,
but the challenge is to make
a kid-friendly character.
And if Julian comes out
with a realistic zombie,
he's guaranteed to go home.
I think this kid just wanted,
like, a break dancing zombie.
It's the first day of
the imaginary friend challenge,
and Laura is concerned
about my design.
It's your responsibility
as a designer
to take that concept
and expand on it.
It's coming across too gruesome.
This is pretty daunting.
I'm not used to doing
whimsical at all.
There was a challenge
just like this in Season 3
where we had kids come in.
And these kids
had so many ideas.
In Season 3, Rod ended up doing
exactly what the child wanted,
and he got kicked off for it.
And I don't want to see
the same thing happen to Julian.
We got to bring it
into a concept
that's fun to look at.
We decide to make some changes.
Instead of just
a plain hair mohawk,
we decide to go
with a bone mohawk.
Instead of splitting the zombie
straight down the middle,
make it asymmetrical.
But I'm a little worried
that this is straying
a little too far away
from what Andrew wants,
and I don't want
to disappoint him.
All right, let's do this.
Yeah, just go for it.
- How you doing, man?
- Good.
So he's got three heads, huh?
And he can move his heads
up and--
He can go like this
with his heads.
Ben is the
last person on my team,
and I can see Ben in the finale.
He's one of the best sculptors
in this competition.
So you have to sculpt
three different faces.
There's gonna be two heads
that are actually on the arms.
Then there's gonna be a big head
that sits over the model's head.
And since Blayne wants
this character to have no legs,
I'm gonna have my model
on his knees.
Do you think
you can pull it off?
Yeah.
I am worried about Ben
on this challenge,
going this big.
I think this is
crazy enough to work.
This is a huge undertaking.
I get it.
I know everything
that I'm risking here.
Rather than sculpting the head,
I decided
to fabricate the chest,
because the shape of the chest
is gonna dictate
the shape of the head.
So I decide to leave
all the sculpting
and molding for day two.
So I start working on the body.
I create a simple chest harness.
From there, I grab foam padding,
and I start gluing
and pinching it
to actually build up the overall
silhouette of the character.
Once that's done,
I coat the foam in latex
so I can start adding paper
towels and more latex over it
and make all the pinch points
look like muscles under skin.
That's his lower jaw.
Yeah, the whole head
is gonna be a mouth.
Hi, everybody.
Hey!
Hello.
Alexandra named it Bella.
It's a mermaid.
She wants coral reef
embedded in her skin,
which is difficult
to make beautiful.
This is coral,
what you're doing here?
Correct, yes.
I'm thinking of whether
you actually need
this right here in the center.
It's really not attractive.
Mr. Westmore
is absolutely right.
My model has a very pretty face,
and to sculpt something over it
is really just unnecessary.
Oh, Blayne even
did you a sketch.
You don't even have
to worry about anything.
That's right.
Now, how are you
going to paint your eyes?
I'll paint the detail over,
and then put a shine to it.
If you have a black iris,
put a dot of highlight into it,
because I know judges
haven't really liked it.
So spend time
and really concentrate
on your eyeballs.
What did Andrew come up with?
He wanted
a zombie break-dancer.
He's a big fan of the scary,
but I'm also trying
to translate it
into more whimsical look.
The only way you're gonna get
any whimsical in here at all
is to really give
yourself a good smile...
Smile, mm-hmm.
...on your lower piece.
I mean, if it's too--
The higher up
and the straighter it gets,
it's gonna be come more horror
than it is whimsical
or fantasy.
- This was her drawing.
- Oh, my gosh.
The character
has buttons for eyes.
And Laura had a great idea
of using glasses,
and then fabricating buttons.
Could be the rims
with the handle.
Oh, that would be cute.
That could be too, yeah.
Button eyes tend to be
a little creepy-looking,
but Jordyn was pretty specific.
And so I don't want
to scrap it completely.
To make this
nice and whimsical,
those buttons need to be big.
Definitely.
But that's a good
idea on a stick like that.
Yeah.
- Bye, everyone.
- Bye!
That's time, everyone.
So it's day two of our
imaginary friend challenge,
Got 9 1/2 hours
in the lab today,
and I've got a whole bunch
of stuff
that I got to get finished.
Ready to release your
inner child today?
I start working
on the main head.
I need to mold these bastards
within, like,
the first hour and a half.
I need to get
this thing finished
so that I can mold
all three of these
at the same time.
Her legs will be inside.
I see Logan's mermaid tail,
and it's really ugly.
Did you have to make it
really bulky right here
to make it work?
It's just this really weird,
blocky form
with duct tape around it.
It can't be that;
like, it just can't.
It's gonna look awful.
Rayce points out
that it's bulky,
which I completely agree with.
So I have to start over.
You can take that
and kind of twist it.
The new design for the tail
is a little bit more shapely
than the one I had before.
It's a combination
of cutting out foam,
cutting out strips
of armature wire
to create some structure
and some strength.
And it's starting
to come together.
Oh, they're hearts.
So cute.
I'm going to sculpt the cowl
and leave the big rabbit ears
tied back into the hair
so I can glue down a wig.
Sculpting is just repetitive,
and it's-- now I'm stuck
in my own thoughts.
And I just start thinking
about my family.
These challenges are
getting really difficult.
Mm-hmm.
I really miss my family.
Mm.
I don't know; it just sucks.
I'm just--
I'm crying sculpting.
And it's getting worse.
You okay?
You need to take a minute?
_
It is really, really difficult.
I walk outside, and I don't
want to walk back in.
_
It's day two in the lab,
and Emily is very much
missing her family,
so I'm worried for her.
_
This competition
is so important to me,
and I've worked so hard
to be here.
So I come back in,
and I'm ready
to put my full effort
into everything
and get out of this funk.
I cried it out.
I'm not gonna give up.
I finish the faces.
Gonna run them into the molder
as fast as possible
so I can start molding them
in Hydrocal.
Hydrocal sets up faster,
and the heads are huge,
so I'm gonna do them
at the same time.
And I've got three of them,
so this is quite a task
in and of itself.
What's up?
Just setting up.
Yeah, you're good, though.
Having Anthony's full
attention is really great.
We're gonna work
as hard as we can
to make sure that we both stay
here for as long as possible.
Get underneath
that chin a little bit.
Smooth that down a little bit.
Adios, guys.
Good luck.
After I get the mold done,
the rest of the day will be
figuring out
how to fabricate
this crystal collar piece.
I've never really done
fabrication before,
so I'm not really sure
exactly what I'm doing.
I start hot-gluing
the crystals,
and then I place cotton
and latex
so that it looks as though
the crystals
are coming out of her skin.
I'm just using all the advice
that Laura gave me,
and I'm figuring it out
as I go.
Looks good, Darla.
Thanks.
I love the teeth, love them.
I'm a little worried,
because there's still a lot
I have to fabricate and paint.
And I'm not going to get my head
until application day,
so I won't know if it really
fits until the last minute.
How many minutes does it say?
I think we're under ten,
but I can't read it.
Seven, it's at seven.
Sure, that sounds about right.
All right, everybody,
that's time.
Now that I'm so close
to top five,
like, now I got
to really go for it,
and I'm trying to do that
on this challenge.
Oh, gosh, here we go.
It's application day,
and we have four hours to apply
and one hour Last Looks.
Ah, fuck.
And the first thing I see
is a big chunk of my ear
just taken out.
Oh, no, my foam.
You can fix this.
Yeah.
You just have
to glue it together,
and then you can
cotton in latex,
and then cavo.
I just have so much to do,
and this is just
taking time out to fix this.
It'll take maybe half and hour
more of your time.
Yeah.
But it's worth it.
- Hello, hello.
- Hi.
_
You're a big-ass monster.
That's for sure.
Fuck.
Awesome.
- All right, ready for these?
- Yeah.
Today I have
to run the polyfoam heads,
and then I got to create
an entire foam suit,
and then cover it in fur.
There's just so much to do
that it's just mind-blowing.
What are you gonna do
about the wings?
_
If you want, lay them out
and tell your model
to glue them for you.
Ben's running around
multitasking like a madman.
The furnies get done
here, man, seriously.
Why-- You gonna sit in it?
What?
- I need somebody in it.
- I'll sit in it.
As a coach, I can't
do the work for him.
So his model helps him
fabricate things,
and I'll just be
in the suit all day.
You look good in this.
Why do I feel like a king?
As it sits right now,
it's very much
like this is a chest plate
that just happens to look
like a bottom jaw.
The only unique thing
about my design
is this giant mouth
opening and closing.
The closer you bring
this to his head,
maybe there's, like,
a little bit of batting
to kind of pull this up
on the back.
If that doesn't work,
my concept is shit.
This is gonna be
a weird piece to apply.
The appliance
covers her entire face,
but then there's a big hole
in the center,
so there's definitely some edges
around the mouth
that I'm gonna have
to worry about.
There's only six of us left,
so one little mistake
could end up putting you
on the bottom.
Awesome.
I'm amazed at how
well this lined up right here.
Yeah, that's great.
I'm a little torn about which
way to go with the paint job,
but I decide to go
more realistic,
just because the sculpt
is already so cartoony.
If I go with more of
the bright purples and reds
that Andrew was asking for,
it may not read as a zombie.
30 minutes, guys.
30 minutes, Ben.
This is the biggest
thing that I've ever created,
and I'm not even sure
how this thing's gonna turn out.
Do you want one of these wigs?
Yeah, just throw
them both in there.
Ben is going into Last Looks
with a week's worth of work
that he has to complete
in an hour.
That's time, everybody!
He definitely bit off more than
he can chew on this challenge.
And I didn't quite see a way
to rein it back in.
Is that sweat?
Yeah.
I don't think I've ever been
this terrified
in this competition.
This is weird.
Never been on this side.
Trying to get you situated.
My model has absolutely
nothing on him,
so I need to start
buttoning everything up.
I'm using hot glue guns,
safety pins,
everything I can to start
gluing this fun fur down.
I grab some Kryolan
colored hair spray
and start blending the colors
and painting some polka dots.
It makes the fun fur
look appropriate, not so solid.
Makeup, makeup.
I am not terribly experienced
with beauty makeup.
Like, if you put
something, like, right here,
it gives it, like,
a different effect.
I'm getting advice
from my model,
and it seems to be working.
I still have to zombify
B-boy Z's hands.
So I rush to get everything
glued down and painted
as fast as I can.
Ten minutes, everybody.
It's time!
This thing is not finished,
and I'm afraid
this could end badly
for both me and Anthony.
Oh, my gosh.
They're so cute.
Welcome back
to the reveal stage.
You remember these guys.
Oh, yeah.
Are you guys excited
to see your imaginary friends?
Yeah!
Me too!
But before we see them,
I want you guys
to all go stand with the artist
that you worked with.
Come on, Maya.
How are you doing?
Hi!
- How are you?
- Good.
All right, guys,
before we see your creations,
let's say hello to our judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve
Makeup Effects Studio,
Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening, guys.
- Good evening.
- Hello.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
Hi, everybody.
Hello.
And creature and concept
designer Neville Page.
Hi, kids.
Hi!
Okay, this week
your Spotlight Challenge
was to work with these
adorable kids
and help bring their
imaginary friends to life,
so let's take a look
at your creations.
You ready?
Ready.
It's not the
cleanest makeup I've done,
so I don't think I'm on top,
but I'm thinking
I'm in a good place
for the sheer fact
that the kids
are enjoying the character
so much.
Jordyn's eyes just light up,
and I'm really happy
with the character.
I think she looks beautiful,
and she does sparkle.
It's amazing.
I wish I had more
time for this makeup,
'cause I know I could have
done a lot more with it,
but I am happy with it.
And I really, really,
really hope Maya likes it.
- Looks good.
- Yeah?
He's like a monster.
It's funny, right?
I'm not happy with it,
but Blayne's really excited
to have the three heads.
I did a lot of work
within these last two days.
Hopefully that'll be
the thing that saves me.
I think Alexandra's
really liking it,
but for me,
this could either be a winner
or an absolute disaster.
I know the judges
aren't always fans of fun fur,
but that's the foundation
of my character.
And I'm just praying
that he doesn't faint on stage
and horrify a bunch of kids.
So what do you guys think?
Did they do a good job?
Yeah!
All right,
well, thank you, kids,
for coming to see us tonight.
Go ahead and say good-bye
to your artists.
Give me a hug.
Bye, guys.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look
at the imaginary friends?
I'm confused.
Can you turn that way for me?
I'd just like to see this side.
He's got a great profile.
It seems really... pointless,
for lack of a better word.
Nice bling.
You can tell
that this is Darla's work,
because she does this thing
with these bone lines.
I think this is cool,
the way she did that treatment
where she had all the crystals
coming out of her.
This is a tough challenge.
It is.
If you imagine this
on a Saturday morning
sort of variety show,
I think it works really well.
This would have been
a good week
for her to do one of her
really fabulous big hairdos
with the ears up in it.
_
I'm very nervous,
because I love this character,
but all these makeups on stage
are awesome,
and I have no idea
where I stand.
Tell us who made your favorite
imaginary friend
tonight on Twitter
using hashtag #FaceOff
This would have been
a good week
for her to do one of her
really fabulous big hairdos
with the ears up in it.
She challenged herself
to find a different shape.
I actually love
that the ears sweep back.
_
I'm very nervous,
because I have no idea
where I stand.
I'm scared.
Well, hello.
Who do we talk to?
I do love the palette of this.
The biggest problem is
the one-dimensional paint job.
It looks like he didn't
finish painting the eyes.
I love all the shapes.
It's really quite incredible.
I think that the colors
are simplified
to make it say,
"little kid."
And these shapes
are so gorgeous.
Mm-hmm.
I don't think this is sculpted.
Does that look sculpted?
That's sculpted, but this is
something fabricated with latex.
It's really good.
Look at the color in there.
In two days?
This is a crazy amount
of work to have done.
Okay, the judges
have scored your creations.
Let's find out
what they thought.
Emily.
Logan.
Congratulations,
because you are safe this week
and can head
back to the makeup room.
Thanks.
All right, that means
the rest of you
were the best and the worst
this week.
And the judges
would like to speak with you
to find out more
about your work.
Darla, you're up.
Hello.
Why don't you
start off by telling us
how your child informed
your decisions in creating this.
Her imaginary friend
has a sparkly blue diamond face
and black buttons for eyes.
I wanted to incorporate
as much of what Jordyn wanted.
And this is the first time
I've really fabricated anything.
So I'm really happy with it.
I'm happy with it too.
I really like your integration
of the diamond concept.
You really got the vibe
of this challenge
and did a great job
putting your skills to use
and coming up with something
that fit.
Thank you so much.
That was a really clever way
to create the button effect
with those glasses.
I love the crushed stones
that you put on her chest,
intermingled with your crystals
jutting out.
And when she's done
with all of her diamonds,
she can bring them
on over to my house,
and I'd be very
happy about that.
The fabrication is great.
The implicit collar
with these crystalline forms
is beautiful.
It frames her nice.
And the wig is a great choice
to go with,
because it keeps her beautiful.
Very solid character.
Thank you.
Darla, please step back.
Ben, please step to the center.
Would you please tell us
what Blayne asked you for
when he described his friend?
Blayne asked
for a flying character
with three heads,
no legs, and a tail.
I tried to go
as cartoonish as possible.
I think you certainly
got that part down.
Unfortunately,
I think your main head
is very one-dimensional.
I'm really disappointed,
because his eyes
are not finished.
His paint job's not finished.
It's lackluster this week.
Where you may have gone wrong
is actually trying to do
exactly what
the client specified.
This ends up being three very
simple carnival masks on limbs,
and nothing more.
You simply took on
too much work.
By the time you've sculpted
and molded three heads,
there's very little time
to concentrate on the quality.
Ben, if you'd please step down.
Adam, please step forward.
So tell us how Lance motivated
this character for you.
Lance wanted wings, six arms,
two horns, giant monster.
He wanted to name it Godzilla,
but I explained what copyright
infringement was, so...
So his name is Lazor.
He's a junkyard monster
that eats toys.
And as he eats more,
he grows larger and larger.
This was a very smart
direction to take it.
Using head movement
to get this giant animation
was very successful.
When Barney has nightmares,
this is what it looks like.
It's a very difficult thing
to utilize your skills
and give us all the things
we're looking for
while trying to make it
look childlike.
And you did that so wonderfully
and to such great effect.
Thank you.
The paint on the chest,
all the translucent colors,
so well done.
I love the
different-sized teeth.
It's really imaginative.
Great job, honey.
Thank you so much.
Adam, you can step back.
Julian, you're up.
Tell us how Andrew's ideas
helped you create
this character.
Andrew wanted me
to make a realistic zombie
with half of his face gone,
and with a mohawk,
and kind of
a hip-hop B-boy.
So I had to come
to a happy medium
by making this kid-friendly
as well as scary.
I'm not terribly thrilled
with this.
It lives in this space
between zombie makeup
and then trying
to make it kid-like.
And it didn't go far enough,
so it just ends up
in this design purgatory,
sculpturally
and with the color.
I don't believe you did
a good paint job on it.
There's not enough delineation
between the sides.
It's very murky where you
actually sculpted skin.
I know he wanted a zombie,
but this doesn't even look
like a zombie to me.
There's just some odd
shape choices
that don't seem to have
really much purpose,
even just artistically.
I just find it confusing
as a concept.
Julian, thank you very much.
Please step back.
Thanks.
Thank you, guys.
Coaches, do you have anything
to say to the judges
before they make
their decisions?
Yeah, you know,
Ben's shown you guys
some really incredible makeups
with really strong subtleties.
So knowing what he's capable of
would hopefully pass him
on to the next one.
I'm gonna speak out for Julian.
I think he went outside his
comfort zone a lot this week.
He did a good job understanding
what the kid wanted
while taking in the notes
that you guys
have been giving him
week after week.
And he still has
a lot more to show.
Well, thank you, guys.
Please head back
to the makeup room
while the judges deliberate.
All right, judges, let's start
with your favorite
looks tonight.
Why don't we start
with Darla's work?
I think she did
a really great job
in translating
what Jordyn asked her to do.
I mean, she had the beautiful
crushed stones on the chest.
The whole thing felt
like it really belonged
in a child's film
or a child's video game.
Oh, definitely.
That's really what they're
trying to do in this challenge,
is please the kid
but also please the judges.
And that's so difficult.
She's got a
real gift at simple form,
plainer shapes.
It's kind of fascinating.
All right, let's move on
to Adam.
It was really clever,
and the paint job was awesome.
The head movement
was my favorite thing.
It's very simple.
It worked so well.
He basically did everything
one man could possibly do
within the time that he had.
Adam seemed to really sum up
the overall vision
of a kid character.
It felt like
a full-size, walking toy.
Okay, judges, let's move on
to our least favorite makeups
this week.
Why don't we start with Ben?
Ben, for the
best reason possible,
failed badly.
He wanted to please the kid
and to do every single thing,
but that literal translation
of every detail
is exactly what shot him
in the foot.
The design of the yellow head
is so retro,
but not in a good way.
The surface of the sculpt
is asymmetric; it's rough.
I just don't think he had
enough time
to paint them properly.
Let's move on to Julian.
The bone mohawk...
These forms are so arbitrary
on his chin,
on the back of the neck.
I didn't get it.
That is not a zombie.
There's nothing about that head
that says zombie to me.
It just looks like
a dilapidated mohawk skull.
It never got to childlike.
It just got to basic
and rough and rudimentary.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
Yes, we have.
Okay, let's bring them back out.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about tonight's top looks.
Darla, we liked the sort of
fantasy path that you took,
and we thought that you did
a great job
capturing your child's
imaginary friend
in a very graceful way.
And Adam, you found a way
to embrace your client's
various wishes
but still delivered
a really fun,
satisfying,
and cohesive character.
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner of tonight's
challenge is...
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner of tonight's
challenge is...
Adam.
You managed to find a way
to deliver on every front
for this challenge.
Job well done.
Thank you so much.
I finally won
my first Spotlight Challenge.
It feels good.
And this is a good way
to enter the top five.
Adam, congratulations.
Thank you.
So, Anthony, because
your last team member
is on the bottom tonight,
you could be eliminated as well.
So you're gonna stay here
with Ben and Julian.
The rest of you can head
back to the makeup room.
Ben and Julian,
please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Ben, we appreciate that you
wanted to stay true
to your child's vision,
but you really needed
to streamline those ideas
into something
that you could complete.
And Julian,
though the B-boy angle made him
really fun and playful,
your attempt
to identify a concept
within your child's ideas
fell rather flat.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home tonight
is...
Ben.
We know how capable you are,
but we just didn't
see it this week.
Your sculpting and paintwork
were both poor and unfinished.
Ben, I'm sorry, but that means
you have been eliminated.
Julian, you're safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Anthony, I'm so sorry,
but Ben was
your last team member,
which means you, too,
have been eliminated.
I just want to thank you for
joining us again this season.
It's always awesome
to see everything
that you have to offer.
Once again,
you did a great job.
Thank you so much.
Just excited to get a chance
to work with Ben
and the other members
of my team.
Ben, I think you know that
I'm a huge fan of your talents.
You've done some wonderful
things here.
I think you're
an amazing artist.
You're gonna do just fine, man.
Thanks.
It's been great having you both
here with us this season.
But if you'd please
head back to the makeup room.
Thank you both.
- Thanks, guys.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
- Bye, guys.
Aw, buddy.
- Sorry, dude.
- It's all right.
I gave it my best shot.
I probably went a little bigger
than I should have.
It's me.
Aw, brother.
And him.
And me.
I'm most bummed not for myself,
but mainly for Ben.
He had it in him
to go all the way.
You know,
I had a hell of a run,
going from former Marine,
working on helicopters.
From here on out to the end,
you know, I know from experience
that it's only gonna get harder.
As long as each person
takes something with them
that they've learned from me,
then I have done my job.
I'm glad to have learned
a lot from you, actually.
Likewise.
Yeah, man.
Good run.
Coach Anthony is the greatest,
and he knew how to push me
in the right direction.
This experience has been crazy.
It's meant a lot to me.
I put myself out there;
I stuck to my guns.
I'm just gonna keep doing it.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net