I think she's
pretty damn fabulous.
There's a severe
lack of detail.
This works very well.
I congratulate you.
Huge honor.
Thank you.
Previously,
three Face Off champions
led their teams of five artists
through a challenge
of astronomical proportions.
Whoo!
Team Rayce dominated,
and Logan's
magnificent sculptures
- gave him his first win.
- Thank you.
But Gregory's monkey
fell short,
and Team Laura
lost its first member.
Now 14 artists remain,
and tonight they battle
to win a monstrous challenge.
We want to be really
frightened by these creatures.
I'm screaming and jumping
up and down, "Yay!"
Watch your nose.
The pressure is on as one of
the world's biggest movie stars
joins this weeks panel,
Josh Hutcherson.
The concept feels cohesive.
In the end,
only one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2015 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
This is Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Oh, my God,
what are we doing here?
What is this?
We're at this large
empty stadium.
I hope this isn't
a football challenge.
It's like being
in the Roman Colosseum.
Feel like a gladiator
walking in for battle.
If we're gonna have
to fight to the death,
I call dibs on the ax.
- Who... Is that Glenn?
- Ve and Glenn.
I see Ve Neill
and Glenn Hetrick
standing there with McKenzie
and all of these flowers
and these gold emblems.
Is it what
I think it's gonna be?
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
Welcome to the Historic
Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum,
a national landmark
that has hosted
some of the largest
sporting events in the world,
including Super Bowl VII,
the 1959 World Series,
and the 1932
and 1984 Olympic Games.
This week's challenge is
inspired by sporting events
that aren't always
fun and games.
Films like The Hunger Games
and The Running Man
feature deadly competitions
wherein game engineers
forced participants
to fight for their lives,
fending off everything
from their fellow competitors
to vicious animals
and poisonous plants.
So, for your next
spotlight challenge,
you will play the role
of an evil game engineer
and create your very own
deadly predator.
I'm pumped.
I like gnarly beasts.
I like to make them mean
and just nasty.
Now, in order to make
these designs truly unstoppable,
you must incorporate
the elements
of a deadly animal
and an exotic plant.
Each of these plants is paired
with the emblem
of a deadly animal.
Working in teams of two,
you'll choose a plant and animal
and use their exotic features to
inspire your deadly predators.
That's cool.
Your teams have been
randomly assigned.
Kelly and Daniel.
Ben and Darla.
Julian and Adam.
Anthony and Logan.
Emily and Regina.
Stephanie and Alan.
Rob and Jamie.
Go ahead and stand
with your new teammates.
Let's go.
Kelly and Daniel,
you're up first.
- Wanna go with the scorpion?
- Yes.
Kelly and Daniel, you picked
the scorpion and delphinium.
Ben and Darla,
you picked the ram and cactus.
Julian and Adam,
you have the bat
and the sugarbush protea.
- Go get that pig.
- Anthony and Logan,
you have the warthog
and the American pitcher plant.
Emily and Regina, you have
the hyena and shampoo ginger.
Stephanie and Alan,
you picked the thorny dragon
and the cockscomb.
Rob and Jamie, you have
the piranha and blue thistle.
All right, now you worked on
The Hunger Games films
together,
so your creations
helped the franchise
become a worldwide phenomenon.
Now, it's not easy to combine
the features of a plant
and an animal,
so what advice do you have
in order for them
to make their creatures
cohesive?
In The Hunger Games,
the games makers created deadly
hybrids that were called mutts.
They were not cute.
They were not funny.
They were deadly killers.
We want to be really frightened
by these creatures.
And also, I don't want
to see someone
with a flower around their head.
Create your own
predator creature,
and integrate elements
from your plant and your animal.
Thank you, guys.
Now before I send you off
to work on your designs,
I have a big announcement
to make.
Oh, God.
One of the stars
of The Hunger Games franchise
will be joining us
onstage this week.
He has won all kinds of awards
for his role in the films,
including MTV Movie Awards,
Teen Choice Awards,
and The People's Choice Award.
Peeta himself, Josh Hutcherson.
The inner fan girl nerd
is just, like, screaming
and jumping up and down, "Yay,
we get to meet Josh Hutcherson!"
I'm such a huge fan of him.
He is such a sweet guy,
an amazing young actor,
and he is a huge fan
of Face Off,
so I'm very excited
Josh is joining us.
- I like him even more now.
- Yeah.
All right, it's time to start
working on your designs.
- Good luck, everyone.
- Good luck, guys.
I'm really excited
about this challenge.
The fact that these are all
genetically modified creatures,
you can really do
a lot with that
and make things
really terrifying.
We need to bulk out
the shoulders.
Our concept
is going to be this ram
that's got cactus spikes
coming out of his head.
He hangs around dark crevices,
and he's there
just to pummel you.
Are the horns gonna
attach to the cowl?
- Yeah.
- Okay, I like that.
With the texture from the plant
and color from the hyena.
I like the idea of it
blending into its surroundings,
so it would be the form
of the hyena
- and then just layering it.
- Yeah, no, I totally get it.
We come up with a predator
that incorporates
scaling of the plant to blend
into its surroundings,
and I really like the idea
because nothing's scarier
than something that's hiding
in plain sight.
- Can I sculpt the face?
- Yeah.
Okay.
It's a human genetic hybrid,
so it's made to be a warrior.
Our plant is
the sugarbush protea
and our animal is the bat.
- Want to do a chest piece?
- I don't think we should.
I think we should
focus on things
that are going to give us
a strong silhouette.
Adam sketches this very
humanoid-looking bat,
so the batty nose, batty mouth,
it looks really badass,
and I think it's gonna kill it.
Like Gill-man features, but
then we'll do the piranha jaw.
My partner is Jamie,
which is fantastic,
because she's really talented
and we have a lot in common.
Do you want to do
a body piece, too?
Yeah, that would be perfect.
Our concept is to make
a more modernized version
of the Gill-man.
I want to incorporate
piranha teeth
with armor around the eyes,
and then the blue thistle,
I want to bring it
up from the teeth
to where it actually looks like
it's growing out
of the Gill-man itself.
All right, everybody.
Let's go back to the lab.
I'm really, really excited
for this challenge.
Alan and I are ready to bring
our deadly predator to life.
This is exciting.
We have 5 1/2 hours in the lab,
and the first thing that we do
is pick our models
and start sculpting right away.
Me and Logan are the warthog
and the American pitcher plant
and we decided
that this character
is this gigantic
monster creature
with this open, rotting flesh
that resembles
the American pitcher plant.
Dude, I'm excited.
This is fun.
- I am too.
- Anthony starts on the face,
I start on the cowl, and since
the boar's nostrils are so big,
we use them as eyeholes,
so that gives us
a different shape
that is distinctly less human
and more boar-like.
Hey, guys.
We have a hyena, and we have
the shampoo ginger.
Whose is this?
Is this yours?
- Yeah, it's mine.
- Oh, that's a good sketch.
I haven't seen
a lot of things like that,
and I know the judges are
looking for something unique.
Emily is on my team,
and Regina is on Rayce's team.
Love the concept,
and I'm looking forward
to working with the other
coaches on this challenge.
This is the one I've seen
that's the most unexpected.
Definitely you guys
are working to think about
ways of incorporating this
even more.
- For sure.
- So that way you're not
just sculpting
a literal translation of...
- The lizard.
- Yeah.
Stephanie and I get the thorny
dragon and the cockscomb.
And our concept is
this dragon character
that's very spiked out and
has a hand base like a lizard
but has very vibrant reds,
greens, and pinks
to represent
the cockscomb flower.
Stephanie is sculpting the face,
and I am sculpting the cowl,
and I'm feeling really good.
That kind of shape might be
kind of cool to put into here,
- for, like, venom glands.
- Ooh, I do like that.
I think I don't wanna go
too bulky away from the face
because that might have been
our mistake last time.
My partner is Daniel.
We're both on Anthony's team,
and, last challenge,
Daniel and I
ended up being
one of the bottom looks,
so we have something
to prove this time.
We have the scorpion
and the delphinium.
We're gonna combine
the hard shell of the scorpion
but still have the forms
of the petals of the flower
in a gladiator helmet
that's part of her.
She is her own armor.
Wanna extend the armor
down to the nose?
Yeah, I think that's cool.
What do you think?
I think one design
looks very feminine,
and one reads more menacing.
The face is half-sculpted,
and I look over at Regina's cowl
and it's not matching up.
So you can kinda get...
It just doesn't look like
they would fit together.
- Maybe keep it very uniform.
- I'm really confused,
because I'm doing my part
to replicate the original idea,
but I feel like my direction is
not the same direction as hers.
I don't want to sculpt
and then change it
and just eat the rest
of the time.
Because we're already
eating into our time.
I'm freaking out.
Emily and I keep on
going back and forth,
and we're losing so much time.
What do you want me
to change on it?
So I know what I can do.
This isn't gonna work out.
I need a direction where
to go, and I'll follow it.
Today's the first day
of our predator challenge.
There's two hours
left in the day,
and we still don't have
a clear idea of what we want.
So what do you want to do?
I think we should change
the concept.
Ultimately, Regina and I
decided to scrap the face.
There's still time to catch up
to everyone, okay?
Gina and Emily,
they've lost a lot of time.
Every decision they make
from here on out
has to be perfect, otherwise
they're going to be in trouble.
These things have to scare
the pants off ya,
so create that powerful feeling,
that could be your ticket.
- Hi, everybody.
- Hi.
Our initial idea was doing,
like, a four-legged bat,
but it was a little ambitious
for just the two of us.
In looking at the face,
I like the way you're tying
all this into it.
I mean, your plant
works really well,
but it's a nose
we've seen a thousand times.
Maybe open the nostrils
a little more, flare them,
just to give us another little
bit of bat type of look.
Our animal is the ram,
and the cactus is--
what we're gonna do
is end up putting
probably some spikes.
- I love it.
- Awesome.
It's a really unique concept.
Let's see the face.
I'm bringing in some
of the features of the ram
but making it
a little more demon-like
but keeping those eyes human.
When you put the human eyes
in there...
Do you think it will just
take away from it?
Take away from it,
make it look like somebody
that's wearing a mask.
Okay.
So we had a shampoo ginger
plant and a hyena.
Now, you're going
with a hyena face.
Mm-hmm.
- I see literally nothing there.
- I'm still working on that.
Okay.
Let's see your cowl.
This is reading
like you've made a flower
and you're forgetting
your animal.
Your creature has to be scary.
So keep that in mind
as you're working on this.
- Okay?
- Okay.
We have the piranha
and the blue thistle.
Seems like you're doing
a very literal face on here.
In the nose area,
maybe do something interesting,
add a little bit
of thistle into it.
And that would take it away
from holding a picture
and going, "Oh, my God.
It's a piranha."
So maybe put some nostrils
down in here, then, or--
- You could, yeah.
- Okay.
Mr. Westmore's a legend
in the effects world,
and he knows what
the judges want,
so we know we have
to take his advice seriously.
Good luck to everybody.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
Okay, everybody, that's time.
By the end of day one,
I'm really stressed.
We have a face and a cowl
that still needs help.
So Regina and I have
a lot of work to do tomorrow.
- Let's go.
- Good morning.
Today is day two at the lab,
and Kelly and I need
to finish our sculptures,
make the molds, and be ready
to run this thing.
Wow.
I'm real excited.
_
That is scary.
Just gonna go over
and brush out all of this stuff.
The first thing
that me and Logan do,
we go to our sculptures to
finish the rest of our details.
Right now, this area's
still very friendly.
I would really suggest
looking at gravity
and how it would affect
this guy's mouth.
I have never sculpted
any face piece this big before.
And I'm having a hard time,
so Logan jumps in
and starts putting on this lip
that sticks out
a little bit more,
and the silhouette
that it's adding
definitely is
a little bit better.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you.
- Sculpt's looking good.
- Thanks, dude.
I get my sculpts to a place
where I'm very happy,
and I take it to the mold room.
I'm the first one molding,
so it feels good.
At this point,
I'm feeling like Adam and I have
a really good handle
on our time management.
I like that.
Emily and I talked last night
and changed our concept.
We've decided that I'm going
to sculpt the face,
she's going to sculpt the cowl.
Regina wants
to bring the mohawk
- down the middle, like the front.
- Oh, cool.
So we're taking the scaling
from the shampoo ginger plant
and having the silhouette
of a hyena.
It's sneaky, it's creepy,
and it's a different
kind of predator.
Looking around,
we're very behind.
I'm feeling
really nervous about it.
It's intimidating.
So some
of the important details
that I'm working on on the cowl
are separation
between the horn and the skin.
So if you come around in here,
it breaks the surface.
It looks more like one piece of
flesh that's being integrated.
Anthony gives me
some real good advice
on how to build up details,
to really give it
that human, creepy feel.
This is cool, guys.
Yay.
While Alan is molding the face,
I'm looking at the cowl.
I'm getting a little bit worried
that we may not be doing enough.
Whenever something is really
hard next to soft tissue,
there's going to be a wrinkle.
Laura's helping give the cowl
some secondary form
to make it
a lot more interesting.
But we're already too far
into day two.
We can't really make any
dramatic changes to our concept.
Much better.
This needs to get molded
right now.
I get a little lost
sculpting the cowl,
and I realize
I took way too much time.
You got it?
In the back of my head,
I'm like,
"Get to the mold room,
get to the mold room,
you need to get there now!"
We have three hours
to finish the mold,
and the big issue that we have
is the cowl.
Has a lot of details that make
it very complicated to mold.
Ooh, shit.
I'm freaking out.
This is the most detailed
and hardest mold
I've ever done.
And I have to prevent anything
from happening
like what happened last week.
We don't have enough plaster
bandage to even do the job.
After being bottom looks,
I don't want to be there again.
It's day two in the lab,
and our challenge this time
is to make a deadly predator.
I wanted to get this done
a while ago.
I don't want to rush the mold
and risk ruining all the detail
in my sculpture.
Don't worry.
We're gonna do it.
Kelly's freaking out, so I'm
trying to make her feel better.
We'll be good.
I'm not worrying about it.
We're going to get this done.
So I start cutting out leaves
that will create
the rest of the head form
on the cowl,
and I take the dremel tool,
and I just start adding
a basic texture to it.
- I start coating those in latex.
- That's very cool, bro.
- Want me to get one?
- No, I got it.
Because we only have
a face and a cowl,
we need something to give it
that hyena quality
and something that brings it
to the next level.
I see the hemp in the mold room,
and I figure that
this could work as hair,
so I take acrylic paints
with a little bit of water
and I mix hemp with it,
then I lay them out to dry,
so I have
all different shades of brown.
Color done.
Time's running out,
and we want to incorporate
the leaf aspect of
the blue thistle to our makeup.
So I grab a piece of L200,
I draw the pattern,
I cut out around the shape,
and then I form it
to the bust that we have.
The leaves are going
to fit in there perfectly,
like they're growing
out of the head,
almost like dreadlocks.
It's getting
towards the end of the day,
and I start prying
this cowl mold apart,
and, luckily,
the back half pops right off.
But now I gotta
get the head out,
and Darla comes
running in to help,
because we need to get this
thing open as fast as we can
- so we can clean it out.
- There's just a lot of suction.
It's taking a lot longer
than we want to,
but not having this cowl
tomorrow is not an option.
We finally get the core out
of the second half of the mold,
but we're not going to have
enough time
to clean it out properly,
which means that we could have
an unusable foam piece.
That's time!
We're both a little scared.
It was so rushed
trying to get that done.
So we're keeping
our fingers crossed,
but we know that
if we have any issues
we're just going to have
to use what we got.
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab
and one hour of last looks.
- Ooh, this is rough.
- The cowl is not too bad,
but it's got excess foam
all over it,
so I grab a razor,
start cutting this thing off,
start making it look pretty.
Nose isn't too bad.
Overall, it came out nice.
Uh-oh.
Ooh.
Our foam piece
is a pretty big mess.
It's like rubber.
Like sawed rubber.
And that's really bad,
because we're going to be
spending most of the day
patching it.
Let me get my scissors
and start cutting the seam.
Mmm, the smell of foam latex
in the morning.
- Hey, how's it going?
- This is you today.
- Regina.
- Nice to meet you.
My plan is to fabricate
the chest piece and back piece,
and Regina is applying
the makeup,
and then we'll both work
together on painting it.
I'm going to take the hemp
and start layering it.
Today is going to be
a crazy day.
Don't let me slow you down.
- Lean your head back.
- Mm-hmm.
- There you go.
- Watch your nose.
Ben and I put the cowl on
our model, and it's way too big.
It's just another thing
that sets us back
because we have to cut away
all the excess to make it fit.
I'll cut this at a bevel.
This way, you can taper it in
a little bit more.
All right.
_
Oh, my God,
it's gonna be so awesome.
I'm so pumped!
What do you want to base it as?
Like a muted green.
Our paint scheme is inspired
by the sugarbush protea.
Green is not something
I'm used to using.
I think we can go
a little bit darker with it.
I'm just hoping it looks
natural and realistic.
So you don't have
any brushstrokes.
If you take a watered-down
white or cream color
and speckle that,
it'll push all those veins back.
Okay.
We start painting,
and we know immediately
that this is going
to take a long time.
We've got a lot
of ground to cover.
Anthony and Logan right now,
they're moving pretty slow.
And I'm worried
about the paint job,
because they have
a pretty intense cowl.
I just hope they can finish.
When everything's done
with some black,
hit inside these holes,
even create a couple more,
just to kind of
take your eyes off those.
You're starting
on the detail painting,
but you still have
a lot of patchwork.
The edges on Alan and
Stephanie's face aren't perfect.
There's an edge there.
Get those all squared away
before you start airbrushing.
There is so much
paint work to do
on top of all of the patching.
They may run out of time.
Ten minutes, everybody.
You guys gotta close your kits.
Are you gonna bring out
more highlights in the face?
We're running out of time, and
we don't have any hair on it,
and it's really dark right now.
We need to lighten up the face,
so it doesn't get
washed out onstage.
That's time!
At this point,
it would be a miracle
if this makeup is safe.
Let's do this.
It's last looks.
Me and Logan have one hour left.
And we immediately
start painting
like there's no tomorrow.
My sole job
is to lay all the hair,
but it's not hair, it's hemp,
so I use hot glue
to create beads
on the end of the hemp,
so the latex of the cowl
has something to adhere to.
This is the fun part.
Jamie starts gluing the teeth
in, it's a scary piece,
and Jamie and I
are just ecstatic
to see this creature
come to life.
This thing has
got to look scary,
and that makes the paint job
very important,
but it's looking
a little too yellow,
so I take him down
with a bit of a green tinge.
15 minutes.
That's time, everybody!
- Good job.
- You look awesome.
- Looks cool.
- Oh, man.
My only concern
is the paint job.
It's not as finished
as I wanted it to be
and I start to worry
I could be going home
for this makeup.
Welcome to
the Face Off reveal stage.
Now, as you know, one of you
will be going home tonight,
but before we see
your creations,
let's say hello
to our series judges.
- Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening, guys.
Hi.
- Ve Neill.
- Hey, everybody.
Hi.
- Neville Page.
- Hi, guys.
Hello.
And, as promised,
joining us tonight
is one of the stars
of The Hunger Games films.
Please give a very warm welcome
to Josh Hutcherson.
Hey, guys, no, no, no.
Clap for you.
I'm just here to judge.
You guys did all the hard work.
It's great seeing
Josh Hutcherson,
and it's really exciting,
because now he get to see
our creations.
Josh, thank you so much
for being here tonight.
Of course, yeah.
I'm very excited.
So you and Ve spent
a lot of time on set together.
How was it to have her
do your makeup?
It's the best.
Ve's the best.
Nothing's a big deal,
everything's laid-back,
and she has fun with it,
and that's a good vibe
to have on set.
And makeup genius
on top of it all.
- You're making me blush.
- Aw.
So Ve tells us
you're a big fan of the show.
I am.
I binge watch, actually.
I'll sit down, and all
of a sudden, five hours later,
I'm like, "Oh, my God,
that was a Face Off afternoon."
All right, well, this week,
your spotlight challenge
was to create a hybrid
animal/plant predator
inspired by films like
The Running Man
and, of course,
The Hunger Games.
Josh, would you like
to take this one?
Absolutely.
Let's take a look
at your creations.
I couldn't be happier.
He fits the bill
of the massive character.
The only thing
I'm concerned about
is the way that
she's holding her weapon.
And if that's my main concern,
I'm good.
I'm really proud
of what me and Darla created.
This thing
is menacing-looking.
I'm pretty happy.
Only issue is,
makeup seems a little bit
brighter and greener
than we anticipated.
Maybe we should have changed it.
To see what it looked like
at the lab
and to see what it looks like
now, it's really rewarding.
Out of everything
we struggled with,
it worked out.
He just looks yellow,
and I start to worry,
because that's not scary.
He is a scary-looking guy.
Colors are popping, and
everything is just so awesome.
It's great seeing
this creation come to life.
Judges, it's time to take
a closer look at our predators.
- Wow.
- That's cool, man.
Look, here's the floral detail
up here.
That's kinda cool.
Pretty frightening.
I like that the eyes
are really wide.
It kind of gives it
that warthoggy feel.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
- Dink, dink.
- Hey, now.
I like the paint.
It's accurate for what it is
that you're trying to say.
Just, actually, side view
for a second, if you don't mind.
Oh, the side view's good, too.
Yeah.
You can see
the plant influence there
- with the different ruffles.
- Oh, yeah.
Thanks.
Oh, it's so cool, this
cutaway, you can see through it.
Can you turn
all the way around?
- Yeah.
- That's cool, man.
Resembles bone and a horn.
That form language
is totally unique.
Thank you.
It's a batichoke.
He's not as scary
as the others that I saw.
The judges are really
examining our makeup,
and the color doesn't look
scary enough.
At this point, I'm just really
hoping that we're at least safe.
The shapes are great, but
the color choices are strange.
He's not as scary
as the others that I saw.
The paint job
is looking too blotchy,
and he doesn't look
scary enough.
I'm just hoping
that we're at least safe.
Thank you.
She is creepy
and scary-looking.
That's a really, really
good job using the hyena form
to create something
that's almost demonic.
The jaw's power is, like,
all the way back there, too.
Top to bottom,
really good palette.
The unfortunate thing
about this
is a lack of detail
in the paint job
and the softness of the skull
make it exactly
what I asked them not to do.
That's pretty impressive.
I like how the jaw
comes out like a real piranha,
kind of, like, aggressive jaw.
Open your mouth for me.
Cool.
- Groovy.
- Thank you.
So, Josh, what did you think
of tonight's makeups?
They were all so cool,
and I feel like
I would run from that on set.
Very creepy.
And I have to say
congratulations to the coaches.
I mean, your presence is
definitely making an impact.
- Really.
- Thank you. Appreciate it.
Okay, the judges
have scored your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Logan and Anthony.
Daniel and Kelly.
Rob and Jamie.
Congratulations,
because you are all safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Thanks.
The rest of you were the best
and the worst this week.
The judges would like to
find out more about your work.
Emily and Regina,
if you'd please step up.
Tell us about your character
and who did what.
We incorporated the plant
into the texture
and used a little bit
of the plant color
and the silhouette of a hyena.
Emily built the front piece,
the back piece,
and did all the hair.
I sculpted a little bit
of the face, she did, too,
and we worked on
the cowl together as well.
I think it's fantastic.
Using the size of your model,
you created a character
that's lithe and dexterous,
and that's what
makes it dangerous.
The proportions
are absolutely gorgeous.
- Thank you.
For me, you killed it.
You captured that predatory look
in this creation,
and the colors
are just so organic
and really fantastic-looking.
- Thank you.
The concept feels cohesive,
as, like, this hybrid animal.
And I like how the chest comes
out like the ribcage of a hyena.
And, also, she looks like she
really enjoys being a predator.
- Thank you.
No question, this is a
beautiful character head to toe.
The silhouette is marvelous.
The use of the hemp
is so smart.
- It's beautiful.
- Thank you.
Emily and Regina,
if you'd please step back.
Julian and Adam, you're next.
Tell me about
your plant/animal choice
and who did what
on this creation.
We got a bat
and a sugarbush protea.
I drew a concept of
a sleek bat assassin warrior.
I sculpted the cowl
and fabricated the pieces on
the back as well as the arms.
Julian sculpted the face, and
we both tackled the paint job,
and we both did
a lot of the detailing.
Looks like a psychedelic
artichoke with a bat face on it.
I think there's a little bit
too much plant in it for me,
and if you wouldn't have
painted him lime green,
I think he would have been
much scarier-looking,
'cause the face is really good.
You have so much of the plant
already in the shape of the head
and the shape of the back
of the head and the arms,
that I think you maybe
could have gone
darker with the color
on the face
to get more of the bat involved.
Thank you, guys.
Please step back.
Thanks.
All right,
let's talk to Ben and Darla.
Please step to the center.
Could you tell us what your
creature and your plant were
and kind of who did what
on the sculpture?
We had the ram and the cactus.
I primarily sculpted the face.
Ben primarily sculpted the cowl.
Ben did a lot of the ridge work,
and then I went through
and did the striations
along all the horns.
- I think it's so cool.
- Thanks.
Looking into that face,
the darkness of the eyes
and then all the shapes
coming out,
the technique on it
and the coloration,
the painting, everything is
so demonic ram-cactusy.
It's pretty awesome.
I'm a big fan, for sure, yeah.
This is my favorite makeup
I've seen on Face Off.
Wow.
You've done some things here
with the forms
that could so easily
have gone south on you.
- I'm so impressed.
- Thank you.
This thing scares
the heck out of me.
He looks like something
that's been
out in the desert for years,
- and that paint job is awesome.
- Thank you so much.
Ben and Darla,
if you'd please step back.
Stephanie and Alan,
please step forward.
So tell us
about your plant/animal fusion
and the division of labor.
Our inspiration was
the thorny dragon and cockscomb.
He's supposed to be
a stealth predator and venomous,
that's the saliva,
and all the horns are actually
protruding venom.
Stephanie sculpted the face,
I sculpted the cowl,
she detailed the face,
and then we both shared
the labor on the paint.
It's too soft
and too devoid of texture.
The masseter muscle
on the maxilla and mandible
feel goitrous
more than it does powerful.
- Yeah, right in here?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I was trying to go
for a venom sac.
Okay, that explains it,
because that does feel
completely incongruous
to the rest of it,
but knowing that that probably
is the venom sac versus a muscle
is a good idea,
just not well-executed.
It's got almost an anime
cartoon aesthetic to it,
and that lends to
an unfortunate lack of ferocity,
which is what
we were looking for.
The fact that you made him
all yellow makes him not scary.
He just looks like
a little kid's candy pop.
Thank you both.
If you'd please step back.
Thank you, guys.
Please head back
to the makeup room
while the judges deliberate.
All right, judges,
let's start with your favorites.
How about
Regina and Emily's work?
Totally put together well.
Loved the hemp fibers
and the little grass treatments.
She was mean, sleek.
Because of also
the smaller model,
the proportions were great.
They did a great job
of striking that balance
of finding notes that say hyena
without directly putting hyena
anatomy onto a person's face.
I'm thrilled
with their approach.
All right, let's move on
to Ben and Darla.
I thought the face
was really great.
That thing was
so realistic-looking.
It had that dried out,
skeletal effect.
It was almost like a ghost ram.
Ben's sculpture of the cowl,
that back view...
- Oh, yeah.
- ...is so gorgeous.
All right, judges,
let's move on to the makeups
that didn't quite work
so well this week.
Why don't we start
with Julian and Adam?
The bat and the sugarbush.
They did exactly what
we told them not to do.
They did a bat face with
the artichoke head in the back.
The color really killed them.
I think what you're saying
is absolutely right.
If you had put
some more darkness into it,
made it look a little more evil,
that would have really done
a lot for me.
All right, let's move on
to Stephanie and Alan.
It wasn't scary-looking.
It was like
a little kid's lollipop.
It was just too sweet.
It was yellow...
And you know what else,
I think it was a mistake
that Alan put those pouches,
those goitery-looking things.
Like, to add on,
like, venom sacs,
you got to make 'em venom sacs
and not blobule jowls.
All right, judges,
have you made up your minds?
- Yep.
- We're there.
Okay, let's bring them
back out.
Glenn, tell us
about the top teams.
Emily and Regina,
between the super cool
facial shapes
and all the fabrication,
your character
really came together.
Ben and Darla,
we were all taken aback
by your bold concepts
and incredible shapes.
Okay, which team
came out on top?
Our top team tonight is...
Okay, which team
came out on top?
Our top team tonight is...
Ben and Darla.
This is one of the most
incredible concepts
that we have ever seen
on the show.
There were such clever nods
to the forms
of both your animal
and your plant.
- Amazing.
- Thank you.
Ben and Darla, excellent work,
but as you know,
we can only have one winner.
- Glenn?
- Tonight's winner is...
- Ben.
- Nice.
That cowl
was just awe-inspiring.
I made a promise to myself
that if I ever won
a spotlight challenge,
that I'd propose
to my girlfriend.
So, Stephanie Rae Goreman,
will you marry me?
Ben, congratulations,
and congratulations to you
as well, Anthony.
Thank you.
All right, Ben, Darla,
Emily, and Regina,
you're all safe
and can head back
to the makeup room
with your coaches.
All right, guys,
that means the rest of you
are on the bottom this week, and
one of you will be going home.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about tonight's bottom teams.
Julian and Adam, while we
thought the face was menacing,
the paint job
undermined your character.
Stephanie and Alan.
While the sweeping shapes
of the face and the cowl
were really cool,
the light color palette
made him feel friendly
instead of scary.
So who is going home tonight?
The person
going home tonight is...
Alan.
Such a tough night.
None of the makeups were bad,
but ultimately the venom sac
negatively affected
the appeal of your character.
Alan, I'm so sorry,
but that means
you have been eliminated.
Julian, Adam, Stephanie,
you are safe this week.
You can head back
to the makeup room.
I've been there before, too,
man.
So many times in auditions,
I've been told "Believe in
yourself" and then get told no,
it's the hardest thing
in the world,
but you're an artist,
and you're gonna keep at it.
Thank you very much
for your honest opinions.
I want you to go out of here
with your head held high, man.
Alan, if you'd please
head back to the makeup room
- and pack up your kit.
- See you later, guys.
- Good luck, dude.
- Good luck, honey.
- Bye, Al.
- It's hard to leave now,
making it only this far.
I have no regrets.
I've gotten
a lot of experiences,
I've made a lot of new friends.
Hey, thanks for picking me.
Glad I picked you.
I've grown quite a bit as
an artist in this competition.
And I'm going to continue
to do makeup
till I can't do it no more.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net