The concept feels cohesive.
Looks like a psychedelic
artichoke with a bat face.
This is my favorite makeup
I've seen on Face Off.
Previously on Face Off,
Ben and Darla's cactus ram
brought Ben his first win.
Nice.
But Alan fell short
and was the first
on Team Anthony to be sent home.
Now 13 artists remain,
and tonight they'll be dealt
their toughest challenge yet.
Having a panic attack
right now.
Now I know why people freak out
on Face Off.
It's time, everybody.
Ah, shit.
Might be putting a makeup
onstage that's not finished.
It's really hard
not to love it.
Thank you.
In the end, only one will win
a VIP trip from
Kryolan Professional Make-up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2015 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
This is Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Wow, look at the chandeliers.
We're walking through
this really cool casino.
People are gambling.
It's just
a beautiful atmosphere.
- Look at this.
- Nice.
We're like, "What's the deal?"
I have, like, a million things
going through my flipping head.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Welcome
to The Normandie Casino.
This is a popular location
for filmmakers
in need
of that classic Las Vegas look,
but it's right here
in Hollywood.
It's been featured in movies
and television shows
like The X-Files, Big Love,
and Buffy The Vampire Slayer.
And whether you're playing
Texas hold'em
with your poker buddies
or screaming "Blackjack"
on a casino floor,
this week's challenge involves
some classic characters
you're probably
very familiar with.
They make up the royal court
of the gaming world.
Nice.
King...
- Oh, my goodness.
- Queen,
jack, and joker.
Nice.
Now, in Tim Burton's
Alice In wonderland,
Helena Bonham Carter's
highly exaggerated version
of the red queen of hearts
played a pivotal role
in establishing the film's
outlandishly stylized setting
and tone.
So with that in mind,
- your first individual...
- Yes!
...spotlight challenge
is to choose a card
and bring that character
to life
in an outlandish and quirky way
worthy of a Tim Burton film.
Oh, my God.
And you must also somehow
incorporate your card's suit
into your makeup...
diamond, club, heart, or spade.
If you get the joker,
you can choose any suit you want
to incorporate into your makeup.
I'm thrilled that
it's an individual challenge,
'cause I get to show
what I have to offer.
This is awesome.
Jamie, you're first pick.
King of spades.
- King of clubs.
- Jack of spades.
Queen of hearts.
Queen of diamonds.
King of diamonds.
Jack of hearts.
- Joker.
- King of hearts.
- Jack of diamonds.
- Queen of clubs.
Queen of spades.
Jack of clubs.
All right, it's time
to get started on your sketches.
Good luck.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
The jack of diamonds
is the virtue of patience,
so I'm thinking of a character
that has been waiting so long,
he's just completely old
and decrepit.
So it's a whimsical character
yet scary at the same time.
My king of diamonds
is a greedy, lonely king.
One diamond that a witch
gave him is making him sick.
And to push the diamond factor,
I'm gonna give him
a diamond-shaped face.
I'm excited to have hearts
as my suit.
The jack of hearts,
specifically,
represents jealousy.
So he is the advisor
to the king of hearts,
but he is secretly in love
with the queen,
and so he is very jealous
of the king.
I'm gonna build his face
into a heart shape
by sculpting the beard and hair.
I think it's really gonna
capture the essence
of this challenge.
I get the king of clubs,
and the first things
that enter my mind
are jokes and plays on words.
So I'm doing a king
of nightclubs
who's this slick,
rat pack entertainer.
And if a party needs
to be thrown, he's throwing it.
My queen of spades
is this judge-like character.
When you walk
into her courtroom,
it's her decision whether you...
...or you're let free.
The hair will be sculpted
into the headpiece,
and it'll read like a spade.
_
I'm in trouble.
All right, everybody,
let's go back to the house.
It's day one in the lab.
I have 5 1/2 hours.
I chose king of spades,
which is traditionally seen
as David in David and Goliath.
So I want to pick
a big, burly male model
and then style the wig
into the shape of a spade.
Finally, it dwindles down
to one male model
and one female model,
and the male model gets chosen.
Now my whole concept
has to change.
And it's time
to start sculpting,
but I have no idea what to do.
So I start sketching it out
in clay
to see what I can come up with.
Hey!
Hey, Laura.
- Hey, guys.
- How you doing?
- Hi, guys.
- Hello.
So what are you doing?
I have the king of spades,
but I have a female model.
Oh.
Gender change is automatically
gonna be a challenge,
especially with proportions.
- I'd say keep it fun.
- Yeah.
I wouldn't make it too...
- Serious?
- Serious.
And I think you should make it
more of a whimsical character
so that the judges don't see it
as a woman underneath,
you know?
- A woman underneath a man.
- Yeah.
For my new concept,
my king of spades
is a very prideful, short man
who holds a big sword
but looks completely ridiculous.
Okay. We'll do this.
Okay.
So what you got?
Got the jack of clubs.
The jack of clubs
represents wisdom,
so I immediately think
of this older advisor
to the king of the underworld,
and he helps lead people
to the underworld.
I like the cheekbone.
I like how gaunt it is.
I'm sculpting the club form
directly on the forehead
using the cheekbones
as the side of the clubs.
I like the idea that he was
branded with the club symbol.
I really see
a lot of potential in Julian.
It's an incredible asset
to be able to think
outside the box.
So I got the king of hearts.
The king is stabbing himself
in the head with a knife.
Right, suicide king.
This is my favorite card
in the entire deck.
I decide that
the king is depressed
because the queen of hearts
was killed in front of him.
And I chose a female model
because I want this king
to look long,
kind of drawn out, thin.
I like
where you're going with it.
Okay, cool.
Oh, this is kind of fun.
Queen of hearts.
Yes, I don't want to go
too Alice In Wonderland with it.
Absolutely, yeah, I--
- I'm a little nervous,
because it can't look
like all the queen of hearts
that have been done.
But I do want
to take the evil route.
It could be any kind of heart.
So even, like,
the human heart is okay?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Okay, all right.
So I decide that she keeps
all the hearts of her victims
on a picket fence
around her neck,
and she has a huge,
asymmetrical, red wig.
I kind of do love this.
Thank you.
Shit.
I'm not liking
what I'm doing right now.
My sculpt looks like a man,
not a queen,
and now I'm worried.
Doing it.
This is a confused piece.
He's got such a strong brow,
a strong nose, a strong chin--
too monster.
Daniel's concept is very scary,
very serious--
not really the point
of this challenge.
I think you should start again.
I don't believe it.
Anthony wants me
to start from scratch,
and I have no time.
People are already finishing,
but I know if I don't do this,
I'm gonna be in trouble,
definitely.
Do it?
Okay, let's go.
It's the first day
of our playing card challenge,
and I decide to destroy
my sculpture and start again.
I got to think
a little bit more,
because I need an idea,
not just, like, a bunch of clay
with nose and ears.
Here we go again.
Hi, everybody.
- Hi.
- Hey, how's it going?
It's time to show me
what you've been dealt.
I picked the jack of spades,
the one-eyed jack.
So he's gonna be
a musketeer-style character,
and then I'm gonna incorporate
the actual spade
as a patch on his eye that's
actually sewn into his face.
It's more horror...
Okay, I see what you're saying.
Than it is whimsical
and Tim Burton.
- Yeah.
- Be careful with that...
- Okay.
- ...so it doesn't look gory.
I have the joker.
I'm thinking of him
more as a toy.
I want to do a face
in the front
and a face in the back
with a different expression.
You still have reality
going on there,
so I would take it
and go for the full fantasy.
Okay.
You are in clay hell.
Yeah.
Finally I came up
with a new design
for my queen of diamonds.
She's so vain,
and she collects diamonds,
and she eats them,
so her lips and face
will be a diamond shape.
Elongate the face
to create the whole diamond.
- Like this.
- Good, good.
Thank you very much.
My character
is the queen of clubs.
My concept is this aged,
heavier-set queen,
and I want to incorporate
the shape of the club
in some natural wrinkle lines
that complement her face.
I think your whole concept
of your symbol
is going to get lost.
These things have to have
more definition.
You got to be able to see it.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
I think this is ready.
I really want to get
this face knocked out
for my jack of diamonds.
Yeah, that's better, man.
The mouth is looking
really cool
'cause it's sunk in
like he's got no teeth,
real old-looking.
And now I'm ready
to start molding this thing.
Just a little frustrated.
Something's feeling weird
about this character right now.
I think that the old age
is hindering you.
The wrinkle patterns
are blending in
with the cheekbones too much,
so the club forms need to be
a little more obvious.
First idea is not
always the best.
This is a pretty big change.
I start scraping the old-age
sculpture off of the face,
so now I'm making my design
thinner and younger,
and I think that will help
show the shape of the club.
Time is of the essence.
I got to get out of here.
Good luck, all right?
All right, you know
the direction you're going?
I do.
Glad we got a chance to talk.
I'm most concerned about Logan,
because I want to make sure
that he is pushing his character
as far as it will go
before he molds it.
See you, guys.
That's time, everybody.
It's the end of day one,
and I'm rolling
with the punches here.
I changed the sculpt,
and I'm happy to have done it.
But I am behind schedule,
so I need to be quick tomorrow.
It's day two of our whimsical
playing card challenge,
and I have 9 1/2 hours
and a lot to do.
Good morning.
I have to finish up my face
super quick,
get my cowl busted out,
and get everything molded
and cleaned.
It's gonna be sweet.
- Ah!
- It's gonna be sweet.
Do it.
Let's do it.
I think it's better.
It's a lot softer.
_
While my face mold
is setting up,
I move on to the hair.
I'm hoping that
by sculpting the hair,
it might make mine stand out
a little bit more.
So I start rolling out
individual noodles of clay
and then lining them up
along the base structure,
and then I'll be
smoothing it out,
so it doesn't look
quite so ridiculous.
I'm feeling
a little bit better,
but I know it's still a risk
to do a gender-swap makeup.
But it's getting
a little bit better.
The face is starting to look
a little bit more like a man.
But I know I need to spend
more time on this.
Yeah, I'd try to get these
in the mold room
by the five-hour mark.
Gonna have the biggest spade
of any spaders.
Since I'm making
a musketeer-style character,
I want to make the head
into a spade shape,
so I cut out around the shape,
and I start using the heat gun
to get some texture
into the foam itself.
I'm excited because I've never
made a hat like this before.
I've made small hats
for my kids
but nothing
for a fabrication piece.
Dude, that's badass.
That's cool.
Right now
my joker's going to have
a face in the front,
face in the back.
But because I'm running
out of time,
I'm not gonna sculpt
the second face.
Instead, I'm going to finish
the first face
and run a copy and latex.
Then I'll have two faces.
It's definitely
something different
than anybody else is doing
in the room.
That's pretty good.
I find my red wig that I wanted
and just start brushing it out.
And I'm using cotton and nylon
to create a shape,
and I start darkening areas
and making it more Burtonesque,
and I spray it with glitter
to make it classy.
I have this idea
that I could actually
make the broken heart bleed.
The idea for the chest piece
is to create this heart.
I want to make him look
as if he is broken
and devoid of all the blood
in his body.
It could kind of lead
more towards horror, which--
and you'll get kind of dinged,
like, "Where's the quirky
of this character?"
Rayce is right.
The design that I have
is too horror,
and it's supposed to whimsical.
What the hell else
am I supposed to do?
This is the first
individual challenge,
so I need to stand out.
Oh, God.
I think it could go either way.
I just want to let you know
that it could go either way.
It's day two
of our playing card challenge,
and Rayce says to me,
my chest piece is too horror.
Do you think I should just cut
out the broken heart altogether?
And then the only appliance
that I have would be the face.
And at this point,
I'm just like,
"I have to scrap
my chest piece."
Focus on the face.
Get this thing
in the mold room.
Every second counts.
Now all I have is a face piece.
I'm sitting here, like,
having a panic attack right now.
Doubting yourself wastes time,
and nothing gets done.
Now I know why people
freak out on Face Off.
Thank you.
See you later.
Yeah, see you, Laura.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
My time in the lab
is almost at an end.
I'm very confident
that they will get the job done
and get it looking good.
- Good luck, guys.
- Good luck, see you tomorrow.
I open my face mold,
I clean out the clay,
and it's done.
I still have to figure out
what my paint scheme
is gonna be,
so I pour gelatin
into the face mold,
so I have some sort of piece
that I can practice
pre-painting on.
One hour, everybody.
I just need this gelatin
to cool down,
so I can peel it out.
Oh, yeah.
The gelatin is still
tacky and gummy,
and this is just a nightmare.
I'm starting to freak out.
If I don't get this gelatin
cleaned out,
I don't have a foam piece,
and I'm screwed.
This was probably
a really bad idea.
Time is dwindling,
and I run with the mold
outside to the pressure washer.
And I'm spraying like a madman
and pouring out
as much as I can.
It's working, but it was
a huge waste of my time.
It basically took away time
from me being able
to work on anything else.
Just struggling with this.
That's time, everybody.
It's the end of day two.
I'm feeling a little behind.
The mold is ready for foam.
Thank God for that.
I still have to figure out
my paint scheme.
I'm gonna have to really hustle
to get everything done tomorrow.
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab
and one hour at last looks.
I know I got to get
this face painted, hand-painted,
and then this guy's got to get
a wig and a full costume.
I like the nostril hair.
Yeah.
- Cool.
- It looks pretty good.
That looks really good.
My prosthetic looks great,
but I get some bad news.
My model is not
going to be there.
Let's see if your new model...
Looks anything like Kevin.
- Looks anything like Kevin.
- I'm hoping.
- Julian.
- Augustine.
Hi.
How are you?
All right,
who's our replacement?
Is it Omar?
Hey!
Omar has a much narrower,
thin face.
It's gonna completely change it
from, like a wide diamond
to, like,
a really, really thin diamond.
And I got to try and fit
Kevin's face onto your face.
All right.
I'm gonna make this work.
I'm rolling with it.
Is that gonna be my hair?
Yeah.
That's awesome.
Because my wig
is so big and heavy,
it could easily fall off
if she moves a certain way.
So I have to pin-curl
my model's hair,
so I have pins
to anchor the other pins to.
Hopefully it'll work.
I'm sorry if I'm hurting you.
_
So my plan for application day
is to apply the cowl
and then apply the face piece.
Are you gonna put this
over the face?
Should it,
or should this go over that?
This is gonna have
to come over this.
Yeah.
And then Anthony comes by,
and he goes,
"No, no, no, no, no, no,
do the other way."
I'd almost consider
cutting this.
Right here?
Then this can come over that.
It's good advice,
but that means
I have to cut around the cowl
to make this face work on her.
It's gonna take a lot of time
out of my painting.
The only problem with it is,
she's very feminine.
I put the wig on her,
and it's not working.
_
I am so lost, because all of
the wigs that would have worked
have been taken
by all of the other contestants.
I pick out this wig
that wasn't my first choice.
But I go with it
because I'd much rather have
a makeup out on that stage
than have nothing at all.
- It's time to go.
- Yeah.
I'm applying a base coat
over all of the foam pieces.
And then I go through
and do a darker color
into all of the grooves
and cracks of the hair.
So far it's coming along
really nice.
- It's not white.
- It's still Tim Burton pale,
but it's not, like, clown pale.
Yeah.
I am panicking
about the beauty makeup.
We have a subtle face,
so we need to do
the same thing for the paint,
not go crazy.
So a little bit exaggerate
but still beauty.
That's just subtle enough.
I wouldn't go too dark there.
Okay, cool.
I feel like I have
a lot to do, and I just don't...
I would say
spend as much time as you can.
Hold off on packing up your kit.
So behind on this.
I'm still trying to figure out
how to get
that second face applied,
and I haven't even finished
painting the front face.
You don't have a back face?
I do.
I just don't know
how to put it on.
I'm concerned because now
I know that it's gonna be
a last looks thing.
It's 30 minutes, guys.
It's time, everybody.
Ah, shit.
I don't think
I'm gonna get this all done.
Good luck.
I still got to put this face
on the back and paint it.
It's an extreme amount
of work to do
for my first
individual challenge.
Might be putting a makeup
onstage that's not finished.
It's coming off right here.
At last looks, we have one hour,
and the first thing I notice
is that my lip just came loose.
I don't want to go home
because of that.
I absolutely need to add
that face in the back.
- Do you feel like it's
gonna fall off at all? - No.
If I don't get that done,
then I don't have
the character that I want.
Emily, do you have one second?
Emily's incredible.
She told me,
"When you put the eyelashes,
just ask me,
and I do for you."
Without Emily,
I have nothing to show onstage.
Thank you, Emily.
I put the crown on,
and it's just another thing
thrown into this tornado
of crap.
And I know it'll probably
end me up in bottom.
Ten minutes, everyone.
All right, guys, that's time.
Thank you.
I just feel broken right now.
All I can do is hope
that I'm safe.
Welcome
to the Face Off reveal stage.
As you know, one of you
will be going home tonight.
But before we see
your creations,
let's say hello
to our series judges.
Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Ve Neill.
Good evening, everybody.
- Hi, Ve.
- Hello.
And Neville Page.
Hi, guys.
- Hi.
- Hi, Neville.
And we have
a very special guest
joining our panel tonight.
He is a true triple threat,
having won five Emmys
for his work
as a visual effects artist,
two Academy Awards
as a production designer
on Avatar and Tim Burton's
Alice In Wonderland,
and he just directed
his first feature film,
Maleficent.
Please give a warm welcome
to Mr. Robert Stromberg.
I am a huge fan of his work,
and if there's anybody
who knows the Tim Burton
Alice In Wonderland feel,
it's Robert Stromberg.
Thank you so much
for being here, Robert.
It's a pleasure to be here.
How about we check out
some makeups?
Definitely.
Okay, this week,
for your first individual
spotlight challenge,
I asked you to each choose
a royal playing card
and bring it to life
in an outlandish and quirky way
worthy of a Tim Burton film.
Champions, let's take a look
at your proteges' creations.
He's way too vampire to me,
but I think he has
a dark Tim Burton look to him.
All I can think about is,
it may look good from afar,
but up close, it's rough.
It is really rough.
She really pops onstage.
I'm just like,
"Ooh, I love you.
You look so good."
I think she looks fantastic,
but she's got a goatee.
She's elegant and beautiful
and bearded.
He's looking really good,
but I'm still worried
that they're gonna think
that my concept
is too on the nose
or just too out there.
I'm ecstatic right now.
I'm feeling like
I could have a top look.
I'm just hoping that it's
whimsical enough for the judges.
It stands out
but not in a good way.
It doesn't read
as a king of clubs.
It just reads as a pimp.
He's doing his jig,
and it's really funny.
It looks great.
He looks just like
the way I envisioned him.
This is not 100% my best work,
but she looks like a queen...
sort of.
I'm really happy
with the silhouette.
It looks very royal.
I feel really happy
with what I've accomplished
in the past two days.
You really can't tell
which side is which,
so I'm excited
about how this looks.
I feel like it's whimsical.
It really looks like
what I had envisioned,
and I'm really happy
with this one.
The sculpture looks nice.
It's just, everything around it
is just terrible.
And I'm embarrassed
to be saying that it's mine.
Okay, judges, why don't you
check out the royal court?
Looks like this edge is
really rough along the bottom.
Just a little.
Thank you.
Oh, this is
quite a bit rougher up close.
Wow.
It almost has
a carved wood feel to it.
There's just too many
different elements going on.
Yeah.
This makes me sad.
I love that it has
that very clear,
easy-to-read emotion.
I do like
some of the paint work,
even though it's very simple.
Thank you.
His patch is a bit too big.
It looks like it's patching
the whole side of his head.
I might want to see
the rest of it,
how this transitions.
Oh, man.
I see Glenn pulling
the actual appliance.
The appliance
is falling off my model's face.
I'm probably going home
because of that,
and I'm crushed.
Tell us who made your favorite
quirky royal character
tonight on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
Ooh.
Oh, man.
The appliance came loose.
This is terrible.
I don't want to go home
at this point.
I'm frustrated
because I really wanted to shine
for the first
individual challenge.
These edges are ripped out.
We have several blowouts.
This gives bee-stung lips
a whole new definition.
It destroys any of the beauty
that was intentional.
I think if I had this
in one of my films,
I would want the eyes
more readable.
Thank you.
Nice.
I really like this one.
That profile,
between the hair and the piece,
is gorgeous.
Thank you.
This is really interesting.
She was really smart.
She left it way down here,
so it wouldn't affect his mouth.
- Yeah, it was very clean.
- Yeah.
This is some rough stuff, boy.
And I don't understand what
the story could possibly be.
Okay, the judges
have scored your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Kelly...
Ben...
Regina...
Rob...
Logan...
Stephanie...
Adam...
Congratulations,
because you are all safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
All right, that means
the rest of you
were the best
and the worst this week,
and the judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Darla, please step up.
Tell us about your character
and how you used the card
to drive your design.
So I had the jack of hearts.
My character is the royal
advisor to the king of hearts,
but he's secretly in love
with the queen,
and so he's jealous of the king.
I think it's brilliant.
Very stunning.
And I particularly love
the application technique.
I can't look at it and go,
"Here's exactly how you did it."
That thrills me to no end.
The subtlety of the paint work
around the edge of the heart,
that's very sophisticated
modeling technique.
I love this.
Thank you.
Really nice job
framing the face
and the decision
to sculpt the hair.
It's a really nice
interpretation of your vision.
Thank you so much.
Darla, please step back.
Thank you.
Jamie, you're next.
Can you please tell us
what card you have?
The history
of the king of spades
plays off of David and Goliath.
But instead of playing,
like, the tall, proud man
that David is,
I decided to make a very
proud person but very small.
He's a little bit
of a dandy, then.
Yes.
I'm not sure that
that was such a good choice.
The kings
are supposed to be regal.
The sculpting on it
is very, very rough,
and you could have put
more texture into the face.
There's some good shapes
happening,
but it's
all about the execution,
and the sculpted hair
feels more like the top
of a Klingon's head.
It has that shape
versus styled hair.
The paint job is very drab.
You've got to be able to deliver
that killer paint job,
and that didn't happen.
Jamie, if you'd please
step back.
All right, let's talk to Emily.
So tell us about your character
and how the card inspired this.
She is the queen of hearts.
Immediately I thought
of human heart,
so I wanted to incorporate
the hearts into her collar
and play with the shapes.
Everything about this
is so beautiful.
From the head shape to profile,
it's a beautiful,
beautiful design.
Thank you.
When I did Alice In Wonderland,
we would have gobbled that idea
up about being real hearts,
and they would be beating.
I think you did a good job.
Thank you.
There's one thing about this
that, honestly, I hate,
and that is
how much better you are
than I was when I was your age.
It's really hard
not to love it.
Thank you.
Emily, you can step back.
Thanks, Megan.
Nice job, lady.
- Thanks.
- Nice.
Anthony, please come forward.
Hey, Anthony.
Tell us about your character.
The king of hearts
was once this great ruler,
and the spades attacked
and killed his queen,
which caused him
to have a broken heart.
Honestly, I feel like
there's a few problems here.
I think that the paint work
feels muddled,
like a combination
of many thoughts
that didn't coagulate
into one single form.
The hair is an absolute mess.
And I'm using a nice word.
No.
In close-up, it's so horrible,
it's not even
a good clown makeup.
Anthony, you can step down.
Thank you.
Daniel, if you'd please
step up.
Please tell us the concept
behind your makeup.
I got the queen of diamonds,
and she's hunting for diamonds
in all the kingdoms.
This is conceptually
unintelligible to me.
If you weren't telling me,
I wouldn't have known
that's the queen of diamonds.
One of the huge mistakes
that you made
was trying to put
a three-dimensional diamond
on her mouth,
because it looks like
she's deformed.
I feel like you went into it
with a little bit
of uncertainty,
and being whimsical is not being
afraid to go too far.
Daniel, you can step down.
Thank you.
Julian.
Julian, would you please
tell us about your character?
My card was the jack of clubs,
and he made a deal
with the king of the underworld,
so he helps with ferrying
the dead to the underworld.
This is a really interesting,
bizarre-looking makeup.
I like the way that you actually
did take the shape of the club,
but you have this great little
damaged section of his forehead.
And it's really out of the box.
I really like it.
Thank you.
It's not on the nose,
it's not literal,
and that's a good thing.
Yours is one of the only ones
that stood out.
You have shown
some serious skills
in the sculpting, painting,
and applying of the makeup.
Thank you.
Julian, please step back.
Thanks.
Thank you, guys.
If you'd please head
back to the makeup room
while the judges deliberate.
All right, judges, let's start
with your favorites tonight.
How about Darla's work?
I love it.
She's the only one
that pulled off the pointy chin
and had it work visually.
Yeah, technically solid.
The overall graphic of it,
very solid.
I think
it was absolutely stunning,
and she put the rest
of the competitors on notice.
She is going to be
a force to be reckoned with.
All right, judges,
let's move on to Emily.
Just stunning.
The hearts with the arrows
and the whole schmegegge,
it was awesome.
She did heart face, heart hair,
hearts around her collar.
It would have seemed like
too much of a good thing,
but because they were nuanced,
they just echoed.
All right, judges,
let's move on to Julian.
I do admire the subtleties
of the scarring,
and there was a certain flow
to it.
There's some beautiful
sculpting and painting on it.
It's just its own unique vision.
All right, judges,
let's move on
to the looks you like the least.
Let's talk about Jamie's work tonight.
It's a king's face
with a spade haircut.
That's not a very good idea.
She had the choice
not to use that head piece.
She could have put
real hair on it.
Which I think she should have.
There was too many pieces
that didn't fit together.
Let's move on to Anthony.
You can't overlook
the paint job.
I've seen more kingly bowls
of spaghetti,
to be honest with you.
Simple illustration-style
makeup,
it's the hardest thing to do,
because it's just
a couple colors and some lines,
and they have to be perfect.
Visually, it read more
like a hybrid tribal mask
than it did a playing card.
Okay, let's move on to Daniel.
He was so lost.
That was so shoddily sculpted,
applied, and painted.
At the core of it,
the problem is,
the concept for the makeup
is nonexistent.
Why didn't he at least
do some sort of
cool, monstery-looking queen...
Precisely.
...with, like, diamonds
protruding out of her skin
and give it the Tim Burton look?
At least it would have been
something creative.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- We have.
- Yes.
Okay, let's bring them
back out.
So, Glenn, tell us
about the top looks.
Darla, your jack
had a powerful presence,
and you really impressed us
both with
your beautiful application
and your technical prowess.
Emily, your queen was replete
with graceful forms
and great colors,
and it all came together
into a beautifully unified
finished product.
Julian, the sculpture
of your face
showed some strong
technical talent,
and the uniqueness
of your character
stood out among the crowd.
And, Laura,
I've got to congratulate you
since all three top looks
came from your team.
It's all them.
All them.
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
Tonight's winner is...
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
Tonight's winner is...
Emily.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
It's weird.
You gave us such a thoughtful
and artistic makeup tonight.
We just cannot wait to see
what you put in front of us
next week.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you so much.
I am thrilled.
I win
the first individual challenge,
which is so nice.
I'm just so happy with it.
I'm glad the judges
liked it too.
All right, Emily.
You, Darla, and Julian
can all head back to the makeup
room with the coaches.
All right, guys,
that means the rest of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be going home.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Jamie, you had
some good ideas this week,
but you were let down
by poor execution
in your sculpture and painting.
Anthony, though your makeup
did portray some emotion,
at the end of the day,
we couldn't really tell
what we were looking at.
And, Daniel, though
your character did appear royal,
there were some fundamental
flaws with your makeup
on a conceptual level
that left it incoherent.
All right, Glenn,
who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Daniel.
Your character suffered
from many technical flaws,
and ultimately
it felt uninspired.
I agree.
Daniel, I am so sorry.
That means
you have been eliminated.
Jamie and Anthony,
you're both safe this week.
You can head back
to the makeup room.
Don't give up.
I mean, you made it this far
because you have talent.
Learn and give this
another try.
Thank you.
I will.
Daniel, it's been great
having you here with us,
but if you'd please
head back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Take care.
I've been doing makeup
for about, like, eight months,
so the next step for me
is learning more and getting better.
Oh, no.
- Daniel?
- Yes.
Having Anthony as
my coach and teacher
inspired me to learn a lot.
My experience at Face Off
was incredible.
I think ***
you can do whatever you want.
Just try hard and you can get it.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net