To win the money,
that would change my life.
I don't want
to let myself down,
but I also don't want
to let Rayce down.
Falling short
would be devastating.
I'm hoping
that they call my name.
In a season of champions,
four artists have excelled.
But which three will rise
and make it to the finale?
Make sure that you give this
your all.
I don't want this to end.
If there were even an hour
I needed to work my hardest,
- it's right now.
- You're all I got left.
I wish we could keep everybody.
Shit!
Oh, my God.
This is not working.
Tonight, we'll know
who's in and who's out.
In the end, only one will win
a VIP trip from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand-new 2015 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
This is Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
We head out this morning
and we end up at
an old West town.
- Horseshoes?
- Jail.
I see a picture
of Emily on there.
We're looking around,
and see the blacksmith's shop.
There's a bank that has
piles of gold.
And we see McKenzie has a
beautiful dress and high heels.
First of all,
why is she wearing this?
And second of all,
why are we in a western town?
- Good morning, guys.
- Good morning.
Welcome to Paramount Ranch's
Western Town.
These dusty streets
were a popular stomping ground
for jangling spurs
and stagecoaches
during the golden era
of Western filmmaking.
John Wayne, Bob Hope
and Kirk Douglas
used to ride horses
on this very trail.
- That's awesome.
- That is cool.
We're here today
because this year marks
the 50th anniversary
of the hit television series
The Wild Wild West.
This classic series took stock
characters of the old West
to a whole new level
by fusing them with
technological wizardry
that we've seen featured
in dozens of other films
and television shows,
like Dr. Who, Hellboy
and Sherlock Holmes.
Steampunk.
Cool. That's cool.
All right, so for
your spotlight challenge,
I want you to take things
a step further
by reimagining a classic
Western character
as a steampunk cyborg.
Oh, man.
I do really dig steampunk,
and I know this is
an opportunity
to fabricate something.
So I'm really excited.
This is a dream challenge.
Now, throughout this ranch
are the typical establishments
you'd expect to see
in the old West.
And each one represents
a classic Western character.
So if you pick the saloon,
you'll be making a barmaid.
The undertaker's parlor,
an undertaker.
The bank equals a bank robber.
The jail represents
the sheriff.
And the blacksmith
is exactly that.
A blacksmith.
Now, before you get started,
I know what you're thinking.
Steampunk is not easy,
because it's such a specific
and intricate space.
Well, don't worry, guys.
I always have your back.
I'd like to introduce
a special guest
who just so happens to know
all things steampunk.
Glenn, come on out.
That's awesome.
Yeah.
It's Glenn, thank God,
because I know nothing
about steampunk
except for
there's lots of beards.
- Thanks for being here.
- Thank you for having me.
Every season, the artists are
terrified of doing steampunk,
because they know what I know.
Glenn is intimately familiar
with this world.
So I thought I'd have him
come out here today
to talk to you about where
people go wrong,
and how to get it right.
At the core of
the steampunk aesthetic
is a combination of two
elements,
a Victorian or Edwardian
fashion sense,
combined with antediluvian
technology.
What that means is,
technology from a previous
civilization
that has been rediscovered
and is now powered with steam.
And exceedingly important
is making everything look
like it has a purpose.
Do not glue gears or rivet
brass plates
onto an area that doesn't
make any sense.
It must look like it works.
I'm not a fan of steampunk,
and I don't watch Westerns.
I get what cyborgs are,
but to then factor in
these other two elements?
This is going to be a rough one.
I'd go stake your claim
on one of the storefronts
by removing the ring of keys
out front,
and then get started
on your designs.
Remember, guys,
this is your last chance
to prove to the judges
that you deserve
to make it to the finale.
On my mark, get set, go.
Drinks.
My character's a barmaid.
She's going to be sexy,
but also hard core.
Most important is to sell
the idea that she's a cyborg
underneath and over the top
of the flesh.
This is an opportunity
for me to fabricate
a mechanical arm that she could
serve drinks from,
with a tank on top
and some gauges on it
to tell you how much is left.
I want this to be the best
character I've made so far.
These are all genres that
I'm not very comfortable with.
I picked the keys
for the blacksmith,
and I have absolutely no idea
where to start
with this character.
It's really stressful,
because this is
the last challenge
before the finale.
And if I can't come up
with a design,
that could be it for me.
And I don't want to go home yet.
I got the steampunk
bank robber.
He's kind of an expert thief.
He's going to have a cyborg arm
that is also his weapon.
I know Glenn's going to be
looking for originality.
It's going to be really tough
to impress him,
so I want to make sure
I go all out.
I don't do robots.
I'm not familiar with them.
But reading about it,
the undertakers
make the coffins,
they dress the bodies,
they bury them.
Because it's a cyborg,
I want to break up
the human form,
and I'm going to go
with a coffin shape.
I want to be in this finale
so bad.
I cannot be the one
eliminated on this.
In the entire time
that we're sitting there
thinking about our characters,
I don't come up with anything.
And that's really scary.
I just-- like, I have to focus
on this.
I don't know what
I'm going to do.
Let's go back to the lab,
everybody.
We have five hours in the lab
today-- first we pick our models.
And then I go to my station
and start sculpting the chest.
I'm going to make a coffin chest
to break up the human form.
I'm not really too sure what
I'm going to do for the face.
I'm just going to focus
on this chest
and get him sculpted and molded
so I can run foam latex today.
Old West barmaids
are very voluptuous.
So my barmaid is going
to be well-endowed.
And I almost am taking her
into a caricature.
What you doing there, bud?
Uh, nothing.
Not over here doing anything.
I'm going to sculpt out
a full chest piece
that has some bajungs
that are about this big.
Other people seem like
they've got a direction,
and I still don't.
The first thing I do
is gather some materials
so that it gives me a few more
minutes to think about it.
But I really need
to get this nailed down.
Ooh, it's hot out.
I got a barmaid.
Okay.
My only concern
is the size of the hoots.
And with all the other
things to do,
is sculpting a nice set
of hoots, like, the way to go?
It really is ridiculous,
Rayce points out,
that it's just a waste of time.
So we scrap it.
_
I think Logan definitely has
the ability to go to the finale.
He reminds me a lot of myself,
coming in with not
a lot of experience
and having to learn an insane
amount every challenge.
I may only have
one team member left,
but I'm happy I got Logan.
- Hey, what's going on?
- Well, I got a bank robber.
Yeah, that's exciting.
Laura and I start talking
about the concept,
and I start telling her
exactly what I want.
And because I don't know
how to draw,
she draws out
what I'm describing.
- Do you do much fabrication?
- No.
Julian's got
a lot of fabrication,
something that he's never
done before.
But if he leaves himself enough
time to do that fabrication,
I'm sure he can pull
something good off.
- All right, have fun with the L200.
- Well, yeah.
- So you got blacksmith.
- Blacksmith.
Trying to get myself
in some sort of direction.
At this point, I started coming
up with potential concept ideas.
He heaps the metal
somewhere inside of him.
Yeah!
I like the idea
of this blacksmith
who replaced his heart
with a forge.
And he has an iron jaw
embedded into his flesh.
I like that.
That makes a great silhouette.
- Okay.
- And it gives him
kind of a menacing look
as well.
It's kind of silly,
but it's something.
It's better than-- you know,
it's better than not having
a concept.
I work on the chest
for about 2 1/2 hours.
And I'm ready to mold.
I need to get
this chest out today,
because I need to pre-paint
and fabricate
on top of the foam tomorrow.
Hi, everybody.
- Hey, how's it going?
- Hi.
I chose the salon,
which is the barmaid.
All of these tubes will be
pumping steam into her
and her arm device.
- How's your beauty makeup?
- I have not done much.
- Okay.
- And I do need to work on that.
This is the type of makeup
- that can't be subtle.
- Right.
She can have eyeliner.
You can use lashes.
You can have red lipstick
to really kind of bring it out.
- Thank you, sir. Appreciate it.
- Good luck.
I want to fabricate his arm
into some type of weapon.
I want it maybe have something
that rotates like a gun barrel.
If you don't have time,
don't worry about it rotating.
Just selling the idea that
he has the ability to shoot,
it will sell your concept.
Thank you.
So I have the blacksmith,
and the idea is that
he implanted a furnace
into his chest.
Even if you just did doors
and you put some LED lights
where you really
couldn't see into it.
You could just see
some glow out of it.
I'm going to let you
get back to work.
- Thank you.
So I have the undertaker.
For the chest, I want to go
with a coffin shape.
I'm going to do a lot
of fabrication on the chest
to have all the different
pipes and liquids.
Okay, now with the face,
are you going to cyborg
a section of it?
I'm not too sure what I'm
going to do for the face yet.
This is what
the judges are going to look at.
And all the rest of this
is kind of like window dressing.
This is what's either going to
make you or break the challenge.
I wish we could keep everybody
that's here,
but someone's going
to have to go.
- Thank you so much.
- Good luck.
Well, good-bye, everybody,
and my best wishes
to all of you.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Bye-bye.
I'm super frustrated right now.
I'm, like, super
fucking frustrated.
Mr. Westmore wants me
to focus on the face,
but I don't know what to do.
I don't know anything
about cyborgs or steampunk.
This is a mess.
We're this close to the finale,
and I'm scared.
I don't want this to end.
I'm, like, super
fucking frustrated.
It's day one in the lab,
and this is the last challenge
before the finale.
I have no idea what I'm going
to do with the face,
and I don't have much time
to make decisions,
because I need to get this chest
out or I will be screwed.
Try to stay away
from sharp edges.
My main goal with this sculpt
is to suggest beauty
on top of cyborg.
So I start sculpting in
mechanics.
I take pre-made pieces
and I impregnate
the clay with them.
That gives me the best effect
of mechanics beneath
beautiful surfaces.
Almost there.
- See you tomorrow.
- Breathe, breathe.
- See you guys.
- Bye.
A cyborg isn't a full robot.
It's a person
with robotic parts.
So I want to create
a metal dome
where half of it is metal plate
and the other half
is see-through glass,
so you can see all the gears
on the inside.
So I have this dome
that I'll be able to fit
into my cowl sculpt tomorrow.
Do you know the time?
56 minutes.
Shit.
I have an hour
to finish this mold,
and I'm still applying
UltraCal to it.
Finally, the mold is done.
But it still has to dry.
So I can't open it yet.
Why are you freaking out now?
Why do you have to get the chest
mold out right this second?
Because I have so much
to fabricate on it.
Because if not, then there's
really no point to it.
15 minutes, everybody.
I'm just going to go for it.
I'm going to open it.
But it's scalding hot,
because it's still curing.
Uh...
Which means it could crack.
And I have minutes left.
I got it.
I got my mold done just in time.
I don't know how that happened,
but it did.
That's time.
Let's go home.
Tomorrow, I can focus
on the face and fabrication.
So I'm feeling a lot better.
And it begins.
It's day two of
the steampunk challenge.
We have 9 1/2 hours to work.
That's awesome
that we all wore black.
Today I have to finish
the sculpt on the face,
sculpt the cowl out,
and I need to fabricate
this arm piece.
I'm thinking about going
very scarred and wrinkled
on the face.
I just want it to look
like this unsavory character
that you wouldn't want
to run into.
And your eye flows with this.
And it's all over that.
Julian is working
on the bank robber,
and he's going to try his hand
at fabrication
for the first time ever.
Hopefully you'll have enough
time at the end of the day
- to make this shoulder piece.
- Right.
Figure out what you're
gonna do with the face?
I'm thinking about doing
like a metal beard.
I slept on it last night and
I was thinking about the face.
The concept behind the beard
is that it has a respirator
attached to it.
So he doesn't breathe in
all the chemicals, or whatever.
Okay. Steam-powered mask?
- Yes.
- That will look cool.
I feel like if I incorporate
the metal mask,
it'll make it steampunk
and cyborg enough.
Get the goggles sculpted first,
and then worry about
the little details.
I spent a few hours
working on the face sculpt.
I decide that instead of having
connected goggles,
I just want to have
two eye pieces that are embedded
into the skin
around the eye sockets.
Because it's that
sort of classic
steampunk aviator-style goggles.
And in order to sell
the steampunk aspect
of this challenge,
I really need to make sure
that these goggles
look steampunk.
- Looks good.
- Cool. Thank you.
Is this the fabrication table?
My big challenge today
is fabricating the arm device
to completion.
So I'm hard at work
fabricating this arm
using L200 foam, glues, tubing.
Whenever you're ready,
let me know.
I'll go in and I'll kind of show
you how to use that waxer.
Rayce shows me
this waxing tool,
which I've never used before.
And it actually does
a fantastic job
of melting away L200 foam.
So I can carve out
filigree out of foam.
It's great, and I just hope
the other contestants
don't see me using it,
because it's perfect.
- You like messing with that?
- Yeah, it's cool.
It's very similar to tattooing.
Formaldehyde
and some kind of salt.
Because my character's
a mortician,
I want the embalming liquids
to be part of the makeup.
So I take clear hair gel
and mix it with acrylic paint,
and I paint it into the bottle
so it looks like
there is a liquid inside.
And I'm liking
the way it looks.
Are you gonna be able
to have enough time
to fabricate this arm today?
I'm going to do my best.
I've roughly drawn out a shape.
Since I'm not familiar
with fabrication at all,
Laura draws out how I can get
the shape that I need.
So that's pretty helpful.
After Laura leaves,
I finish molding.
And then it's time
for fabrication.
I have to work on this arm now,
and it's just the bane
of my existence.
This is the challenge
before the finale,
so I need to make sure
that I'm showing how much
I want to be in the finale,
by really stepping out
of my comfort zone.
I'm just worried that maybe
I'm attempting to do
too much stuff
that I don't know how to do.
Fucking steampunk.
I'm using the hot glue gun
to try to glue
these pieces together.
But it's not holding
the right way.
I'm using the heat gun
to keep it in shape.
It's just a mess, just trying
to figure this stuff out.
Time is running out.
I don't even know
if what I'm doing
is right or wrong
at this point.
I'm screwed.
It's day two
of the steampunk challenge.
It's finally come down
to the fabrication.
And time is dwindling,
but I need to make sure
that this doesn't look cheesy.
So I'm going balls to the wall
trying to do something bigger
just to show how much I'm trying
to get into the finale.
I have to just keep going,
and hopefully I'll be able
to figure it out.
She's a barmaid.
She serves drinks.
So I'm fabricating tube
down through her finger
so she can dispense
whiskey into a glass.
I'm not sure exactly
how to make it work.
This is just
an engineering thing
that I have to work on
application day.
- Ah!
- Darla, pull yourself together.
I know.
It's just one of those days.
That's time, everyone.
We're all stressed out.
Tomorrow's the last opportunity
to show the judges
that we're worthy
of the finale.
- Your arm looks awesome.
- Thank you.
I have to do a good,
clean application,
but I'll have all the parts
to do it.
We get back to the house,
and I think everyone
is a bit nervous at this point.
When we started we had so many
people in the house.
And then now it's just four.
There's so much
that has happened,
and it's unbelievable.
And I'm really excited
to just work my hardest
and make it to the finale.
It would be really hard
to get this close
and then not make it.
To have the opportunity
to win the money,
that would change my life
in so many ways.
Tomorrow is going to be
a long day.
It's application day,
and we have four hours
to do this makeup.
I have to do the fastest
application as I possibly can,
- so I can spend the rest of the time on...
- Awesome!
- Painting and stuff.
- ...finishing this thing.
Logan got as far as he could
on the fabricated arm.
But is there going to be
enough time
to put it all together
and leave time for those
all-important details?
Well, I'm going
to do it in an hour,
and then spend the rest of the
three hours doing fabrication.
- Good morning.
- How's it going?
How are you?
I've got some stuff to do
before I'm gonna
be starting on you at all.
When the models arrive,
I'm not quite ready
to start application,
because I still have a fair
amount of fabrication to do.
Once I get all the pieces
of the armor glued down,
I take it back
to the spray booth
and spray-paint
the whole thing black.
What are you staring at?
Just the symmetry
of the cheekbones.
The right side
of his prosthetic
looks really, really weird.
There's something
definitely off.
You make me nervous
when you stand there
staring quietly.
This one's
in the wrong spot, so...
With this character,
where she has to be beautiful,
you have to make sure
that these prosthetics
are wonderfully symmetrical.
That should be further down.
The whole thing
needs to go like this.
This side is crooked,
and he's absolutely right.
It's coming off.
But I'm in a frenzy, because
there's a lot of work to do.
- Come down a little bit.
- Yeah, that's better.
I apply the face to my model,
and my edges are kind of wonky.
And if I try to do
a realistic flesh tone,
it's going to look silly.
So instead of going
with a realistic character,
I'm going to go
with a stylized character.
I use the Kryolan aqua color
to create corrosive skin,
the same texture that I used
for the rust on the chest.
If I can color-match him,
then I don't have to worry
- about painting his arms.
- Yeah.
Getting natural-looking
skin tone is pretty difficult,
because skin is very
translucent.
And when you're painting
on a foam piece,
there's no translucency
whatsoever.
So the trick is to do
multiple layers of washes,
flecking and airbrushing
and veining and mottling.
So I'm just flecking
as fast as I can.
Time to patch you up.
Everything gets laid down,
and it's time to start blending.
Blending is key here.
I'm just really worried
about that chest piece
being all gross
and crazy-looking.
The chest piece area
is starting to look
a little bit gross,
and that is absolutely not
what I want of this character.
It's got to be beautiful.
So I started blending edges
with Cabo-Patch.
And I go over it
and over it again.
So you've got an hour left.
Maybe just continue
to make that chest work,
because another thing
is every time she moves,
this neck is crinkling
and mushing.
I'm already behind schedule.
Now I'm actually worried
about the makeup.
It's almost the end
of application,
and I'm falling behind.
I still have to figure out
how I'm going to get
this giant armor
to look steampunk.
Pour into there.
Make a nice little
oatmeal consistency.
Luckily, Laura suggested
mixing corn meal
and latex together,
and then smear it onto the armor
just to give that rusted look.
And painting on top of that.
It is a really cool effect.
I think you got,
like, 20 minutes.
So take a minute to pack up.
I only have the first layer
of the PAX skin tone base
on the model.
And I still have a ton
of work to do.
So I'm going
to have to prioritize
whatever little time
I have left.
That's it! Time's up!
Oh, God.
I hope I have everything.
Leaving the lab,
I'm really nervous.
If you do a good makeup
but it's still not exciting
or it doesn't fit the challenge,
that's what sends you home
at this point.
And tonight, we'll know who's in
and who's out.
I get to last looks,
and I have one hour.
Can you hold the wardrobe
off to each side
while I'm doing this?
One of the most important things
I have to do
is glue the forge
onto the L200 base.
I'm happy with the way
the forge turned out,
and now I just have to make him
dirty and sweaty.
_
I don't know what happened.
It doesn't look as good
as it did
when she left the lab.
There's some serious edge
texture issues going on,
so I'm scrapping the idea
for the arm gag.
I don't have time for it.
I need to focus on making
this roughness softer.
If there were ever an hour
I needed to work my hardest,
it's right now.
That's not going to work.
I start fussing around
with the vacuformed dome.
It's taking forever just
to fit it inside the foam latex.
Screw it.
So I decide to scrap it.
Now I need to do as much
detail work as I can.
Ten minutes, everybody!
- That's time, everyone.
- Whoo!
To me, it reads steampunk.
It reads cyborg.
It reads Western.
But I'm worried that it's not
going to be enough.
Welcome back
to the reveal stage.
As you guys know,
only three of you
will earn spots tonight
in this season's finale.
Which means one of you
will be eliminated.
But before we get
down to business,
let's say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve
Makeup Effects Studio,
Mr. Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening, guys.
- Hey.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist,
- the lovely Ve Neill.
- Hi, everybody.
- Hey.
- Excited?
- Terrified?
- Both.
And creature and concept
designer Neville Page.
- Good evening.
- Hey.
All right, guys, this week
your spotlight challenge
was to choose a classic
old West character
and reimagine it
as a steampunk cyborg.
So with only three finale spots
on the line,
let's take a look
at your creations.
I'm concerned that Glenn's
not going to think
it's steampunk enough
or cyborg enough.
So I'm scared.
I just want to be in the finale
so bad.
I just hope this makeup
is good enough.
The fabrication is very rough,
but he still looks like
a villainous bad guy.
He is a really cool character.
I think, as a character,
it's one of my favorite pieces.
Technically, though,
I failed on a number of points.
And I hope it's not too much
to send me home.
There's three other really
strong artists right now.
And I'm very concerned that
my concept isn't good enough.
I'm hoping that my application
is strong enough
to carry me into the finale.
Okay, judges.
It's time to take a closer look.
This is a nice
paint job on this.
- I do love the colors.
- Yeah.
- This confuses me.
- Yeah, me too.
But I do love the tubes.
I got to see this.
Ah.
I know it's the top
of the head,
but I wish that there was a bit
more control and purpose
- to what all this is.
- Mm-hmm.
Because it feels like...
- A bunch of gears.
- Sort of.
- Yeah.
- It really does
have an overall great look.
But the sculpting is so rough.
It's just harsh carvings,
which is too bad,
because the whole idea
is very cool.
I think this piece is bad.
I don't think it's meant
to be wrinkled like that.
It's just so rough.
Especially for it being one away
from the finale.
Up close, I know
the judges are pointing out
some of the seaming, some of
the weird wrinkles going on.
Nothing I can do about it now.
That's cool.
A little drink dispenser.
Can you bend it at all?
Is it...
Okay. Good.
I hope as a package,
this is worth it
to get me into the finale,
because it would absolutely suck
if I went home for this.
Tell us who made your favorite
Western steampunk cyborg
tonight on Twitter,
using #FaceOff
I think this piece is bad.
I don't think it's meant
to be wrinkled.
I know the judges
are pointing out
some of the seaming,
some of the weird wrinkles
that are going on.
- I like this idea.
- Yeah.
- A lot.
- And I like how this
is all solid
and in the anatomical form.
Let's take a look at your arm.
That's cool.
A little drink dispenser.
He's paying attention
to making this functional.
I hope as a package,
this is worth it
to get me into the finale,
because I want to prove myself.
So it would absolutely suck
if I went home for this.
I love that the theme of this,
with him being a blacksmith,
that the actual core of the idea
is the core of the makeup.
That feels very metallic.
You know what's
a nice little touch
that we have not seen
a whole lot of--
The sweat on his brow.
- It's on his arms too.
- Thank you.
All right, guys.
The judges would like to speak
with each of you
before deciding
who will make it to the finale.
- Darla, you're up.
- Okay.
Tell us about the concept
behind your steampunk-inspired
blacksmith.
He took out his heart
and replaced it with a forge,
so that he could focus
on his work.
Pretty much every element
of this challenge
was outside my comfort zone,
but all that considered,
I'm pretty happy with it.
I see your self-questioning
present in this week's work.
But I do really like
the overall look.
Thank you.
What I like about your makeup
is the core theme
is center to the character.
It is a very clean character.
I would have liked to have seen
just a little scroll work
on this jaw piece,
or some riveting or something,
because this part up here
is very plain.
And I do like the addition
of the sweat.
That was a really nice touch.
That really helps with the theme
of being the blacksmith.
- Thank you. Thanks.
- Nice job.
He's got a cool look overall.
The skin growing over the piece,
that takes the character
to a whole new level.
Thank you.
Darla, you can step down.
Thanks, Alex.
Julian, you're next.
Julian, tell me about
your bank-robbing,
cowboy steampunk cyborg.
My character originally
started out as a miner.
There was an accident,
and all the mechanics
on the top of the head
are keeping him alive.
It was my first time
working with L200.
Well, I do love me a cowboy,
so I do like this character.
I do like the scar on the face,
but the sculpting
doesn't look like flesh.
I think your greatest success
on this one
is the overall silhouette.
But the brain feels like
bits and pieces just glued on.
I think you did a great job
embracing the Western aesthetic
of what we were talking about.
And I love the reveal
with the hat.
But one of my problems
with the makeup
is the top of his head
is too high.
Some really great things.
Some other things
that I've got to sort
of pick apart a little bit.
Julian, please step down.
Thanks.
Thanks, guys.
Emily, please step up.
Oh, gosh.
So, tell us about your
steampunk character, please.
He's a mortician.
He's not very familiar
with the chemicals they use
to embalm the bodies.
Mixing them corroded the metal,
and his skin's starting
to turn to metal.
The overall color of this
is so beautiful and harmonious.
I just love the fact
that he's become so oxidized
and so patina'd
by this chemical reaction,
which I think
is really quite nice.
- Thank you.
- What are the bottles
on his chest made of?
I found baby powder bottles.
I just-- I vacuformed it
and used hair gel, and I just
tinted it with acrylic paint.
Is this something
you've done before?
No.
There's a lot of overwhelmingly
genius decisions
that you're making
to do things quick,
and it works out
extraordinarily well.
The texture of the skin
is really cool.
And I love the fact
that the paint's
all sort of dark
around the hairline,
so it's burnt out, smoked out.
It's really pretty, honey.
Thank you.
- Emily, you can head back.
- Thank you. Thanks, Marcus.
- Good job. - Nice job.
- Thanks. Thanks.
All right, let's talk to Logan.
Logan, tell us about how you
used the steampunk aesthetic
on your barmaid character.
She's classic barmaid.
She serves drinks
through her arm device here.
And what about the filigree
on her forehead?
Filigree
was hand-sculpted.
Well, I think that
in and of itself is impressive.
I also think it's an incredibly
articulate conveyance
of that archaic technology
that we were talking about.
What I do not think is great
is some of the edging
and blending work
from her breast to her chest.
Really rough.
I really like this character.
It's so unfortunate
that you had
so many problems
in this area right here,
because this is a mess.
But I think the design of it
is really cool.
And I love this headpiece.
To do filigree right
takes time and patience.
So it's impressive that you
pulled off what you did
with that piece alone.
Thank you.
- Logan, you can head back.
- Thanks.
All right, you guys can all
head back to the makeup room
while the judges decide
who will move on to the finale.
Oh, my God.
All right, judges.
Well, you have some
big decisions to make.
Why don't we start with Darla.
Well, Darla did another
exceptional application
and a beautiful sculpt.
I think it was missing
a little bit
of some of the steampunk
componentry
that we would have liked
to have seen.
But all in all,
it was a pretty solid character.
And it was painted beautifully.
The chin piece
was beautifully executed.
And she did that one extra
fine little detail
that we've so rarely seen,
sweat.
All right, judges,
let's move on to Julian.
He really worked hard
at getting that whole
cowboy aesthetic down.
And he did a really great job
at them.
The dirtiness of the clothes
really pulled
that whole thing together.
The concept, with
his arm being augmented,
that's right-thinking.
The execution of it
was lacking precision.
But it was his first time
using L200.
- That's pretty courageous.
- Yeah.
All right, let's move on
to Emily.
This little girl is
absolutely phenomenal.
She completed an entire makeup
with sort of the half face,
and then all this mangled
jaw area
that facilitated in putting
her steampunk elements over.
Okay, that's really smart.
Emily is fearless
in three categories--
fabrication, concept and form.
That kind of range is,
at any age, admirable.
All right,
let's move on to Logan.
Cool barmaid. Bitching arm.
He achieved one of the
most steampunk-looking objects.
He insculpted that
filigree on the plate in her head,
and the way that it just
divides her face in half.
It's all beautifully
encapsulated
within the human form.
As much as I love the design,
he should have thought
about that chest piece
right out there in the middle
of her body.
Blatantly bad edges.
As a design,
this is on the right track.
Incredibly tough
decision this year.
This is one of the closest
it's ever been.
All right, judges.
Have you chosen
your final three, then?
Yes, we have.
Let's bring them back out.
Welcome back, guys.
It's time to find out
who is moving forward.
So, Glenn, who is the winner
of this challenge,
and the first person
to make it to the finale?
The winner of tonight's
challenge,
and the first person
moving on to the finale is...
So, Glenn, who is the winner
of this challenge,
and the first person
to make it to the finale?
The winner of tonight's
challenge,
and the first person
moving on to the finale is...
Emily.
Oh, my God.
We love the weathered
and oxidized paint
on your character.
Though he was not
traditionally steampunk,
he still very much
evoked that world.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
_
I'm going to start to cry.
What?
I'm the youngest person
to ever be on Face Off,
and I'm in the finale.
It's so awesome.
I will never forget the way
I'm feeling right now.
Emily, congratulations.
You have earned the first spot
in the finale.
Thank you.
Glenn, who is the next
person to make it to the finale?
The second person that will be
joining us in the finale is...
Darla.
Thank you.
Oh.
We really liked your choice
to make the blacksmith
profession
the central component
of your character.
And you delivered, once again,
your signature style.
A beautifully clean,
finished makeup.
Thank you so much.
I don't even know what to say.
I am shocked. I'm in.
I made it to the finale.
And that is the most
incredible thing.
Congratulations, Darla.
You've earned the second spot
in our finale.
All right, guys,
this is the hard part.
We have two artists left,
and only one of you
can join us in the finale.
Glenn, who has earned
the last spot?
I do really want this spot.
I'm hoping that
they call my name.
I'm ready to go further.
More than anything,
I want a chance to prove
that I can do some of the things
that they think I failed at.
I also don't want
to let Rayce down.
This was an awfully
difficult decision.
The third and final spot
goes to...
Logan.
The overall aesthetic
of your barmaid
felt really well-conceived,
and the sculpted filigree work,
particularly on her forehead,
was just really beautiful.
Thank you.
I'm incredibly grateful.
This is where I've been hoping
to get to the whole time.
I feel like this is now
a competition
that's starting for me.
- Logan, congratulations.
- Thank you.
Unfortunately,
that means, Julian,
you have been eliminated.
Julian, it has been
an absolute pleasure
to have you here with us.
And I got to tell you,
you've done some amazing things
this season.
This is definitely
one of the worst situations
we've been in
in terms of picking
our final three.
You guys all killed
this challenge,
and I'm proud
of all four of you.
- Thank you.
- Julian, it's been
great having you here with us.
If you would please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you.
- See you.
- See you, guys.
- Thank you, Julian.
- Good luck.
It stings a bit that I've been
through every single challenge,
did some cool makeups and did
not make it to the finale.
But this whole competition
has really put everything I have
to the test.
I hope that I made my family,
my girlfriend proud,
because I'm proud of myself.
Congrats again to you three.
I'm excited to be able
to call you finalists.
Nice work.
Oh, my gosh.
But your night isn't over yet.
This season's finale
is going to be
- the most difficult one yet.
- Oh, no.
You guys have these amazing
champions in your corner.
So we're raising
the bar on you.
Aye, aye, aye.
What bar are we raising?
Oh, no.
I don't feel like I'm ready
to start the finale.
We just went
through hell and back.
What are we doing?
Why are we still on stage?
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net