I think you did
an astounding job.
I just don't get it.
Love it,
and I love how you're thinking.
Thank you.
Previously on Face Off...
Jamie's wooden bridge troll
earned her her first win,
but Anthony stumbled,
and Team Rayce suffered
their second loss in a row.
Now ten artists remain,
and tonight all bets are off.
Models, come on out.
Ooh.
I've never body-painted
before in my life.
I don't need this now.
Changing it halfway through
isn't helping.
I'm not comfortable
changing my entire paint job.
You will be the one going home.
It looks like a little kid's
painting at a county fair.
In the end, only one will win
a VIP trip from
Kryolan Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2015 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
This is Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Oh, well, here we go.
This is so weird.
Beautiful.
We walk into the lab, I
see all these different hats,
and I am pumped.
The hats are wild
and very inspiring,
so I'm really excited to hear
what the challenge is.
Hey, guys.
Hi.
Well, as you can tell,
this is gonna be a fun one,
so let's get to it.
Some of Hollywood's
most unforgettable characters,
like The Cat in the Hat
and Davy Jones,
they're not only known
for the roles they play,
but also their singular hats.
In this Foundation Challenge,
you will select
one of these hats
and use it to inspire an
original character of your own.
This is really cool.
Before we get started,
I'd like to introduce you
to today's special guest judge.
Last season,
she joined the Face Off family
when she filled in for Ve
on the judges' panel.
Please give a warm welcome back
to Oscar-winning makeup artist
Lois Burwell.
Lois Burwell, makeup legend
and judge from season seven.
She's known for her work
with Steven Spielberg
and her realism.
I'm really stoked
that she's gonna be judging
our Foundation Challenge.
- What a great hat.
- Thank you very much.
It would be rude not to,
wouldn't it, on a hat challenge?
All right, well, you've seen it
all in your storied career,
and you've brought so many
incredible characters to life.
So what is it about a hat
that can make
a character stand out?
Well, the wonderful thing
about a hat
is that it frames the face.
So the hat complements
the makeup, the character.
Be inspired by the hat.
What are you gonna be looking
for in today's final makeups?
Not only technique and skill,
but more importantly,
a clean makeup.
All right, we started
this season with 15 of you.
Now only 10 of you are left.
So winning today's challenge
and its prize of immunity
means more than ever.
Immunity would be fantastic.
With me being in bottom looks
last challenge,
it gives me the ability
to try things
that I would never try before.
Your models
and your makeup stations
have been randomly assigned,
and on Lois's go,
I want you to grab a hat
and get to work.
You have two hours
for this Foundation Challenge.
Ready, set...
Go.
- This one.
- Shit, this is heavy.
Hey, let's see if this fits.
I grab the poofy dandelion hat.
It's fluffy.
I immediately think Dr. Seuss,
so I'm thinking cute, like,
Whoville-style character.
Yay.
Okay, let's go with that.
Let's see
how this fits you first.
Ridiculous.
I end up picking a ship hat.
I thought I would make
a pirate.
But no ship's captain
would wear a hat that looked
like a ship on his head.
It's a silly hat.
So I don't know what I'm doing.
I guess I'll just make
a dead ship's captain.
Arrgh.
- I'm gonna make you all wood.
- Okay.
A wooden boy.
I have the top hat,
and I'm really excited,
because my kids will like
my concept,
which is a dark version
of Pinocchio.
Geppetto didn't save Pinocchio,
and he's still trying
to find his father
after all these years.
This is if you stayed in
the whale longer than expected.
I am creating this asymmetric
goddess-style character
in a tin-foil dress.
I picked a really big,
busy hat.
It's full of metal
and rhinestones...
It's gonna get uncomfortable
kind of fast.
So I start gluing
crushed rhinestones on my model.
I want it to be more sparkly
and gold and silver,
and on the other side, I want it
to be more blue and purple.
Oh, gosh.
Give me your whimsical face.
My hat is this cool toy,
tinker, metal, old-school hat.
It's just obnoxious.
It's great.
A little trim-trim.
My character is, like, the
Willy Wonka of the toy world.
You look so good.
Five minutes, you guys!
You got five minutes left!
Time's up.
Brushes down.
Yay.
All right, so tell us
about what you created today.
So I wanted to go
with a smaller hat.
I just made, like, an evil
Victorian queenlike figure.
When you do a lip line,
you will find
if you just put a finger here,
and then work like that...
Hmm, oh.
...you can gauge
the movement of the actor,
and you'll get a finer line.
- It's a nice makeup.
- Thank you.
I thought, "What if
Pinocchio wasn't saved?
What if he was lost at sea?"
It's an amazing backstory.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
This section here, I think,
is the area that works best.
But if you just added
some highlights going through,
it would've made the whole thing
feel more three-dimensional.
- Yeah, I agree 100%.
- It's a very nice makeup.
Thank you very much.
So she is
the emperor's daughter,
and she has two sides
to her-- a dark side,
and then the other side,
she's more serene.
This is a huge amount of work.
I like very much the use
and understanding of color
and the transition
from one color to the other.
- It's very well done.
- Thank you.
So I've created
a nomadic warrior.
I wouldn't have used
so many pieces.
I would have concentrated
doing one thing
extremely well.
- But it is a good makeup.
- Okay.
Thanks.
Looking around the lab
is really cool,
because people went
in a lot of different directions
with this one.
The hats were so different,
and there's some
really interesting makeups.
I don't know who's gonna win.
Okay, Lois.
So how did they do today?
Everyone did
exceptionally well.
I'm really impressed.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
All right, who created
your favorite looks, then?
Rob, I thought the work
said something
about the simplicity of the hat
being translated
into a simple makeup.
- Thank you.
- Emily...
you achieved
a huge amount of work
and translated the hat
into that makeup superbly well.
Thank you.
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner this week is...
Emily.
You have an understanding
of color, form, and shape.
- Very well done.
- Thank you.
Emily, congratulations.
As the winner
of today's Foundation Challenge,
you have earned immunity
in the next Spotlight Challenge.
How's that feel?
It feels really good.
Doesn't it?
I bet.
I'm thrilled.
It's exciting because who knows
what the next challenge
could be?
They're getting more difficult.
Lois, thank you so much
for being here today.
It was a pleasure.
Oh, thank you for having me.
It's a delight to be back.
Nice work today, you guys.
I will see you tomorrow for
your next Spotlight Challenge.
- Bye.
- Thanks.
- Night-night.
We arrive out to Canyon Ranch,
and I am not much
of a nature boy.
I'm not a happy camper.
So I am looking out
for rattlesnakes, bugs,
any of God's creatures
that could kill me.
So I'm really looking forward
to going back to the lab.
Does McKenzie always
hang out in the woods?
Hey, guys.
Hi.
Welcome to Canyon Ranch.
This beautiful wooded landscape
has been featured
in a variety of television shows
and feature films,
including The Office,
Sons of Anarchy,
and my personal favorite,
True Blood.
All right, let's talk about
your next Spotlight Challenge.
Mankind continues
to be fascinated by royalty.
Now, while royals
rule over humans,
nature shows us
that this social stratum
actually exists
in other species
that represents more than half
of all known living organisms.
In fact, you may even have
a few by your feet
at this very moment...
insects.
Oh.
I'm feeling really pumped.
I'm thinking about sculpting
little appendages
and just nasty,
like, awesomeness.
Deep in these woods,
you will find
several elaborate habitats,
along with an image
of a unique insect.
Working in teams of two,
you will select
an insect and habitat
to inspire
a beautiful insect queen
and her companion.
All right, why don't you
go ahead and select a teammate?
Did you just--
What's up, brother?
Now, before
you can get started,
there is a big part
of this challenge
that I haven't told you about.
Oh.
You're not gonna be working
in the lab this week.
In fact, this entire
Spotlight Challenge
will take place
right here in the woods.
- What?
Are we camping here?
I don't really understand
what that means.
So are we sculpting
in the forest?
Models, come on out.
Oh, God.
Um...
Oh, God!
Shit.
Models, come on out.
Um...
This is new.
So obviously, this is
a nude body painting challenge.
Yeah.
Okay.
I don't body-paint.
I don't need this now.
- Rob, you all right?
- I'm all right.
All right, thank you, models.
Why don't you go ahead and take
your places in your habitats?
All right, now,
I know body-painting
is a difficult task
and requires
a very specific skill set.
So I brought in an expert
to give you some advice.
He's an award-winning
body-painter
whose work has appeared
in Playboy and Fangoria.
You may also recognize him
from season two of Face Off.
Please give a warm welcome
to Nix Herrera.
Nix knows body-painting
so well.
I'm super excited that
he's gonna be giving advice.
- How are you? Good to see you.
- Good.
All right, so tell these guys
what you've been up to lately.
I have a brush line
coming out for body-painters,
and I'm getting ready
to do some work in Hong Kong.
Well, for a lot of
special-effects makeup artists,
body-painting is way
out of their comfort zone.
So what advice do you have
for these guys
to make a beautiful
body-painting?
I think the first thing
is just remember,
you have a full body
as your canvas.
Take advantage
of this opportunity.
And insects have
a lot of colors.
Have fun with it.
As a reminder, one of your
characters must be a queen,
but the other could be anything
that you'd like, even a blend,
where your model completely
disappears into the landscape.
All right, guys, you'll have
5 1/2 hours for this challenge.
Your coaches will be by soon
to see how you're doing,
and Nix here will also check in
with you in a couple of hours
to make sure that
you're all on the right track.
All right, on "Go,"
you'll select your habitat.
Make sure
that you choose wisely,
as your final makeups
will be photographed
presiding over their kingdoms
for the judges
to see on the reveal stage.
So, Nix, would you like
to do the honors?
I would love to.
Your time starts now.
We all start running
through the woods
like crazy people looking at
the different insect habitats.
Jamie, you okay with this?
- I'm okay with the honey bee.
- Cool.
- You want ladybug?
- Let's do it.
You want to do
this, European hornet?
- Yeah, or...
- We're doing it.
Don't have time
to think about it.
- Let's just grab it.
- Okay.
Darla and me pick
the jewel beetle
because its back is metallic-y
greens and blacks and blues,
and I'm seeing pinks and oranges
on its stomach.
This could be something
really, really, like, elegant.
I'm Darla.
Our models come over,
so we meet them,
and we just start kind of
looking around at our habitat.
So we'll just paint him
not to specifically disappear,
but to match the wood.
Our concept is
to create a insect queen
using our female model
and then use our male model
to create a burned log.
I think that'll look
really nice.
Liberating walking around
in the nude, isn't it?
_
If you were to ask me
to devise a challenge
that was my worst nightmare,
it would be nude body-painting
in the forest,
'cause I've never
body-painted before...
Um...
...and I'm gonna have to explain
all this to my wife.
We're gonna make you up
in probably those colors.
We end up getting
the cuckoo wasp,
and it has a very unique
color scheme to it.
It's got greens and blues.
It also has red in the abdomen.
She's the queen
protecting the larvae.
You'll be embedded in the sand.
It's really important
that this looks good on photo,
because that's all the judges
are gonna see.
So we really have to make sure
that we plan this out perfectly.
Something I was thinking of
is painting, like, his back,
so that it's,
like, the back of her.
We choose the European hornet.
I have this concept
that I really love--
making the female the thorax
and the head of the queen
and making the male model
the abdomen.
Well, I want to blend him
right into the background.
I've seen really nice blends,
and now that I finally have
the opportunity of doing
something like that myself,
I'm gonna try my hand at it.
If he's going to be
blending into the background,
my piece is gonna be
the main focus,
so she's got to be
pretty freakin' badass.
And maybe turn
a little bit more other way.
So how I'm
gonna pose her is having
the back showing
this wonderful thorax--
just reds and blacks.
I'm not as in love with it
as I was my original concept,
but I'm still
gonna make this work.
So it's the
queen of the ladybugs
coming out of the leaves,
but then
she's giving life to you,
and it's all these larvae
returning to the earth.
I picked the ladybug
because it's an insect
that we can make read
as a ladybug easily.
I come up with this take
on the famous image
of God and Adam touching fingers
from the Sistine Chapel.
You're gonna see it,
and you're gonna know
exactly what it is.
Do you want me to
start blocking her out?
Yeah, go ahead.
I'm just gonna start
laying down the dirt tones
on him.
I'm going to take
the male model
and do the blend work
for the ground and the larvae,
and he's gonna start
blocking out for the ladybug.
I definitely got to bring
my game to this one,
because I was in bottom looks
last time,
and I really need
to step it up.
- Hello.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Laura and Anthony come over
to see what Jamie and I
are working on.
- So you're doing the honey bee?
- Yes.
We're gonna take
our female model,
and we're going to make her
into the queen bee,
and then we're gonna take
our male model
and make him into a drone.
We're gonna just really
enhance their natural curves
and bring it into the honey bee
pattern, then coloring.
Have you guys
thought about your poses?
- Yes, we have a picture.
- Oh, okay.
They are going for
the feel of a honey bee
with high contrasts
of black and yellow and white.
It's a little bit more abstract,
which is the smart way to go.
Ooh, what do y'all got?
Did y'all already
position them?
Yep.
We're going to have him
as actually a larva with sand.
So larva, as in worm?
Yeah, with some kind
of pattern on his back.
Do you have
a picture of the worm?
- No, we don't.
- You're just gonna wing it?
We were planning to.
You may want to think about
the concept a little bit more.
I don't want you going up there
and having to explain
to the judges, where they're
gonna be like, "What is that?"
Like, "Oh, that's a larva."
"What does a larva look like?"
"Oh, we didn't have pictures,
so we made it up."
Okay.
I'd rather not change
our concept right now,
but she does actually open
my eyes to other possibilities.
Could turn him into the thorax.
Or you could turn him
into the thorax.
That would be pretty clever.
The abdomen of this bug
is in stark contrast
to the upper part of the body.
I think it would be cool
if we put them together
to create one bug.
We'll start butt-to-butt.
_
Something like that.
What do you guys think?
- I think we're good.
- All right.
I like that.
It's very straightforward.
A lot of people are doing
some really creative things.
I think you guys are
the only ones that are doing
- just a straight blend.
- Yeah.
If the blend falls short,
you will probably be
the one that could be...
- Going home?
- ...going home.
I'm really
worried for Ben and Kelly,
especially after seeing
everybody else's concept.
The posing
that they're trying to do
doesn't really tell any story,
and their characters
don't interact.
I want this composition to be
really beautiful, you know?
Well, let's figure out
how those two
need to be put together
so we can keep moving.
I'm not really comfortable
completely changing
my entire paint job.
I just don't want to see
you guys in trouble.
No, I didn't either,
but--
Well, changing it halfway
through isn't helping,
so let's figure something out.
I just--
I just don't want to see
you guys in trouble.
Well, changing it
halfway through isn't helping.
Kelly's making
a queen European hornet,
while I'm working
on the camouflage
that I want to do,
and then Anthony walks in,
worried about the direction
we're going in.
And I think just shifting
a little slightly
creates a better composition.
All I can really do
is try to rotate them
around the tree
so it's still utilizing
the forms that Ben
had already painted,
but also make it
just slightly more interesting.
That is more interesting, 'cause
at least it shows some depth.
What do you think?
I have no idea, man.
We got three hours left.
I'm not completely comfortable
with moving these models
right now.
Hopefully, that doesn't bite me
in the long run.
Just looking out, guys.
I'm just a little concerned
about them getting
everything finished in time.
I don't want the members
of my team on bottom.
I don't want them going anywhere
because of a boring concept.
Thank you.
How are you brushing?
Are you patting?
I'm doing a mixture of both.
- You are?
- Patting seems to work.
We're really excited
'cause we both feel
a lot better about this concept
than the original one.
At this point,
it's just on how we execute it.
Being that neither of us
have actually body-painted,
we still are a little bit
worried about pulling this off.
Yeah, I brush it, and then
I pat what needs a little more.
So, making him a log
and leaves and branches,
that's a lot of work.
Stephanie and Darla's concept
is beautiful,
but camouflage makeups
are extremely difficult.
Have you tried
different positions,
or is this the first one
you tried?
I mean, that was the first one
that we got to that made sense.
_
Mm-hmm.
I've already got
the base all laid out,
but I know I'm not
a strong body-painter.
Laura is really great
with concept design,
so I decide to go
with Laura's suggestion.
She's down.
He's still back here doing this.
So our new concept is that
we're going to use
our male model
to create the wingspan
of the beetle.
We have leaves
that we can... use.
- Okay.
- Cool.
I get the look of it,
but I'm a little bit nervous
about the fact that
these are dark, green,
opaque leaves,
and we're trying to make
translucent wings.
- What's your plan?
- I'm doing this.
And then I'm gonna stipple
tinted latex over it
so that I can get
the translucency appearance.
Look straight, hon.
I love the honeycomb pattern.
I think that it would be
really neat
to incorporate that pattern
onto my queen.
It's risky, because
if it's not done right,
it looks ridiculous
'cause it's so geometric.
I'm nervous, but I feel like
I need to make her
more interesting,
so I'm gonna try it.
I don't body-paint,
so I'm glad we have Nix
as our guest mentor.
- Nice to meet you.
So what do you guys
have going on?
So we picked the ladybug,
and we were inspired
by classic art.
I love it.
It's a great concept.
Thank you.
With your stuff,
you're getting to the point now
where I think
it's getting a little busy.
So I think if you crispen up
a couple of spots,
so there's a little bit
of depth, so it's not so muddy.
Cool. Keep it up.
You guys are doing awesome.
- All right, thank you so much.
- Keep it up.
What are you guys
going for here?
We're gonna do a
queen bee and a drone bee.
I love the colors
that you have going on.
One thing that I found
for making the color pop
is paint it with white and then
airbrush yellow over it.
That'll give it more dimension.
- Thanks, Nix.
- Good luck, have fun.
Thank you.
All right,
so the head is her head.
- Is that right?
- Yep.
I like it, and then
for all of the shimmery,
reflective parts of it,
I'm trying to figure out a way
to get that
to translate into it,
whether or not it's airbrushing
or brighter color,
so that it has depth,
'cause right now
it's just a little--
- It's flat.
- Yeah, a little flat.
Okay.
And you have
the European hornet?
- Yeah.
- You're doing the camouflage.
I think I just want to make him
disappear as much as possible.
One of the things that's
gonna be challenging is,
because the sun
is constantly moving,
it's gonna change
the colors of your background.
Every once in a while, come back
to your spot, photograph it.
_
Yeah, I'm not gonna
keep you much longer,
'cause you have
one of the hardest ones to do.
- Kelly?
- Hey.
- Hi, how you doing?
- Great.
You are covered in body paint.
Well, it happens.
- The hair looks awesome.
- Thank you.
I think the only thing
I'm a little worried about
is how much actual paint
you have on the body.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
He's actually going to be
her wings.
Is the color from her
gonna translate into him?
Mm-hmm. We want to
use metallic airbrush colors
just to give it a shimmer.
Yeah, try to pop those colors.
- There's iridescent powders.
- Okay.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
- Yeah, thank you.
- Yeah, keep at it.
I'm gonna head out.
Good luck, guys.
Thank you.
Just give me a basic shape
to work with.
I got you.
Adam and I decided
to switch off,
so I'm going to add the
Kryolan aquacolors to the face,
while he's adding the texture
of the larva on the male model.
What color lips we going, Adam?
White for the lips.
Okay.
Have you airbrushed
the shiny spots?
I want to make sure Rob and Adam
both paint the larva correctly.
To make those larvae pop,
you have to create
a little bit more contrast,
and add shiny highlights
to make 'em feel
like some kind of larva bug.
So it's kind of a dance
back and forth
where you can see how it starts
to look more wormlike.
Mm-hmm.
Darla's still
working on the wings
that we're gonna put
with our male model,
and I continue painting
our female model,
and we're both frantic,
trying to finish our makeups.
- You doing okay?
- Yeah, I'm just tired.
It's a rough challenge.
Because we spent so much time
working on our first concept,
I don't know if we're gonna
have enough time to finish.
I'm just worried that
literally just his arms are showing,
and we're gonna
get killed for that.
- That's not good.
- Yeah.
And it would be me going home.
I'm not a body painter.
This isn't what I do.
To know that I could go home
for this is really,
really frustrating.
Literally,
just his arms are showing,
and we're gonna
get killed for that.
Okay, let me start airbrushing.
Yeah.
I think it's time to airbrush.
Because we spent so much time
working on our first concept,
I don't know if we're gonna
have enough time to finish.
But I've spent too much time
on these wings,
so it's too late to go back.
Just need some highlights.
Yeah, and then I need to paint
the fuck out of these wings.
One hour, guys.
This is Last Looks.
Good luck.
See you mañana.
Good luck, dude.
This is looking really nice.
- All right, good luck, guys.
- Thanks.
I got a lot of shit to do.
I want to go in
with some more reds and yellows,
get cream foundation
around the eyes,
and just make sure
everything is painted.
- More yellow?
- Yeah.
That line--
Yeah, right there.
It's too harsh
compared to the rest.
We don't have much to do.
We're just gonna add
a little bit more feathering.
Jamie and I feel
really good about this.
That looks cool.
I've never done hair.
I've seen my wife do it.
That's about it.
Hey, we can just do this.
So I hold my tablet up
as a mirror.
Thank God for our model
to do this to her hair,
or we would've been screwed.
We're running out of time here.
Ten minutes, everybody!
You have ten minutes left!
All right, guys, time is up!
I can't wait to see your work
onstage tomorrow.
Go get some rest.
We're gonna get some time
to work with the photographer
to make sure our models
are positioned correctly,
but unfortunately,
we don't get to see the photos,
and I'm really concerned that
our male model in underutilized.
So we're just keeping
our fingers crossed
that everything looks good,
and tomorrow at the reveal
stage, we'll find out.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
As you know, one of you
will be going home tonight.
But before we
see your creations,
say hello to our series judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
- Hello.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
- Hey, everybody.
- Hey, Ve.
And creature and concept
designer Neville Page.
- Hi, guys.
- Hey, Neville.
All right, guys, so this week,
I changed things up
a little bit on you.
Your Spotlight Challenge
was to create
two body-painted characters--
an insect queen
and a companion character
of your choice.
Your creations were photographed
in their habitats yesterday,
so let's take a look
at the final images.
I've lost two
contestants in a row,
but I still have
Adam, Logan, and Rob,
and I think all three
of these guys have the chops
to take it all the way.
So I just hope their images
stand out onstage.
This definitely looks
like a complete insect,
regal, queenlike character.
You almost can't tell
Armando's a person under there.
I think it looks fantastic.
There's definitely some issues
with the position of the models.
It looks like the wings are
coming out of the female's neck,
instead of back.
I'm really hoping
that we'll be safe.
The light isn't
hitting it right.
It looks just like a flat image,
and the earth tones
that I put on there
are really muddy-looking.
I'm really worried
about this one.
We're so happy.
Like, it just looks
the way we wanted it to,
so we hope that the judges
like it as well.
I'm starting to notice that
there needs to be more darks
in certain areas
and lights in other areas.
I'm worried about this one.
All right, judges,
why don't you take a closer look
at the photos?
This is really clever
the way they used
that second body, I think.
So smart.
The whole thing
is one big illustration.
There's a lot of
attention paid to creating
a false light source,
and it makes everything pop.
Yeah.
So I guess their second person
must be the wings,
'cause I can see the hand
on the outside.
Right.
It just feels
like it's an underutilization
of that body.
I'm really scared
because the wings may look
just a little bit too high up,
or they're gonna think
that we should've utilized
the male model more.
_
Oh, don't be too harsh.
It's my first time
body-painting.
Ugh.
This is not good.
Tell us who made your favorite
body-painting tonight
on Twitter, using #FaceOff
So I guess their second person
must be the wings.
I'm worried because
the judges are gonna think
that we should've utilized the
male model a little bit more.
I like the way
the wings are painted.
I'm not as crazy
about the body paint
on the featured performer.
You guys understand what
we're looking at there
with the second body?
I don't know what
that second body is.
Her left thigh is gorgeous.
You just don't see it
on the rest of the body.
- Yeah.
- You don't.
Unfortunately, I think
the ladybug is dreadful.
_
Wow.
This is really pretty.
Look at the striations
in her legs.
I love the additional texture
on her shoulders and chest too.
The camouflage is successful,
but it doesn't complement
the main figure.
I love the colors,
but I feel the fact that they
put that black muzzle on her
is kind of not a good idea.
All right, guys,
the judges would like to speak
with each of you to find out
more about your work.
Logan and Julian,
please step forward.
Tell me how your chosen insect
inspired you
to create this body makeup.
I observed that the abdomen
had a starkly different
color scheme
from the upper part of the body
and it would be
a good opportunity
to incorporate the second model
in that part of the bug.
We had some guidance from the
coaches, Laura in particular.
I fabricated the wings and
mainly painted the male model.
I predominately took on
the female model.
I think you were
incredibly successful.
Thank you very much.
This is a brilliant use
of the two human forms.
I love the paint job.
I love the coloration,
the iridescence in the legs,
so I have to commend you
on that.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
I think it's really
a very smart choice,
the combination of the bodies,
getting that inverse leg
with his elbow.
Really, really good.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
Logan and Julian,
if you please step back.
Thanks.
Darla and Stephanie,
you're next.
Would you please tell us
what insect you had
and who did what
on the character?
We had the jewel beetle.
I was focusing primarily
on the male model.
I fabricated the wings
and applied them
and painted them.
I did most of the painting
on the female.
I think you made a big mistake
by not camouflaging
your model's breasts.
They're accentuated, which
gives her a more human form
than it does an insect form.
The jarring thing
is really the wing placement,
because it starts to feel like
it's more connected to her head,
but the graphic design
feels good.
It's just
some missed opportunities.
Thank you.
Please step back.
All right,
let's talk to Rob and Adam.
Tell us how your insect
inspired this design.
I thought it would be
a fun play on visuals
to do the Sistine Chapel's
God and Adam.
I did the ladybug queen.
I outlined the face.
Rob came in and did
some hard lines on the face.
And then I laid the base
coat down for the larva itself.
The ladybug doesn't feel
elegant or queenlike.
I just can't get away
from the face.
It has almost a Cowardly Lion,
kabuki hybrid going on,
and that's a big problem.
So have either one of you
been to a county fair?
Not in a while.
Okay, well,
you could've fooled me,
because the face on the ladybug
looks like a little kid's
painting at a county fair.
She's a queen. You should've
made her beautiful.
This is not working for me.
Rob and Adam, please step back.
Emily and Jamie,
please come forward.
Tell me about the insect you had
and how it inspired
your makeups.
So our insect is a honey bee,
and our story
behind our queen bee
is that one of the drones
have fallen in love with her,
but she's kind of giving him--
The buzz-off?
Yeah.
And division of labor?
Emily focused mainly
on the female,
and I focused on the male.
I think you guys
did a great job.
The way that you created
an insect-y feeling
with the broken-up panels,
it's a stunning final image.
Thank you.
Emily, I have to compliment you
on this queen.
The face makeup is
one of the prettiest paint jobs
I've seen on this show.
Really well done.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Emily and Jamie,
you can step back.
Ben and Kelly, you're up.
Tell us what insect you had
and how it inspired
your creations.
We had the European hornet.
My original concept was
to integrate the second model
to be the abdomen,
but Ben was very driven
to blend the second model
into the background.
Now, Ben,
how do you think they are
as two characters together?
I don't think they go together.
I really wanted to do
a camouflage pattern.
I felt strongly about it.
I have problems
with your female.
Her face looks
very animalistic.
It looks more like a muzzle
than it is insect-looking.
Did you guys work well
together on this one?
We pretty much just worked
on our own, for the most part.
'Cause it definitely
feels like you guys were doing
two separate things that
ultimately work independently,
but as a unit,
I just find it boring.
I hate it as an overall image.
I think there's some good work
within it,
but here's the thing
about a team challenge--
it requires teamwork
to succeed.
Thank you.
You can step down.
All right, please head
back to the makeup room
while the judges deliberate.
Let's talk
about this week's makeups.
Why don't we start
with Logan and Julian?
I love the makeup.
Really good integration
of the second character,
using it as the abdomen
for the wasp.
I think Logan's paint job
was absolutely gorgeous on that.
They knocked it
out of the park for me.
The thing that impressed me
the most was the fact
that they had addressed every
square inch on both bodies.
It actually looked
like exoskeleton plating.
All right, judges, let's
move on to Darla and Stephanie.
This is in the middle for me,
because it just
didn't quite get there,
but it is not a total failure.
I actually think that the
painting on the wings is superb.
I felt that they didn't take
advantage of their second model.
I saw it as lost opportunity.
They highlighted
the whole bosom area,
which was a mistake, because
that said human right there.
All right, let's move on
to Emily and Jamie.
It's the graphic design
of this that makes it so beautiful.
I really like the
composition of their photograph,
and I like their story.
The queen is gorgeous.
And Jamie's execution
felt appropriate
for a drone worker bee.
Judges, let's move on
to Rob and Adam.
Rob's responsible for that
hard line graphic to the face,
which is the biggest problem.
And it could have been pretty,
but this was just
a hokey-dokey paint job.
All right, judges,
let's move on to Ben and Kelly.
She painted a black
muzzle on this thing,
which gave it
an animalistic look.
Ben's camouflage
is more complex.
I don't know
that I needed to see it.
He came into it adamant
that he was doing camouflage.
This was not a team challenge
for them.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
Yes, we have.
Okay, let's bring 'em back out.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about tonight's top teams.
Logan and Julian,
you did a great job
with your color palette,
and we love
the unconventional choice
to turn your two models
into one.
Emily and Jamie,
we thought you achieved
some truly beautiful forms,
particularly on the queen,
and your partnership produced
a striking final image.
All right, Glenn,
which team came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
So, Glenn,
which team came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Logan and Julian.
The way that you used
your models as one
is something
that could've gone really wrong,
but you managed it
incredibly well,
and you gave us
quite a provocative image.
- Well done.
- Thanks very much.
Thank you.
Logan and Julian,
excellent work,
but as you know,
we can only have one winner.
Glenn?
The winner of tonight's
challenge is...
Logan.
Good job, buddy.
There was a lot of great stuff
going on in your image,
but it was the queen
that was the standout.
I appreciate it.
I win the body-painting
challenge,
and I've never done it before
in my life.
If I can do a body-painting
challenge and win,
then I think I can do
just about any challenge
on the show and win.
All right, Logan,
you, Julian, Emily, Jamie,
and Darla and Stephanie
are all safe
and can head back to the makeup
room along with the coaches.
- Seriously?
- Oh, shit.
Okay.
That means the rest of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be going home.
If you'll please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom teams.
Adam and Rob,
we loved
some of the finer details,
but the broader graphic design
was flawed.
Ben and Kelly,
there were redeeming elements
of your makeups,
but your poor teamwork showed
in the image
presented to us this evening.
So who is going home tonight?
The person
going home tonight is...
Rob.
While you didn't do
anything horrific,
we had a really hard time
distinguishing any standout
contribution of yours
in these creations.
Okay.
Rob, I'm so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
That means Adam, Kelly, and Ben,
you guys are all safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Rob, I know you guys are better
than what you presented us,
so I really look forward to
seeing what you come up with
in the future,
and good luck, darling.
Thank you so much.
Rob, it's been so great
having you here with us,
but if you'd please
head back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thanks, guys,
really appreciate it.
Good luck, Rob.
Yeah, I'm a little surprised.
You know, for being
my first body-paint,
I think it was a great job.
- Oh!
- No, Rob.
- What?
- Yeah.
_
My family is my life,
and it's hard
because I wanted to win it
for them,
but they're gonna be really
proud of me for what I did.
It's been a blast.
I've done a lot of things
I'm happy with.
I've met a lot of great people,
and I don't regret a thing.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net