Previously on Face Off...
All right, Glenn,
who is moving forward?
Emily.
Darla.
Logan.
Congratulations.
But your night isn't over yet.
- Oh, no.
- We're raising the bar on you.
Ai-yi-yi.
We just went
through hell and back.
What are we doing?
Why are we still onstage?
Find out who wins...
- Oh, my God.
- ...right now.
This is crazy.
Welcome to the Face Off finale.
This season's finale is going
to be the most difficult one yet.
Oh, no.
You guys have these amazing
champions in your corner,
so we're raising
the bar on you.
In fact, it is so tough,
that we've brought back
the entire eliminated cast
to help you.
- Seriously?
- What?
Guys, come on out.
- Jamie.
Jamie.
Can I just go hug?
- That's a trip.
- Oh, my God.
I'm so happy to see Jamie.
I'm so happy to see
everyone onstage.
Before I tell you more,
why don't we get you guys
some new teammates.
Darla, you get first pick.
I pick Rob.
Emily, you're next.
Adam.
- Logan.
- Julian.
Anthony.
Jamie, come on down.
Ben.
Stephanie.
Regina.
So cute.
Gregory.
Daniel.
Get over here,
you sculpting wizard.
Kelly, come on.
Well...
Good seeing you, man.
Okay, you have your teams,
and you know the finale
is going to be really tough.
But I didn't tell you why.
It's because each team will be
creating four characters.
Holy shit.
Wow.
Okay.
That is a massive amount of work
to do in a short period of time.
So it might be
a little difficult
to fall asleep tonight.
Okay.
That's all that I'm gonna
give you for now.
No.
That's not enough.
I'll tell you everything else
tomorrow at the lab.
Have a good night.
- Hi, Emily.
- Emily, my Em.
Oh, my God.
It's my mom.
I'm used to
talking to her every day.
It's the first time
I've ever been away from her
and my family.
Are you eating well?
Yes.
Are you sleeping well?
Yes, I'm sleeping fine.
This whole competition
just has been about them
and me missing them,
and it's been hard.
It's weird,
'cause I can only see
this much of your face,
but that's okay.
There it is.
It's my boyfriend, Alex.
And I am so excited to see him.
It means the world,
and it gives me that extra push
and motivation.
Oh, my gosh,
it's so great to see you.
I miss you.
I miss you so much,
and I can't wait to see you.
It's not home without you.
Are you leaking?
No.
My wife, Sarah,
is there on-screen,
and it's great to see her face.
I love this stuff.
I know it makes you happy.
I am so proud of you.
For you to go this far
is amazing.
I can't wait to see
what you've done.
I've got the most incredibly
supportive wife in the world.
And I just want to show her
what I can do.
I miss you so much.
I'll see you real soon.
Just keep doing your thing,
though.
You got this.
Okay.
Bye, baby.
Bye.
All right, I love you guys.
We love you, we love you,
we love you.
All right, bye, guys.
To see them and see how happy
and supportive they are
and how proud they are of me
is just--
it's the extra boost
that I need for this finale.
Ooh.
Oh, my God.
Cool.
So we walk into the lab,
and I notice they
put a red carpet down for me.
And I'm just--
I love it.
Ooh.
Ooh, fancy.
- Oh, God.
- Good morning, everybody.
Morning.
It's time to end the suspense.
Today's box office is dominated
by blockbuster franchises
that extend well
beyond the screen
into memorabilia,
amusement park rides,
and video games.
But what do the biggest of them
all have in common?
Films like
Star Wars, The Avengers,
and Guardians of the Galaxy
have an incredible team
of characters
who band together
to take on the bad guys,
and that is your
final Spotlight Challenge.
You're going to create a team
of four characters
that could star
in a new film franchise.
- All right.
- Oh, my gosh.
But before you
can create your characters,
your films are gonna
need a genre and a title.
So let's start with the genre.
- Emily.
- Oh, God.
Please choose one
of the three monitors.
- Two.
- All right.
What's behind number two?
Post-apocalyptic.
Logan.
Three.
Sci-fi.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
There you go.
And Darla.
I guess I'll take one.
Fantasy.
Yes.
That's awesome.
Okay, you've got your genres.
Now you'll each be coming up
with your own movie title.
You've got one minute to choose
up to ten words
from this board.
Now, you don't have to use
every word that you choose.
But when I call time,
you'll only have five minutes
to come to a consensus
with your teammates
on the new title.
Your minute starts now.
Paradise, reckoning.
- Destruction.
- Attack.
Warriors. Up, up.
My team's calling out words
at me.
- Fortress.
- Invaders.
Destroyers, attack.
You know, we can be
good guys too.
Oh, okay.
I grab what I think I need,
but it's frantic.
- Destiny and realm.
- Destiny.
Destiny.
I don't know where it is.
- Emily, grab empire.
- What?
- Empire.
- Ten seconds.
Empire.
Oh!
Five, four, three
Galaxy, where's galaxy?
It's at the end.
- Time's up.
- Okay.
Oh, my God.
All right, gentlemen,
let's start with--
it doesn't need to be big.
Just take a word.
Nuclear paradise.
Nuclear reckoning.
When I ran up,
this is what I grabbed.
Ooh.
Cosmos warriors.
Journey to destruction.
Taking.
You said, "Taking Paradise."
Beyond the spirits of Eden,
instead of gates.
There, that's it;
that's our winner.
Okay, guys, your time is up.
I need your new film titles.
Darla.
- Ooh.
- The Spirits of Eden.
Nice.
Emily.
Paradise Reckoning.
Okay.
And Logan.
The.
Fortress.
Very cool.
Well, these are
some truly unique titles,
and I can't wait to see
how your characters turn out.
And I know some other people
that are gonna be excited
to see them as well,
the ones who buy the tickets
to these huge blockbusters,
the public.
What?
We have invited people to a VIP,
after-hours experience
where your characters
will be on display
at Universal Studios
Hollywood theme park.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
What?
They'll check out your work
and vote for their favorite.
And I'll share that result
with the judges
before they choose
this season's winner.
Oh, my God.
All right, we'll
see you guys in a few days
at Universal Studios.
Good luck.
Let's draw out
four silhouettes.
Do we want
to go animal or human?
Good question.
We need to start with
their origination.
What about they were all
science experiments in a lab,
and that's the same fortress.
- Yeah.
- Right.
Almost like the
island of Moreau.
I like that a lot.
The backstory is inspired
by The Island of Dr. Moreau.
They'll all be animals
that were tested on
and have evolved into
intelligent versions
of those animals.
I like the idea
of the lizard soldier.
Okay.
The commander is going to be
an iguana
who's a big and imposing leader.
The second character
is going to be an armadillo.
They'll be the weapons expert.
Third, we have the mechanic
of the ship.
What's another animal?
One that doesn't care
for its own hygiene.
Okay.
I decide she's going to be
the mechanic skunk
that needs to quarantine herself
inside a cryo-tube
because she stinks.
And the last character will be
a hammerhead shark assassin.
And that's definitely
what we're gonna do here.
Okay.
So what are you thinking, girl?
All right.
I definitely want to
incorporate the elements.
The idea is that they
can control these elements.
The Spirits of Eden is a movie
about four elemental spirits
who band together
to fight off evil
after Adam and Eve
are cast out of the Garden.
So we have three girls
and one guy.
Yeah.
For air, like, the satyrs,
which are the ones with, like,
the ram horns and,
like, the bottom half's like
is, like, the hooves.
Right.
They play
that flute-type thing.
The air spirit is part faun
and part woodwind instrument.
It would be interesting
to have...
Merman.
A merman.
'Cause they're gonna expect
a mermaid.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
For the water spirit,
I want to do a merman
and make him
very strong and rugged.
- For the fire one...
- Yes.
I'm wondering if it
would look cool to actually do,
like, sculpted flames.
The fire spirit
has a stone torso
with flames around her face.
The costume would be the tree,
and then the worm--
then you could actually
put her arm in the worm,
and you could actually
do her arm.
Oh, my God.
Our earth spirit
is going to be a worm
wrapped around
a trunk of a tree.
I'm really happy with the way
my team is working together,
and I'm really excited about the
direction that this is headed.
I can incorporate flowers
that she would push out,
and they would grow as the
judges came up and looked at it.
This is why I wanted him.
I want to have a metal
one, a glass one, a wood one,
and a leather.
Go, go, go.
Yeah, that one.
Paradise Reckoning
is a post-apocalyptic take
of The Wizard of Oz.
We're gonna need a lot of clay.
After a nuclear disaster,
four characters start mutating
from the radiation
into the elements
that they were injured in.
I'm sculpting
the last character,
who was in a car accident.
He's got shards of glass
embedded into his chest.
Jamie is blocking out
the wood character,
who was in an explosion
where he flew into
a pile of pallets.
Adam's starting to
fabricate the armor
for the metal character,
who is a member
of the bomb squad.
And Regina and Kelly are working
on the leather character.
She is the assassin,
and she's using the leather
to patch and protect herself.
The sculpts that we're
getting done today
cannot be in the mold room
later than two hours.
Yep.
- Hey.
- Hey, Laura.
Ooh, already,
you're off and running.
Yep.
- There he is.
- Hey, guys.
Rayce shows up,
and I start filling him in
on my concept.
Yeah, I like it.
And I start sculpting
the hammerhead face.
I put Ben on the skunk face.
I put Gregory
on the armadillo face,
Julian on the lizard face,
and Alan on the lizard cowl.
Today's all about making sure
everybody is on the same page
with what the characters
are supposed to look like.
I want to see the character
that they would sculpt
anatomically first
and replace the flesh
with metal.
Cool.
- Hi.
- Hello.
What's up?
So I have fantasy.
I heard, my favorite genre.
It's gonna be a worm.
But keeping the face beautiful
is what's gonna
make it attractive.
Attractive female face
on top of a worm body?
So we explain
our concept to Laura,
and her initial reaction
is not good.
- This is an attractive look?
- Yeah, yeah.
It'll be definitely--
I mean, not that.
But, I mean, it will be.
As expected, Darla
is doing something beautiful.
But that worm,
I'm not sure that's
a very attractive character.
It's getting frustrating
because I thought the concept
was already nailed down.
You're always talking
about doing something
they've never seen before.
That's true.
That's definitely something
they've never seen before.
You know, like, I'm trying
to think outside the box.
This is not the challenge
to be wasting time,
and I'm getting scared.
There's so much work
going on with that worm.
It's the first day
of the finale challenge,
and Laura's concerned about some
of my decisions, conceptually.
She doesn't like the tree
with the worm idea
for the earth spirit.
You can put vines.
You can put, like,
wood textures.
You can put
all these wonderful things.
I was originally thinking
about doing sort of,
like, an earth goddess
and having vines
wrapping down her legs.
That would totally fit.
Thankfully, our concept
finally comes together.
It's a beautiful woman
wearing a tree trunk dress.
And the mushrooms
growing out of her
create a really nice silhouette.
- Is that mushrooms?
- Yeah.
It's those mushrooms
that grow sideways out of trees.
- Yeah.
- Cool.
- I like this.
Wow.
Hello, everybody.
- Hey, Mr. Westmore.
- Hey.
- I have sci-fi.
- Mm-hmm.
And Alan and Julian are both
working on the ship's commander.
I would almost like to see,
in this little ridge that
you have going like that,
go on and bring it on down
'cause it just adds
another dimension to it.
It takes it away
from a human form.
This is going to be
an armadillo.
You know, an armadillo
has all the battle armor.
Don't cut yourself short here.
If your armor isn't going
to come this far forward,
you'd better take it
a little further back,
just to protect yourself.
Okay.
- This is your skunk here?
- This is the skunk.
Take your forehead up
and make this all one piece.
Otherwise, you'd have
to put on eyebrow blenders
to get rid of the eyebrows.
Absolutely.
Our genre's
post-apocalyptic.
Because there's radiation,
their accidents started
to fuse into them,
and then they started
to build armor.
This one had the wood started
to be infused into his chest.
What's important with
this is gonna be the paint job.
Keep the wood lighter
so it looks like
it's really a whole pileup
of the wood you have going on.
This is the metal character.
The suit saved his life,
so he doesn't take it off.
But he repairs it.
You could have a
burn on him or something
to be able to show
that a bomb went off.
Yeah.
So each of my characters
represents one
of the four elements.
Mm-hmm.
The first character
is the water element.
Being water,
it's flowing, and it's soft.
So you want to keep
the face soft
and not get so angular.
Okay.
This is the earth character,
which hasn't been started yet
'cause it took a while
to kind of hone in on.
Wow.
Very, very interesting.
But essentially,
it's going to be
a fabricated tree structure
coming up into
that mushroom growth.
You want to make sure you kind
of get these into the face,
as opposed
to just doing a pretty face
and having the rest--
it becomes a costume then.
Absolutely.
The last character
is our fire character.
The idea was sculpting blue
and white flames flowing up,
like, her neck
and into her face.
You're talking
about blue and white.
You're talking about
a gas fire.
I would get a little bit
of red in there.
This could be all red
that's behind her.
Okay.
Good luck to all three teams.
- Thank you.
Thanks.
Keep leading these troops.
I like where you guys
are going.
Have fun.
See you, guys.
- See you.
- Bye, guys.
- Jamie.
- What's up?
Can you take this to mold?
I finish all the pieces
for the glass character.
But we're running out of time,
so I grab everyone,
and we're all working together
to mold everything
at the same time.
And we're ahead of schedule,
so I feel good.
That's time, everybody.
I should just
slow everyone down.
It's day two.
We have ten hours
in the lab today.
Do you want me
to finish this up
or jump on the cowl?
We got to pick up the pace
a little bit.
My plan today is to make
each of these sculpts cohesive.
So I'm gonna be incorporating
a metallic design
for the characters,
because each
of these characters,
at some point had
repeated tests done
on certain areas of their body.
So we have a lot to do.
I'm gonna start
on the hammerhead.
All right.
My team's finishing
their sculptures
while I start working on
the face
for the glass character.
The center of his face
is exposed
with the glass around it,
so I'm going to make
rubber glass,
which is a silicone material
that looks like glass.
Mix ratio is 3a 1b.
But I am awful at math.
I'm gonna go with 20 grams.
And if you mess up the ratios,
then you won't get
the end results.
No, what?
Two, four, six.
In school, it's like,
"Oh, you'll use this
in the real world."
No, we won't.
I'm so bad at all of this.
It's a mess.
Six, seven, eight, nine.
So 960 in total.
I need a calculator.
I hope I got the ratios right.
Stephanie is working on the
chest piece for the air spirit,
and it looks fantastic.
Rob has to fabricate
the entire tree trunk dress
for the earth spirit.
And Daniel is going to mold
the fire spirit torso
while Anthony
jumps on to the cowl
for the earth spirit.
I start sculpting the face
for the fire spirit,
and I'm a little worried
about the sculpted flames
not reading correctly.
But I'm confident that I can
really represent the fire
without trying
to go super literal.
Kind of, like,
building up the flames
so they're
a little more stylized.
Yeah.
Oh.
That's time, everybody.
It's day three of the finale,
and we have 9 1/2 hours
in the lab today.
All right, plan of attack.
My team is hard at work
fabricating
and refining the sculpts.
And then I have to finish
a sculpt
on the fire spirit face,
which because of the flames
is gonna be really complicated.
So this is just a mess.
I'm working on the face
for the glass character.
But the glass is not sticking,
and it's eating up
a lot of time.
I'm feeling very, very nervous.
I have too much to do.
This is the most important part
of my character.
It has to be right.
What are you planning
on doing today yourself?
- Just the glass.
- Okay.
I'm getting really frustrated,
because we have a lot to do.
But I'm going to take my time
and make sure
this is done right.
Time is ticking down.
I'm feeling pretty good
at this point.
Everybody's trying
their hardest.
But there's a lot of fabrication
that still needs to be done.
I'm well into my day of painting
these cowls and face pieces,
and I decide to check
on Gregory's progress.
These are gonna have a buckle
here and a buckle here.
I like your innovation,
but I'm absolutely serious
when I say this type
of stuff does not matter.
I realize that he's not
prioritizing very well.
If we don't get this shit--
this thing solid
from an appearance standpoint,
the superficial shit, wearable,
I'm boned.
Now I'm really freaking out
because I thought
everything was under control.
But we're actually way behind.
This could be really bad.
I like your innovation,
but I'm absolutely serious
when I say this type
of stuff does not matter.
It's day three
of our finale challenge,
and the armadillo shell
is behind schedule.
It's cool, but we can
gaff tape this together.
And you would've saved yourself
whatever time it took you
to cut this and shape it
and put it on.
I explained very briefly
to Gregory what I need.
And I think he understands
what's on the line here,
especially for me.
My motto for Face Off has been
no time for hot glue,
only enough time for tape.
This is the finale,
and the pace
needs to be kept up.
You can pull it just as tight
around her as you want.
But it's gonna be comfortable
because there's padding
all the way around.
Okay.
- Good luck.
- Bye, Laura.
- Have fun.
- Okay, thank you.
- See you, Logan.
- See you, bro.
You're kicking ass.
Just keep doing it.
Thanks, man.
The olive?
Huh.
It's getting
towards the end of the day,
and the shirt for the earth
spirit is coming together.
And the skirt
is more or less done.
Both of the staffs are finished.
And the face
for the fire spirit
has been molded
and cleaned out.
- Can you go grab some stencils?
- Yes.
Thank you.
Time, everyone.
Everything's coming
together really well.
I feel like I'm really
set up for application.
Luckily, I've got four
amazing artists to help me out.
Oh, my God. Here we go.
Nice outfit.
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab,
one hour of Last Looks.
Team Logan.
This is also our
last day of Face Off.
It's gonna be crazy.
How are you feeling?
My role today is to teach him
how to manage his team
and just make sure
that he's not forgetting
any important steps.
So you know who's gonna
be applying what?
- You got that all planned out?
- No.
Hello.
So you are the wood guy.
We have a lot to do today.
But we have a strong team,
and we're ready to work.
I can't believe it's all over.
Like, this is it.
Right away, I start working
on the wood character,
applying the cowl and face.
Because the leather character
has a lot going on,
Regina and Kelly are gonna share
the responsibility
of applying these pieces.
Adam's working
on the metal character
while Jamie's applying the chest
for the glass character.
I don't know how
this is gonna work out.
I'm born.
My team's working
on the earth, water,
and wind spirits
while I start to apply
the fire spirit character
and paint
all the stone texture.
But I still need to make sure
that every single character
ends up as a fully-finished,
beautiful makeup.
Darla.
- Yeah, that's looking great.
- Okay.
Darla and Emily
both want this really bad.
And they seem like they've
set themselves up for success.
Look out,
armadillo coming through.
Ben is on the skunk.
Julian moves on
to the iguana commander.
Alan finishes the fabrication
on the shell.
Gregory is working
on the hammerhead
while I'm focusing
on the armadillo face
plus bouncing around
between each character,
making sure
they're all on the same page.
Don't cut it off.
I'm starting to see
these things come together.
And I really feel like Logan
has got something special.
I feel like he could do this.
He could be the new champion.
I'm really out
of my comfort zone,
painting like this.
I look over at Adam's character,
and it's too pink.
- What do you want to do?
- I want to change it.
- Entirely?
- Yeah.
I want it to be more rust color,
more reds, yellows, oranges.
So I go in,
and I start just micromanaging.
I want them to be
in the flesh tone range.
But it's not supposed
to look like super skin tone.
Okay.
Adam's not happy about that,
but I don't have time
to think about his feelings.
This is the finale.
Everything needs to be perfect.
I'm losing my mind.
Oh, welcome.
Welcome to Face Off.
Daniel!
Get me some more moss.
Hey, guys.
No.
You have one hour left.
This is Last Looks.
- Oh, my God.
- Good luck, everybody.
To finish the fire character,
I go through and add
a little bit
of the Kryolan black eye shadow
along her hairline,
just to give it depth
and really make it pop.
Jamie, I got to figure
something out for this,
'cause this is not working out.
I'm really nervous right now,
because there's a lot
still to do.
We have a lot more to paint.
Put some fabric over it.
What kind of fabric?
Should I give him, like,
a vest or, like, a harness?
I just got to work
as fast as I can.
Are we gonna put the tail on?
The skunk tail
becomes a priority.
- It's just gonna hang loose.
- That's fine.
That's better than too heavy.
It's got me concerned.
I know it can't go on
at the weight it is.
We'll tuck the skunk tail
into her belt,
let it hang limp.
That will achieve
the silhouette.
15 minutes, everyone.
Oh, my gosh.
Pull.
Oh, my God, Jamie.
That's time, everybody.
Hugs all around.
When Last Looks
is up, I'm nervous.
I didn't get a chance
to get everything painted
the way I wanted,
but I'm hoping for the best.
You are gonna be up here.
Step back a little bit.
Move forward.
Hey, everyone.
How you doing tonight?
Yeah.
Welcome to the Face Off finale.
Okay, let's do this.
Whoo-hoo.
There's a lot of people.
This is cool.
So cool.
- Great.
- Wow.
_
Oh, I didn't know they're here.
The judges are here.
- Wow.
- This is really cool.
That's really great.
It's silicone glued on
to a single piece of clear.
Those are Dorothy's shoes.
This is interesting
'cause they sculpted
what looks to be leather.
Like, it's almost
like somebody else's skin.
- Right.
- Cool.
_
Well, that's actually
The Cowardly Lion.
It's definitely
a success in terms
of integrating
their fabricated pieces
with the wardrobe.
It seems to have
an element of Mad Max.
Yeah?
I don't understand
what we're looking at,
but it looks pretty cool.
The set looks amazing.
And then all the characters
look incredible.
And this is our work out there.
And now people
are reacting to it,
and it's really cool.
I can't believe
this is happening.
They look beautiful.
I love the
scrolling on the face.
It's great.
Oh.
- This chest piece is amazing.
- It really is.
And I love the
asymmetry of this.
Everything is
detailed and intricate.
Really pretty
little beauty makeup on,
which is real subtle.
It conveys the idea.
I mean, it's so hard
to indicate flame.
- I mean, after all.
- It's pretty.
I like how her lip color
even matches the green in her.
Oh.
A lot of thought
must've gone into making
that flower thing happen.
But the thing is,
it's not as if they invested
all that time in this
and shortchanged the makeup.
Do you like how they came out?
Yeah.
I'm so happy.
I'm just so happy right now.
These characters
have come to life.
And to see them in the scene
exactly how I imagined them,
it's so incredible.
I love this.
It reminds me of one
of my things from Star Trek.
Oh, my gosh.
_
Oh, God.
I like that a lot,
especially the nose
and the face.
Cute.
- It is cute.
- Yeah.
All these tones
are so beautiful,
these browns
and taupe-y greens.
It's really pretty.
Why does she have a tool belt?
Because she's actually
the mechanic too.
Oh.
They definitely have
a team theme going here.
I like the tuft of fur coming
out the bottom of the tail.
That's great.
And this is Commander Talon.
He's the leader of the group.
Wow, this is quite beautiful.
It has really nice details
happening on the side.
These characters
are incredible.
And I'm having a blast.
I see smiles from the audience.
And that's a win on its own.
I think this was definitely
my favorite
'cause I feel like
it's so much more intricate.
I like The Fortress. I
thought it was beautiful.
It's got a great story to it.
Just really well done.
My favorite movie
is Paradise Reckoning.
I kind of, like, related
to those characters a lot.
It's time for
the audience to leave,
and I'm so scared.
$100,000, a car,
and everything else
is depending on this moment.
It's nerve-racking 'cause
now this is the moment of truth.
Tell us who made your favorite
new film franchise team tonight
on Twitter using #FaceOff
All right, judges,
so what do you think
of the new franchise film stars
you saw tonight?
I have personally
department headed
five mega-movie franchises.
And I got to tell you,
I think you guys
did an amazing job tonight.
Really, really exceptional,
kids.
Nice work, everybody.
Okay, now, there is a lot on
the line tonight for you guys.
The winner will receive
a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand-new 2015 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
All right, guys,
the judges would like to hear
from each of you
before choosing
this season's winner.
Logan, you're up first.
Please step forward.
What's up?
Logan, tell us about your
sci-fi feature, The Fortress.
They were all,
at one point, lab experiments,
and they took over
the SS Moreau.
Now they travel
throughout the solar system,
trying to stop other labs
from doing the same thing.
I think you guys
did a great job.
It's an extraordinarily
cohesive group.
You did it with the biomechanic,
cybernetic enhancements.
And I like the fact
that you went through
and personalized
each with that element.
I also love Mako's face.
The way that you worked those
subtle shapes over the eyes,
it just all works together.
Thank you very much.
I love your skunk character
because there's
some really subtle,
beautiful paint
on this character.
This could be a really fun movie
to watch.
Maybe one day it will be.
You never know.
There's a few things
I want to compliment you on.
One of them is creating
characters that actors
are gonna be inspired
to partake in.
And you've very much succeeded
in that area.
Thank you.
Thank you very much, Logan.
All right, Emily, you're next.
Would you please tell
us about your characters
in Paradise Reckoning?
After a nuclear
conflict, the world was ending.
And it was split up into mutants
because of all the radiation.
So in this sterile world,
they find a pure human baby.
And the baby
brings them all together.
And it's a spin
on The Wizard of Oz.
Every single one
of these characters
has an amazing paint job
on them.
I especially love
her bodice thing.
I actually thought it looked
like patchwork skin to me.
Very impressive.
- Good work, sweetie.
- Thank you.
This is so ambitious
and adventurous.
And as a movie franchise,
this group,
they feel very much
like they are associated,
from a creative standpoint.
I think that you
were very successful
in creating a lot
of very intelligent pieces.
I also love Shard's
broken windshield on his chest.
It really looks exactly
like a broken windshield.
Thank you.
Thank you, Emily.
Darla, you're up.
- Hi, Darla.
- Hi.
Tell us about
The Spirits of Eden.
After Adam and Eve
were banished
from the Garden of Eden,
evil started to take over.
And so the four
raw elements--
earth, wind, fire,
and water--
had to band together
to fight off the evil.
I think that you absolutely
nailed the genre of fantasy.
Thank you.
One of the things
that we all noticed
was the high-resolution
finesse of detail
on the earth element.
This is a beautiful,
beautiful lineup.
Thank you.
With your wind character,
the body piece is amazing.
It is probably my favorite piece
of wardrobe sculpture
I've seen on the show.
And the horns are a shape
that I have never seen.
The idea is that she
herself is a wind instrument.
- That makes it even better.
- Ooh, I got the chills.
I think you did an excellent
job with your characters.
You've created prosthetics
that blend right
into the middle of their faces.
You did such a great job.
Thank you all so much.
- Thank you, Darla.
- Thank you.
It's time for you all to head
backstage
while the judges decide
who will become
this season's champion.
All right, before we begin,
I should let you know
which team the public chose
as their favorite.
And that would be
Darla's characters
from The Spirits of Eden.
- Hmm.
- Awesome.
So you can take
that into consideration
when making
your final decision tonight.
Let's get into this.
Why don't we start with Logan?
They were playful
and cohesive as a team.
I absolutely agree.
I mean, each one of them
had a unique character
that was immediately visible.
I love the hammerhead
shark character.
I think that was fantastic,
particularly in terms
of hiding the eyes.
The iguana character
had amazing primary
and sub form in the sculpture.
I did love that paint job
on that skunk.
I thought it was really
beautifully done.
Okay, let's move on to Emily.
Just beautiful
control with paint.
She just picks out some
of the most beautiful palettes
to paint with.
That wooden guy,
that was gorgeous.
I liked how realistic it was.
I think Emily
is loaded with raw talent.
Shard had that beautiful
chest piece,
which is all silicone
on a clear piece of plastic.
It immediately read
as a broken windshield.
All right,
that leaves us with Darla.
Well, she came out with four
beautifully-rendered makeups,
absolutely exquisite
on those women.
Blend right in the middle
of their faces.
Really beautifully done.
And the one that really
is a standout character
is the elemental wind.
The genius of doing the holes
in the horns
and the perforations
in the chest piece
as an indication of
some other acoustic element,
that's some high-level thinking.
Absolutely awe-inspiring.
All right,
judges, big decision.
Are you ready to crown
a new champion
and our first
two-time champion?
I think we are.
Let's do this.
All right, guys, one of you
is about to become
our new champion.
And one of our champion coaches
is about to become
our first two-time champion.
So good luck to all of you.
All right, Glenn,
tell us about tonight's makeups.
Logan, the fun factor
of your characters
really drove home the
team aspect of this challenge.
And the paint work on several
of them was exceptional.
Emily, you put on a really wild
display of creativity tonight,
and they all clearly
went together.
But each was also
distinctly different,
which is an impressive feat.
Darla, you gave us an array
of fantasy characters
that read superbly from afar.
But each of them also had
unique and gorgeous detail
when we got up close.
All right, Glenn,
who is the winner of Face Off?
The winner of Face Off is...
All right, Glenn,
who is the winner of Face Off?
The winner of Face Off is...
Darla.
Congratulations, you
are the new Face Off champion.
This is--
this is crazy.
That's like--
it's crazy.
I'm so excited,
and I'm so proud.
I'm so happy.
I can't really keep it together.
I'm very happy for Darla.
Of course, I'm bummed.
But I think it motivates me
to do better.
I've definitely
found my passion.
I'm proud of everything
that I've accomplished.
This competition's definitely
given me the confidence
to just make stuff.
And, of course, that means
that huge congratulations
are in order to Laura as well.
You are the first-ever repeat
champion of Face Off.
How about that?
I'm very excited,
because winning Face Off
is a life-changing experience,
and I'm overwhelmed with pride
that I accomplished it twice.
It's an exhilarating feeling,
and I'm glad.
I'm so honored.
Come on up here and celebrate.
Come on, judges too.
Come on.
Congratulations.
You're so good at this.
Thank you.
It was a great
experience for everybody.
But it doesn't seem right,
just one person winning this,
when we all are so influential.
- You're still gonna cry?
- Yes.
I'm so grateful to Laura.
I've grown so much as an artist.
This has been a really crazy,
crazy ride,
and I can't wait to see
what's next.
Thank you all at home
for watching us tonight.
Join us again in July
for another exciting new season.
Have a good night.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net