I am absolutely thrilled.
It's very problematic.
On a scale of one to
ten in the creepiness,
he is a 15 1/2.
Thank you.
Previously on Face Off...
Ben's futuristic villain
brought him his second win.
But Jamie was eliminated,
leaving Team Anthony
with just two artists.
Now eight artists remain,
and tonight,
they strive to win two
incredibly colorful challenges.
Please give a warm welcome
to Gabriela Isler.
This is the best challenge.
Oh, what?
It's the crappiest situation
you can be in right now.
_
The forms are just stunning.
In the end, only one
will win a VIP trip from
Kryolan Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand-new 2015 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
This is Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
_
You'll be fine
in the next challenge.
Yeah, I'll just--
I'll bounce back this time.
It was just not good for me
last challenge.
I don't want to be on the bottom
continuously.
I want to show the judges
that I have cool ideas
and the technical skills
to do it.
You'll be fine.
I'm thrilled
I didn't get sent home,
'cause now I can redeem myself
with a better makeup this time.
This competition
is getting way harder now,
so I got to keep on trucking
if I want to win.
- This is so pretty.
- Dolphins.
We're in Long Beach.
The sand's nice,
and we see dolphins,
but I have no idea
what we're doing.
I hope we don't have
to run in the sand.
We walk up to McKenzie,
and she's standing
near a bunch of models.
What's next to them?
And there's
tables set up with bowls,
but I can't see what's in them.
I don't see any makeup kits.
I'm not entirely sure
what's happening.
All right.
Hey, everybody.
Hello.
Today's Foundation Challenge
is gonna be a blast.
It's inspired by an ancient
Hindu religious festival
celebrated all over the world
as winter ends
and spring emerges
with its abundance
of beautiful colors,
the Holi Festival.
Yes!
I immediately know
what we're doing.
This is gonna be so cool.
Commonly referred to
as the Festival of Colors,
people gather with friends
in city streets,
religious temples,
and even beaches like this
to celebrate
by hurling colored Holi powder
at each other
in a chaotic spectacle of color.
So with immunity
on the line today...
Oh, my goodness.
...your Foundation Challenge
is to create your own colorful
and beautiful makeup
that represents spring.
However, you will not have
your makeup kits, brushes,
or fabrication materials
for this challenge.
You can only use your hands.
There's only eight artists left,
so immunity
is extremely important,
but now we're not even gonna
get to use any brushes.
Talk about holy shit.
Now, the workstations
each have seven different colors
of Holi powder,
and you'll have two hours
for this challenge.
On my go, I want you to select
a model and get started.
You guys ready?
Oh, God.
Go!
McKenzie says go,
and I feel like
I'm running for my life.
Hi.
What's up, dude?
This is for not winning
the last challenge.
This is more difficult
than I'd expected.
The powder keeps blowing
in the wind
and back into our faces.
But it's sticking,
and it's fun.
I'm going for an Indian goddess.
I want to represent
the warmth inside her
that's pushing out
all of this cold.
So I'm using warms in the middle
and fading it out to purples,
and I think it makes her
like a goddess.
She's looking cool.
The phoenix symbolizes
rising from the ashes,
the dead of winter
coming into spring.
So he's gonna be a phoenix.
I'm gonna do
a henna pattern to it.
Ooh, that's so pretty.
I wipe my finger,
and I start cleaning the pathway
for my pattern,
and it's working beautifully.
Is this wet?
I see what you're doing.
I'm going for a sunset
on a beach...
That's the sun.
...with a palm tree
and a river.
These are all spring things
to me.
I'm trying to make leaves.
I don't necessarily have, like,
a specific character concept,
but I'm pulling
color inspiration
from sunsets and sunrises.
So I'm trying
to do some nice blending,
and then I dip Matt's fingers
in the orange powder
to create this feeling
of energy coming into the world.
That's kind of cool.
I want to show the battle
between winter and spring,
so I'm doing a lot
of bright spring colors
bleeding into the blues
and purples
to convey a story through colors
instead of, like,
a literal design.
Sweet.
I have no concept at all.
I'm just going with
the colors of spring
and letting it
go abstract and crazy.
I'm having so much fun
with this challenge.
Ugh!
Never seen Ben look so happy.
He always looks angry,
except for now.
I'm putting angel wings
on your back.
I'm thinking that maybe she's
the angel of spring,
and she floats around,
and she's just
this heavenly being.
Bam.
15 minutes, guys.
Time's up.
Hands and powder down.
All right.
Now, I'm sure you're wondering
who's gonna judge
this challenge.
Well, I have a big surprise
for you.
Your coaches will be the ones
judging this challenge
and awarding
one of you immunity.
Holy crap.
Now, I'm gonna separate
you guys from your makeup,
so it's gonna be a blind pick
based solely on the work
in front of them.
So why don't you guys
go ahead and step to the side,
and I'll bring in the coaches.
Welcome, coaches.
- Hello.
- Hi, McKenzie.
Ready to check out
some makeups?
- Oh, yeah.
- Absolutely.
I like the negative space,
how they put on all the color
and they took away
for the details.
Cool thing I really like,
whoever did this
put down their base tones
and came with, like,
a wet finger
to create all the streaking.
Yet there's no green
or anything in it.
They really played up the whole
Hindu, Indian feel of it.
Love the lotus flower.
The fingers
are very, very bright,
as if they're radiating
some sort of energy.
I think the face
is absolutely beautiful.
You know, the contours
are coming through.
Because they brought in
the orange and the yellows
through here
actually make it look
like there's a light.
It's like--
it's really cool.
The gradation between
the seasonal change as well.
Now, there's nice attention
to where the color is
and keeping it light
in the center of the body.
- I like it.
- Awesome.
Thank you very much.
All right, guys, after
we inspected your makeups,
the coaches
did choose a favorite.
They still don't know
whose creation it is,
but I do.
The winner of today's
Foundation Challenge
and the prize of immunity is...
Stephanie.
Congratulations.
How's that feel?
That feels awesome.
Yes!
I really like the treatment
of the blue
in transition with the orange.
It felt like bounce light
from a two-dimensional painting.
Thanks.
It's a huge relief
to have immunity.
Now, no matter what,
I'm gonna be in the next round.
All right, guys,
head back to the house
and get cleaned up.
I'll see you tomorrow for
your next Spotlight Challenge.
See you.
This is so weird.
We're at the stage,
and it's freaking me out
because this
is where people go home,
and I see these dress forms
onstage.
This is bizarre.
Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- Hello.
Welcome to the reveal stage.
I know, normally,
this is a place
reserved for elimination,
but don't worry.
None of you
are going home today.
Instead, I've bought you here
to talk about your next
Spotlight Challenge.
While aliens are often portrayed
as hideous creatures,
films like Avatar and Species
have embraced the sexy side
of extraterrestrials,
transforming them
from bug-eyed monsters
into out-of-this-world beauties.
So this week's
Spotlight Challenge
is to create
your very own beautiful alien.
Okay.
Cool.
I know beauty makeup very well,
so I feel pretty good with this.
I'd like to introduce you
to a very special guest
who definitely knows
a thing or two about beauty.
She's a fashion model
and beauty queen
who became Miss Venezuela
in 2012
and was then crowned
Miss Universe in 2013.
Please give a warm welcome
to Gabriela Isler.
It's so cool to
have Miss Universe here
because she knows
all about beauty,
so I think this challenge
is gonna be fun.
Hello.
Thank you for having me.
It's an honor and a pleasure.
I'm so excited.
Now, you've won
multiple crowns in your career,
so what advice
can you give these guys
to make sure that their aliens
are truly beautiful?
Beauty pageant
is not just about beauty.
It's the way that you
present yourself.
Have some fun.
Put your friendly attitude
in every single makeup
and enjoy.
Fantastic advice.
Thank you.
All right, guys,
in the Miss Universe Pageant,
all of its participants hail
from the same planet, Earth.
This week, we're going
to broaden that competition.
If this is what I think it is,
this could be the best challenge
Face Off ever.
All right, guys,
in the Miss Universe pageant,
all of its participants hail
from the same planet, Earth.
So this week, we're going
to broaden that competition.
That's right, your aliens
will be taking part
in our very own
Miss Intergalactic Pageant,
and they will strut their stuff
right here in front
of the judges
with the hopes
of being crowned the winner.
I'm so excited.
It's a pageant.
This is the best challenge.
I just love fun characters.
Now, on each
of these dress forms
is a sash with the name
of a different galaxy
that you will use as inspiration
for your aliens.
When Gabriela calls your name,
I want you to come up
and select a sash.
Okay, he looks very excited,
so, Ben,
you have to pick first.
Miss Andromeda Galaxy.
- Emily.
- Miss Pinwheel Galaxy.
- Logan.
- Miss Comet Galaxy.
- Julian.
- Miss Whirlpool Galaxy.
- Stephanie.
- Miss Tadpole Galaxy.
- Darla.
- Miss Sculptor Galaxy.
- Adam.
- Miss Cigar Galaxy.
Kelly, you're the one
with the hat,
so take your sombrero sash.
Miss Sombrero Galaxy.
All right, guys,
this week's winning character
will not only be crowned
Miss Intergalactic
but will also be featured
in a full-page spread
in Entertainment Weekly.
- Cool.
- What?
To have a full-page spread
in Entertainment Weekly
would be absolutely awesome.
It really sells the other side
of the makeup industry
other than just making monsters.
Gabriela, thank you so much
for joining us today.
Thank you for having me,
and you guys enjoy.
All right, it's time to start
working on your designs.
Your coaches will join you soon
at the lab
to see how you're faring.
Good luck, guys.
- Bye.
Pageants incorporate hair,
something I love;
sass, I'm kind of sassy;
and, I mean, come on,
it's an alien beauty pageant.
Pinwheel Galaxy
is full of young stars,
and I conceptualize a character
that has an asymmetrical style
dress,
and I want to incorporate
a big wig
with a pinwheel with rhinestones
and glitter on it.
This challenge, I need to win.
I just want to win it so bad.
The Comet Galaxy
is essentially being torn apart
by a bunch of smaller galaxies,
and my concept is to go from
an organized, beautiful face
to a chaotic, far less beautiful
profile in the back.
This one's definitely
taking me out of my comfort zone
'cause it's a beauty challenge,
but it's an opportunity
to explore some things
that I haven't done before.
My alien
is from the Whirlpool Galaxy.
She's going to have
a very human face,
and I'm thinking of some kind
of elongated head.
I'm gonna go
with a green color scheme
to incorporate the colors
of the actual galaxy.
She's won Miss Whirlpool Galaxy,
so I don't see why she
can't win Miss Intergalactic.
I picked the Tadpole Galaxy.
It looks like a tadpole
with hot, yellowy orange
in the center.
So I want my alien to have
a really long tadpole tail.
The face will be the focal point
and then just more muted
in the back.
I'm loving my immunity.
I can do basically
whatever I want,
but I don't want
to just be safe.
I want to have, like,
a top look at least.
Since the Sombrero Galaxy
is the brightest galaxy
that we can see.
I'm thinking the outside
is just so inhabitable
that she's this beauty
that hides within caves.
I really want to take away
all the human aspect,
so I want to make
huge vacuform eyes.
Very cave-dwelling,
very amphibious kind of a feel.
All right, guys,
let's get back to the lab.
We get back to the lab,
and we pick our models,
and we have 5 1/2 hours
to work today.
The Sculptor Galaxy
is a spiral-shaped galaxy,
so I decide to take
the spiral shape
and kind of put it
on the back of the head
to create sort of an
avant-garde-looking hairstyle.
I'm not entirely sure
if it's gonna work or not,
but I decide
to just quickly block it out
and see how it looks.
- Hey.
- Good morning.
So I have the Cigar Galaxy.
It's pretty much a galaxy
with a lot of stars...
Okay.
So I immediately
attributed that to heat.
My concept for Miss Cigar Galaxy
is that she, over time,
has developed this crest
on her head that gives it
this sort of beautiful form,
but at the same time,
I want that old Hollywood
elegance about her.
I just want to give the judges
something
that they've never seen before.
I think you're on to something
interesting with some of this.
The Andromeda Galaxy is
the largest galaxy in our sky.
I'm kind of playing
with shapes and drawings.
It just has to be
striking and beautiful.
I've really got this cool design
of this three-winged head
with these diamond
three-pointed eyes.
I'm really
stepping outside the box,
but I'm actually
feeling pretty good about this.
So you're putting
multiple eyes on it?
- Yeah.
- Be careful with--
Any time you add
the multiple eyes,
it's always a risk.
I'm looking at the character,
and I realize
adding the extra eyes
could get too arachnid.
This is where I start
to get lost.
You all right?
_
By now, I'm usually sculpting,
and now I feel like my concept
is not working.
_
I'm super lost.
What am I gonna do?
It's day one of our
Miss Intergalactic Challenge,
and for the first time,
I feel lost.
I'm really stuck on my
original idea about the eyes.
Think of something
where you cannot rely
too much on the eyes.
Anthony and I decide
to remove the multiple-eye idea,
and now she has tentacles
that wrap up into a hairdo.
It makes so much more sense,
and it's going to be
an awesome character.
I'm using that shape
to create the head
to give it that asymmetry.
Something symmetrical
is universally attractive.
Laura brings up
a really good point,
that when you're trying
to do something beautiful,
asymmetry can really
throw it off.
And if I take the spiral shape
that I had put on the back
of the head
and just move it around
to the side of the head,
I can essentially create
a more symmetrical,
beautiful design.
That's time, everybody.
Even though it took
me a little bit more time,
I really like this idea because
it keeps my original concept
but turns it into
a much more beautiful character.
- Go.
- Grr. Grr. Grr.
It's day two in the lab.
We have 9 1/2 hours to work.
I'm excited to get into some
detail on the face and cowl.
I've got to get it done.
The face is essentially going
from organization to chaos,
but it's not looking right.
I want to make it more subtle
in its transition,
so it's speed sculpting time.
- Emily.
- What?
Huuuuh!
Oh! Oh, no.
There's only room for one,
Pinwheel Galaxy.
The battle is on
for Miss Intergalactic.
Step it up, Kelly.
All I get for breakfast...
power squats.
Gosh.
Miss Universe said to have fun
and make a fun character,
so that's what we're doing.
I'm using foam tubing
and swirling it like a pinwheel,
and then I'm going to paint it
like a galaxy, add some glitter,
and make it fabulous.
I'm working on the cowl
and taking a lot of inspiration
from the tail end of the galaxy,
making sure the shapes
of the face flow into the cowl.
It looks like
the tail's attached.
Laura's giving me advice
on how to keep the flow
for the tail.
Gouge all of this out
and then round it.
It's looking good.
Yeah.
I think this is gonna be
a four-piece mold, man.
Usually the cowls
are a two-piece mold.
There's a front
and a back that come together.
I'm going for a four-piece mold.
I don't want to have to seam
across these soft blended edges,
and so having two core pieces
that are gonna pop out
in between these three forms
will really give me
a nice, sleek prosthetic
when it's all done.
Hey, one hour.
At the end of the
day, I'm picking out
some Kryolan beauty products
for tomorrow.
I know a lot
of these really nice pigments
will add that pearlescent sheen
that's gonna
make Miss Sombrero Galaxy pop
and look beautiful.
Oh, so many pretty colors.
That's time, everybody.
All right.
Leaving day two,
I'm a little worried.
I only have Kelly and Ben
remaining,
and I think Kelly's
might not be enough.
I think Ben's
could fit the challenge,
but it could be
a little too out there.
There's quite a few
more challenges
to get to that finale, so I'm
hoping that I get both there.
- Go.
- Good luck, guys.
It's application day.
I got four hours in the lab,
one hour at Last Looks.
Four-piece mold?
- Yeah.
- Holy shit.
Yeah, talk about a pain
in the ass.
My face has got beautiful
blend edges,
and I've got a couple
seam edges
that I need to work
on this cowl,
but I'm feeling really good
about it.
You're crazy.
How did it come out?
You might have
to put a blender on it.
Oh, what?
There's a huge indentation
on one side of my cowl.
This is a beauty pageant.
It needs to be symmetrical.
It's just
the crappiest situation
you can be in right now.
I'm gonna try the foam patch,
I think.
Mm-hmm.
It'll at least
fill it in somewhat.
Foam patch is when you mix
foam latex
and you apply it
to wherever you have problems,
and then you cure the foam
with a heat gun.
The foam patch gets rid
of the crater and makes it seem
like that's what I meant to do
the whole time.
- Logan.
- Alyssa.
Good to meet you.
How are you?
I'm good.
You're not gonna have a ton
of stuff on your face.
- That's crazy.
- Pretty nice, huh?
Great to hear.
I'm a little worried
because even though
I don't have a face to apply,
I have to apply the cowl,
two arm pieces,
two chest pieces,
and 12 individual scales
on her face,
so I have a lot to do.
As I'm gluing the face down,
I notice a crease
going from the nose
all the way down the lip.
The whole point
of this challenge
is to create something
very beautiful,
so I'm gonna have to be
really careful to make sure
that I don't end up with
any other undesired creases.
I'm using Kryolan
Aquacolor Dayglow
as well as pink,
purple, and turquoise
to create an artificial skin.
So let me glitter you.
And then I glue glitter.
Ah, it's just so much glitter.
My model loves glitter,
so it's gonna be a perfect day.
This is making my heart happy.
One hour, everyone.
Great, I'm pretty behind.
We only have, like,
an hour left in lab,
and I need to get in to paint.
These tentacles take
so much detail,
and they have to pop.
This is what's gonna
make or break me.
So definitely,
when you airbrush,
have to accentuate
her cheekbones.
I've never done beauty makeup,
so Laura gives me some advice
on where the eye shadow
should end,
the lipstick color.
You wouldn't think
that the hot light
is gonna make much
of a difference, but it does.
It's stuff that I'm not
very familiar with.
15 minutes, everybody.
Because this is a beauty
pageant, I need to get good
at doing beauty makeup
as fast as possible...
That's time, everybody.
Or this challenge can be
the one that sends me home.
Let me see how I like this.
I have an hour left
for Last Looks.
I still have to paint her body
and figure out how I'm going
to blend in these tentacles.
This is going to take up
a lot of time.
Let me know
if I'm being too rough, okay?
I still have a ton of work
to do,
but I need to just focus
on doing the beauty makeup
as best as I can.
Got to get these eyes on you.
I'm scrambling.
This is an important piece,
so I need to focus on the eyes
and shy away
from the beauty makeup.
That's cool.
I have to attach the spikes
on the back of the cowl.
I'm trying to figure out
how to set this hot glue
and not wait for it to hold.
So I shoot the cold air
from the airbrush,
and the spikes are setting up,
and I'm like, "Oh, my God,
I just MacGyver'd this,
and it's working."
Ten minutes, everyone.
That's time, everyone.
Whew.
I don't feel like this
is anything like I wanted.
That ended up being a hot mess.
I just want to be safe.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Now, as you know,
one of you
will be going home tonight.
But before we see
your creations,
let's say hello
to our series judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening, guys.
- Good evening.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
- Hi, guys.
- Hi, Ve.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
- Hello, everyone.
- Hi, Neville.
And joining us tonight
to help choose the winner
of the full-page spread
in Entertainment Weekly
is senior writer
for Entertainment Weekly
Darren Franich.
Darren Franich has got his hand
on the pulse of Hollywood,
so even if I don't win,
I hope he's at least
impressed by the makeup.
Darren, thank you so much
for joining us tonight.
Thank you very much
for having me.
So did you ever think you'd be
judging a beauty pageant?
It was one of my biggest dreams,
actually,
so I'm glad
it's finally coming true
in an appropriately strange way.
Well, I guarantee you
this is gonna be a lot of fun.
All right, guys, this week,
your Spotlight Challenge
was to choose a galaxy
and create an alien beauty queen
to participate in our very own
Miss Intergalactic Pageant.
So let's take a look
at your creations.
Fresh from sector EW-1,
Miss Pinwheel Galaxy
enjoys space, beekeeping,
and is saving up to buy her own
passel of space possums.
She's also a strict vegetarian
and hopes to someday end
animal cruelty
throughout her galaxy.
Say hello
to Miss Pinwheel Galaxy.
It's really nice to
see the overall character.
I'm so happy.
It looks so cool.
Miss Tadpole Galaxy
is from the planet M-13,
where her hobbies include
shopping, stardust surfing,
and dancing.
With a major
in celestial sciences,
she dreams of one day
leading a research team
to discover the far end
of the universe.
Say hello
to Miss Tadpole Galaxy.
I'm really happy with her.
She's just all kinds
of fun and happy
and really killing it
and looking like a beauty queen.
Miss Andromeda Galaxy
loves long walks around Neptune
and eating at the Milky Way.
She hopes to one day meet a guy
who will give her a ring
as big as Saturn's.
Say hello
to Miss Andromeda Galaxy.
I'm not sure if I went
in the right direction.
I really thought
outside the box.
I'm just hoping that the judges
are with me on this one.
All right, we
have Miss Cigar Galaxy.
She hopes to one day command
her own interstellar army
and achieve
intergalactic domination.
Her hobbies include devouring
her mates after fertilization
and knitting.
Please say hello
to Miss Cigar Galaxy.
I know I have a strong concept,
but I'm worried that I may not
do as well as I'd hope to do.
Miss Comet Galaxy
enjoys interstellar travel
and spends her time paragliding
through solar flares.
She dreams of clothing the needy
and increasing literacy
throughout her galaxy.
Please say hello
to Miss Comet Galaxy.
I think she looks fantastic.
The only thing
that I am concerned about
is that the overall shape
of the face is a little bit off.
Miss Whirlpool Galaxy.
She enjoys surfing
through black holes,
Earth gazing,
and dancing in the moonlight.
She hopes to find
Mr. Affirmative one day
and start a colony together.
Say hello
to Miss Whirlpool Galaxy.
She definitely has this, like,
Marilyn Monroe alien vibe
going on,
so I think I might have
a good chance.
All right, now
Miss Sombrero Galaxy.
She loves small animals
and hopes to one day
devour one of every species.
Her hobbies include diving
for gems, ex-husbands,
and giving herself neck rubs.
Please lay hello
to Miss Sombrero Galaxy.
I didn't get to
finish the paint job,
but I think she looks beautiful.
Miss Sculptor Galaxy
grew up near a black hole.
Raised in darkness,
she hopes to bring light
and good fortune
to the universe.
She loves to travel and enjoys
collecting coins and currency
everywhere she goes.
Please say hello
to Miss Sculptor Galaxy.
I'm really proud of it.
She's so elegant.
I really hope that the judges
like it as well.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look at our beauties?
Whatever's happening
with the mouth
takes her from being beautiful
to injured.
It's the one character
that really seems to kind of
tell a story beyond just,
"This is what I look like."
Yeah.
She looks like a microwaved
marshmallow Peep.
I think, with a
better paint job,
this could have been
a lot more interesting makeup.
The nose and the back,
they sort of seem to come from
two very different design ideas.
I agree.
Holy moly.
The combination
of color and form,
it's so stuck on.
Up close, it feels sort of
less thought out.
I'm looking at the judges.
Not sure
how they're feeling about it,
and I'm worried my concept
and design might send me home.
Tell us who made your favorite
alien beauty queen tonight
on Twitter using #FaceOff
It feels sort of
less thought out
the closer up you get.
I don't think the judges
like my makeup very much,
but hopefully
they won't send me home.
When you look at the chin,
that is some really nice,
simple form,
and then it gets excessive.
Wow.
The head is awesome.
- It feels very original.
- Oh, yeah.
It's really quite pretty.
I think it's a beautiful
combination of shapes
that we've never seen before.
It's very brave and original.
This little piece
right here enhances her lips,
and it does retain
the prettiness.
The elegance,
more than anything,
is what struck me with this.
I think because it's so simple,
it was actually quite effective.
Yeah.
This is very busy.
Just a little, head to toe.
It befuddles me that she
didn't put a beauty makeup on her.
I'm just not
sure it goes together.
The ear tentacles,
they don't necessarily seem to
apply to the rest of the design.
This is stunning.
Look at all the detail in this.
This is really gorgeous.
The beauty makeup
widens her face
and makes it
that much prettier.
Thank you.
All right, the judges
have scored your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Logan.
Emily.
Stephanie.
You guys are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you.
The rest of you are the best
and the worst this week.
The judges would like
to speak with each of you
to find out
more about your work.
Adam, if you'd please step up.
Tell us about how your galaxy
inspired your makeup.
One tidbit about
the Cigar Galaxy is,
there's more suns,
hotter planets,
rougher environment,
so I decided to go for something
very rough and coarse
and make that beautiful.
I really want to applaud you
for how brave you were
with your design.
It's amazing.
I've never seen the shape
before.
Thank you.
Can you turn sideways for us
for a moment?
That's just an amazing,
bizarre shape
that is so elegant
from the side.
- Nice work, honey.
- Thank you.
What I'd love to have seen
is the power of that side view
brought into the front view
as well.
I love the way that the skin
sort of gives way
to something that looks
very lavalike and rocklike.
The overall look of this
was so compelling for me.
Thank you.
Please step back.
Kelly, you're up next.
Would you please tell us
how your galaxy inspired
your alien beauty queen?
My galaxy
was the Sombrero Galaxy,
and it has very bright stars,
so the only way
that she can live
is to hide in caves
and live in the waters
because the outside
is just so uninhabitable
from the radiation.
So she's more
of an aquatic-type character?
Mm-hmm.
I have to tell you, I think all
of this is just way too busy.
You don't have any place
for your eye to focus,
so for me, this is not
a really great makeup this week.
What you sculpted, I do like,
but the application of it
makes it look
like a pullover mask.
The sort of mixture of
the fishlike crown on the front
and then the tentacles in back
feel like there's a few too many
things happening here.
Kelly,
if you'd please step down.
Julian, please come forward.
Tell us about your concept
and how your galaxy choice
may have influenced the design.
Well, I had
the Whirlpool Galaxy,
and it's a very new galaxy,
so I wanted to give her
a sleek, elegant look
while incorporating some of
the colors of the galaxy itself.
There's a beautiful thing
happening around the face
with shape.
It's simple
and extraordinarily successful.
Thank you.
I think the forms are stellar.
You very nicely balanced
the alien beauty part
of this concept.
She's absolutely gorgeous.
You did a beautiful job
of shading her cheekbones,
and the treatment
of the eye makeup
is done really, really well.
Thank you.
Julian, please step back.
Thanks.
Darla, please step
to the center.
Can you tell us a bit
about your character
and how your galaxy
inspired the design?
I had the Sculptor Galaxy.
The main inspiration I took was
the spiral pattern for the head,
and it's also known
as the Silver Dollar Galaxy,
so I put silver contacts
in her eyes.
There's this real element
of glamour to it.
There's almost an alien
old Hollywood quality,
like space Norma Desmond
or something like that,
and I really just think
it's very well done.
Thank you so much.
The forms are just stunning.
That is what I want to see
from everybody every week.
I'm really impressed.
Thank you.
She's classy.
She's elegant.
She's beautiful.
We hate it.
- Didn't like it very much.
- You're in trouble.
Darla, please step back.
Thank you so much.
_
Thanks.
Ben, you're up.
Ben, tell us
how the Andromeda Galaxy
informed your decisions
this week.
I pretty much took it
as the opportunity
to make whatever I wanted to,
and then I started thinking
about these eyes.
As an eye piece,
I haven't seen it done before,
and just wanted to play around
with makeup today.
You went a different route
than everybody else,
and I applaud that,
but for some reason,
it didn't come together.
The texture of the plane
directly around this device
begs to be broken up with color,
whether that's speckling
or veining or something.
I think texture and color
could have pulled together
what is a really solid idea.
There's some really beautiful
form work,
and then we get
to this eye thing,
which feels like a '60s Japanese
superhero-type character,
and that is not this challenge.
I love the basic
abstract design of this,
but there's something missing,
and it doesn't quite hit me
the way I think it should.
Ben, please step back.
Thanks.
Thank you guys.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while the judges deliberate.
All right, judges,
so let's start
with your favorites this week.
How about Adam?
An amazing makeup,
an amazing creature.
I loved the
biogeological elements of it.
I loved the way that the lava
melded in with the skin.
I really loved the profile.
We've really never seen
anything like that before.
All right,
let's move on to Julian.
One of the things he did best
was utilize
the actual model's beauty.
The simplicity, I think,
is what we all responded to.
Not a lot of other people
really achieved that this week.
Okay, judges,
let's move on to Darla.
It's clean. It's elegant.
It's classy.
It's just a stunning makeup.
The forms are beautiful.
You could put that character
as a lead alien in a film.
All right, let's move on
to your least favorite makeups.
Why don't we start with Kelly?
She mixed up so many different
colors, purples and pinks.
It looked like it had purple
slugs coming out of its ears.
The edges, where they
even were sculpted, don't work.
The execution of it is bad,
but I still see the potential
in this design.
Let's move on to Ben.
There are so many good ideas,
but it's not beautiful.
There are so many
things that didn't work there,
but it's interesting
that his whole aesthetic
is very much built around,
"I'm gonna take a wild gamble,"
and sometimes it works,
and this time,
it really didn't.
Okay, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- Yeah, we have.
- We have. - Yes.
Okay, let's bring them
back out.
All right, Glenn,
tell us about the semifinalists.
Adam, your character
is striking from afar,
and it managed to create
a wow factor profile
with that cowl
that we have never seen before.
Julian, you did an excellent job
embracing your model's beauty
and enhancing it.
Though she was clearly alien,
she was still a stunning beauty.
Darla,
we loved the inherent glamour
of your character.
She has a sexy,
almost regal feeling
that made her a real standout.
Thank you.
All right, big moment.
Who is the winner of
our Miss Intergalactic Pageant?
The winner of our
Miss Intergalactic Pageant is...
All right, who is the winner of
our Miss Intergalactic Pageant?
The winner of our
Miss Intergalactic Pageant is...
Miss Sculptor Galaxy.
She is not only beautiful,
but the makeup is applied
and painted flawlessly.
We are so glad to see you
back on top this week.
Thank you so much.
I can't believe
that I just won this challenge.
It's exciting to be a top look,
but to actually win
a Spotlight Challenge
is such a great feeling.
Darla, congratulations,
and, of course,
congratulations to our
very first Miss Intergalactic.
The two of you will be featured
in a full-page spread
in Entertainment Weekly.
- That's amazing.
- Congratulations on that.
Thank you.
Darla, you, Adam, and Julian
can head back to the makeup room
with the coaches
and our beauties.
All right, that means
the two of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be going home.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about tonight's bottom looks.
Kelly, some of your sculpting
was interesting,
but the poor application
of your pieces
and rough nature
of your paint work
were underwhelming.
Ben, we appreciate that you
swung for the fences again,
but there were a number
of things, design-wise,
that detracted from her beauty.
So who is going home tonight?
The person
going home tonight is...
Kelly.
We know that you had some
good ideas going on this week,
but it seems that you really
struggled to bring them
all together
into a cohesive, clean makeup.
I had a bit
of a struggle this week,
and it showed.
Kelly, I'm so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
Ben, you are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Kelly, you have done some
inspired and fun makeups for us,
and I really look forward
to what the future
has in store for you.
Thank you.
Kelly, it's been great
having you here with us,
but if you'd please
head back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thanks, guys.
Good luck, sweetheart.
Thank you.
I know that I'm better
than what I put out there,
and if I had to do it
all over again,
I would have made
much better choices.
It's me.
I'm leaving
with a lot of knowledge
and a lot of confidence
in myself.
You have such a creative
passion about you,
and I don't want to ever
see you lose that, you know.
Get over here.
I made it this far on Face Off,
and that's pretty awesome.
I love what I do,
and I'm gonna keep making
my spooky things.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net