She really is amazing.
That is not
this challenge.
I'm really impressed.
Previously on Face Off,
Darla's alien beauty queen
earned her her first win.
But Kelly was eliminated,
leaving Team Anthony
with just one artist.
Now seven artists remain,
and tonight their skills
will be tested
unlike ever before.
This challenge might be
the most daunting
in Face Off history.
This is the hardest
thing I will ever do.
Oh, no.
Just kind of
get, like, a little frazzled
and a little frustrated.
Mm.
Toohm!
I am very happy with this.
In the end,
only one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
This is Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Good morning.
- Hey.
- What's up?
Big winner.
What's up, loser?
Congrats, by the way.
Thank you.
Ben, how does it feel
to be the last man standing
on Team Anthony?
It sucks.
I feel like we had
a pretty good team.
Since I'm the only
one left on Team Anthony,
there's a lot of pressure,
so I got to put my best foot
forward even more so
because, being that
he's such a good coach,
I really don't want
to let him down.
We're in downtown
LA walking down the street.
I'm not familiar with LA,
so I have no idea
where we're going
or what we're gonna be doing.
We finally go
into this beautiful building,
but it's got this
haunted old feel to it.
I'm thinking lots of cool stuff
probably happened here.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Welcome to
the Herald Examiner building.
Once home to one
of the nation's
most highly-circulated
newspapers,
it's now a popular
filming location
for movies like
The Usual Suspects,
Collateral,
and Spider-Man 3.
This week's spotlight
challenge delves
into a type of character
that has inspired
generations of children
and adults alike--
superheroes.
This is awesome for me
because in my younger
artistic days,
I used to attempt
to draw superheroes.
So I'm really excited.
Now, for every Batman,
Spider-Man, and Superman,
there's a Bruce Wayne,
Peter Parker, and Clark Kent.
These alter egos
are seemingly regular guys
who transform into superheroes
when danger is lurking.
So for this
spotlight challenge,
you will transform
a seemingly ordinary person
into an extraordinary
superhero character.
Of course,
there's just one thing.
Always.
Simply making
a superhero character
is way too straightforward.
This challenge might actually
be the most daunting
in Face Off history.
Ooh.
What more could we do?
What is it?
Because you are the alter egos
this week,
and you'll be transforming
yourselves
into superheroes.
Oh, my goodness.
This is gonna be
the hardest challenge
and the hardest thing
I will ever do.
Oh, my God.
Okay, is this excitement
across the board?
Yeah?
Yes.
Now I know it's very difficult
to apply make-up
to yourselves,
so you will have
make-up assistants
on application day
to help you apply
your prosthetics.
Nice.
All right, guys,
go ahead and get started
on your designs.
I can't wait
to see you guys onstage.
Bye.
We're going to be
applying makeup to ourselves.
No big deal.
No big deal at all.
My character has many elements
of my life incorporated
into it,
including a fascination
for dragons
and vigilante justice.
I'm envisioning a new character
in an older world.
I've named him Slayer.
This is a dragon-human hybrid.
He's an immortal assassin,
and he protects people
from corruption.
I'm very excited
and I'm not excited
at the same time.
I'm very introverted, and...
nature was always my outlet.
So for my alter ego,
I want to pull inspiration
from nature.
I want to do a mother
nature-inspired superhero,
who is a healer.
This is gonna be
a cool makeup.
I have nothing solid yet.
I'm just throwing shapes
around and poses.
I'm drawing a blank.
What would I look like
if I was a superhero.
Superheroes
and super villains are cool,
but I don't know what
I'm gonna do for myself.
Growing up, I
was very quiet and shy
and kind of introverted.
So I start thinking
of ways that I can take
those aspects of me
and create the exact opposite.
I want to do more
of a guardian angel
type superhero.
She's elegant and beautiful.
And I want a very
powerful silhouette.
So I'm excited to get back
to the lab
and start working on this.
We get back to the lab,
and we have five hours
on the clock to work today.
Can we see our ugly mugs?
_
To have a live cast
of myself is really weird.
I've got one at the house,
but for some reason, this one
looks like I'm a lot fatter,
which is un-superhero-ish.
But that's okay.
I'll go with it.
Hey, guys!
Hello!
We got a birth-- a
birthday in the house, right?
So everybody get over here.
Aww, thanks, guys.
Thank you.
How many people can say
that they had their birthday
on Face Off?
I can.
This being my first birthday
away from home,
it means a lot to me.
Thank you, guys.
I'm thinking, um,
he was a military experiment.
Mm-hmm.
Instead of doing a superhero,
I'm actually going
for a villain.
I spent five years in the Marine
Corps as a helicopter mechanic.
So my concept is a super soldier
that was in a helicopter crash,
and the government
put him back together
to create this war machine.
This is kind of
like the RoboCop,
Terminator type line.
Yeah.
Ben is the last person
on my team.
So it gives me the opportunity
to give all my attention to him.
Maybe on the cowl,
sculpt the top of your cranium.
He's also my last chance
to get to the finale.
And I hope I can get him there.
He's kind of an anti-hero.
He's constantly fighting
the urge to do evil things.
Yes.
His name is Reckoning,
and he is an anti-hero
who is a human that has made
a deal with the devil
to take up his job.
And he wants to use his powers
for good,
but he's slowly
becoming a villain.
Instead of doing
the traditional, two-horn devil,
I decided to go
with almost like a crown shape.
So I'm really happy and excited
to see
how this is gonna turn out.
My hero,
he fights giant monsters, right?
But he has
no fucking experience.
He doesn't know
what he's doing,
so he's just destroying cities
as he's trying to help people.
I want my superhero
to be funny.
So he's a bumbling superhero
of Japan
who created these gloves.
But the gloves work in reverse
and actually amplify the person
wearing the gloves.
So he's able to grow
to immense sizes.
He tries to help people,
but he's just ruining the city
and millions of people's lives
at the same time.
And much like my life,
he is a fish out of water.
My mom's a wigmaker.
And she's showed me a lot
of the stuff that I know now.
So I'm gonna make sure
that I incorporate a wig
and make it the biggest wig
I have ever made,
because my mom is my superhero.
So the wig's for her.
And I start pulling
the hair back
and just rolling it so it
can get a more simple shape.
And then I use cheesecloth
and wrap it so I have something
to glue the moss on.
Then I spray it black
and then start gluing moss.
It's huge.
And I love it.
What is the idea
behind the whole character?
Um, mostly taking, like,
a post-apocalyptic kind
of world.
I finally have a concept.
And it's a sort of anti-hero.
Like, a part demon.
She protects humans.
And I'm planning
on doing it black and white
like she jumped
out of the comic book.
I work at haunted houses.
I scare people for a living.
So her superpower is basically
scaring them to death.
What does the face look like?
I don't know yet.
That's-- that's
what I'm trying to figure out.
- All righty.
- Um.
And I'm having trouble, like,
nailing down exactly what I
want the face to look like.
And I just kind of get, like,
a little frazzled
and a little frustrated.
Hmm.
Stephanie's losing a lot
of time by not moving ahead.
She needs to come up
with something very fast.
It's halfway through the day,
and I still haven't
started sculpting.
I really want to do well
on this challenge,
but I can't even think
of something to make.
I'm totally lost.
It looks like
a comic book character.
Yeah.
You just need to figure out
the perfect face.
It's Day 1
of our Superhero Challenge.
And I finally have a concept,
but I'm having trouble
figuring out the face.
So maybe
a smaller, subtler piece.
That's what I was-- I was
thinking of just doing a brow.
Yeah. A brow's great.
Just make sure
your makeup looks flawless.
Yeah.
Laura's right.
No matter what I do,
I need to make sure
my makeup looks perfect.
I'm going to do a dome shell,
which is kind of like a helmet.
In the Marine Corps,
I did hydraulic sheet metal
fiberglass work.
So this is really an opportunity
to show some of my skills.
To make this helmet,
I sculpted out in wet clay
and then take it over
at the black floor machine.
That's cool.
And then I can go ahead
and start sculpting the cowl
around this
to make sure it fits.
We have mirrors
set up at our stations,
so I want to do a test makeup
because we are our models.
So might as well test it out.
I'm using Kryolan aqua colors,
lavenders, and greens.
And I hate it.
So I go for my second option,
which is more natural tones.
I use a flesh-tone color,
and I like that one.
It goes with the natural theme.
And I'm so happy
I decided to do this now.
One of the most iconic parts
of a superhero
is how their mask is shaped.
So I'm just going
for one that looks
like maybe a dragon would wear.
The biggest thing
with scales--
you want them to read
from far away,
even if they're subtle scales.
The objective is to subtly
suggest that he comes
from a world with dragons,
but he's still a human.
So I'm putting in scales,
but not too many scales.
There's a lot of freedom
with this particular design.
Because dragons didn't exist.
I'm throwing clay down.
I'm pushing it around.
I'm trying
to get a subtle shape.
I don't want
to do a superhero mask.
I'm going for a more organic,
demonic look.
I named her Doll Face because I
want her to be a pretty demon.
Did you figure
out your concept?
Yeah. Just worrying about
not doing enough on the face.
You just do an immaculate job.
Yeah.
Okay, just--
it's got to be perfect.
30 minutes, everybody.
That's time, everybody.
Okay, good enough.
By the end of Day 1,
I have enough clay
blocked out where I know
what I'm doing for Day 2.
I just got to take care
of my time management
better and finish it.
It's Day 2 of the
Superhero Challenge,
and we have 9 1/2 hours
in the lab.
And I have quite a bit
to get done today.
Should I do some filigree work
on the helmet
or should I just do that on,
like, the portions--
Figure out the face first.
Okay.
The most important thing
is getting the face sculpt done.
And as I'm sculpting,
I start looking at the pictures
I took at the Herald building.
And I realize I can actually
trace some of the filigree
pattern from those pictures
and transfer it onto my sculpt.
So once I trace the filigree,
I press it against my sculpture,
and it transfers the lead
of the pencil onto to the clay.
So now I have an outline
to follow
as I'm placing the filigree.
That's cool.
I'm feeling
good about my sculpt,
so I go ahead
and start molding my face.
I finished the mold
really quick.
But I cannot use foam latex
because I'm allergic to it.
So I run in gelatin.
I let it sit to set up, and then
I'll come back later on.
Yesterday I blocked
out most of the cowl.
I still have to complete it,
and I need to get started
and complete the face.
Do you ever speed sculpt?
Not really.
Laura's concerned
about my time management.
Stand up.
So she gives me some tips
on how to do speed sculpting.
I like using my fingers
and raking the whole thing.
Laura teaches me how to
get the forms in a faster pace.
There.
See how quick that was?
He does like to take his time,
which is a good thing,
but on this competition,
you can't afford
to take too much time.
I got to speed it up.
I want him to look scary
and be disgusting.
I want to show
the skeletal structure
underneath the respirator
because I think
that will really bring out
the villain aspect of things.
And when I open up
that respirator, it will give me
that little creepy factor
that really just sells nasty.
I've been thinking
about making wings for this guy.
Wings?
I'm going to create
some real badass wings
sticking up out of his back.
I've had
this decade-long pursuit
of becoming a military pilot.
I like flight,
and I think it's a cool element
to add to it.
And then I pick out some foam
and some steel bar.
And I run the bar
through the two pieces of foam.
I bend it to the shape I want.
What do you think
of that profile?
And then I gaff tape
it together.
100 miles an hour today.
I put two layers
of cheesecloth on.
One on one side,
one on the other,
and latex them together.
It gives an effect of skin
as opposed to raw materials.
Once I get latex on there, they
start to look like dragon wings.
Dude, that looks awesome.
Shit.
I go to open my face and...
And I can feel the tackiness
of the gelatin
that's on the side of the mold,
and it's not setting.
Oh, no.
I pop it out. Then the edges
are just atrocious.
I can't use it.
I'm really nervous right now
because I don't have a face
for my makeup
and I don't know what to do.
This is not good.
Oh, no.
It's Day 2 of our Alter
Ego Superhero Challenge.
And I'm really nervous right now
because I don't have a face
for my makeup.
The edges are just atrocious.
But I'm not giving up.
I just need to get it
out of the mold.
So I'm powdering and peeling it.
My only option
is to run it in silicon.
But I don't really know
how to use it.
I'm not very comfortable
with it.
We'll see.
How did it turn out?
Not good.
Oh.
But I got to get
this ready for silicone.
I love the size of it.
The arm pieces
are important to my concept
because they're the accidental
reason my character
becomes a superhero.
So I see these buckets
and I think it would be kind of
funny to go really, really big
with these almost non-functional
cannon arms.
So I take these serving dishes
to use as a top for the bucket.
And I'm attaching tubing.
And then I vacuum form it.
And then I cut out the bottoms
of the buckets
so I can put them on my arms.
They look cool.
They need to be painted,
but they're 90% done.
Toong!
I'm gonna get out of here.
All right.
Good luck.
- Cool, man.
- You got it.
Make sure you know exactly
where you're gonna
take this thing.
Okay.
Leaving Day 2,
I think both Adam
and Logan are on track.
But I only have two artists
left on my team.
Bye, guys.
Have fun.
Losing one of them
could really hurt my chance
of going to the finale.
Along with the brow
that I'm doing,
I'm gonna be making a mask
that she holds in her hand
to help scare the other demons.
I start sculpting
a really fierce demon face.
I'm going with,
like, super-arched eyebrows,
and, like, a pointy nose,
and high cheekbones.
It's not totally refined,
but it looks good enough to be
a scary mask.
That's time, everybody.
I think everyone's
feeling a little bit nervous,
but also pretty excited
about tomorrow.
It's gonna be a stressful,
hectic day.
But in the end, we get
to be onstage as superheroes,
and that's a pretty cool thing.
Good luck, guys.
Hey, the models are here.
Holy shit.
It's application day today,
and we have four hours
in lab and one hour Last Looks.
And we are all really nervous.
Laura, look at the edges.
Good mornin'! I know.
I look at my
silicone appliance,
and the edges are stunning.
They're paper thin.
This is just a weight
off my shoulder.
I'm so happy.
That looks really good.
It's a little
bit strange 'cause
we're not waiting on the models.
We are the models.
Um, but we are gonna
be having assistance today.
Hello. Logan.
Nice to meet you.
Good to meet you too.
- Hi!
- Vance.
Hi.
- I'm Carey.
- Nice to meet you.
I have applied makeup
to myself before.
But it's not easy.
So it's really important
for me to get
the cowl completely pre-painted
before I even put it on.
It's just
this and a chin piece.
Okay.
And then the rest
of it is the suit,
which I'm trying
to throw together.
I know that I have
a lot more fabrication
than makeup application.
So the first thing I do
is pull the rest
of the costume together.
I want to make all
that look as good as it can be.
So I start to do
some dry brushing.
Then I just
dress the entire costume.
I just hope I've created
something
different enough that the judges
will be pleased with it.
Hey, Logan, still look cheap?
No, it looks awesome.
I am not a fan of putting
prosthetics on my face.
So that's why I was like,
"I want to make a character
where I don't have
to put as much stuff on."
All I got to do
is put a brow piece on
and basically paint
everything in black and white.
I start from the nose
and then work my way out.
I just got to make sure that it
all lines up and it's not,
like, totally crooked.
Now I have to start
painting like crazy.
_
So it's time
for me to apply a bald cap.
Just kidding.
What I have to do now
is get these pieces painted
and get 'em ready
so that I can apply 'em.
If you're able to start
pre-painting the packs on this.
It's time to take the cowl
and really get that black,
leathery, metal work on it.
And it's looking great.
So once I get
these things applied,
I can just
worry about the wardrobe,
and I'll have an hour
left at Last Looks.
Cold.
Good painting's about layers,
not obvious, bold strokes.
Especially subtleties.
I'm finishing painting
the face.
And the color scheme today
is going to be very flesh-toned
and green.
It's a hybrid
of a dragon and a human,
so I want to incorporate
predominant colors from both.
See you later.
Yeah, bye.
The face goes on,
and from here on out,
I'm gonna be Slayer,
the Defender of Dragons.
Now, how do I go in
and make it more translucent?
I probably would layer upon
layer of a very watered-down
translucent alcohol-based colors
on top of your flesh-tone.
I'm using alcohol colors
to make it more translucent
so we can really get
that looking realistic.
But I'm nervous about using
alcohol paints 'cause
I've only used
them for injuries.
I've done a lot
of things this challenge
that I have not done before.
I just hope it pays off
in the end.
One hour, everybody.
I want to make sure
that I have a graphic look.
That's why I'm going
for the whole
black-and-white color scheme.
But it's looking really muddy
and really gray.
Um...
I'm starting to look
like a blue, vampirey,
weird-- I don't know.
I'm just not liking
how it's all coming together.
And I'm trying
to do some flicking
just to break it up.
I'm looking totally different
than what I wanted.
15 minutes, everybody.
All right, that's it.
Time's up!
I'm really worried
because I'm looking vampirey.
I mean,
I only have one appliance.
There's really nothing else
to distract away from that.
Ugh. It's making me really,
really nervous.
It's game time, baby.
It's game time.
It's Last Looks,
and we have one hour
to finish our superheroes.
I'm really concerned
about finishing the face
and not having enough time
to finish this character
the way I want to.
Wow, I am not good at
airbrushing with my left hand.
Are you kidding?
I really got to punch up
some of the highlights
just to make sure
that I have some sort
of, like, graphic look to me.
But I could still end up
just looking really muddy.
30 minutes.
I can't even airbrush on myself.
I still have some painting
to do and some shading.
But I can't do it on myself.
Do you need it
around your eyes?
- Yeah.
- I'll do it.
We're all competing
to win this thing,
but everyone needs each other
at this point.
Look up for me.
I'm trying to do modeling,
but I can't see.
I know that I've missed
some spots.
So I ask Adam
to hit it for 15 seconds.
10 minutes, everybody.
That looks awesome, Ben.
Looking
at everyone else's character,
I realize I am not a superhero.
This is so stupid.
There's not much I can do.
All right, it's time.
Fuck.
I'm all right,
I'm all right, I'm all right.
I've never been this nervous.
I don't think
I look like a superhero.
Gosh, I just
want this to be over.
Good evening, judges.
How are you doing tonight?
- Great, thank you.
- Bitchin'.
Excellent.
And hello as well
to our champion coaches.
How are you guys doing?
Pretty good.
Peachy with a side of keen.
All right, well,
tonight's gonna be a lot of fun,
obviously.
This week the contestants'
Spotlight Challenge
was to create a superhero
using themselves
as the alter ego and inspiration
for its design.
And not only that,
they had to apply the makeup
to themselves as well.
And I think it's safe to say
that this may be
the hardest challenge
that we've ever done
on this show.
For sure.
All right, are you guys
ready to see
what they've come up with?
- Oh, yeah.
- Absolutely.
- Can't wait.
- Okay, well, let's take a look.
_
All right, let's really
see what these guys can do.
This is a very different
experience coming out onstage.
We have to act,
which is a blast.
I'm lovin' doing this.
_
The makeup alone may
not read as a superhero,
but the character as a whole,
I think that reads
as superhero enough.
This is just a lot of fun.
I knew it was gonna be hard,
but I'm just seeing Glenn
doing his eyebrow.
He is just so stone-faced
while I'm posing, and,
like, "Am I doing this right?"
Yeah, it's nerve-racking.
I have a
love-hate relationship
with this makeup 'cause
I really love the cowl,
but I'm not happy
with how the face turned out.
I've got this gun in my hands.
I've got these creepy eyes,
and I've got
this skeleton face.
I definitely feel badass
right now.
So I'm onstage.
I'm like, "Okay,
I guess I'm a superhero."
I've never been this nervous
in my life.
_
I make sure to
put my cheesy grin on.
And I'm in heaven right now.
This week
was such a tough challenge,
but you guys did a great job.
Okay, before the judges
come to take a closer look,
I do have another huge surprise
for you.
Oh, no.
I wanted to have you
all out here together
before I introduce tonight's
very special guest judge.
He's a comic book industry
legend who has worked
on some of its most
popular and iconic titles
like Spider-Man
and The Incredible Hulk.
He's also one of the founders
of Image Comics and created one
of the most popular comic book
franchises of all time, Spawn.
Please give a big welcome
to Todd McFarlane.
Oh, man.
Hey, McKenzie,
how are you today?
Good.
Great to have you here.
Oh, my God.
That's so awesome.
Todd McFarlane was
just a huge influence on me
when I started drawing as a kid.
It's really cool
to have him here.
Now, there is no one
more qualified than you
to be judging superheroes.
And I know that you
were watching backstage.
Yes.
So are you ready to take
a closer look at these guys?
Yes, we will.
All right, judges,
you ready to do this?
This is a very difference
experience for closer looks.
I don't know if I'm supposed
to act in character
or if I'm supposed
to freeze and be just a statue.
I don't know.
Hi, Logan.
Hi.
You sure got a lot
done this week.
Could you turn sideways
so we can see your wings?
These layers really help sell
these instead
of just being flat.
Can we get a grit right here?
Yeah, there we go.
Give us a couple
of expressions.
_
Yeah.
You look like you're kind
of diggin' this.
Did you have
fun this week, Julian?
Oh, yeah.
Can you give
us a furrowed brow?
That's some nice edges
for something
that you put on yourself.
I think the ears
could have been sculpted
much better though.
I'm sorry.
Let's see this mask.
Were you intending
on holding this up?
Is this your mask?
Yeah.
Okay. So let's see this.
It wouldn't actually
fit my face.
Cool. Thank you.
Hi, Darla.
Hello.
I'm concerned about the paint.
It's starting to crack.
Let's see a look of victory.
I'm trying to make as little
facial expression as possible.
Now give us a look of poison.
I could be in trouble.
Tell us who made
your favorite superhero tonight
on Twitter using #FaceOff
I'm worried that if I
move around too much, the paint
is gonna start to crack.
Now give us a look of poison.
There you go.
I just hope that
the rest of the makeup
is enough to keep me safe.
All right, Ben,
give us that big reveal.
So this is all stuff
that you built, right?
How about some expressions?
You love that big hair,
don't you, girl?
All right, you got a couple
of looks for us, then?
It's awkward.
I completely blank out.
I'm digging
my hole deeper and deeper.
Just made the willow weep,
I think.
Good evening.
You've just been waitin'
to use that hairdo
of yours, haven't you?
Maybe.
Let's see
what these things are.
They're protonic plasma.
It's all very complicated.
You don't want
to hear about it.
Thank you.
Okay, the judges
have scored your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Julian,
Darla,
Ben.
Congratulations
because you are all safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Shit.
The rest of you were the best
and the worst this week.
And the judges would like
to speak with each of you
to find out
more about your work.
Logan, if you'd
please step out.
Logan, I can't wait
to hear the backstory,
but all in your superhero voice,
please.
My name is Slayer.
I hail from the time
dragons ruled,
and I defended them.
Now I defend people.
That's my story.
I'm very impressed
with your conceptual designs
and your technical work.
It's not something
I've seen before.
It encourages us to want to know
more about the backstory,
and its origin
is incredibly impressive.
Thank you very much.
I love this color palette,
and it really gives it a lot
of life.
And I especially love
what you did with your wings.
It really takes your imagination
someplace, which is great.
I am very happy with this.
Sculpturally speaking,
you've nailed it with the face.
You can see that you're able
to emote through it.
Yet you've somehow baked
in that expression,
and it's really
quite accomplished.
Thank you.
You've taken
what is traditional garb--
You've got a mask,
you've got a logo,
but you put it into a frame now
that isn't so obvious.
So I like the whole message
that you're bringing across
right now.
Thank you very much.
Logan, please step back.
Emily, you're up next.
Well, forest babe,
tell us all about yourself.
So I am nature's daughter.
So I heal animals,
and I just help bring the good
out of people.
I got to say, I
love the paint job,
but I'm a little tired
of the big hairdos.
I don't know what
to say, honey.
I'm just very disappointed
that you repeated yourself.
Okay, thank you.
This is, for me, not
appropriate for this challenge.
You look like a hedge
or a topiary.
At this point
in the competition,
without allowing
yourself to evolve,
you're going to be doomed.
Emily, thank you very much.
Please step back.
Adam, please step forward.
Tell us about your superhero
character.
I am the Crimson Wave.
I stuck my arms in these things.
They didn't come off.
And I decided to throw a mask
on, move to Japan,
and save the city.
Makes a lot of sense
when he says it that way.
Yeah.
You've really done a great job
at creating
an overall superhero character.
It's good that this is comedic
because the proportions
are so insane.
If I was 10 years
old, 11 years old,
I'd dig you to hell.
Of all the people up there,
you were the one
that was in character.
And after doing comic books
for 25-plus years,
I dig it.
What really counted
is you made sure that you
hit that one note this week
which was superhero.
And so many pieces of
your design say that so clearly.
And that's what I
love about the makeup.
Thank you.
Adam, you can step back.
Hey.
Good job.
Thanks, Dad.
All right,
let's talk to Stephanie.
Talk to us about how you got
to what is
in front of us right now.
My character is Doll Face,
and she is set
in a post-apocalyptic world.
And she is trying to protect
all the remaining humans
that are left on Earth.
One of the things that I
would have liked to have seen
is that when we asked you
to put the mask up,
you said it didn't fit.
And that's a bit
of a shame to me.
'Cause it would have been kind
of cool if you actually
had the reveal like Beauty
and the Beast, if you will.
For sure.
You have chances to explore
demons in other challenges.
So if you would have
done that extraordinarily well,
I could have gotten behind it.
But the forms are just--
they're too derivative.
The appliance that you have on
is very similar
to what I put on Kiefer.
Did you ever see the movie
The Lost Boys?
Oh, yeah.
So it's a little bit repetitive
and boring for me to see it.
And not only that, I
think you did a really poor job
painting yourself.
You look like an old lady
with red eyes.
Stephanie, thank you.
If you'd please step back.
Okay, thank you, guys.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while the judges deliberate.
All right, judges, let's start
with you favorite looks tonight.
How about Logan's work?
I love Logan's.
It just looked like he stepped
right out of another century.
Yeah, if you can
take him 2,000 years back
and 2,000 years in the future,
I could still figure out the
story that would make him work.
The detailing of the makeup
in addition to everything
else was pretty incredible.
All right,
let's move on to Adam.
Everything
about it was successful.
He literalized it
by making it a comedian.
And that's what makes it also
really good as a superhero.
If I could make an action
figure out of any of you,
he was the guy
that I'd want to bring home
to my eight-year-old son.
He enjoyed it so much.
I forgot it was Adam
under there.
All right, let's move on
to the looks you like the least.
Why don't we start with Emily?
Marge Simpson is Poison Ivy.
That absolutely absurd hedge
of a hairdo.
There was nothing
that suggested that she
had any strength
as a superhero, as a woman.
She was a little bit
shy about who she was.
She was still uncomfortable
in her skin even with the power.
Okay, let's move
on to Stephanie.
The paint job sucked.
That's what really ruined
this for me.
'Cause she looks
like a, you know, zombie.
It was a brow shape
that we've all seen a painful
amount of times at this point.
I don't think
it was a horrible makeup.
It's just that there was nothing
there but gray.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
We have.
Let's bring them back out.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about tonight's top looks.
Logan, your character
certainly has a superhero vibe,
but what we really love is that
he also had a mysterious quality
which made us want
to know more about him.
And Adam, the comedic nature
of your superhero suits
your personality perfectly.
And your performance gave him
extra dimension in life.
All right,
so who is the winner
of tonight's challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
All right,
so who is the winner
of tonight's challenge?
The winner of tonight's
challenge is...
Logan.
Your superhero
clicked in every level.
And you did astounding
technical work,
especially considering
you had to apply it on yourself.
Great job tonight, man.
Thank you very much.
This is a cool moment.
Of all the makeups that I've
done in the competition so far,
I'm most proud of this one.
This is win number three for me
and I'm stoked about it.
Thank to my coach, Rayce.
Thank you.
All right, so Logan, you
and Adam along with the coaches
can all head backstage.
All right, guys, that means that
you are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be going home.
Please step forward.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about tonight's bottom looks.
Emily, the makeup part
of your character
is actually quite beautiful,
but there was
an overall disconnect
with the superhero aspect
of the challenge for us.
Stephanie, on another week,
this demon-like character
could have worked.
But we really didn't feel
like we see you in this makeup.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home tonight
is...
Stephanie.
Yep.
The paint work
was pretty weak, but moreover,
we just didn't feel like you
were inspired by this challenge,
which showed
in the finished product.
I'm sorry.
You know what?
I had a lot of fun
in this challenge.
It might not have shown,
but I did.
Stephanie, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
That means Emily,
you're safe this week and can
head back to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Bye, Stephanie.
Stephanie, it's been a
privilege to have you with us
and show us your talents.
It's in you, we've seen it.
And I'm looking forward
to seeing that in the future.
Thank you.
Stephanie, it's really been
great having you here with us.
If you'd please head backstage
and pack up your kit.
Thank you so much, everyone.
Good luck.
Well, I'm goin' home,
and it blows.
I wanted to win.
That's why I came here.
It's me.
Aw.
But I feel really good that I
made it to the final seven.
What I like about you
is you know what you want to do
and you're passionate.
Watching you grow
this whole competition
has been a privilege.
Thanks.
Even though I didn't make it
through all the way,
I think I did awesome.
I really impressed myself.
It's a bittersweet kind of end
for me.
Especially, like,
me looking like this.
At least I'm goin' out lookin'
like a badass.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net