- Oh, my God.
- This is insane.
This season,
Face Off has a whole new twist.
Three champions have returned to
coach their own team of artists.
- So let's get moving.
- It's insane.
They'll steer their new
proteges toward the finale.
Things are about to get real.
But with a season
full of demanding challenges...
I have a big announcement
to make.
I am freaking out.
It is complete pandemonium.
...and a judging panel
filled with the industry's
- brightest stars...
- I think it's so cool.
...coming out on top will be
tougher than ever before.
What the heck
is happening right now?
This competition is nuts.
In the end, only one
will win a VIP trip from
Kryolan Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Find out
how it all begins right now.
This is Face Off.
_
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
We're in the middle
of downtown LA,
and we have no idea
what to expect.
All of a sudden
these doors open.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
This room is huge.
- Ah, man.
- This is insane.
I can't believe this.
There's supplies everywhere,
paint, airbrushes,
and Kryolan makeup.
It's crazy.
So much stuff to choose from.
I can't wait to get started.
Hello, everybody.
Welcome to Face Off.
I look up,
and I see McKenzie Westmore
walking down the stairs,
and I'm like,
"Oh, my God. This is it."
Hey, guys.
Hi.
This season of Face Off is
going to be unlike any before,
because the competition
has completely changed.
This season
three former champions
will be investing in you guys by
becoming your personal coaches.
What?
Please welcome
your new champion coaches...
Oh, no way.
Season two winner Rayce Bird.
Season four winner
Anthony Kosar.
And season three finalist
and season five winner
Laura Tyler.
This is mind-blowing.
I can't wait to work
with these coaches.
Deep breath.
So how are you guys doing?
- Good.
- Fantastic.
Glad to be back.
Well, this is very exciting
because you guys have a lot
of talent and expertise to share
with this season's contestants.
Now, you guys are not the only
ones competing this season.
Our returning champions are also
competing but not against you.
They will be competing
against each other.
- Oh, yeah.
- Sorry!
- Oh, wow.
- Oh.
All right, so here's
how this is going to work.
Each champion will choose
five of you to join their team.
If someone from their team
wins this season,
that coach wins, as well,
making them the first
two-time Face Off champion.
That's awesome.
However, if all of the members
of that team get eliminated,
then the coach
gets eliminated as well.
Aww.
So today's challenge
is critical because it will be
your only chance
to prove that you have
what it takes
to win before the coaches
handpick their teams.
So are you ready to make
a great first impression?
Yeah!
Whoo!
For your first
foundation challenge,
you'll each pay tribute
to our returning champions
by creating
a companion character
that complements
one of their most iconic
Face Off creations.
- Aw.
- Oh.
We have Rayce's cellist
from our Tim Burton-inspired
challenge...
Yeah.
Anthony's
bioluminescent creature.
Lastly, we have Laura's
Mother Earth creation
from our Earth goddess
challenge.
Now, on my go, the monitor
placed at each section
will display the image
of one of these characters.
There can only be
five companion characters
for each
of our champion makeups.
You better be quick to make sure
that you get the one you want.
You have two hours
to complete this challenge.
Good luck,
'cause your time starts now.
Aah!
- I want you.
- How you doing?
- I'm Gregory.
- Nice to meet you, Gregory.
Augustine.
Nice to meet you.
All right.
I wish I had, like, three hands
and one fourth one to write.
This is Rayce's side,
I believe?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I'm going to work
on your hair first
to get that out of the way.
My name is Emily Serpico.
I'm the youngest contestant ever
on Face Off, which is really,
really exciting.
I live with my parents,
and I'm going to
cosmetology school.
I may be underestimated
because I'm so young,
but I think people are gonna be
very surprised at what I can do.
Did you see what Emily
is doing with the hairdo?
It's like a hat.
- Oh, that's cool.
- Yeah.
So your story is,
you are a poet who's inspired
by Rayce's cellist.
Sweet.
Where are the prosthetics?
Ready to kick some ass.
I am so excited to be here.
I got Anthony's
bioluminescent character,
and I instantly
run toward the prosthetics.
Everybody's digging them up
like they're entrails,
just flying all over the place.
I find some pointy ears
and a brow piece,
and I just start rocking it.
_
I'm a trained artist,
but I've always loved monsters.
At 17 I started doing it
professionally, and I love it.
It's the best job in the world.
All right.
- See, we've got Mother Nature.
- Yeah.
- Now we want Father Time...
- Oh, sweet.
So your head is gonna be
like a grandfather clock
- grew into a tree.
- Okay.
I have my own special effects
makeup shop,
and I've been working on indie
films for about eight years
in North Carolina.
Being on Face Off
is a phenomenal opportunity
for me to break
into bigger films
and major Hollywood
blockbusters.
I like the route Greg is going.
He's thinking outside the box.
I really hope Laura picks me
to be on her team.
So I went straight
towards Mother Earth,
and I'm fabricating
this foam grandfather clock
to impress her.
Yeah, that's good.
- You nervous?
- It's a lot of pressure, man.
My concept is the antithesis
to Rayce's cellist.
You're an angry techno DJ.
It's a risky plan,
but it's not unheard of
for companions to be
very different from each other.
He's going
to be very dark-featured
with a prism laser light show
coming out of his face.
- How long you been doing it?
- A year and a half.
I don't actually
do it professionally.
I've spent ten years in the Air
National Guard in California.
I come from three generations
of military fighter pilots,
but I've always had a passion
for the effects world,
and I really feel like I need
to give myself the opportunity
to pursue it and get paid
to do it.
This is a dream right now.
Got these, got this.
All right, cool.
I'll be right back.
I'm Stephanie, I'm 21 years old,
and I work on the creative crew
of a haunted house.
Eyelashes? Ooh.
When I'm there,
I only have an hour to get
30, 40 people done,
so it's really gotten me ready
to tackle this competition.
I'm making you
one of Mother Nature's babies.
Whatever you need to win,
do it.
_
I am a creative director
in advertising.
_
I started to do special effects
because of Face Off,
but I've only been doing it
for about eight months.
My concept for this character
is, like,
a young brother version of
the character that Anthony did.
Of course I'm nervous
and excited.
I'm everything
in the same package.
_
Uh, well,
it's matching Mother Earth,
so I figure that you should be
like a protector kind of thing.
I've been a makeup artist
for approximately ten years,
self-taught.
I'm also a prop maker
and suit actor,
and since I'm 6'5" I normally
get asked to play the monster
as well as do
the special effects.
This isn't made for you
so I've got to fit it to you.
There we go.
Ooh, all right.
I like that he went flesh tone.
It looks like a more human
version of yours.
Right.
My name is Julian.
I'm from Fremont, California.
My character is a distant cousin
of Anthony's
bioluminescent creature.
Close your eyes.
I went to cinema makeup school
in Los Angeles,
and then I was working
for about five years
before I moved back
to the Bay Area
to help my parents care
for my younger brother Brent.
He has a disease that affects
his speech and motor skills.
Winning Face Off would mean
being able
to help out my brother.
It would also mean being able
to move back to LA
for another shot at my career,
so I'm gonna be going
for all the way.
You guys are all doing great.
You got one hour left.
You're freaking me out now.
I've never had
to create a character
in this short amount of time,
and I'm having a hell
of a time layering
on these laser lines.
Damn it.
I cannot get that paint
to stay down thick.
I start freaking out because I
know the coaches
are watching me.
This stuff's just
not cooperating with me at all.
There's no stopping.
There's no asking for help,
and I start thinking, "Am I
gonna be the only one out there
with nothing?"
We're in the middle of
our first foundation challenge.
Three champions
from previous seasons
are back to be our coaches.
We are creating a companion
for one of their makeups.
And I chose Rayce's cellist,
and my character is supposed
to have what resembles
the prism laser light show
coming out of his face,
but I cannot get
that paint to stay down.
I start freaking out,
because I know the coaches
are watching me.
Dammit.
And I'm desperately trying to
find something that will help.
I think it's interesting
that Logan went black.
Yeah, it's pretty dark
out of the gate.
Finally,
I apply silver metallic paints
that make the prosthetic pop,
and I think
that's a good attempt at making
it a little bit more dynamic.
Yeah, that's better.
Who'd Jamie end up getting?
Oh, Rayce's.
You're going to be a composer.
I'm a sci-fi fantasy chick.
I grew up with Star Wars
on VHS and laser ***
I've been working
as a freelance makeup artist
for about three years.
There aren't many women
in the effects industry,
but we can keep up
with these boys,
and I'm here to prove that.
Blood, sweat, and tears,
I will give everything
I got to be the next
Face Off champion.
Oh, there's Ben.
He's got yours.
- I'm doing Anthony's water guy.
- Uh-huh.
I'm gonna turn
you into his princess.
So crazy,
I never thought I'd ever be here.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I served in Iraq
from 2006 to 2007.
I was a helicopter mechanic
in the Marine Corps.
Growing up, I'd always sculpted,
and I wanted
to fine-tune my skills,
so when I got out of the Marines
I went to cinema makeup school.
A couple of my friends,
kind of gave me a hard time.
They thought that I was just
gonna be dressing hair
and doing fingernail polish,
but later when they saw
that I was making
monsters and creatures they
were pretty blown away by it.
Open up for me.
That don't look too bad.
Whoever thought that a big
burly guy could do makeup, huh?
_
Regina's doing
what I would have done.
Looks like she might be
putting on some ears?
I'm Regina.
I'm 23 from Chicago, Illinois.
I chose Laura's Mother Earth,
and my character's gonna
be her daughter.
I'm thinking "Woodland Nymph."
I'm fine artist trained.
I got into effects
four years ago.
One of my teachers
from makeup school
is Graham Schofield
from season six.
When he was on the show
he made it pretty far,
and I'm hoping
that I get to that point.
Yeah, we're gonna
do other things.
We're doing the fish guy,
and you're going
to be a lionfish.
I'm a concept designer
and art director
for the theme park industry.
I worked on rides
like Transformers, The Ride 3D.
Actually, I wanted to pull out
of theme parks
a number of years ago,
and then I saw that
Neville Page's first project
was designing aliens
on the Men In Black ride,
and I was like, "Okay,
I'm gonna stay on this path."
What I'm gonna do is I'm gonna
make you into the wizard
that actually turned him
into the cello.
I'm rob.
I'm 41 years old.
I work as a collision technician
at my family's collision shop
in Monroe, Michigan.
Special effects
has been my favorite hobby
since I was nine years old,
but when my daughter was born
I took six years off.
She was born with two holes
in her heart
and down syndrome.
Today she's eight years old.
Her name's Riley.
Her holes in her heart are good.
One night when we were watching
Face Off she brought me up one
of my sculptures and said,
"Daddy, you need to do this."
It hit me, you know,
I was like, "Wow, you know,
she understands this."
So here I am.
I'm basically making a version
of Father Time
- to go with Mother Nature.
- Okay.
I fell in love
with makeup in ninth grade.
All throughout high school
I did proms, I did weddings.
I'd create creatures
around Halloween.
Now that I've been doing film
and television makeup
for two years,
I want to win Face Off.
I'm a very competitive person,
and I do not plan on going home.
So I'm turning you
into a dead ballerina
that dances to his music.
Love it.
Watching Face Off
really inspired me.
I knew that I wanted to get
into the film industry,
and I knew I loved makeup,
but because of Face Off
I decided to go to school
and learn the special effects
craft.
After I finished school,
I competed
in three different IMATs.
I took first place twice.
Time is running out and I'm
frantically blending edges,
but the piece is too big
and it's covering her hairline.
What am I gonna
do to cover this edge?
And then I
see this giant pink flower,
so I stick it on my model's head
and I think, "This is burnin'."
Ten minutes, guys.
You have ten minutes left.
Still time.
Time's up, brushes down.
Before I send the coaches
down to check out your work,
I do have another surprise
for you.
Of course.
Hot off the set of The Hunger
Games, Mockingjay films,
please welcome three time
Academy Award-winning makeup
artist and Face Off
series judge, Ve Neill.
- Hey, everybody!
- Hey, Ve!
She's the Aretha Franklin
of the effects world.
I thought I was excited before,
and now I'm ecstatic.
- Well, this is exciting.
- I know, isn't this great?
- I am so happy to be back.
- All right, well are you
ready to help these champs
go see some makeups?
- Yeah, let's go.
- Okay.
Hi, Rob.
Tell us about your character.
He was a dark wizard
that changed the person
to the cello.
Tell me about the choice
of that prosthetic.
I wanted to show the brokenness
of the relationship between
the girl and the cello itself.
I think you did
a really great job.
It really reads wizard to me.
- Very complete.
- Thank you.
This is the ballerina
that is dancing to the music
that is constantly playing.
Explain to me some
of the coloration you chose.
I saw the skirt.
That's why I went with the pinks
and the darker reds
for the shading.
You did a really nice blending
job on just a stock piece.
You've got it down pretty well.
Thanks so much.
Thank you.
So you were going off
of Anthony's character.
Yes, this is a monk lionfish.
You as an artist, how do you
see yourself in this character?
Conceptually this is very
much me.
I like a lot
of story in the character.
Those kind of apes can be risky,
'cause they can hide
some of the details.
Good job on making
the correct choices
- and put them in the right spots.
- Great job, Adam.
Thank you.
This is my lovely sea
sorceress.
I like that you put the stripes
like Anthony
had his blue stripes.
I like the way
you painted around the eyes
and the contacts that you chose,
as well as the pie.
It really makes her eyes
look really big.
Thank you.
So I wanted to make Mother
Nature's dad, Father Time.
He basically is a grumpy
old hermit.
So how many prosthetics
does he have on?
Four, he has a brow piece,
two jowls,
and then a neck piece.
Well, nice job, I think
he looks like an old man.
- Good job, Anthony.
- Thank you.
This is a version
of Father Time,
and I wanted to do
a grandfather clock up here.
We didn't really know
where you were going.
It was very unpredictable,
which I think was a good thing.
A good idea.
So what did you guys
think the makeups?
I think, overall, we were
really impressed with everything
you guys did, and I don't think
there's one person
that we don't think
can take this thing all the way.
- Yeah, great job guys.
- Ve?
Well, I think
there were some very creative
and innovative choices made
today, and I'm really
excited about this season.
All right, guys,
it's time to pick your teams.
Now, we chose this order
by random draw.
Laura, you're up first.
This was so hard.
This choice is so important.
If you don't have
a good framework to work off of,
then your house will fall.
My first pick is--
Laura, who is the first contestant
you'd like
to have join your team.
I picked this person because I
thought their application
was nearly flawless,
I loved their color choices,
and I felt like their character
really fit the parameters
of this challenge.
So I have to go with Darla.
I'm so excited,
not only to be
the first one chosen,
but to be chosen by Laura.
She's been
through two full seasons,
and I can't wait to hear
all that she has to offer.
- Good first choice.
- Rayce.
To me there's many things
that define success
in this competition.
Attention to detail is one
of those I'd like to push so,
Adam, you're on my team, man.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks, man.
Anthony.
My first pick
would actually have been Adam.
There's something
about his visual storytelling.
But Rayce steals him
at the last second.
I really liked her application
of color
and the use
of the depth of color.
I choose Kelly.
Laura, your next pick.
My next pick is someone
who had an amazing application,
so I'm gonna
have to pick Julian.
- Rayce.
- Please don't pick Anthony.
Nobody pick Anthony.
I really want to pick him next.
Anthony, you did a great job.
Get over here.
Aw, man.
Welcome to the team.
- Anthony.
- Alan.
Laura.
So far Laura's
picked Darla and Julian.
There's only a few spots left
and I really want to be
on her team.
Emily.
And there goes another person.
Rob.
Ben.
Laura.
Gregory.
Now that she's picked me,
I'm definitely gonna
bring it for her,
because I want to show her that
I deserve a place on her team.
- Logan, get over here.
- All right.
- Daniel.
- Yes!
Welcome.
I'm gonna
have to go with Stephanie.
Regina, welcome to the team.
Jamie, come on.
We're gonna have a lot of fun.
Yay!
Congratulations, everyone,
on your new teams.
I know it's been
quite an exciting day,
but before I send you off
to move into your new house,
there's just one more piece
of business to attend to.
The champions weren't the only
ones making picks today.
Ve has selected
her own favorites
and a winner for
today's foundation challenge.
That means one of you
will receive immunity in
the first spotlight challenge,
increasing not just
your odds of surviving
but your coach's as well.
Having immunity
for the first round
would especially be good,
because I won't be as panicked
because I know
I'm not going home first.
So this is the big moment, Ve.
Who created your favorite looks?
My first choice is Rob.
You did a really great job of
picking some unusual components
and making
a very cohesive character,
and I love the texture
in the makeup.
Thank you so much.
Darla, you did a beautiful
clean makeup.
I loved your backstory,
and she was just adorable.
Thank you.
Ve, who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner is...
Darla.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Darla,
you created the best companion
- for Rayce's cellist.
- Thank you so much.
Really, really wonderful
story, darling.
Thank you.
I am ecstatic to win immunity.
I'm feeling sheer joy
and excitement,
and a little bit
of shock, maybe, too.
Darla, congratulations.
As the winner
of today's foundation challenge,
you have earned immunity in
the first spotlight challenge.
- How's that feel?
- Awesome.
Darla so deserved this win.
She made all the right
decisions.
Say good-bye
to your new coaches for now,
and I will see you soon for
your first spotlight challenge.
- Goodnight.
- Welcome to Face Off!
As soon
as we go through the gate
and I see the scale
of the house,
that's when it hits me.
I'm finally here,
and it feels really good.
- Wow.
- Guys!
I'm not believing
this is happening.
This house is just incredible.
- Aw, man.
- Oh, my God.
There's these black-and-white
photographs of Anthony, Rayce's,
and Laura's work.
And that's another moment we're,
like, "We're here."
I have never lived in a place
- this nice.
- Ow!
I'm gonna call this home
for as long as I can be here,
and hopefully I'm here
a long time.
Season eight!
- It is hot.
- What is this?
This is crazy.
I think they're leaving us
here to die.
Today is
our first spotlight challenge,
and we are at Vasquez Rocks.
And this has been the place
for many, many, many movies,
and I don't know really
what to expect.
- What is that?
- Oh, my gosh.
We see all these
alien crash sites
and it is crazy.
- That's awesome.
- We round this corner
and then I see this
gorgeous flowing white ponytail.
No way.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit, it's Rick Baker.
Oh, I'm not gonna geek out.
Be cool.
- No way.
- It's Rick Baker.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh!
Rick Baker is "the" makeup
artist, so seeing him is just--
I'm speechless.
- That's awesome.
- No way.
- Is this real life?
- Oh, my goodness.
This is, like, my biggest idol.
I start shaking.
I actually get a tear in my eye.
It gives me great pleasure
to introduce someone who
really needs no introduction.
Legendary makeup artist
and seven time Academy
Award-winner, Rick Baker.
It's an incredible honor to have
you here with us, is it not?
Yes!
You're gonna make me blush,
McKenzie.
That's my goal.
Now you have made
so many memorable makeups
across an incredibly diverse
range
of films like American Werewolf
In London,
Men In Black trilogy,
Star Wars,
Planet Of The Apes.
I mean, just small stuff
we got going on here.
What are some
of your personal favorites?
I would say Harry
from Harry And The Hendersons
is one of my all-time favorites.
I'm pretty pleased
with that one.
All right, guys, let's talk
about where we are today.
This is Double B Ranch
at Vasquez Rocks,
where countless
blockbuster films like
Cowboys And Aliens, Iron Man,
and Transformers 2
have been shot.
Filmmakers come here
when they're looking
for an otherworldly landscape,
and that brings me to your first
spotlight challenge.
You'll work with your champion-lead
teams of five.
Select one of the unique
extraterrestrial crash sites
around you here,
and use the evidence
from the wreckage as inspiration
for two aliens that might have
emerged from that crash.
Oh, my God.
I love aliens,
so I am so
excited for this challenge.
Why don't you go ahead
and stand with your teammates.
Winning team right here?
We got this.
All right, guys.
I have a big surprise for you.
Rick will be joining us
on the reveal stage,
but he's also going to consult
on your designs today.
I'm gonna start crying.
What are you gonna be looking
for in their final makeups?
The good thing
about doing an alien
is that you can do anything,
but just because you can do
anything
doesn't mean that you should.
I would like to see a nice
clean, well-thought out design
that I'd recognize as something
that's definitely alien.
You know, something
like Glenn Hetrick.
You know what I mean?
Oh, you went there.
Wow, okay.
All right, it's time
to get started, guys.
On my go I want
you to select a crash site
and begin working
on your concepts.
Rick will come by shortly
to collaborate with you.
- Is everyone ready?
- Yes.
All right, go.
- Oh, I got it.
- Get it, get it,
- get it, get it.
- You want this one?
Oh, my God.
I just touched it, it's gooey.
Team Laura,
we got to the egg crash site.
It's organic,
so we can think about
natural lifelike creatures.
Very, very slimy.
There's gold right here.
What would they do with it?
Team Anthony picks the crash
site that has the aircraft
that's all blown to pieces,
and there's guns, missiles,
gold.
It's just a big hodgepodge
of craziness.
This is the liquid they use to be
able to live in our atmosphere.
We could do an alien
in another alien world.
- I like that.
- Yeah.
Team Rayce picks the crash
site with the cryogenic pod
and alien crystals
coming out of the ground.
All right,
so let's get a little powwow
going for character design.
You guys want to do spines
on the top
of the head, on the back?
It could be on the back
of the arm too.
Maybe we can make it look like
the big monster has four legs,
but then give the little monster
little--
- Hi, Rick.
- Hey!
My team just barely starts
sketching and I look over.
Rick Bakers sitting right next
to me and I'm just--
What's your concept here?
What are you thinking?
Since there's a drill,
they go from planet to planet
and just take
whatever they want to,
and we're thinking there's gonna
be a warrior
that protects a little alien.
So the little alien is the one
that controls the plane
and it's gonna wear a helmet
all the time,
and then the larger alien
is the protector.
When they get
out of the aircraft,
he's the one
that's gonna protect her.
My only worry,
and since it is Face Off
and it's supposed
to be about makeup,
if one of them is just a helmet,
I don't know.
It seems kind of like a cop out
if you don't see what's inside.
- Hey, guys.
- Hello.
What's going on here?
We are piecing together
a story from this alien
drunk driver-ing.
What do you think happened
here?
This is clearly
not a and-alone ship,
so it's a escape pod,
and then we have the mutilated
deer over there so--
- Who did that?
- Well,
this is a predatory Cro Magnon
species relative to this planet.
So do you have some designs
for these things yet, or--
For the Neanderthal style I
thought, "We are in the desert,"
so the most resilient thing
that popped in my head was
a king scorpion.
It's arachnid,
so it'll be a combination
of spider, scorpion,
and grasshopper with,
like, a black outer shell,
and the tissue inside
is either pink or red.
I don't want to go purple.
I thought it was a little
too hokey.
Yeah, I don't know
that it's too hokey.
I like the idea
of a nice contrast like that.
Okay,
and then they've been working on
the higher intelligence alien.
We're going with an old,
aged wiser look,
and it's a water-based creature
that is capable
of interstellar travel
and that resembles
more traditional aliens.
Sounds like you guys
have some go ideas,
and I'm really curious
to see the final results.
So what are you thinking
happened here?
An alien transplanted
three eggs onto a desert.
As they landed,
two of 'em got out,
and the aliens
that came out of it are aquatic
instead of desert creatures.
We're gonna
have one more developed.
So it's going to blend
into the surroundings,
and the youngest one
just hatched,
and the female's gonna
be more smooth and slimy.
We were also gonna
go with claws.
Mm-hmm.
But we didn't want
to be too earthy.
"Too earthy"
meaning like earth--
Earth creature, yeah.
I get into this all the time
with Barry Sonnenfeld
when I'm doing the
Men In Black movies.
He says, "You know,
do something that doesn't look
like it's from this planet."
So I do something that doesn't
have eyes and a mouth,
and he goes, "I can't tell where
he's looking and how am I gonna
know when he's talking if he
doesn't have eyes or a mouth?"
You know,
so it's a delicate balance.
Hearing Rick give us advice
about our makeup,
it's probably one
of the greatest moments
I can ever say,
like, happened to me.
'Cause I mean,
it is Rick Baker.
Okay, so we've got enough down.
We've got enough pictures.
Let's go to the lab
and get started on this.
Sounds good.
Hey, does anyone want to go
for a ride in the jeep?
Hey, guys!
We walk into the lab and it
hits me for the first time,
"Oh, my gosh,
we're finally here."
Oh, my God.
This is the lab of my dreams.
There's an entire wall of
Kryolan Aqua Color,
amazing wigs,
and fabrication stuff
that I could never afford.
It's like Christmas over here.
I'm used to working
in my parents' garage--
half of a garage.
So this is just unbelievable.
So let's get moving.
Got to get some clay.
My team has a really solid
concept, I think,
but now we have to get sculpting
as soon as possible,
because we only have six
and a half hours in the lab
today.
The delegation is first order
of business.
I am sculpting the cowl
for the arachnid.
Regina's sculpting the face.
Rob volunteers for fabrication.
- So you want me to cover ears?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna build it out here
and then carve
in more of the divots.
As I'm working
on the face sculpt
for our higher intelligence
alien, I'm trying to do
these geometrically-shaped
mechanical gills over the mouth.
Do you want
them to be the same size,
because it's saying "repetition"
and then in your mind
it's saying "mechanical."
Sculpting mechanical parts
is not easy.
Pinch that in a little bit.
I know
that Anthony just started,
but there's some fundamental
form language issues with it,
and I'm really worried
about that.
If you have different sizes,
there's more organic language
happening here.
Yeah.
So we're now calling it
like "The Older"
- and "The Younger."
- Okay.
Our concept
is that one of them
hatched earlier than the other
and has already started
adapting to its environment.
The things that we would really
like to accomplish today
are both faces and both cowls,
as well as the back piece
for our older alien.
Luckily, that's five pieces
and we have five people
on our team.
Only concern, maybe that
these are getting a bit thick
and this might be a bit thick.
So this is the first time
we get to see
any of the artists sculpt.
And you might just want to make
the back the interesting part
and keep all of this smooth.
And I'm feeling
like I got a pretty strong team.
I'm gonna make you a--
Gonna make you a thing.
Uh, how are you guys
doing your ears?
Oh, yeah.
We didn't talk about ears.
With our concept,
we have the big male brute
and our small female pilot.
Ooh, yeah, right there.
I'm sculpting the male face
while Daniel
is sculpting the cowl.
Alan is fabricating armor
for the suits.
Jamie is sculpting
the female face,
and Ben is blocking the cowl
for her.
Can you see the glimmer
of sweat on my forehead?
Anything that's gonna be
humanoid is going to have
a similar muscle structure
as what our own is.
I definitely know
what the judges are looking for
and anatomy is always a key part
of it.
- Pull that out.
- Yeah.
They'll look like it's kind
of pulling in a little more.
- Yeah.
- Even though these are aliens,
they have to still be based on
some kind of realistic anatomy.
Hi, everybody.
Hey, Mr. Westmore!
Mr. Westmore is a legend
in the effects industry.
He's an Oscar winner,
and if there's one thing
I've learned
from watching the show
is if he gives you advice,
you take it.
Let's see
what you have going here.
Now what is this one
supposed to be?
This is the aquatic one.
What we're trying to do is
basically make horizontal gills
almost like a respirator
to give it this fishy vibe.
Mm-hmm.
It doesn't read that way though.
You're coming down here,
you've got lines here,
and these are straight.
- It's all over the place.
- Okay.
It's really gonna
look amateurish.
You have a big sculpting
background?
- Mm-hmm.
- You do? All right.
My heart drops into my stomach.
The fact that Mr. Westmore
is questioning my sculpting
abilities-- that's scary.
It needs a lot more work.
It is the first challenge,
and I'm losing my mind.
You see what I mean here,
where you're coming down here?
- It's all over the place.
- Okay.
It's really gonna
look amateurish.
It's day
one of our alien challenge,
and Mr. Westmore
doesn't like my sculpture.
Do you have a big sculpting
background?
- Mm-hmm.
- You do? All right.
It needs a lot more work.
It's like,
"Where do I go from here?
What am I supposed to do?"
I don't--
I don't know.
I'm lost.
I know there's a lot more work
to do.
Yeah.
Just be careful
with the angular point to it.
It can still be angular,
but it needs a lot more work.
Now let's see the cowl there.
In my mind I'm going towards
this ancient sea reptile.
Mm-hmm.
All these little angles,
all these little things
you have in here, roll them.
Not just scars in the sculpture.
Otherwise it's just gonna look
like you took a tool
- and scratched through it.
- Right, right.
Good, let's see the other
pieces.
That's coming nice.
Just looking at it in profile
here as opposed to these
laying almost flat like this,
if you actually raise them up
a little bit
you would have
a more interesting profile.
- Absolutely.
- Yeah.
We're thinking something
that has hatched
and is now trying to camouflage
itself to its new surroundings.
The skin is kind
of like the desert lizard.
You might texture
this a little bit more.
It's so nice and subtle,
I'm afraid that once this is
all painted it's not gonna read.
- Okay.
- This is the older one,
so he's going to be elongated
but also starting
to take on more human features.
I would try to put a little
- but more alien in the nose.
- Okay.
As opposed
to making it too human-looking
and then it makes it look like
it's a person with a mask on.
Okay, let's see your last head
there.
This one is the cowl
for the youngest,
and so it's a little bit less
defined as the older.
And you're doing that spine
that you have on the back
continuing?
- Yes.
- Good.
We've got two aliens.
There is the big
muscle-bound one,
and then there's the smaller
pilot of the aircraft.
Wow, very nice.
And then he's gonna be covered
here with a suit?
Yes, actually--
Is that what you're building
over there?
Yeah, I actually draped
the whole back end of the suit
so it actually accents nicely
and showoff
more of that muscle structure
and bone structure,
so you can see the whole back
of the head.
Good idea.
Good.
Let's go on to the next and see.
I wanted to kind
of get this down.
- Right.
- He's gonna be the one
taking the beating out there
in the battlefield.
Aggressive, very nice.
You know, one thing I think
would be an interesting thing
is make some separate lips here,
and use the same textures
you have here
to run right into the mouth.
Mm-hmm, awesome.
Are there any similarities
in your two cowls?
These were the similarities
right here.
Since he's the bigger creature
we went with her a softer form.
I would rethink the cowl
just to try to pull
a little bit more of that
into this or vice versa.
That makes sense.
Good-bye, everybody.
Good-bye!
All right,
let's talk about this fella.
I think what I should do
with this, in all honesty,
is cut all of this down,
do almost a flat nose
with nostrils--
slits, like right here.
Mr. Westmore's advice
just completely
changed my entire design.
I mean,
I'm back to the drawing board.
So I'm adding eyes
on either side of the face
and rounded shapes in the nose.
I'm hoping it's going
to make my makeup better.
Anthony's
starting over right now,
and I
think it's the right decision.
The face is the most
important part of the character,
and it needs to be right.
Make the details
a lot more subtle.
- Okay.
- All right, guys.
We got to head out,
so good luck.
I will be back tomorrow in
the beginning part of the day.
So if you can mold,
crystal clear, dulling spray,
and dust.
It's time for me
to leave my team on day one,
and I'm feeling pretty good,
but I'm hoping some of the molds
can get done so that tomorrow
we can get these characters
pre-painted.
Even though we're here to coach
and guide them,
ultimately they have to do
things for themselves.
We're out. Bye!
We're running out of time,
so as soon
as Jamie's done with the face
I take it into the mold room
and start molding it.
It's really important
to get this face out today,
because we want to be able
to have a foam latex piece
to put up against the cowl
and know exactly where that edge
line is so we know if we
need to bring the cowl forward
or push it back any further.
You know how it goes.
I would just get
this done and finished,
and then we can worry
about other stuff tomorrow.
Yeah. What I'm doing today
is a lot of fabrication.
I need to do a chest plate
for the arachnid,
and I still have to work
on our invading alien.
I have to work on weapons,
so I wanted to get as much done
as possible.
I'm gonna go on the arm
like this.
Awesome.
I just did them
like little pockets
and then, like,
tapered them down.
My face sculpt
is all blocked out.
I'm starting to go
into a little bit of detail.
We should definitely add,
like, the dryness--
the texture to it.
To, like,
at least the outer edges
- on this side I think.
- Yeah.
Darla's right next to me
working on the younger alien,
so I'm taking Laura's advice
and I'm looking back and forth
at both of them
and making sure they look like
they're from the same planet.
Hey, everybody,
it's 30 minutes!
So I have a couple more things
to do tomorrow.
That's time, everybody.
Wow.
It's the end of the day,
and I'm very happy
with the way that
the new sculpture is coming out,
but we have no molds done,
and Rob is still working
on the fabrication.
So I'm really nervous
about tomorrow
because we still have a lot
of work to do.
There's only two days left,
and I don't know
how we're gonna get it done.
Uh-oh.
Hey, guys.
Come on in and gather round.
Oh, my God.
Real monkeys!
There's monkeys!
It's crazy!
Wait, where's my sculpture?
I have another big surprise
for you.
There's a huge piece
of information
that I didn't share
with you yesterday.
Oh, no.
There's something happening,
and I don't know what it is,
but things
are about to get real.
Even the coaches
don't know what's going on.
This is completely crazy.
Your spacecraft
didn't crash-land on Earth.
- Oh, no.
- Oh.
It crash-landed on a planet
controlled by primates
who are not happy
to see your alien invaders.
So you'll each be choosing
one of these simians
as inspiration
for a third character.
- Yeah.
We had a plan,
and now that's out the door.
I can feel the nerves
radiating off of my team.
This is already
a tough challenge,
and now it's gonna
get a little tougher.
Everything changes,
and I'm freaking out.
This competition,
it's unbelievable.
We're going to be in trouble.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net