This was a very smart direction
to take it.
It's lackluster this week.
It is spot-on, perfect.
Previously on Face Off,
Adam's imaginative monster
brought him his first win,
but Ben's design decisions
sent him home,
making Anthony
the first returning champion
to be eliminated.
Now only five artists remain,
and tonight they'll toy
with disturbing designs.
So scary.
Oh, my God.
But as the finale approaches,
some artists will crack.
Are you talking
about starting over?
Yeah.
Today is lost.
Holy shit!
That's it, I'm done.
It is absolutely thrilling.
In the end, only one will win
a VIP trip from
Kryolan Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand-new 2015 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
This is Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
What's up, brogan?
I'm starting to feel,
like, creatively drained.
I didn't do so well in
the last spotlight challenge.
And we're all just
exhausted at this point.
I can't stand whimsical.
We're almost done.
You're almost to the finale.
Just push through it.
A big part of the reason
for being here
was because
of my younger brother Brent.
He has NBIA,
which is a neurologic illness.
I'm trying to raise awareness,
and if I win the money,
I would donate
a large portion of it
to research for his disease.
We've got our
work cut out for us.
Definitely, but we can do it.
If I'm gonna get
to this finale and win,
I'm really gonna have
to bring my A-game.
Team Laura in the finale.
Top five and Team Laura
in the finale.
We walk into the Bob
Baker Marionette Theater,
and I'm so excited.
I love the energy of puppets,
and I think it's so cool to see
all the different marionettes,
and I can't wait to hear
what our challenge is.
Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Welcome to the historic
Bob Baker Marionette Theater.
Bob Baker was a legendary
puppeteer and marionette maker
who spent a lifetime
creating incredible pieces
to appear alongside some
of Hollywood's biggest icons,
like Judy Garland
and Elvis Presley.
His work has also appeared
in major motion pictures,
like Close Encounters
Of The Third Kind
and Addams Family Values.
It's pretty amazing, huh?
Oh, this is awesome.
This enchanted setting
is the perfect backdrop
for your spotlight challenge,
because this week
you'll be creating
and original character
inspired by a classic doll.
I'm pretty positive
that this is gonna be
another whimsical challenge,
so I'm worried.
I have brought seven
classic dolls
for you to choose from.
However, before you
make our choices,
there's something else you need
to know about the dolls.
Of course.
Not all cultures
consider them child's play.
That's so scary.
Oh, my God.
This darker side
of the doll world
has led to some
iconic horror films,
like Poltergeist,
The Conjuring,
and of course, Child's Play.
So for this week's
spotlight challenge,
you won't be creating
something happy and pretty.
_
You'll be creating an evil,
demonic doll character
inspired by one of these dolls.
Oh, God.
Logan, you're up first.
Voodoo doll.
Ventriloquist.
Baby.
Porcelain doll.
The ragdoll.
Oh.
This is so creepy.
Now, I want you to make sure
that you tap into
the colors, materials,
and cultural history
of your dolls for inspiration.
See you guys on the reveal stage
in a few days.
Have fun, and good luck.
Bye.
I'm actually pretty excited.
This is pretty fun.
I picked the baby doll,
and I decide that my character
is used for religious practice.
When a human touches
the baby doll,
that human's life-force
is sucked into the doll.
I come up with this doll face
that's cracked open,
with a tentacle monster
on the inside of it.
I actually had a porcelain doll
when I was a little girl,
so this is bringing back
a lot of memories.
I think a good way
to make this doll really creepy
is to make it appear broken.
I'm going to keep the classic
porcelain doll
shape of the face,
but then add a lot
of cracking texture.
I'm pretty excited
about this concept.
I picked the voodoo doll
because there
are certain elements
about the voodoo doll itself--
the stitching, the burlap--
that are very unique
as opposed to the other dolls.
I decide that my character
is a child
who was tortured with
a voodoo doll relentlessly,
to the point where it started
to transform him physically.
So I'm turning a man
into a doll.
I am so excited.
I picked the ragdoll.
I decide that the family dog
took this ragdoll
out in the rain, ripped it up,
then the little girl brought it
back into the house.
And it's soaking wet,
and it starts to mold,
and it's slowly
killing the family
by releasing mold spores.
Oh, God, it's so creepy.
I picked
the ventriloquist dummy
just 'cause I've always been
kind of creeped out by it
since I was little.
My concept is that he was carved
out of a sacred tree
by a witch to be her minion.
So I want to incorporate
wood texture into the sculpt,
try to figure out how to get
a rigid jaw piece
to get that flapping motion.
All right, guys,
let's head back to the lab.
We have five
hours in the lab today,
and my priority is not even
to think about the face.
It's just to get the chest done.
There's no exceptions.
Since I'm creating
a ripped-fabric look,
I need to find something
that will give it
that fabric texture.
And I see crepe wool,
which is used for hair work.
That'd be neat.
It's exactly
what I want to sculpt,
so I'm not gonna sculpt it;
I'm gonna mold it.
What are you trying to do?
I'm making a mold
of this texture,
so then I can put the clay in it
to get the fabric.
Oh, yeah, yeah, okay.
Once I have my mold,
I roll out the clay
into little logs,
and I press it into the mold,
and then I just pull them apart
and place it all over the chest.
All right.
Hey, Laura.
Hey, how you guys doing?
I'm great.
Oh, gosh, where are the dolls?
They're over
in the corner there.
Oh, my God, they're creepy.
Yeah.
You excited
about this challenge?
Yeah.
I got the baby doll,
so I came up with a story
where a baby is a portal
for demons to come through.
I think if you
can pull this off,
it'd be great.
But if everyone is just
doing faces and cowls,
they're gonna be able
to put more time into that.
Right.
Which could make their faces
and cowls look better,
if you're not careful.
I understand.
I don't want Logan and Adam
to lose that risk factor.
I don't want them
to play it so safe
that it bores everyone.
But it's getting that time
in the competition
where you can't have
one slip-up.
I only have two artists
left on my team.
I don't want to lose
anyone else.
I'm gonna do
a broken porcelain doll.
Oh, it's so creepy.
Once it's glued back together,
the little girl doesn't want
to play with it anymore,
so then the cracks are now
where the evil comes from.
You could actually
exaggerate the head,
I think, a little bit.
A little bit further?
- Further.
- Yeah.
If I sculpt the head
just a little bit too big
for the body,
that'll really help kind of
sell the creepy factor.
And that's exactly what I want.
After I finish the chest piece,
I run it to the mold room
and start molding
as fast as I can.
I need to get this done
so I can start
sculpting the face.
Hi, everybody.
- Hey.
Hi.
- Hi, Logan.
- Hey, Mr. Westmore.
How are you?
I'm essentially creating
a human-voodoo doll hybrid
- these will be forms...
- Okay.
...to which I will
apply the burlap
where it's been
infused into the flesh.
That should work very well.
When you get down
to your edges here,
make sure you get
all those down,
as opposed to getting
a hard edge right there.
All right.
This baby doll
is actually a portal
for demonic possession.
There's something
coming through the doll
from hell or another dimension.
You're really going way out.
Yeah.
Be careful.
Don't lose "baby doll,"
that you all of a sudden
wind up making a monster...
Right.
That doesn't really relate
to what the challenge is.
I understand what
Mr. Westmore has to say,
but I don't want to put a big,
baby-headed doll out there.
I'd rather go complete 180
and at least make something
different that stands out.
- Well, good luck.
- Thank you very much.
I selected
the ventriloquist dummy.
This is actually
gonna be wood grain here?
Yes.
Old carved wood.
Okay, I like what you're
doing with the mouth here.
Now, you can glue this down
nice and tight,
so when he does open his mouth,
that will work the same way.
Okay.
So this is the porcelain doll.
Porcelain doll.
I'm gonna make it
look as though
it's broken into large pieces
that have been glued
back together.
You've got such a nice
base sculpture going for you.
Be careful with the cracks now.
Okay.
Usually there's a major spot,
and then from the place
they've originally cracked from,
it thins.
It's almost like a few
little branches off of it.
Yep.
Now, you have the ragdoll.
What are you planning
on your facial sculpture?
I'm going to make button eyes,
and have one here, one that
kind of popped and falls.
You know what'd be interesting
is to take
some good-size thread
and attach it up in here
so it looks like the thread
has actually come loose.
- Good luck.
- Thank you so much.
Good luck, everybody.
Your sculptures look wonderful.
- Thanks.
- Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
My mold's not very ready.
But if I don't get
this chest done today,
I will be so far behind.
So I need to open it now.
As I pull it apart,
it opens nice, but then...
Holy shit!
It just falls.
I expect to see this mold
just in pieces
when I lift it up.
Oh, no.
And all I'm thinking is,
"That's it, I'm done."
It's the first day
of our creepy doll challenge.
And as I pull it apart,
my chest mold just falls.
Holy shit!
I expect to see this mold
just in pieces.
But I pull it up,
and the mold is thick enough
where it was able
to take the blow.
Wow.
How did that not break?
It has a slight crack in it.
But then I realize
it's supposed to have
that distressed look anyway,
so it's okay.
So what are these gonna be?
Burlap.
I think it'd be much easier
to lay the burlap over the top,
instead of sculpting
the burlap.
I essentially need to sculpt in
basic forms on the face
to represent burlap.
And I'm usually very receptive
to Rayce's inputs,
but he's got his own aesthetic;
I have mine.
It's not that I'm trying
to, like, totally
disrupt your design.
It would actually be
more realistic.
All right, are you
talking about starting over?
To do that, yeah.
Ultimately, this is my project.
This is my character.
It's my responsibility
and my burden.
Rayce is my coach.
But he's been right repeatedly.
So this is challenging.
That's looking better?
Yeah, I think that's great.
Looks like you're
in a good direction.
Have fun.
See you.
See you, guys.
- Later.
- See you later.
- Bye.
- See you.
One hour.
I know I want to distort
the human face a lot.
I'm just worried
about pulling it off
in a way that doesn't
look goofy.
I'm just starting to take
into consideration
how to turn up the flow
and go in and out
of the pieces of the face.
I really love it.
Day one is winding down.
Finally I realize that
I originally had liked my plan.
I just needed
to execute it better.
There's no point in wasting time
or crying over it.
And I tear the clay
all the way off
to essentially just reset.
This is not a great way
to start out the challenge.
I look around, and I see a lot
of progress everywhere else,
and zero progress on my face.
That's time, everybody.
Today is lost.
And for the first time
in the competition,
I'm leaving the lab
without being satisfied.
And that worries me.
It's too close to the finale
to be going home.
Morning!
Good morning.
It's day two
of our creepy doll challenge.
We have 9 1/2 hours in the lab.
First thing that I need to do
is finish both of these sculpts.
What I'm gonna do is
have these little cracks
in certain areas.
Cool.
I start adding really small,
fine cracking detail,
as if it's an infection
that's spreading.
I'm really happy with the way
things are looking,
but I do need to get
into the mold room
about halfway through the day
to make sure
that I have enough time
to get both of the molds
ready for foam.
So creepy.
So you started over.
Rayce notices that I've
removed the entire face.
What made you start over?
I think I threw
clay on too fast,
and it just didn't look right.
I'm gonna start
with a foundation.
Then, on top of that,
I can build detail.
It's more authentic that way.
I need to more deliberately
lay down the seams, you know?
I'm a little shocked, but...
I actually really like the idea
that Logan decided
to start from scratch,
because now he's
going to be able
to put in some more
anatomically correct forms,
and I think that the burlap's
gonna lay over
those forms better.
If you go too far
with the texture...
It might come off
as, like, a wooden...
It will come off as,
like, a tree-type creature.
In order to give this cowl
the appearance
that it's made of wood,
I start sculpting lines
on the side
of the back of the head.
I've never sculpted hair before.
And I've only just now
sculpted wood texture.
So I'm trying to do
two different things
that I've never done before
in one sculpt.
It's a little more difficult
than I pictured.
This wig is the ugliest wig
in the wig room.
I'm going to create
a jute dreadlock yarn wig.
I take a hideous blonde wig,
cut off the top,
pre-cut some jute,
and I start gluing it down,
and then I start to unravel
the jute to break it up
and give it more
of a distressed look,
but it's taking forever.
Is there a power tool
or something you could use
to create it?
Laura suggests
that I start sanding it.
It's working beautifully,
and it's taking
a lot less time.
I'm looking at Adam's sculpture,
and there are some things
that are just
really throwing me off.
I think it would be wise
to bring out some of the doll.
I'm trying to get away
from this person in a doll mask
as much as I can.
I'm just really concerned.
He could save this
in the paint,
but I'm really worried.
You just want to be careful
with going too extreme.
Rayce just keeps telling me
that I may be sidestepping
the challenge
and not going "doll" enough.
I am going really big on this,
and standing out
could put me on bottom.
I just don't want to put
a big baby out on the stage.
But now there's
this nagging worry.
I could be
just fucking this up.
I don't have time
to deal with this,
but at the same time, I do know
that if it's not up to par
with everybody else,
it could send me home.
I'm just getting frustrated
at this point.
I'm completely lost
with my concept.
I'm worried about him
not reading "doll" enough.
It's day two
of our creepy doll challenge,
and Rayce is a little worried
that I'm not going "doll" enough
and that my character
could send me home.
Rayce is right.
It is really pushing
the boundary
of what this challenge is.
But in this competition,
it's more than just
addressing the challenge.
It's showing who you are
as an artist.
And I'm all about
pushing boundaries.
I love looking different.
So I decide to just
embrace this opportunity
and go out of the norm
and just have fun.
So I'm just moving forward.
All right,
I'm gonna let you go.
- We'll see you, good luck.
- See you.
Thank you much.
See you, guys.
Have fun.
For my voodoo doll,
I think it'd be neat
if there was a pin
going through him entirely.
I think that gives a more
interesting silhouette.
But I need to find the lightest
weight materials possible
to make this pin.
I find small-gauge
armature wire,
small foam tubing,
and actually a clown nose
made of foam.
I glue it down
and start painting.
I think it will definitely sell
the voodoo doll part of it,
as opposed
to just a burlap doll.
So I think that's something
that has to be a part
of my character.
Really like that.
Thanks, man.
Kind of want it.
My plan for the wig
is to do a hairstyle
like a porcelain doll
with the big curls
and just really try
and make this wig
as messy and dirty
and ugly as possible,
but still kind of fitting
that doll character.
Sick.
We have less than an hour,
and I make flat mold
specifically for the shoulder
that matches up with the top
of the chest piece,
and I have to get these done.
Oh, shit!
I just cracked my mold.
The most important flat mold
completely breaks
down the center.
I literally do not
have time for this,
so I'm just gonna scrap it,
but it's not good.
Shit.
That's time.
Now I don't have that piece.
I have to figure something out
during application.
I don't feel good,
and it sucks.
It's application day
for the doll challenge,
and we have four hours
in the lab
and one hour at last looks.
Pretty decent.
The first thing I do
is look at my foam pieces.
The edges around the eye
are great,
and for the most part
everything else is.
Like, the wig's gonna
cover all this anyway.
The edges are nice and thin.
Ew.
Ew, Darla, that's sick.
But if those cracks
don't stand out,
then it's kind of
a wasted effort.
So I need to get
these pieces applied quickly
so that I leave myself a lot
of time for the paint job.
How are you?
- How you doing?
- I'm good.
Good to see you again.
So you're
a demonic porcelain doll.
- It's going to be awesome!
- Yeah.
I'm pre-painting the face piece,
and the details are coming out.
The tentacles look
nice and slimy.
I'm also applying a black
mesh screen around one eye.
This allows her
to see through it,
but because there's
no light inside,
it just looks
like an empty socket.
- Is that comfortable?
- Yeah.
I apply the face to my model.
It's actually fitting
really well.
I still have
to make the doll face
read more "doll face."
But it's looking
to be a promising character.
I need to start working
on this paint job.
Because this is a doll
that's supposed to be
from the 17th century,
I need to make sure that this
looks very, very old.
It looks like old paint, right?
Right.
If you find the place
that just doesn't
have a lot of visual interest,
just cover that up, or cover it
on the top of the head.
Laura suggests
I mix up some alginate
and apply it
onto the foam latex.
When it dries, it actually
starts to crack and shrink.
And this could be
a really cool texture
for chipped old paint.
Even if it does fray
a little bit and come up,
it'll actually
kind of add to the look.
I start laying in the burlap
on the face.
I take pieces that are bigger
than what I need,
adhere them, and then trim them
to sell the idea that this whole
thing is stitched together.
I think it looks great.
I start sponging
on a layer of pax paint
that has that sort of pink,
peach porcelain color to it.
And once I get the base layer
of pax on,
I use a wash
of alcohol-based paints
that I've thinned down
so it's very watery.
I brush this color
over the cracks,
and then I use a sponge
to wipe away any of the excess.
This is a little bit
of trial and error.
But now that I've got
the hang of it,
I'm just gonna
go to town with this.
- That's really cool.
- Thank you.
That's a nice effect.
Because I scrapped the shoulder,
I need to figure out
what I'm gonna do instead.
So I decide to use cotton
to fill it in,
because it's so much of a gap.
And I add thread to the edges
so it looks like the doll
has been ripped apart
and all the stuffing
is coming out.
So now it looks
like it's a complete character.
I start to airbrush
a mocha-brown color
into all the creases,
and I start dry-brushing
with a highlighted color.
I've never done
this type of paint job before,
so it's definitely
something new to me.
But it's starting
to look pretty cool.
You have to take
many steps back and squint
to make sure that's
not looking muddy.
Overall contrast, you need
to bring this chest out.
You'd want to go in
with the blacks
and spray it, though, first.
Rayce is trying
to explain to me
what he thinks would look best,
and it's just not sinking in.
You're throwing
a lot of things at me.
What are you thinking
I'm supposed to be
doing right now?
I mean, I can't even think
about what I would be doing
by myself.
Now I'm doubting myself.
It's stressful.
Ten minutes.
That's time, everybody.
I am nowhere near
proud of this piece.
I still have to work
on the eyes
and do a whole lot of work
to the mouth.
I could be screwed.
This is probably the most
I've ever had to do
in last looks.
I have to finish puppet paws,
apply a face, apply a wig,
and just finish the makeup.
I'm sweating bullets.
It doesn't look good,
and I'm desperately
trying to fix it.
I start with giving some depth
to the eye,
and then I'm going
to be painting
for the entire hour.
Okay, keep your mouth
closed for a sec.
I still need to attach
the doll pieces,
address the back of the neck,
address the front
of my model's neck,
airbrush everything,
and tie it all in together.
I've got a bit to do.
I'm just scatterbrained
right now.
Luckily I got done
with my paint job,
so I'm really able to focus
on detail work.
Perfect.
I need to make sure
this paint job really pops.
Not having the finishing details
can send you home at this point.
Ten minutes, everybody.
That's time, everyone.
I take a step back
and look at the makeup,
and the paint job is not
exactly where I want it to be.
I think it looks
a little too muddy.
So I'm nervous about this.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
As you know, one of you
will be going home tonight.
But before we see
your creations,
let's say hello
to our series judges.
Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening, guys.
Good evening.
Ve Neill.
Hi, everybody.
Hi.
And Neville Page.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
And we are very lucky
to have a special guest
joining our panel tonight.
He's a true Hollywood
triple threat--
writer, director,
and producer--
and it just so happens
that he created the most iconic
evil doll character
in film history, Chucky.
Please give a warm welcome
to Don Mancini.
Thank you.
Thank you guys so much
for having me.
It's really exciting.
Don Mancini created Chucky.
Out of all the demonic dolls,
he made the most demonic doll.
It's awesome.
I hope he likes mine.
Thank you so much
for joining us tonight.
I'm thrilled to be here.
This is exactly
in my wheelhouse.
I'm really curious to know
what you think it is
about Chucky
that has resonated
so strongly with audiences.
There's something almost primal
about a creature that looks
human but is not quite.
I think that's
the essence of it.
All right, well,
you ready to see
what these guys
have come up with?
Definitely.
Me too; let's do this.
Julian, you're up.
It's really creepy.
It's just up to the judges
at this point
whether it's enough.
I think I did a good job.
He's a scary character.
I'm definitely happier
than I thought I was gonna be.
I'm thrilled.
She's so creepy.
This is definitely
my favorite makeup
that I've done
in this competition.
I really love my character.
She's creepy,
definitely has an impact.
Everything turned out
exactly the way I envisioned.
So I'm proud of it.
All right, judges,
why don't you go ahead
and take a closer look?
It reminds me a
little bit of the zombies
from John Carpenter's movie
The Fog.
I wish that the hair
and the skin
differed in tone.
I just wish all the tones
had a lighter range.
It does read wood grain,
but there's almost
too much of it.
It's kind of Chucky-esque,
isn't it?
With the stitching
and the raw eye.
This is awesome.
I almost wish there were
a few more of them.
But I love it.
It's a simple solution
that really helps to convey
the inspiration for the makeup.
Jeez!
No, thanks.
These cracks
are so well rendered.
It really looks like porcelain.
Phenomenal.
She did the wig really well.
Just looks like
a filthy, dirty hair
that a child's played with
forever, you know?
Thank you.
I'm kind of disappointed
that this part here isn't
a little bit more realistic.
It's confusing, too,
as to what's going on.
These don't really look
like cracks,
and this doesn't really
look like hair.
I have something that looks
completely different
than all the other contestants,
and I'm worried that it's
so far from a makeup
that it may put me
on the bottom.
Tell us who made your favorite
evil doll character
tonight on Twitter
using hashtag #FaceOff
The hollowing out of this eye,
it almost comes out of, like,
a bad pirate eye patch.
All I really have on stage
is a cool concept,
so I'm hoping that's enough.
I love that none of the
facial features are addressed
it's completely anonymous.
Still, the whole thing
is so expressive.
I love the way that the hair
affects the entire
overall silhouette.
It's not just hair.
Thank you.
Okay, guys, the judges would
like to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Logan, please step up.
Tell us how your voodoo doll
inspired your creation
here tonight.
He was a victim
of voodoo doll sorcery,
so much so that he started
to become a voodoo doll himself.
Now he has this misguided sense
of vengeance.
I like the overall vibe
of the character.
If you integrated the magical
component a little more,
it would take it
away from scarecrow
and more
into voodoo doll for me.
But I do really like
the overall concept.
Thank you.
I really like this character.
You did the literal translation
of the doll,
but all in all,
he's a darn
scary-looking dude.
Good job.
Thank you.
The palette of this
is really fantastic,
almost like
pointillistic paintings,
where all the bits and pieces
create the palette.
Head to toe,
it's a solid, solid character.
Thank you.
I feel like some
of the stitching
and the raw flesh effect
around the right eye
reminds me of Chucky.
It reminds me of, like,
Bride Of Chucky,
Seed Of Chucky era.
Yeah, I dig it.
Thanks very much.
Logan, you can step down.
Good job.
Thanks.
Emily, please step up.
Please tell us
about your ragdoll.
A mother made this doll
for her child,
and then the dog
takes it outside,
rips it up,
and it gets all moldy and gross,
and the doll gets angry,
'cause she's not wanted,
and starts slowly
killing the family.
She is terrific.
Thanks.
Did you lay out crepe wool
and mold it?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah? Really clever idea.
I think you did
an excellent job, darling.
Thank you.
I think this is so effective.
The simplicity of the face,
how you just have
the button eyes
and there's really no nose,
I feel bad for her
as well as being spooked.
I love it.
Thank you.
The use of the extraordinarily
long dread extensions
did more than just add hair.
It massively affected
the overall silhouette
of the character,
and that is so impactful.
So I'm impressed.
Thanks.
Emily, please step back.
Okay, thanks, Megan.
Good job.
Thanks.
Julian, please step up.
Tell us about your
ventriloquist dummy character.
Back in the 1600s,
a witch carved
this ventriloquist dummy
out of a sacred tree
as a demonic minion.
There's a few details
that make it difficult
to read easily.
I would probably adjust the wood
so that it feels
more wood-like
and maybe less textural.
I also think a fake
large sculpted eye
would have sold it
a bit better.
Okay.
He almost can appear
like a zombie
rather than specifically
what you're going for.
This is effectively creepy,
but there, for me,
was a little bit
of a dissonance there.
Sure.
It doesn't immediately convey
the idea
of a carved wood puppet.
Something more angular
and chiseled
would have helped a lot.
Also, some other tones
to pull the hair
away from the face,
that would have helped too.
Julian, thank you.
Thanks, man.
All right, let's talk to Adam.
Tell us how your doll
inspired your work this week.
When someone touches the doll,
their soul is sucked in
as this stark, elemental,
greater being comes out.
It's just too big conceptually.
I'm just not sure
that it's that appropriate
for this specific challenge.
I agree.
The remainder of the doll,
the portion of the doll
that we still see,
that should have really looked
like a rubber doll.
And I also think
that these big gaping holes
around the eyes
do not read "doll-like" either.
You didn't quite get
to the doll zone for me today.
Okay.
You have to be a little bit
more conscious
of what the physical
parameters are
of plastic being stretched
by a demonic entity.
And I think
that's what's missing,
is the animated quality
of what has happened to this.
Adam, please step back.
Darla, please step up.
Tell us about your concept,
please.
She was a little girl's doll.
The girl dropped her,
and she broke.
So she cast it aside,
and the doll found
this enchanted mirror.
She uses the mirror
to attack people
that are looking
in other mirrors.
She's amazing.
Thank you.
This captures
what is fundamentally
most effective about
the living doll concept
and why it's
so primally frightening,
because it's
so freaking disturbing.
Congratulations.
Thank you so much.
You've managed to get
the proportions so doll-like,
and the head is creepy
and swollen.
It is absolutely thrilling.
Thank you so much.
I love the sheen on the skin.
The paint job up close
is spectacular.
I love the dark sockets.
It just gives it
that spooky look.
Holy cow, dude.
I don't know how you did it.
It's amazing.
Thank you.
Darla, please step back.
Thank you, sweetie.
All right, thanks, guys.
Please head back
to the makeup room
while the judges deliberate.
All right, judges,
let's talk about
tonight's evil dolls.
Why don't we start
with Logan's?
It was a guy
turning into a doll.
He should have just said
it was a doll.
Right.
I really did
like the complex colors.
There was purples,
and there was pinks.
There was a variety that made
one harmonious palette.
All right,
let's move on to Emily.
I love that simple face,
but so much emotion
really comes across.
I love characters
where you can see
the broken heart
inside the monster,
and I feel that she really
accomplished that.
How she laid those
buttons falling off
and the eyelashes,
everything was just
so beautifully done.
All right, judges,
let's move on to Darla.
The porcelain and the cracks
were all weathered with
really nice yellows and browns
to stunning effect.
That character is so creepy,
so spooky, so beautiful.
That could have gone
on camera right now.
It's an incredibly
effective evocation
of the living doll concept.
All right, judges,
let's move on to Julian.
It's a good idea
to have it be so old.
It takes it
out of the expected.
But I don't think he applied
the right sculptural
and painting techniques
to give it the clarity
it needed to tell his story.
It needed some paint
that was once there
that has weathered off.
Exactly, like whitewash,
like, chipped away
with darker tones underneath.
That would have been awesome.
Shape-wise, it just
didn't work for me.
All right, why don't we
move on to Adam.
I just really appreciated
the originality of that idea,
of a doll possessed.
But the fact that he
left one human eye in there
and blocked out the other one,
that made no sense to me.
I couldn't agree more.
It looked like what it was,
which was a piece of cloth
stretched across the hole.
It was so contrived,
it didn't communicate the story.
All right, judges,
have you made up your minds?
We have.
Okay, let's bring them back out.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about tonight's top looks.
Emily,
you made such clever choices
with your materials
and concept this week,
and we thought that they
complement each other
beautifully.
And Darla, you nailed
the shapes of the face,
and the paint job looked
like real cracked porcelain,
even up close.
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner of tonight's
challenge is...
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner of tonight's
challenge is...
Darla.
Thank you.
People at home
may not understand
how technically difficult it is
to pull off that kind
of sculpting and painting.
Those shapes and textures
are really tough.
Unbelievable work this week.
Thank you so much.
I'm so excited
to win this challenge.
This is a really important time
to be winning challenges.
It just gives me
that extra spark.
Darla, congratulations.
You and Emily are safe.
Logan, you are also safe.
You can all head back
to the makeup room,
along with your coaches.
- Good luck.
- ***
Unfortunately, that means
the two of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be going home.
Please step forward.
So, Glenn,
tell us about the bottom looks.
Julian, you definitely captured
the doll in your makeup,
but the shape of your face and
some of the painting techniques
soften the overall image.
Adam, love that
you think big-picture,
and while the faraway read
was really good,
there were just too many things
that didn't quite come together.
So who's going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Adam.
You have given us
some insanely cool concepts
this season.
But this one was just
a little too far away
from this week's challenge.
It's all good.
Adam, I'm so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
That means, Julian,
you are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Adam, I'm really sorry
to see you go,
but where you're going
is probably straight to work,
because you're
a very employable guy.
Thank you.
Adam, it's really been great
having you here with us.
But if you'd please
head back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thanks.
Good luck.
I really just wanted
to show people my designs,
and I did that.
They didn't like baby arms.
I have no idea what's next,
but I got affirmation
I can make monsters.
I'm really impressed
with everything you did.
I'm so thankful
for this opportunity.
I've had such a
great experience
and I've done so many
amazing things on the show
that I can't wait to see
where that takes me.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net