Oh, my God,
season 8.
Let's go.
I am Naomi Smalls,
and I am 21 years old.
Check your lipstick
before you come for me.
Naomi is a tall glass of water.
She has legs all the way up
to her asshole.
Language!
From Naomi Campbell
and Biggie Smalls.
First one,
I don't blame them.
I'm obsessed
with '90s supermodels.
I'm gonna set myself
right in the center.
Yeah, spotlight on me.
Naomi is a fashion girl.
She's fucking fierce.
We'll see.
How you doing mis amores?
Do you want to see my cuckoo?
Honey, your cuckoo
is the first thing we noticed.
How are you?
I'm from Puerto Rico, but
I live in Austin, Texas, y'all.
I call myself between
pageant queen and performer
'cause I do comedy,
I do campy sometimes.
Sometimes?
You know.
I'm sexy as a goddess is
and funny as a clown.
Are you ready for me?
Oh, my God,
the room is huge.
Fantastic,
so my cuckoo have a space.
I need a space--
Watch out,
new thunder effects.
What's up, nerds.
Ah!
My name is
Dax ExclamationPoint,
and I am the queen
of all nerds.
It's Storm.
I'm a cosplayer, and my look
is very inspired by,
like, science fiction
and comics.
Superheroes.
Just strong, bad bitches
who don't take any crap
from anybody else.
You do you, girl.
So I'm just gonna sit
right here.
Okay.
Can I get some brunch?
Country breakfast is ready.
Hola.
The beauty is here.
My name is Naysha Lopez.
Can we call her NayLo?
Element of my drag
has to be appearance.
It sounds so shallow,
but my drag is flawless.
It's gorgeous.
It's stunning.
It's everything.
Did I say it was stunning
and gorgeous?
Did I say that already?
Okay.
That lady repeats herself.
Naysha is here!
Yes, my sister!
Whoo!
Continental sisters.
Oh, yeah.
So you're Puerto Rico also,
or from Austin?
I'm originally
from Puerto Rico,
but, um, I live in Chicago.
That's a little frog
in Puerto Rico.
They are so annoying.
Why is she squirping
like a chirper?
You don't even understand
what she's saying,
but you don't really care.
Shantay, she sprays.
No need to adjust
your TV sets.
This acid trip is all real.
Watch out, bitches.
Here's Acid Betty, and I am from
Brooklyn, New York.
My drag style is completely
over-the-top.
Basically, a drug trip
without the drugs.
I kind of want to run around.
The main bullet point
of Acid Betty is she's a bitch.
That's it.
Even Bianca
won't fuck with her.
That's the T.
Wait, I want to put my stink
all over this place.
I'm excited to be here.
Come on, like,
before we all hate each other.
Everybody say love?
Good morning.
I didn't realize
this was happening today.
My name is Robbie Turner,
and I'm the kindest queen
you'll ever meet.
I'm trying to give
old classic Hollywood.
Rita Hayworth hair,
Jean Harlow robe.
Gorgeous.
Yes, Turnter Classic Movies.
14 years of drag?
I know, can you imagine?
I'm only 12.
You don't look old.
I know I don't.
Yes!
Oh!
Yay!
Oh, Kim Chi!
I came to chop
suey the competition.
My name is Kim Chi,
and I came here
to destroy everyone...
with my makeup.
I'm known for crazy,
over-the-top,
pure anime fantasy.
She's ani-major.
Hi, I'm Naomi.
This is beautiful.
Seeing Kim Chi on Instagram
for so long,
double-tapping everything,
I'm fucking starstruck.
I want to go subtle
with everything, so...
I may come across as shy
because I'm soft-spoken,
but...
donut come for me,
because I'll destroy you.
Get it, "donut"?
I love her,
but she ain't right in the head.
Whoo!
Thorgy with a T-H and orgy,
and I feel incredible.
My name is Thorgy,
and I'm 29 years old.
I'm not 29 years old.
Where did that come from?
I'm colorful, I'm fun,
and I'm a fashion clown.
A-Thorable.
O-M-baby Jesus.
My drag style
is kind of incredibly eclectic.
I can be campy,
but also I can be,
like, fucking fierce.
I'll take all of the above,
please.
Hi, guys!
Fuck you, Thorgy.
I know Acid Betty very well.
Lord, it's gonna
be the shitshow.
She's gonna be a lot.
She's gonna be extra.
Oh, really?
She's gonna be a diva.
Ooh!
Girl.
NY in the house.
My name is Bob The Drag Queen,
and I am 29 years old.
My drag is funny.
It's irreverent.
What you see is what you get.
My bodysuit says it all.
Unt?
Oh.
Yes!
Take it!
Swim through!
Yeah!
I'm hilarious, beautiful,
talented, and humble.
Ha!
How are you?
Now just one more.
The New York girls,
they get really excited.
And they just talk
over one another.
Thorgy, you are--
Whoo!
Take it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Too real.
New York, New York,
New York.
If you can tuck it there,
you'll tuck it anywhere.
Maybe some of
the other queens are, like,
resentful that there's so much
New York City representation.
There's a reason New York City
has some of the best
drag queens in the world,
and that is a fact.
This is a gag.
The children don't even know.
All right, ladies.
Let's turn up the juice
and see what shakes loose.
Uh-oh, this is trouble.
Don't say "Beetlejuice"
three times.
Too late.
I'm Laila McQueen,
and I'm 22 years old.
Laila is like a whorey,
quasi-rock star.
I don't want to say gothy,
but, like, gothy.
Yes, goth!
Hi.
You had the smart idea.
I'm gonna tell you
a story about flats.
No.
14 hours from now,
we're all like, "Ugh, ow!"
She's like Sketchers,
it's the S.
Laissez les bon temps rouler.
What she said!
My name is Chi Chi DeVayne,
and I don't get ready,
I stay ready.
Okay, she cute.
Oh!
Hey!
My drag is that
real Southern
dragged out style of drag.
Creole fish.
It's like a whole nother level
of drag right here.
If you made it to
"RuPaul's Drag Race,"
you made it, honey.
Dirty South represent.
Well, I'm a cheap queen.
She's on a budget.
Um, I don't mean cheap.
Resourceful.
Yeah, resourceful.
Chi Chi walked in
in a trash bag.
Chi Chi will take herself
out in a trash bag.
Hefty, Hefty, Hefty.
It's Derrick, bitch.
Ooh, hit me baby.
Yeah!
My name is Derrick Barry.
I'm 32 years old.
I may look angelic,
but I am not that innocent.
I'm a Britney Spears
impersonator.
I impersonate her
six nights a week
on the Las Vegas Strip.
I would love to believe
that I'm the best
Britney in the world.
That's what people say.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey!
How are you?
Derrick Barry
is huge competition.
She is a quasi-celebrity.
Okay, I want to know
who else did this.
Who else has been
carb-free for two weeks?
Hello, hello, hello.
Beautiful.
Welcome, ladies.
Come through, hat!
Now, are you ready
to make herstory?
all:
Yes!
Well, guess what?
You already have.
This is the 100th episode
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
And they said it wouldn't last.
Now, an occasion
such as this
demands to be acknowledged
on an epic scale.
So I've arranged a photo shoot
with some extra special
guest stars.
The Barbie Twins?
Ruth Bader Ginsburg?
Ready for your close-up,
because if you get upstaged,
this 100th episode
could be your last.
Now, let's go.
Whoo, baby, start them engines,
because it's time for
"RuPaul's Drag Race
Season 8: RuVealed."
Yes, honey, watch along
with Ru and I
as we dish and take you inside
the dragster studio.
Uh-huh, all will be
revealed, honey,
so jump in and hang on.
May the best woman,
best woman win
Welcome back.
Smile.
Time for our first challenge.
Naysha Lopez,
welcome, darling.
In honor of our
100th episode,
I've gathered the champions
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
Legendary!
BeBe Zahara Benet.
Tyra Sanchez.
Raja.
Sharon Needles.
Boo.
Chad Michaels.
Jinkx Monsoon.
Work!
Violet Chachki.
And Bianca Del Rio...
could not be here
so we just hired a circus clown.
The weird thing is, nobody
could tell the difference.
Now, for your first
photo challenge,
we are going to take
some photographs
with the great Mathu Andersen.
We're gonna find out
if you have what it takes
to stand amongst greatness.
Got it.
Faces on lock, and go.
Body.
Face.
Why, she's covered
in black cock.
Sorry bout it.
Queens of a feather
stick together.
Next,
Bob The Drag Queen.
Lil' Kim up in the house.
She's trying to keep it
fresh and clean.
Yeah, you got one more left.
I'll just looked shocked.
I like her.
She's silly.
She's keeping it editorial,
real and art.
Yes.
Acid Betty, we will see
if you have what it takes
to sit among
the goddesses, all right?
Yes, RuPaul,
very intimidating.
Sitting next to
these wannabe-ass drag queens.
Well, you passed
the acid test, Betty.
Come through, Kim Chi.
Yes, give me anim-azing.
Go big, Naomi Smalls.
Oh, all of that right there.
Naomi Smalls
looks really hot,
but she does have cliff hangers.
You see her toes, like,
literally
clinging onto the shoe.
Boner killer.
Wah, wah.
Robbie Turner.
This sleeve happens to be
in my light, darling.
Well, you should move.
Rawr!
Know your place, bitch.
Season eight winner.
Season four winner.
Difference.
Gorgeous.
Welcome to my home.
Thank you, darling.
Sharon, did she try
to come for you?
Oh, yeah,
she came for me.
Next up, Thorgy Thor.
It's time for a queen orgy,
Thorgy.
Whoo!
Looking good,
feeling Thorgeous.
Next up, Chi Chi DeVayne.
Nice.
Pose the house down.
Dax ExclamationPoint.
Get it.
Take it to the Dax.
Cynthia Lee Fontaine.
Model for me.
Escándalo.
You own everything.
Except for that sofa.
It's a rental.
Laila McQueen.
Oh, okay.
You remind me of a dog trying
to get comfortable on the couch.
Everyone is so gorgeous,
and here I am looking
like a Beetlejuice trash bag.
Oh, my God.
She's like the Hamburglar
scurrying around behind people.
I'm lovin' it.
Stripes, girl.
From Las Vegas, Nevada,
Derrick Barry.
That's it,
make them your backup dancers.
Yes.
This is the last shot.
Hit me, baby, one more time.
Oh, she's toxic.
Girl, the season of Britney
jokes has only just begun.
A legendary design challenge
from a past season.
Ugh.
Derrick Barry
is not creative.
He will definitely
have the hardest time.
Aww, leave Britney alone!
Or don't.
We'll be right back.
Hey, we're back,
but weren't
those commercials great?
Ladies,
over the past 99 episodes,
I'm sure you've yelled
at your TV,
"Girl, I coulda slayed
that challenge."
Now it's your chance
to prove it.
For this week's maxi
challenge...
Where my judges' table at?
A legendary design challenge
from a past season.
It's your job
to take the materials
and make them your own.
Now to assign the looks,
I've chosen one of your names
at random.
Robbie Turner.
Now, Robbie, you get to assign
all the queens' looks
and choose your own.
It's time
to bring back my girls.
From season one,
Shannel,
presenting the Drag on a Dime
thrift store challenge.
Latrice Royale,
presenting our Pride Float
challenge from season four.
Next, Violet Chachki,
presenting the Money Ball
from season three.
It's time to assign
these three looks.
All right, Robbie Turner,
who gets Drag on a Dime?
Naysha.
Who gets Float Your Boat?
Naomi.
Who gets Money Ball?
Acid Betty.
Psst, it's not real money.
Next up, Jinkx Monsoon,
presenting the Sugar Ball
challenge from season five.
Tyra Sanchez,
presenting the Glitter Ball
challenge from season six.
Chad Michaels,
presenting the Post
Apocalyptic Couture challenge
from season four.
All right, Robbie,
who gets Sugar Ball?
Cynthia.
Who gets Glitter Ball?
Chi Chi.
That's a good one.
Who get Apocalyptic Couture?
Laila.
Doesn't she mean post
apocaloptic--couture?
Serving the Cake Couture
challenge from season three.
BeBe Zahara Benet
presenting the Hair challenge
from season three.
Well, Hello, Kitty.
Hey, kitty girl.
Hello Kitty Couture challenge
from season seven.
All right, Robbie,
who gets Cake Couture?
Thor-gy.
Yes, it's Thorgy.
Thorgy, fuck my life.
Who gets Hair Ball?
Kim Chi.
And who gets Hello Kitty?
Dax.
Meow.
Next up, Raven,
presenting the Gone With
the Window challenge
from season two.
Next up, the Pit Crew...
Oh, ho, ho, ho.
From season three.
Next, the bitch is back,
and she brought Sharon Needles,
presenting the Bitch Ball
challenge from season four.
Okay, Robbie,
who gets Gone With the Window?
Bob The Drag Queen.
Yes.
Who's gonna get a big
Christmas package?
Derrick Barry.
Yes.
And, Robbie, does this mean
you're going to be doing it
doggy style?
Can you believe I forget
to pick a theme for myself?
Guess who gets stuck
with the poodle?
It's a real doggy downer.
Now if I've said this once,
I've said it 100 times.
Literally.
Start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
Yeah!
All right!
Oh, my God.
Let's do it.
All right,
this is kind of interesting.
I'm super excited
about this challenge
because I've watched
every episode,
and I could kill
any one of these challenges.
Whoo,
this is fun.
We'll see.
Oh, these are shitty bags.
So I'm looking through
my materials,
and I realize
that a lot of these things
can't be made into clothing.
Dog chew toys, ropes.
You guys, I brought treats.
Dog treats.
It's just a couple of treats.
Have you ever tasted one of
those for real?
Uh, paging Nomi and Cristal.
You know, I'm from the South,
we eat everything, honey.
Possums, rats, raccoons.
Possums?
What did she call me?
She's just country as fucking
catfish sandwiches.
She's like country.
There's so much stuff that I'm
trying not to get overwhelmed,
and, like, I got this and this
and this and this and this.
I don't do drag on a dime.
I don't sew.
I'm a pageant girl.
I brought so many
beautiful garments.
I spend money.
Make it work, bitch.
Make it work.
There is so much stuff to use.
My theme for the challenge is
The Queen Who Mopped Christmas.
Season 8 greetings.
My strategy
for this first challenge
is to basically still come out
with my Britney look.
Like, I just want to add to it.
So what kind of vibe
are you going for?
Like,
this Christmas skirt.
Like a tree skirt,
but then I don't know
how to finish a whole outfit.
Girl.
Derrick Barry
is not creative,
obviously 'cause
he's impersonating someone else
his whole life.
He will definitely have
the hardest time
with this challenge.
And I'm like stuck on
what to do for the top.
Santa baby,
you better come quick.
Coming up...
My fucking panties just ripped.
This some bullshit.
I have no clue how she's gonna
fix this outfit.
I think she's done.
Whew, it's gonna get tore up
right after this.
Welcome back.
Runway number 100 dead ahead.
I actually
do a lot of pageants,
and I won this pageant.
It's an international pageant.
It's called Miss Continental.
And it is one of
the most prestigious pageants.
I've heard of it.
Yeah, so I'm
a former Miss Continental.
That's awesome.
Yeah.
I hate pageants.
Girl, I've done,
like, two pageants.
And you didn't win them, and
that's why you hate pageants.
Exactly.
I knew it.
That always happens to someone
who don't win.
Bitch, I was robbed.
It just sucks that pageants
get such a bad rap.
I owe a whole lot
of my work ethic
and who I am
to pageant experiences.
So, Derrick, how long
you been doing Britney?
I started on Halloween 2003.
And how long
you been doing drag?
Halloween 2003.
I've been doing Britney
for 12 years,
and I think a lot of
the other girls
are not gonna think I can do
anything else.
I have to prove
that I can do more than Britney.
I find
there's two breeds of queen.
There's Halloween queens,
and there's pride queens.
I was a pride queen.
Really?
I, like, started drag
on Gay Pride wearing,
like, a shitty potato sack
and a wig from, you know,
who knows where.
Was that this Pride?
Ooh, I like her.
Oh you little bitch.
Oh, Laila!
How long have you
been doing drag?
I've been doing drag
for two and a half years.
Does your family
support your drag?
My family doesn't know
that I do drag.
They don't know?
Really?
No.
At all?
Like, my mom thinks
I'm a makeup artist.
Has your mother ever seen you
in drag ever,
like pictures or anything?
Well, I've shown her
pictures of me in drag
and she thinks they're, like,
makeup jobs that I did.
She doesn't recognize
that it's me.
Stop.
Really?
Yeah.
Um, does she have a TV?
Finding out that I do drag
because growing up,
I always felt like I could
never be the model child
that all Asian mothers want.
I've already disappointed her
so many times in her life.
She could even stop
talking to me.
And...
And you know, I'm just scared
of letting her down again.
Uh-oh.
What's the matter, girl?
Speak it out.
I go to put on my outfit
and what happens?
Pop.
My outfit has just ripped apart.
This some bullshit.
My fucking panties
just ripped at the last second.
And it's all coming apart.
This some bullshit.
Fuck.
I am going into panic mode
right now.
Girl, you cannot go home,
not on the first day.
I want this so freaking bad.
Like, I'm so distraught,
I don't even know
what I'm doing now.
I have no clue
how she's gonna fix this outfit.
I think she's done.
I hope you know
the lip sync song,
'cause your outfit
is crumbling before your hands.
Listen, never count anybody
out on this show.
Whew! Tell 'em, Michelle.
Here we go!
Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk
Head to toe,
let your whole body talk
And what.
Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
Michelle Visage,
happy 100th.
Happy birthday,
gorgeous.
Style superstar,
Carson Kressley.
You look amazing for 100.
I know, I don't look
a day over 95.
And the straight talking
Ross Mathews.
Now, on a scale of 1 to 100,
how excited are you?
Like, a dragzillion.
And the fabulous
Nicole Richie.
Hey, kitty girl.
Hi, gorge.
Your dress is very
"Wizard of Oz."
Are you a good witch
or a bad witch?
Or a sandwich.
Now I'm thinking
about a sandwich.
This week, our queens posed
with Drag Race champions.
And tonight,
they're debuting
their own creations
based on a design challenge
from the anals
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
Michelle,
did I say that right?
Eh.
Eh, close enough.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
The realness
First up, Acid Betty,
Money Ball.
Well,
bitch better have my money.
I do freaky drag,
and I think I do it the best.
The drag scene should not
be homogenized.
Therefore, Acid Betty
is here to represent.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
make it rain.
Cash is queen.
I own everything.
Bob The Drag Queen,
Gone with The Window.
Yes, honey,
lead with the bag.
I love it.
This outfit shows
I have the ability
to make a finished garment.
The fabric is hideous, but
the construction is everything.
No shade,
but that dress looks like
it was made out of curtains.
And does her carpet
match the drapes?
Dax ExclamationPoint,
Hello Kitty.
Hello, Herve Leger.
Hello, Angeline.
Meow.
This outfit
is totally me.
I love Hello Kitty.
Anything a 12-year-old Asian
girl wants, I want it more.
I do love a pink pussy.
It's better than a purple one.
Why it got to be purple?
Naysha Lopez,
Drag on a Dime.
Fashion sure is changing.
I am serving Greek goddess.
Face, body, glamour.
Peek-a-Ru, I see you.
Uh-huh.
A dress that makes cents.
Not dollars.
Kim Chi, Hair Ball.
You got a little--
I've made a lion outfit
inspired by Givenchy.
Yes, the lion stomps tonight.
A golden treasure.
This outfit is big, grand,
and conceptual.
It's Kim Chi.
She stepped that pussy up.
Meow.
Cynthia Lee Fontaine,
Sugar Ball.
Gumdrop it like it's hot.
I feel like a goddess is
at this moment.
It's sugar, azúcar.
Are you ready for my cuckoo?
Yeah.
Yes.
Now see, that's the real sugar
right there.
That's her sugar walls.
Whoa!
Naomi Smalls,
Float Your Boat.
Washington's cross-dressing
the Delaware.
She has my dream chest.
Yeah.
I'm trying to give you
'90s supermodel walk,
and this boat is covering
half of it.
When I can finally
step out of this boat,
that's when the judges
can really see
the true Naomi Smalls.
Land ho.
I am giving you
Naomi Campbell
strutting down
a Versace runway.
That boat looks heavy.
Aren't there any seamen
to help her?
The seamen
are all below deck.
Okay, y'all are just dirty.
Chi Chi DeVayne,
Glitter Ball.
You know I always say, when
life hands you disco balls...
What do you do?
You make an outfit.
Yeah.
After my little meltdown,
I'm just gonna
roll with the punches,
and I'm really feeling this
disco queen kind of vibe.
It's a dream come true.
Sparkle, Chi Chi, sparkle.
Yes.
Balls to the walls.
Thorgy Thor,
Red Velvet Cake Couture.
This is feeling
a little menstrual.
I'm glad you said it,
and I didn't.
I don't wear gowns,
but for this challenge
I just wanted to feel decadent,
and I still kept
with my cartoon hair,
giving you cream cheese
realness.
Oh, happy birthday!
Have her cake
and serve it too.
Robbie Turner,
Bitch Ball.
Who let the dogs out?
I love two bitches
on a runway.
I think I'm looking more like
a sheep than a poodle.
The dog is looking at me like,
"Get me the fuck
out of here."
I'm looking at the dog like,
"Get me the fuck
out of here."
This is not going well.
I give this look about
a canine out of ten.
Uh-huh, she's spayed,
and she's throwing shade.
Both those bitches
are over it.
Derrick Barry,
The Queen Who Mopped Christmas.
Well, hey, y'all.
I'm giving you
Christmas in Vegas.
I'm serving body,
but I'm also giving comedy.
Whoa!
Ho, ho, ho.
She's trimming her bush.
Is that mistletoe
or camel toe?
Girl, I could see her urethra.
She's putting the X
back in Xmas.
Yes, she is.
Oops, she's doing it again.
Laila McQueen,
Apocalyptic Couture.
Now, her pussy's not on fire,
but her shoulder is.
This look
is classic Laila.
I'm loving this cute
little jacket I made.
I'm giving you, like,
a post-apocalyptic,
like, devil commander, like,
the world is over,
and I'm here to take over.
Laila McQueen,
Beyond Thunderdome.
The realness
Bam! Commercial time.
Okay, my girls served chic,
now we critique.
Welcome, ladies.
When I call your name,
please step forward.
Bob The Drag Queen.
Dax ExclamationPoint.
Cynthia Lee Fontaine.
Chi Chi DeVayne.
Thorgy Thor.
You are all...
Safe.
Safe!
Now, you may leave the stage.
Bye-bye.
Ladies, you represent the tops
and the bottoms of the week.
You don't know them like that.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
Acid Betty.
I love that you're different.
Every inch was kind of
covered with a thought.
To me,
that's what drag is about.
And then the photo,
you seem like you're a little
bit more of the avant-garde,
artsy, like, you're giving me
Tunnel 1993.
I was there.
I might've seen you there.
You might've.
Great job.
Next up, Naysha Lopez.
You're gorgeous.
Thank you.
You're giving me Eva Longoria,
Miss America.
I think, Naysha,
you're beautiful,
but when you're part of
an ensemble photo,
you really want to stand out.
The dark hair and the dark top,
I don't think it works
in this picture.
That big gold piece
just makes you look thick,
and I just don't think
it looks good.
This is actually the first
garment I've ever made.
I don't really sew.
All right, well,
thank you very much.
Next up, Kim Chi.
Hi.
Your photo,
it's pretty fabulous.
And I really like
your runway look.
You were giving me, like,
this Cowardly Lion anime
ferociousness.
I think it totally worked.
All right, lion queen.
Benefit of the doubt
and say
the walk
was a character choice.
In my personal eyes,
I'm an anime character
who works
as a high fashion model.
You're just a total nerd.
I am.
I love that.
And by the way, I like that
you kept your areolas bald.
The breasts are the windows
to the soul, for sure.
Man, she is so wise.
Next up, Naomi Smalls.
I love that you
are rocking a boy chest.
You're giving me
like, '70s "Studio 54."
The Pride Float
was beautifully decorated,
but it became really cumbersome.
And I almost saw you thinking,
"I have to get back in that boat
and strap it on."
And I'm saying that
about the boat.
Yeah, I know, how many times
have you said that in your life?
Girl.
Yeah.
But the picture.
Hello?
And it's a big butt.
Bam!
I believe they call that
serving it.
Okay.
That needs to come through
with everything that you do,
whether you're dragging a
50-pound boat with you or not.
Next up,
Robbie Turner.
Your photo, I loved,
because you're giving me kind of
funny glamour there.
And now, the bad news.
Fur?
It's like a fringe.
Fringy kind of
carpety-looking stuff.
You're literally a blob.
We lose all shape, and
from the side, it's even worse.
And you got to choose
your challenge.
I actually forgot that I--
to choose one for myself.
I didn't have
my '40s dress pattern,
but I was trying to
figure it out.
So, it was like a series
of misfortunate events.
Ain't nobody gonna talk
about the fact
that she is holding a bag
of dog doo?
Next up, Derrick Barry.
Your look tonight,
it's adorable.
I will say it's pretty simple.
I like the comedic moment
where you trimmed
your holiday bush.
And then your photo,
like, everyone in this photo
looks like
they're your backup dancers,
and you're the star.
Wow.
We've seen Britney now.
My personal challenge to you
is to show me everything else
but Britney.
Gimme--gimme more.
I do want to see more of it,
but we do want to see
other things.
Up next,
Laila McQueen.
Hi, Laila.
Hey, bitch.
I love the shoulder detail.
Did you sew that?
I sewed the jacket, yes.
That's pretty impressive.
Thank you.
But I felt like the bottom
half was just a cop out.
To me, it's just like,
Wynonna Judd opened the oven
too quickly and got
a little, like, you know,
burnt on the outside.
In the picture, we lose you
crumpling up into a ball.
You're with all these
kind of legendary people,
and it's almost like your
body's saying "I'm not worthy."
Do you think
that your missteps
would warrant you
in the bottom?
I don't think that I am
the least put together.
Who do you think
is the least put together?
I think Naomi.
Her look is very plain.
Do you agree with that,
Naomi?
No. I tried to take something
that was from a past season
and make it new and fresh.
Well, thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
While you untuck backstage,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right now, just between
us squirrel friends,
what do you think?
Let's start with Acid Betty.
In the photo, she looks great,
but she is this punk girl.
Like, give me
a little screaming...
Ahh!
Tongue out punkness.
I don't hate her photo,
and like her name implies,
she's kind of a trip,
and she's a little East Village.
Well, you know, I did
a lot of antacid in the '60s,
and I think that Acid Betty
really represents that.
Alright, Naysha Lopez.
Her photo, unfortunately,
I think she got lost.
And also,
don't stand on that stage
and tell us
it's the first dress you made.
I mean, this is not the place
you make your first dress.
You make your first dress
when you've learned that
you're gonna come on the show.
Or you make them
when your mom's at work,
and you're in the sixth grade.
Chile, we have all been there.
All right, next up,
Kim Chi.
I love the photograph.
She was kind of
the queen of the castle
in this anime jungle.
Everything about her tonight
made me happy,
except for
that lumbering walk.
Right, because
she was serving a little bit
of Sasquatch on the runway.
Sasquatch that walk.
You can say Yeti that walk.
Yeti that walk.
Next up, Naomi Smalls.
All I saw
was a really tiny thing
lumbering with
a heavy ass boat.
Sorry boat it.
Contrast of her like,
fumbling with the boat.
It's like a cartoon of an ant
carrying a giant piece
of cheese.
Well, that's the picture
of the day.
It says,
"bow down, bitches."
If she doesn't bring
the photo her
to this her,
to me, she's gone.
Moving on down
to Robbie Turner.
This look in her photo
is probably her go-to look.
It's that Carole Lombard
meets Carol Burnett.
But what we saw today
was basic.
She said
she forgot to choose
a category for herself.
If she put any creativity
into that,
she could've turned it out.
And that's a shame,
because I like
what I saw in the picture.
A doggone shame, I'd say.
Her Britney is amazing.
We know he can nail
the Britney thing.
I mean,
the photo was phenomenal.
I'm glad she brought it
the first episode.
Now bring Derrick Barry
to the table.
Laila McQueen.
She did the most
basic bottom half to that.
I expect so much more.
This is season eight, and
the bar has been raised so high.
There was just
nothing standing out for me.
The worst picture
of the week, by far.
Youch!
Interesting
because she is an artist.
That warrants
a second chance to me.
Silence.
I've made my decision.
Whose look gets the hook?
Find out after this.
Oh, my sweet gherkins.
It's time.
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Acid Betty...
you're safe.
Thank you.
But does she have change
for a 20?
Kim Chi, your photo
and main stage presentation
wigged us out.
Condragulations, you're the
winner of this week's challenge.
No T, Ms. Chi, whoopee!
You've won $3,000
from selfieonastick.com.
The original and the best
selfie on a stick.
Say hi, everybody.
Cheese.
Bitch,
I just won $3,000.
This win means I have a place
in this competition,
and I am a force
to be reckoned with.
Derrick Barry, you're safe.
Thank you.
Naomi Smalls, you're safe.
Fun fact, Naomi backwards
spells I moan.
Naysha Lopez,
you are gorgeous, but...
Thank you.
The judges felt shortchanged
by your Drag on a Dime.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
Naysha, please. Ugh!
I am absolutely gagging.
I don't deserve
to be in the bottom two.
You have some queen
rocking this $5 dress.
I don't get it.
Robbie Turner,
your photo was iconic,
but on the main stage,
you screwed the pooch.
Ru?
Laila McQueen,
you are an edgy artist,
but your photo and your
Post Apocalyptic Couture
were not earth-shattering.
Robbie Turner...
You're safe.
Oh.
All right.
Wow.
Laila McQueen,
I'm sorry, my dear,
but you are up
for elimination.
My heart drops,
but I'm not gonna be
the first one to go home.
I'm gonna do every kind of
quasi-gimmick I have.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies,
this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
For you to lip-synch
for your life.
Yas! Season 8 light cues.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
I stand here
waiting for you
To bang the gong
Speaking of Lady Gaga,
I was on her holiday
Muppet TV special,
and I've never seen in my life
that many costume options.
If only fame
had an I.V., baby
Could I bear
Being away from you
I found the vein,
put it in here
I live for the applause,
applause, applause
I live for
the applause-plause
Live for
Live for the way that
you cheer and scream for me
The applause,
applause, applause
Give me the thing
that I love
Turn the lights on
Put your hands up,
make them touch
Make it real loud
Naysha is always giving
like, beautiful, sexy,
J.Lo bombshell,
I feel it.
Ooh
Touch, touch
Laila is giving you sex
on a stick, and it's awesome.
She is looking
so good right now
throwing her body
all over the floor.
I live for the applause,
applause, applause
The secret to keeping a wig
on so you can do that
is spirit gum plus bobby pins.
Make them touch,
touch
Put your hands up,
make them touch, touch
A-R-T-P-O-P
Good job!
Ladies,
I've made my decision.
Laila McQueen,
shantay, you stay.
Truly, the first cut
is always the deepest.
You may join the other girls.
Thank you.
Naysha Lopez,
out of 100 queens,
you are by far
one of the most beautiful
to grace the stage.
Thank you, Ru.
And I'm sorry
to see you go so soon.
I'm sorry that I
wasn't able to show you
everything that I had to offer.
Thank you, Ru,
for this opportunity.
Thank you.
Now, sashay away.
Love you, beauty.
I am first to go, and I feel
like I didn't let Ru see
what I'm all about because
there's so much more to me.
Ru, I want to thank you
for the platform
that you have given me
because not everyone
appreciates it.
I thank you for that
from the bottom
of my heart.
Well,
condragulations, ladies.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get an "amen" in here?
all: Amen.
All right,
now let the music play.
Oh, my gag!
First episode up,
first queen down.
And next week, we start
another 100 episodes.
And it's gonna be pitch
perfect.
Watch.
Bye!