It's absolutely spectacular.
It was just a mess visually.
I thought
it was very successful.
Previously on Face Off...
Ben's stunning sculpture
wowed the judges,
and the bottom four artists
received some unexpected news.
No one is going home.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
And tonight they'll
head into uncharted waters.
Hey, guys,
want to go for a ride?
- This is so exciting!
- I am terrified.
Shit.
_
But not everyone
can handle pressure.
Seriously, like,
what am I gonna do?
- Should I give up?
- Oh, this mold's fucked.
I really love this thing.
You messed it up.
In the end, only one will win
a VIP trip from
Kryolan Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand-new 2015 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
This is Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- This is so rad.
- It is pretty awesome.
We're all feeling really good
this morning 'cause,
hey, we're all safe,
and it's a beautiful sunny day,
and in the distance
we see this huge ship.
We see McKenzie standing there.
Oh, boy, here we go.
Hey, guys,
want to go for a ride?
- Yeah.
- Definitely.
All right, come on board
the US Coast Guard
Cutter George Cobb.
This is just awesome
because the Coast Guard
protects our borders,
and for them to have us on
this ship with them is an honor.
- Oh, man.
- This is so exciting!
What is this ship's
general purpose?
It's, uh, ATON.
It aids navigation.
Whoa.
Does that mean
we're taking off?
- Yes.
- Awesome.
Take it away,
Cutter George Cobb.
We are underway at this time.
Ready, set...
Good-bye, LA.
Bye.
Good-bye, coastline.
What is that?
- Is that-- I don't know.
- A lighthouse.
It's pretty surreal to just
be hanging out on a boat.
I'm looking out
in front of the boat.
I make my way to
the back of the boat,
and before I know it,
I don't see land anymore.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- You having fun?
- Yeah.
Well, are you ready to learn
about your next challenge?
- Yes.
- All right, come with me.
Okay, guys.
The United States Coast Guard
does a phenomenal job
protecting our nation's maritime
interests all around the globe.
This year, they're celebrating
their 225th anniversary.
We are very lucky to have them,
but, in ancient Greek
and Roman times,
mariners
like Jason and his Argonauts
had to fend for themselves,
battling all manner
of sea creatures
to complete their epic quests,
and perhaps the most deadly
of them all
was also the most beautiful...
The Sirens.
I love sirens.
I love that sexy, edgy, but full
of glitter kind of character,
so I'm super excited.
It was said that sirens
used their incredible beauty
and alluring songs
to lure mariners in,
leading them to a watery grave.
So, for this week's
spotlight challenge,
you will be working
in teams of two
to create your very own
beautiful and deadly siren.
Oh, my God.
I am terrified
about the challenge
because beauty is not my forte.
Do you guys
mind helping me out?
Of course.
Oh, nice.
So these are the names
of some of the ocean's most
beautiful yet deadly creatures,
and you'll be using them as
inspiration for your creations.
But, before you pick,
your randomly assigned teams
are Sidney and Omar,
Brittany and Nora,
Evan and Jason,
Ricky and Ben...
Yeah, buddy.
Scott and Stevie, Kevon and Meg,
Missy and Libby,
Jordan and Jasmine.
Go ahead and stand
with your new teammates, please.
- Okay.
- What's up?
Omar and Sidney,
you're up first.
All right, guys, it's time
to start designing your sirens.
Remember, your sirens need to be
both beautiful and deadly.
Good luck.
I can't wait.
- Whoo!
- Thank you.
The coloring is what's gonna
be so important on this.
Yeah.
We got the
Peacock Mantis Shrimp,
and with the way
the coloring is and the fact
that there's a little bit
of white around its eyes,
we lean towards geisha.
Also it has a strike
similar to the force
of a .22 caliber pistol,
so we think, "Assassin!"
Something that draws you in,
and, with one strike,
it takes you out.
Dagger hands.
All right, here's our
textile cone snail.
The concept for our siren
is there's a beautiful thing
that's coming out of something
that resembles a shell.
She is going to have flutes
on the end of her fingers,
and she's gonna play some kind
of instrument,
and that's gonna release
pheromones into the air,
and after our siren lures men
into her midst,
she's going to reveal
nasty, sharp teeth
that she can sink
into her victims.
I think we really
got a good shot with this.
We picked the Flabellina
Nudibranch just 'cause
we have no idea what it is.
We're on Face Off.
We're living on the edge.
Sexy, but deadly.
Nora and I discussed that
we want to do a face piece
and a chest piece.
We decide to put e-wire
through the hair
to illuminate our creature
a little bit.
We also want to do
some cool nails
just to keep that beauty aspect,
but also make them pointy
so that they're a little deadly.
I'm gonna need to just
mold up my fingers
with her finger measurements.
I saw this. You hold this.
- You block up the clay and--
- You make the thing, and then--
You do dental acrylic!
Everything's very elongated.
The Yellow Boxfish
secretes poison from its skin,
so our siren
is poisonous to the touch.
Jordan sketches out
this beautiful shape
around the head
that gives it a box-like effect
but with more rounded edges.
We also want to give it
a slightly bondage look
to give it
that dangerous effect.
All right, guys, time's up.
We got to head back.
I need to get you to the lab.
All right.
Snailed it.
Hanging out
on a ship was really cool,
but we are ready
to get into the lab.
I think we're gonna have
really cool makeup on our hands.
It's time to choose
our models and start sculpting.
You can go about
this far if you wanted to.
All right.
We picked the Blue Sea Slug.
It has a lot of ridges
where the tendrils are,
so Ben's gonna sculpt
a cowl piece
that has a lot of those ridges,
and I'm gonna do a chest piece
that incorporates a lot of that
into a bustier kind of look.
- What about a purple fishnet?
- No.
It's a little
too tongue in cheek I think.
It is. It is.
Well, I want to be able
to cover the bald cap
even if we bring it, like, here.
We picked
a Portuguese Man O'War,
and we come up with
this warrior princess concept.
We do know we have
to keep her beautiful,
so we don't want to go overboard
by doing too many prosthetics.
So, Omar's in charge
of the cowl,
and because this is
a jellyfish-like character,
I think it'd be really cool
to do some nernies.
Nernies are latex brushed
on a table, and when it dries,
you roll it up
to give these cool tentacles.
Should I sculpt
this with a safety just in case
- that doesn't work?
- Okay, yeah.
We picked
the Blue Ring Octopus.
She is beautiful enough
to get them close but then
is deadly enough
to keep them there,
so our design
incorporates a cowl,
octopus-like suckers
on the appendages,
but it has to be
a beautiful creature,
so we're gonna make the cowl
and other additions
secondary to her beauty.
Hey, guys, we're here
to come check on you.
- Hey, what's up?
- Hi!
We want to do
a Japanese assassin.
And we're gonna do a hairpiece
that kind of looks
like chopsticks.
In this area here,
extend that whole thing.
Give it a little bit
more fantasy.
Awesome.
So we've got
Flabellina Nudibranch.
What are you gonna do there
on that piece?
This pattern's gonna
continue up
and fade into the chest piece,
and we're gonna have chiffon
fabric hanging on her shoulders.
Is it gonna be so subtle
it's not even worth doing?
That's what I was wondering.
It's gonna be more trouble
to glue this sucker down
if you don't make
it a little thicker.
What you've created
there is a giant blender,
so make it into something
that actually is part
of your character.
We got the Surgeonfish.
We're gonna have these shapes
kind of going throughout.
What are you doing there, now?
These are nice and soft
as they're going up,
and then all of a sudden
on your chest piece,
it's like
all these little accents
that you have everywhere.
So we should mimic the cowl
and bring it around here?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
We chose the Yellow Boxfish.
Our main concern
was how boxy the head was.
To me, because you've
rounded it all off,
this looks like you've
put a cap on somebody.
I would beef this up
back here and maybe
put your point back up
in here, 'cause it-- it could
wind up looking
like a bathing cap.
Yeah.
We chose the Textile
Cone Snail,
and we don't want to distract
from the human form too much.
With the face, it looks like
the person had an accident.
I think that's where
I'm having the problem.
It's just the face.
They hate it.
The face is either going
to keep you or lose you,
and the way you've done the nose
and those cheek bones,
you're gonna lose
the beauty part of it.
I'm feeling kind
of slapped here,
but I see it 100% that it
definitely looks not pretty.
For another challenge, great.
I'm not feeling so good.
It looks like
we're gonna have to
start the face over
from square one,
and that is really scary.
To mee the face looks
like the person had an accident
they're recovering from.
Mr. Westmore drops the bomb
that he hates my face piece.
I wouldn't waste your time
with anything from there down.
I'm not feeling so good
about it.
There's no way
to use what we've already done.
Take this off,
make this into a forehead,
possibly, that comes down
to here,
and do a nice beauty makeup,
a really nice beauty makeup...
Okay.
Sure.
...that ties in with
your colors and everything.
Time to start over.
- Good luck.
- You'll get it.
- You got a lot of work to do.
- Thank you.
All right, guys,
we're heading out.
- Can't wait to see your sirens.
- Bye.
- See you guys later.
- Thank you.
The second Mr. Westmore
walks away,
I start just tearing
that clay off
and starting over.
I start incorporating
these beautiful,
kind of fluted shapes
that come down very organically,
just like the end of the fluting
on our reference photo,
and I'm feeling really,
really good about it,
way better than I was
feeling 20 seconds ago.
My goal, personally,
is to make the cowl
as beautiful as possible.
So I decided to take
Mr. Westmore's advice
and add a little bit more clay
to make up
for the size of the wig.
I'm feeling good
about what we've done,
and it's just a matter of
cranking out the mold tomorrow.
It's almost the end of day one,
and I'm struggling a little bit.
I'm nowhere near finished
with this cowl.
It's looking too much
like a dinosaur head.
That's time, everybody!
Time's up.
So since I'm not gonna
have a finished sculpt today,
we're not gonna be able to do
any pre-painting on this cowl.
It is very risky
because we only have one shot
to get this right, and since
we only have one piece,
this has to be perfect.
I'm looking at the torso shell,
and I'm starting
to doubt myself.
I don't know how I can make
this shell feminine.
This has to be sexy
and covering up a woman's torso
is not sexy,
so forget about it.
I get a new one,
and I start sculpting on it.
Instead of having
a big, thick shell,
I'm going to create
the soft, feminine fluting
that kind of matches
the mollusk part of the snail.
So what do you think
of this form here?
What do I think of that form?
- Yes.
- I think it's beautiful.
We have absolutely no time
to waste.
We have got to work fast today.
Today, I have to finish
sculpting that cowl,
and overnight, I thought,
"Why not make the fins
fade into the back of the head?"
I feel that is a very good idea
because I don't need
to start over.
I just need to redesign
a little bit
and cut away
some of the extra clay.
I'm trying
to decorate the bodice
so it's not
just, like, a flat piece,
and I see these feathers
and I'm like,
oh, you know what?
They would actually kind of make
a cool little fish bone,
and maybe that would help
incorporate the deadly aspect.
So I take these feathers,
and I start stripping them down,
and I think
they're looking pretty cool.
I'm liking the chest piece.
It seems to be matching up
with Nora's face piece.
So we take them both into
the mold room to start to mold.
- Yep.
- Cool.
I'm a little concerned
because if the tips
of the tentacles
get stuck in the mold,
they're just gonna break off,
but hopefully it'll be nice
and clean and quick,
and we'll have time
to make sure everything
gets applied correctly.
I finally get a good hold
on this sculpture,
and I think it looks great.
So it's time to get it molded.
- Do it like that, man.
- Okay. You got it?
- Yep, yep.
- Cool, cool.
So while Sidney's
getting the mold prepped,
I start fabricating the staff.
We're using a piece of foam
that I shaped,
and then I hit it with
some acetone to dissolve it
and it gives it
a nice coral look,
and then I give it a basecoat
with black acrylic paint.
Scott and I decided to make
the suckers out of silicone.
I make a plate mold
to sculpt out
all of the suckers,
block them out,
and fill that up
so that tomorrow,
I can keep making
several castings of those.
The siren's song is so,
so integral to the siren lore
that I'd feel
it would be inappropriate
to ignore the mythos of it,
so I am fabricating
an instrument.
- Do you like it?
- Yeah, it looks good.
_
I go to open the cowl mold,
and it is just not gonna move.
It's locking up.
Shit.
_
Okay.
I'm basically thinking to myself
"This could be it."
I mean, this could
totally ruin everything.
_
This is the crème de la crème
of our make up
and seriously, like,
what am I gonna do?
Should I give up?
- Ugh.
- We're gonna have to bust this.
I panic,
and I break it to get it out.
_
- Okay, hold, you want to wreck it?
- Yeah, yeah.
Oh, this mold's fucked.
We're gonna have to bust this.
Trying to get this mold unlocked
is just wasting a lot of time.
I panic, and I realize I got
to break it and get it out.
I'm feeling terrible because I
have to destroy this thing.
Oh, damn it.
Look at how bad that is.
The damage is pretty severe.
It's cracked
in about three or four places,
and it's the key to the makeup,
and I just am pretty sad
about it.
- I have to go back in.
- Oh, yeah.
Just go, man.
I got it.
When we run the foam,
I'm thinking we're gonna
have a pile of torn-up,
shredded cowl,
and I just hope
that it comes out.
Her hair might
be brighter than the lights.
I need to test the e-wire
and make sure that everything
is in working order.
This will really
make our siren glow
and pull in our inspiration
from the Flabellina Nudibranch.
So I'm taking four strands
and putting them at different
places throughout the wig,
that way it's nice and
comfortable,
and nothing's gonna move
anywhere.
Here we go.
The shell piece on the head
is going to be pretty big,
so I'm gonna
have to cast that in poly foam.
Poly foam
is a lot more beneficial
in this case because it
is a lot more durable.
It's a lot lighter,
and it'll hold its shape better,
but I can't get that done today.
All right, guys, time!
We're gonna figure it out.
Come on.
All right.
Whew.
I hate when I have to run poly
foam the day of application.
That's always risky
because if something goes wrong,
that's time I can't afford,
but I have no choice, so I'm
just gonna hope for the best.
Are you serious?
Somehow there is the cowl
standing there in front of us.
This is not the prettiest cowl,
but it is still way better
than we expected.
That's not bad.
- How are we looking, Brit?
- Not so hot.
What's going on?
- We lost all the tips.
- How's the headpiece looking?
We got those tips,
but it's majorly cracked.
Fuck.
All of our tips on our
chest piece are not there.
So we got to get
some makeup sponges
and make ourselves some tips.
- Yeah.
- Let's just get right on that.
Rather than trying
to refabricate the tips,
it's gonna be a lot
quicker for us to take
some white makeup sponges
and cut them down
into fine points.
It's a small setback,
but I'm fairly confident
that this'll work.
First thing I'm gonna do
is cast up that poly foam shell.
So I grab all this poly foam,
and I mix up a lot, 'cause
it's a pretty big shell.
Shh...
And I look over,
and these magnificent wings
are about to get swallowed
by this big-ass volcano
of poly foam.
Fucking shit.
_
Fortunately, I catch it
before it ruins all of them.
I think I'm just gonna
suggest to Ricky
that we put the one
with the poly foam on the legs.
Hello, how are you, Rachel?
Geisha assassin.
And you're gonna be like that,
and then do what you do.
The edges look horrendous.
The seams in the cutting edge
on this cowl are terrible,
so I'm just gonna
start seaming this thing.
This is probably the best
it's gonna get.
This is the last thing
that we needed right now,
because we don't have
a lot of pieces,
and the ones that we do have
need to be really good.
Soon as I finish this patch
we're working on,
you're gonna be able to tell.
It's gonna be fine.
Luckily, the patchwork
hasn't taken us too long,
so everything looks great,
and we both start
applying our pieces.
Get comfy here.
Ben applies a wig cap
and begins applying
the cowl piece,
and as he does that,
I begin applying feathers
to these fins
so that it creates the shape
of the Blue Sea Slug,
like a very flamboyant
Vegas drag queen.
They are looking fantastic.
Should I do the black
or the teal down the center?
I think black.
I start painting her up
with yellows and oranges,
but I have to tone
down the orange a bit,
so I start layering
a brown-orange on top,
and I think
it's looking much better.
- What do you think, Libby?
- Yellow's a bit bright.
Cowl's very yellow.
I thought that we were
just gonna do it
all black with,
like, an orange tip.
At this point, I'm confused
about what's happening
with our paint.
It looks like you're covering
up the whole paint job.
Oh, I thought we were
covering up the paint.
Not everything.
I'm not necessarily a huge fan
of the paint job.
I feel like we're going
in two different directions.
I think that's good on the orange.
One hour!
While Meg is taking care
of the beauty makeup,
I'm in charge of the shell.
I give it a nice,
sexy gloss look.
I spray it with glitter.
It's starting
to look pretty good.
15 minutes, everybody!
That one is so badass, dude.
Now I'm able to see
what everyone else has done.
They have chest pieces,
breast pieces, wigs,
and we just have a staff
and a cowl.
All right, guys, brushes down!
That's time!
- Than you.
- Yes! - Whoo!
At this moment,
I'm feeling 50/50.
I do like my make-up,
but I don't know
what the judges are gonna think.
We get to last looks.
We have one hour left.
We have a lot
of airbrushing to do,
and we need to get the acrylic
rods in her chest,
and I still want
to do glitter detail work.
I think we can tag-team this,
and we can get it done.
I know they're gonna
check your palms.
We have to finish
the beauty makeup,
finish our paint job,
apply the nails,
change up some of the wardrobe.
We have a whole bunch to do.
I go to apply the shell,
and I am using Velcro
to stick it on there.
Dude, you can
see all this Velcro.
And then I got a big
strap exposed,
so I have to find the filler.
I start stuffing seaweed
into this thing.
So I'll make this seaweed
a little more purposeful.
If I can freaking line
these lips.
Killing me.
So Sidney's trying
to do a beauty makeup,
and he's having a little bit
of trouble.
- No, I can do that.
- You can do that?
Thank God
our model was stepping in,
and she's getting it
done very well.
I think it looks fantastic.
The paint job looks muddy,
so I'm putting more black in it
to get it to pop a little bit,
but at this point
we strayed very far away
from the inspiration.
Ten minutes!
Evan's cutting in
with the airbrush
while I try really hard
to make that wig look pretty,
but I know beauty makeup,
and this is not gonna be
the prettiest thing.
It would have looked really
cool, but we don't have time.
That's time, everybody!
There you go.
I'm feeling like we missed
the mark on making it beautiful,
and I'm like,
"Well, hope for the best."
Welcome to the Face Off
Reveal Stage.
You know
our incredible series judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening.
Oscar and Emmy award-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
- Hello, everyone.
- Evening.
And creature and conpt
designer, Neville Page.
Hi, guys.
Now before we see
your make-ups,
there's something very important
that I have to tell you.
Two of you will be going home.
My stress level
is going through the roof,
'cause it's like, now my chances
of going home have doubled.
Okay, guys, this week
your Spotlight Challenge
was to choose a sea creature
and use it as inspiration
for your very own
beautiful but deadly siren.
Let's take a look
at your final creations.
I don't feel safe.
We just have a staff and a cowl.
I don't know if this is gonna be
enough for the judges.
She's definitely beautiful,
and she definitely looks deadly
at the same time.
I think we've got a good chance
to be in top looks tonight.
The way our model dances
is just gorgeous.
I could not be more happy
with that.
The paint job is muddier
than I thought.
If I'm on the bottom again,
I will be going home.
I think she looks good.
She is really terrifying,
and she definitely has that kind
of Greek look to her.
I just hope we're safe
because it's my first time
using such crazy colors.
She's not as beautiful
as we want her to be.
When those judgeget up close,
I have no idea
what they're gonna think.
I don't know
what to think at this point.
We're the only ones
that didn't do a cowl,
and two people are going home.
Okay, judges,
go ahead and take a closer look.
The silicone is over tainted.
There's no translucency.
I'm having problems
with these forms.
They're so random.
The paint job is random.
None of this is highlighting
their sculpting at all.
Yeah.
I really like the way
that they're forcing us
to focus on the face,
but all of these shapes
fight the model's anatomy.
These are weird.
- I like it.
- Okay.
It's kind
of a stay-away feature.
That's why I don't like it.
Such a confused set of forms.
It doesn't represent
the reference material at all.
The paintjob is muddy.
The cowl does not look amazing.
Beautiful little details
and textures,
but it disappears
with the paint.
I'm afraid that they're
gonna fucking crucify us.
All right, guys, it's time
to get on Twitter and tell us
who made your favorite siren
using #FaceOff
This framing face is--
a bad choice.
It looks like two people
working against each other.
I'm very, very worried
because they're gonna look
at that cowl, see that it sucks,
and send me home.
I kind of like the shapes,
especially in profile,
but the transitions, ugh,
it's a travesty.
Gorgeous blends.
You can't see where one thing
starts and the other stops.
Yeah, I love this chest piece,
the look of motion that it has.
Incredibly unique.
I've never seen
anything like this before.
This is a mess, you guys.
So sloppy in its application.
It looks like she's been shot
with a paintball gun.
These shapes are leaning
towards such a unique vision.
I've never seen
anything quite like this.
Yeah, well, that's...
the Flabellina.
They really captured
sculpturally what the forms are.
All right, guys, the judges
have scored your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Jason and Evan,
Jordan and Jasmine,
Ricky and Ben,
Scott and Stevie.
Congratulations,
because you are all safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
The rest of you were the best
and the worst this week.
The judges would like to
find out more about your work.
Kevon and Meg,
would you please step up?
Tell us about the concept
behind your siren.
We had the Textile Cone Snail,
and our siren
is playing her siren song
on this little harp,
and as she plays it, a pheromone
is released from her fingertips
that lures people in
so that she can get close enough
to bite them
and inject them with venom.
I sculpted the front
and back here.
I did the shell.
Meg did the face.
She also fabricated
the instrument.
What do you think
of this finished product?
- I think it's okay.
- I like it.
I-- I'd go out with her.
That's a little worrisome to me.
Not only that
you would date her,
but the fact that you don't
realize how gorgeous that is.
Oh-- oh, I'll--
I'll take that.
Thank you.
There's some really fantastic
decision making.
You didn't try
to cover the entire body.
You picked exactly the right
things to focus on.
I think it's amazing.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
She's so creepy and
so beautiful at the same time.
I think you guys
did a fantastic job.
Thank you.
There's a-- just a hint
of beauty makeup in there
which is critical
'cause otherwise,
she would have been
very bland and monochrome.
It's a great job with this one.
- Awesome.
- Okay. Thank you.
Kevon and Meg,
please step back.
Fuck.
Sidney and Omar.
Please tell us how
your Portuguese Man O' War
inspired your creation.
We tried to emulate the spine
on the Man O' War,
and she lures her pray with
a lure on the end of her rod.
The best part of your whole
makeup job is your wardrobe.
She really looks like
she's wearing a helmet, guys.
She has a ton of hair.
You should have figured out
a way to use her hair
and put these spines
someplace else on her body.
You messed it up.
How did you guys
break down the duties?
Well, I decided I was
gonna sculpt the cowl.
I went with, you know,
running the silicone,
and then we both worked
on the staff.
Both worked on the staff.
When you look at some of
the other creations this week,
there's massive amounts of work,
so I'm not sure
what the two of you were doing.
The paintjob doesn't feel
like patterning or natural.
She does not look
like either a siren
or a Portuguese Man O' War
inspired character.
Sidney and Omar,
you can head back.
Missy and Libby, could you
please step to the center?
Tell us about your character
and how it was inspired.
We had the Striped Surgeonfish.
We used the inspiration
in the cowl, in the back piece,
and in the front piece
with these spines.
And who did what?
I sculpted the cowl,
the face piece,
and Libby sculpted the arms
and the chest piece.
The form and color
don't relate back to
your Striped Surgeonfish.
There's a nice silhouette
going on,
but the head piece is
so out of balance.
For me, that's not
the biggest problem.
I really do like the fact that
it's out of proportion.
But the transition
between the prosthetic,
and the model's face--
I've seen football helmets
that blend more seamlessly
onto a player's head.
Yeah,
I sculpted the face piece,
and in the mold,
it got air pockets--
Ohh.
Basically, so I had to put
the cowl,
like, over the face piece.
Okay.
What man is gonna
go to that thing?
- Kevon, probably.
- She is frightening.
Right over there.
- Right over there.
- Maybe.
One of the elements
of this challenge
was to create something
that can lure men in.
This poor darling doesn't have
anything that's alluring.
Missy and Libby,
please step back.
Nora and Brittany.
Tell me about your concept
for your siren.
Our siren has been wronged
by all these different men
who have come
into her coastline,
so she has all these bits
and pieces of each guy
that she consumed and destroyed.
I sculpted the chest piece.
Nora did the face piece.
I did the wig
and all the wiring
and I did a little bit
of the costuming.
I really love this thing.
Thank you, Glenn.
You exercised
very wise restraint,
and the color
throughout the appliance
is extraordinarily cohesive.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
The interpretation
of the Nudibranch's appendages,
those little tendrils,
are beautifully crafted
on the sulders.
Beautiful work.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
I love the fact
that she actually has hair.
It does bring in the coloration
of the slug,
and she looks absolutely
beautiful.
Thank you.
Nora and Brittany,
you can step down.
All right, guys, if you'd please
head back to the makeup room
while the judges deliberate.
Thank you.
All right, judges,
let's talk about the looks
you liked the most tonight.
Why don't we start
with Kevon and Meg.
I think that they
really hit all the notes
that we were looking for.
It's definitely a siren,
definitely looks like
it could be
a creature from Greek mythology,
but it's still beautiful.
The face was just so stunning
and so unique.
Even with those teeth,
she still looked appropriately
beautiful.
Okay, let's move on
to Brittany and Nora.
They nailed the form language,
particularly in the shoulders.
The fact that they figured out
a way to incorporate
that bright orange
and that lavendery-blue color
was really well done, I thought.
All right, judges,
let's move on to the looks
that you didn't like
so much this week.
Let's start
with Sidney and Omar.
It was one of the
biggest disappointments.
- It looked like shells or--
- Cabbage.
Cabbage is never good
for a character.
Unless it's like a taco guy,
or something.
It's like-- it was like
a Cabbage Patch fish.
The shapes were so nebulous.
And this is supposed
to be a beautiful siren.
This has to be appealing,
has to be luring men to her.
It looked like a little boy
with a helmet on.
I don't know
what they were doing.
Did they, like, go to a bar
for one of the two days
that they had?
All right, let's move on
to Missy and Libby.
It was a giant helmet.
And where does that come
from, anyway?
Where was that inspiration
for that head shape?
I have no idea.
I thought there
was some really beautiful
sculptural ideas in the head,
albeit disproportionate,
and I don't think they're
appropriate for this challenge,
but I did see promise,
even though it became
a muddy pile of confusion.
All right, judges.
Have you made your decisions?
- Yes, we have.
- Yes.
Let's bring them back out.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about tonight's top teams.
Kevon and Meg.
We love the wild shapes
and the monochromatic paint job,
and you definitely nailed
the deadly beautiful aspect
of this challenge.
Nora and Brittany,
the beauty of your makeup
was not only
in its general aesthetic,
but in its subtle forms
and its flowing color gradients.
All right, Glenn,
so which team came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
All right, Glenn,
so which team came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Kevon and Meg.
What a cool character this was
with her beautiful head-to-toe,
fleshy paint job
and that super-adventurous
chest piece.
- Fine work.
- Thank you.
Kevon and Meg, excellent work,
but as you know,
we can only have one winner.
Glenn?
The winner of tonight's
challenge is...
Meg.
Good job.
Thank you.
This makeup was
all about the face
and finding that perfect balance
of beautiful and deadly.
- Very well done.
- Thank you.
I win the challenge.
It's an overwhelming feeling.
I'm just really, really proud
of what we accomplished.
- Meg, congratulations.
- Thank you.
You, Kevon, Nora, and Brittany
are all safe and can head back
to the make-up room.
All right, guys, that means that
you are on the bottom this week,
and two of you will be
going home tonight.
Would you please step forward?
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom teams.
Sidney and Omar, you guys
struggled to find
a graceful way to integrate
your inspiration animal,
and the paint seemed unfinished.
Missy and Libby,
we also saw few signs
of your inspirational animal,
and there are
just too many disparate ideas
going on for your design
to work.
So who is the first person
to go home tonight?
The first person
going home tonight is...
Sidney.
Your contribution to this makeup
seemed very minimal,
and the one piece of yours
that we did see
didn't give us a great sense
of your future potential.
Sidney, I'm so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
It's been great
having you here with us,
but if you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
It is really disappointing
that I'm going home,
but everybody's so good
this season
that you could do a good makeup
and get kicked off.
What can I do?
So who is the second person
going home tonight?
The second person
going home tonight is...
Omar.
Your cowl sculpture
sort of resembled a brain
or a cabbage, which is
the opposite of beautiful.
Omar, I'm sorry,
but you have also been
eliminated.
Missy, Libby,
you're both safe this week.
You can head back
to the makeup room.
Omar, even though
this is the end
of your journey here
on Face Off,
tomorrow is the new journey
for you, so good luck.
Thank you.
Omar, it's been great
having you here with us,
but if you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you.
I am disappointed that I'm not
gonna be able to show
a lot more of what I can do,
but it's a competition,
and I knew I was gonna be
surrounded by amazing artists.
- Aw.
- Seriously?
And me.
I've definitely learned
a lot about myself.
Okay, all right, guys.
I was only here
for a short period of time,
but I was really pushed
to my limit.
I've learned that I can do this.
Moving forward, I'm gonna
continue doing special effects.
I love it, it's my passion,
and this is not the end
of the line for me.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net