It's a
competition like no other.
Get ready for Face Off.
Tonight, the show
of 1,000 faces
reaches one epic milestone.
This is the 100th
episode of Face Off.
Ahh!
It's till un-death do us part
in the biggest celebration
in Face Off history.
I'm part of the 100th episode.
This is crazy.
You could be in big trouble.
I've made a huge mistake.
I'm excited to see these guys
and get them married.
Oh, yeah.
In the end, only one
will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan Professional Makeup
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand new 2015 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
This is Face Off.
Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
We are walking
through a graveyard.
These types of places
really creep me out.
Dead bodies everywhere.
Angel of Death would be amazing.
Grim Reaper would
just be cool too.
Then we see
this huge mausoleum.
And I think, "Oh, my God.
Please don't make me
go in there."
Oh, my God.
Wow.
Inside the mausoleum,
there's a hallway of tombs
all the way to the ceiling.
Oh, my God.
Then we see McKenzie standing
next to a table
full of pictures of couples.
I hope these people aren't dead
and they expect me
to bring them back to life.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
Welcome to
the Pasadena Mausoleum.
As you can see,
I have something
very special in store
for you this week
because this is
the 100th episode of Face Off.
This is huge.
This is awesome.
I've been watching
Face Off since season one,
so I'm really honored
and excited to be a part
of this milestone.
Yes!
There's only gonna be
one 100th episode of Face Off
and we all get to be in it.
This is a really cool moment.
Well, in honor
of our anniversary,
we're gonna mark this occasion
with one of
the most special events
in many people's lives...
a wedding.
Ooh.
In films like The Corpse Bride
and Beetlejuice,
we saw that love truly has
no bounds
and can continue way beyond
until death do us part.
So for this unique
spotlight challenge,
you'll be working
in teams of two,
but your models
won't be the ones
that you're used to.
Instead, each team
will choose one
of the real life
engaged couples
on these tablets
and transform them
into a whimsical
but macabre duo.
Yes!
In fact, we're going
to do something
that we have never done before,
and it's huge!
Your corpse-like couples
will be getting married
on the Face Off reveal stage.
- Ohh.
- Oh, that's nuts!
And, as an ordained minister,
I have the honor of officiating
the wedding ceremony.
All of these couples
are gonna get married
in our character makeups?
That's insane.
- Wow.
- What? That's so cool.
Oh, my God.
All right, well, you're
gonna need some teams
before we get started,
so why don't you go ahead
and choose your own teammate?
- Oh, my goodness.
- Brandon?
- What's up?
- Jasmine?
- Yes.
- Dude, awesome.
Yes.
Okay, it's time to choose
your engaged couples.
Libby and Brittany,
you're up first.
All right, guys,
each of your tablets
has been preloaded with a video
that will help you
get to know your couples.
Try to find something unique
about them to help
drive your creative choices.
Remember, you're only
creating makeups
for the biggest day
of these people's lives.
- So no pressure there.
- Wow.
- God.
- Good luck. Bye, guys.
- Bye.
- Let's do this!
All right, well,
first things first,
we need to watch this video.
Let's meet our couple.
My name is Serge Conis.
I'm from Tampa, Florida.
I'm Charlotte Langley
from Florida, too.
I enjoy classic
game collecting.
Yeah, we like video games.
I'm pretty excited
with the couple.
They seem very fun, very nerdy.
Kinda like myself and Ricky.
If we could make me
look hot--
Got it.
Yeah.
So our concept is Serge was out
by the pool playing PlayStation,
and they both fell in
and got electrocuted.
- This is gonna be super cool.
- Yeah.
- I'm Tom.
- I'm Liza.
And we're from
Tustin, California.
We love cats so much, we were
probably cats in another life.
Tom and Liza's love for cats
begs for a feline character.
Our dream wedding theme
would be Beauty and The Beast.
So we ultimately come up
with a felined
Beauty and The Beast.
I mean, even making
him large in a--
- But still non-threatening.
- Yeah.
Liza is gonna be a cat lady.
She's in love with her cat
and, in the afterlife,
her cat is living his fantasy
out by being the beast
he thought he was in real life.
- That would be fun.
- Yeah.
Hey, guys.
I'm Leah.
Hi, I'm Andrew.
Was it love at first sight?
What do you think?
Nope.
Leah and Andrew
have big personalities.
We both like playing games.
I'm really competitive.
I proposed Christmas morning
with my family in Houston.
We could always tie in
the Christmas part.
That would certainly
add in the whimsy.
Right.
Because they were engaged
over Christmas time,
we decide that
they are carolers.
He steals her away
to the woods and asks
for her hand in marriage
and they get lost
and freeze in the woods.
We have to shoot
for top look this week.
Yeah.
We are Cassandra and Matthew.
Hi.
Our proposal was
in the Grand Canyon.
I took her out
to the Black Bridge
over the Colorado River
while the sun was setting.
- It was really beautiful.
- What are we gonna do?
Ooh, I mean, they said
they got engaged
on a bridge.
Maybe they committed
suicide together
so they could be
together forever.
Maybe he hit a rock
and got a broken neck.
- Yeah.
- He's gonna have a broken neck.
In order to keep it
more whimsical,
she's gonna grab him by the hair
and pick his head up
to give him a kiss.
That will add a bit
of physicality to it
for the reveal stage.
- This is gonna be cute.
- Yes.
My name is Michael.
I live in Los Angeles
with Devin.
So I'm stoked that
we've got the gay couple
because I'm gay.
I'm all about
gay marriage rights.
I like to do makeup,
I like to style wigs,
even though that's what
I do for a living.
If I'm doing drag,
we'll go out together.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Michael is so creative.
I like to paint, draw.
Michael is an artist,
so I think we're gonna try
to play off that.
We decide we'll do
an artist chick.
She draws a character
in her sketch book
and falls so madly in love
with it.
She is so distraught
that she can't be with him,
she stabs herself through
the heart with her art supplies.
Her sacrifice brings
the drawing to life.
The drawing is so deeply in love
with her
that he ends up taking his life,
and it reunites the two of them.
I like that idea.
That's-- that's good.
Hi, I am Kelly Vince.
Hi, I'm Rudy Castro.
Brittany and I choose
Rudy and Kelly.
- I love you.
We love nature, fantasy,
and magic,
and I would love to be
in the magical woods.
A fantastical, woodsy wedding.
- Yeah.
- "Fantastical woodsy wedding."
We also have to remember
the-- the dead part.
Everything they're talking about
is life and light and nature,
and trying to bring
the macabre back in
is going to be really tricky.
All right, guys, let's head
back to the lab.
We're going to need
more time to think about this.
Yes!
We get back to the lab.
Ricky and I start
on our sculptures.
Right away, I'm gonna work
on Charlotte,
and he's gonna work on Serge.
We have to keep her pretty
on her wedding day.
Hey, Missy?
I might need you to step aside
for me for a minute, yeah.
Okay.
Let's try and get
something set up
in with-- at least
the next hour or so.
Kevin and I still haven't
come up with a concept,
and I'm starting to stress.
I'm gonna watch this
one more time.
I'm Jamie Hutchinson.
This is Chris Whitney.
- This is our dog, Porta.
- Porta.
She's a pug.
Jamie is the most positive
person I've ever met in my life.
We're like yin and yang.
She balances me out.
Chris is more on
the negative side,
while Jamie is very positive,
so we want to bring that out
in their makeup.
I like the idea
of her looking angelic,
him looking demonic.
Finally, we decide
to make Chris a pug demon
and Jamie this ethereal,
moon-like angel
because she is the light
to his dark.
Could the horns be shaped
kind of like pug ears?
- Like this?
- Yeah, let's do that.
Once we get sculpting,
Kevon takes the bride
and I take the groom.
Hey, guys, we're here
to take a look at your work.
Hey.
All right, so how do you feel
about this challenge?
We had a really hard time
finding a concept.
So tell us what you've kind
of settled on then.
We are doing a tree-like
creature for him
and a water goddess for her.
When they hold hands,
they're going to be
melding into each other.
- Yeah?
- I do like that a lot.
- Yeah.
- Oh, okay.
Show us what you're doing.
I'm working on her piece.
I wanted to bring
some of the shapes
from his face into her.
Right, by extending this--
bit of a crown
right here in the front.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
And I was actually about
to start softening this out.
This is a totally different
design than that.
This looks more
of the whimsical death
that we're--
we're trying to do.
Yeah.
This has more
of a reality to it.
Mm-hmm.
So you might put a little
bit of that into here.
Absolutely.
We got two lovely grooms.
That's gonna be our drag-y,
Elvira-y artist.
You know, I think you
can push it a little more.
You've got this great,
cartoony type of look.
- Angular.
- Make it bigger.
It's okay to do
the cartoony thing?
- Yes.
- Okay.
This is Andrew and Leah.
They were Christmas carolers.
They got lost and froze
in the woods.
What's your faces?
Are you planning on foam
or silicone?
Hopefully going with foam.
Let me tell you-- they are
way too thin for foam.
Yeah.
You'd really have
to beef this up.
For having such a thin
skin on this,
you're not gonna be
able to glue it down.
This is not good.
We want them to look
thin and gaunt,
but we risk losing that effect
if we add more clay onto him.
You could be in big trouble.
Now I'm really worried because
I don't want to destroy
our couple's wedding day.
They are way too thin for foam.
Yeah.
Mr. Westmore's worried
because our sculpture
is almost paper thin in places.
You're gonna have
to run silicone.
Okay.
I'm nervous because
I'm not confident
with pouring up silicone.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Good luck, can't wait
to see it.
- Thank you.
Fortunately, I have more
experience with the silicone
than in the foam, so I think
I can make this work.
- I can nail it, I know it.
- Okay.
We're heading out, guys.
It looks amazing.
Good luck to everybody.
- Thank you.
- Good-bye.
- See you guys.
- Bye.
Just thinking about
just turning the mold now.
All right.
Now that we're happy
with the face sculpts,
I'm gonna take them to the mold
room and start molding.
I really want to get these molds
done by the end of the day,
but there's not much time left,
so I decide to just let the mold
sit overnight.
So I'm looking
at this sculpture,
and I know it's missing
something.
I mean, this guy needs to be
a living, breathing illustration
that just jumped off the page,
and I just cannot figure out
how to communicate that.
That ain't working.
Ahh.
I'm not used to doing
cartoony makeups,
but we've got a solid concept,
so I just need to clear my head
and make it work.
Welcome to Face Off.
15 minutes, everybody!
- That's time, everybody!
- Boom.
- Whoo!
- Come on, partner.
Whoa!
All right.
I'm still feeling like
we haven't caught up
from yesterday,
so we're just
trying to get all of this done
as quick as possible.
Grabbing my little tiny tool.
And matching texture.
All right.
We still have to finish
sculpting the arms,
I have to finish the male face
and cowl.
I'd really like to be
in the mold room
once two hours have gone by.
We've got a lot of molds to do,
a lot of molds to open,
and a lot of molds to clean.
Why don't you just leaven
the clay peels right out?
Just kind of, like, put,
like, sparse, like,
hard brush texture
in certain places.
That's what we talked
about, right?
We really gotta
make this guy more
of a living piece of art,
so I gotta re-work this fast.
So I decide to melt down
some soft chavant clay
and actually brush that
onto my sculpture
that I've already been
working on.
It definitely illustrates
the whole, like, living
brush stroke into the face.
It's looking really awesome.
I like that it looks
like globs of--
Oh-- literally,
you gave me goosebumps.
I'm worried that my face sculpt
isn't as strong
as I'd like it to be,
so I definitely gotta do
a little bit more and push
myself a little bit further
in this challenge.
So I decide to do a chest piece
with a heart that beats.
And these ribs are gonna be
broken out.
Cool.
So that way,
it makes physical sense.
I can cheat more of an
empty gap in the inside cavity
where the heart
could be pulled out.
This character is gonna be
really, really cool.
We open our molds and they are
a complete success.
Everything cleans out perfectly.
We couldn't be happier.
We even have time to do
a first run in silicone.
When it's done,
we should be ready to test.
Right.
Pop it and see how we are.
And we're able to get
two flawless pieces out.
I still want to do a foam run
as a backup,
so we can compare the two
on application day.
I need to get these wings
fabricated for the groom,
so I decide to use Worbla.
Worbla is plastic sheet
with glue on it,
and you can heat it up
and you can basically
form it around anything and then
after it cools off,
it becomes rock hard again.
So I just start cutting
it into strips and wrapping
the metal armature of the wings
to give it some stability.
And it looks like bone,
and it's super strong.
And then I grab a big piece
of dental dam,
and we start zip tying it to it
and then latexing it down.
Aw, that look fucking sweet.
To make this beating heart,
I decide
to do the heart in silicone.
Silicone will give it
more of a translucent,
glossy, living look.
So I rig the heart with some LED
lighting, tubing, and a pump
so that by just moving his arm
just a wee bit,
this heart'll pump and beat
like it's alive.
- Ooh, yeah.
- Yeah, dude.
I think once it's installed
on the complete character,
it'll add that cartoony element.
This is gonna be great, dude.
Hell yeah.
It's time to open our molds.
And they are just not popping.
I hate these things.
I'm so bad at them.
Sometimes the suction
from the clay
is just really strong in there.
We're trying everything
we can think of.
That didn't even budge.
- Uh-oh.
- You having problems too?
If it takes all the strong men
here, we'll get them out.
These molds are just not
coming undone.
- Nothing yet?
- Nothing yet.
Sometimes you need
a much stronger person
to open the molds.
- Missy?
- Yeah?
- Help.
- Oh, do you need help?
Yeah.
Missy is like
the Mold Whisperer.
Just trying to pop--
do you see this?
- Do you see this?
- Oh, my God.
She just-- pop-- bing,
bang, boom and done.
Wait, can you do one more?
- Which one do you need?
- This one.
She just kind of
puts her hands over them
and it's like, dink,
and the molds just pop open.
- There you go.
- You're awesome.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
In this competition, if you know
how to get molds open,
it definitely helps.
One day, I'm gonna learn
how to open the molds
that I make.
I've gotten the shape done
for my head piece
and I'm starting
my yarn-wrapping.
I'm thinking, oh, yeah, this is
not gonna take long at all.
This is going rather quickly.
Two hours later,
I'm finally done
with the head piece.
Hallelujah.
- Come see how good I look.
- Oh, my God.
Yes!
And here comes Ben
with his horns.
Oh, man, this is gonna
take a minute.
- Yeah.
- Here we go again.
Let's play with some more yarn.
I'm gonna strangle myself
with all this yarn.
I hate yarn.
I'm going freaking loony.
One hour!
- Yeah, boy.
- There we go.
- Look at that.
- Beautiful.
No clean napping to do.
It's time to pop the neck mold,
and the back
comes off perfectly.
But we're having a really hard
time getting our bust out.
Oh, shit.
It cracked.
I've only had one other mold
crack on me before this.
I'm not getting upset,
because there's no time to.
I'm gonna try to patch it
with epoxy putty,
so hopefully we'll have
something on application day.
- Tired of wrapping?
- I hate it!
All right, time, everybody!
Boom.
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
Let's see what we got.
- How's it looking?
- Not too bad.
This is an intense amount
of pressure.
You never forget
your wedding day,
and I'm in charge of what
a couple is going to look like
on their wedding day,
and it's the 100th episode.
I'm a mound of nerves
at this point.
Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.
- Yeah.
- It came out perfect.
We're finally able
to see our pieces
and we're very happy
with the result in foam.
Comparing them side by side,
we decide to go with foam
just because it is lighter
and a little more comfortable
for the performer.
Yeah, and we don't need
the silicone then.
Yeah.
Oh, here they come.
- Hi!
- Good morning.
Kelly and Rudy arrive,
and we tell them our concept.
When you're joined together,
your hand fuses
are going to be bark
with water running through it
so that when you hold hands,
it'll be the combination of you guys.
What?
That's awesome.
They love it.
They think it fits
them perfectly.
They couldn't be happier.
- Aww.
- It's so sweet.
I'm just gonna finish patching
and then we'll get started.
Look at this--
Oh, I didn't--!
Tom and Liza are way more
excited about the makeup
than we ever thought
they would be.
So I get started on the cowl
and the helmet
on Tom's character.
- Is that--
- Perfect.
- Does that feel good? Okay.
- Yeah?
There's a lot to do.
But Jasmine and I are already
feeling like we just--
we nailed it.
It looks cool, man.
It looks good, dude.
No.
So I'm gonna have you just
take your tank top off.
Okay.
I start applying
the male shoulder piece.
The foam turned out pretty well.
Where the crack was,
you can't even tell.
It came out good.
It's looking so cool.
And I'm really excited.
Oh, yeah, that's perfect.
Making Jamie's prosthetic blend
into her own face
takes a lot more time
than I thought it was going to,
but it's worth it.
So now I'm ready to slip
the moon cowl on.
- It just ripped completely.
- Oh, no.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
What'd you do?
I just-- I just
destroyed the prosthetic.
I've made a huge mistake.
We have a delicate prosthetic
that is sticky,
and all the edges roll,
you're fucked.
- Damn it.
- Calm down, Kevin.
Re-evaluate, man.
I have no choice but to just cut
these pieces off.
What I'm gonna have to do
is use the cotton and latex
to re-sculpt the parts
that I had to subtract.
Just gonna do it the hard way,
I guess.
This is the quickest method
I have for fixing this.
This is not ideal
for professional makeup,
but it's the best I can do
right now.
I start out basing her
in our pax mixture,
which is our bone color.
Since her skin is so much darker
than the prosthetic,
I really have to layer that up.
Once this layer has dried,
I go over this
with some aqua colors.
- I'm trying this inference.
- Oh, yeah?
Just to give her,
like, a glowy--
- Yeah, that'll be awesome.
- Do you want to do that?
I can't wait to see how
this paint job comes to life.
You can relax that arm.
So I need to get
a wrinkled skin texture
on Charlotte's arms quickly.
So I start wrapping her arms
in plastic wrap,
and it's creating this really
nice wrinkle texture.
By adding the latex over top
the plastic wrap,
it's gluing everything down
while also rubberizing it,
so that she can move around
without anything pulling up.
- You can move.
- I can bend them?
I think so.
Oh, my God, this is
gonna be so cool.
10 minutes, everybody!
That's good enough, dude.
Good job.
- Oh, sorry.
- It's all good.
That's time, everyone!
Oh, fuck.
Time is called and
I'm not feeling great
about this right now.
I just need to figure out
how I want to brush him
'cause they're not
popping off enough.
I have to paint
them like a cartoon,
like a living illustration,
and I have no idea
how to do that.
We only have an hour
and last looks,
and I'm freaking out.
We get to the stage
for last looks
and we have to finish painting
the female character,
as well as detailing out
the male character,
and then getting
their hair done,
getting them into wardrobe.
It's a lot of work,
but I know we can do it
as long as we keep pushing.
Oh, yeah, it looks awesome.
You're like a Jackson Pollack.
Last looks is always stressful
but today, it's extra stressful
'cause, no big deal,
people are getting married
and we have to make their day.
I'm painting as fast
as I can to pretty much
pull this whole
character together.
Right now, he's just
a pale face.
The wing just broke.
Fuck.
Let's get this where
it needs to go.
So we're running low on time.
I get all the tubing lined
underneath the chest piece,
and the heart is in place
underneath the ribs.
Is it stuck?
Oh, oh, oh.
As Serge goes to pull
the heart out,
it starts ripping
the chest piece off.
We can just have it
beat from inside.
15 minutes, everybody!
All right, everybody,
that's time!
You guys are so
freaking amazing.
- Thank you for everything.
- See you out there.
- Congrats.
- Thank you for this.
Beautiful couple.
There's a lot of
emotions going on
because I really want
to be happy for these people,
but I'm devastated.
I can sense that it's not
gonna go in a good direction.
Oh, yeah. We did it.
It's okay.
Wow.
The reveal stage has been
turned into a wedding ceremony
and I'm just blown away.
This is incredible.
I'm so thankful I get to share
this moment.
It's awesome.
- Happy 100th, you guys.
- Yeah.
We did it.
Well, as you can see,
we have some of our couples'
friends and family here
to join us as witnesses
for this very special event.
Good evening, everybody.
Thank you for joining us.
I'm excited to see these guys
and get them married.
Oh, yeah.
All right, for this very
special spotlight challenge,
we asked you to make over
real life, engaged couples
in whimsical macabre fashion.
So without further adieu,
let's take a look
at your final creations.
This is the big deal.
Not only will our look be
scrutinized by the judges,
but also by the couples'
friends and family.
So I really hope they like it.
They look funny and horror
at the same time.
We're really happy
with our makeup.
It's not totally complete
like I wanted,
but they're looking adorable
together.
We hit the mark of whimsy
and macabre with this challenge.
It's like a cartoon
has been brought to life
here in front of us.
They look lovely together.
I can really tell
that she feels beautiful, so,
that's a win for me.
The best work in my entire
career is right in front of me.
They look a-mazing.
Personally, I don't feel like
it is far enough into whimsical
or far enough into macabre.
Despite all of the problems
that we had,
I think they look awesome,
and I'm really happy
with this makeup.
All right, judges,
it's time to take a closer look
at our lovely couples.
I'm guessing they ended up
in the lake,
hence the fish in her hair.
I think this is so funny,
that it's sagging this way,
but his head's hanging
that way.
Yeah.
I think we could use
a lot more of the icicles.
It's too minimal.
That's the thing I actually like
about it, is the subtlety.
It feels authentic,
as a result.
Thank you.
This is fun.
There's a nice depth
to the sculpt.
I love the day glow effect
she has, you know?
Oh!
There's a spider.
- Oh.
Yeah, it reads better up close.
Nice texturing, nice sculpting.
I'm a little confused
with this decision
to end the appliance there
and have her hair
just coming out from behind.
Yeah.
I think they look great,
but I'm still really nervous
that this doesn't fit
the challenge.
They don't look macabre enough
and I am so worried.
It's our 100th episode,
and it's time to get on Twitter.
Tell us made your favorite
whimsical corpse couple,
using #FaceOff100
I'm a little confused
with this decision
to end the appliance there
instead of laying hair over it
to help blend.
Exactly.
I think they look great,
but I'm still really nervous
that they don't look
macabre enough.
Can you tilt your head down?
- Oh, there.
- Look at the kitty.
- I just want to pet the cat.
- Yeah.
This is a cool thing they made
of the hair, too.
Her makeup is beautiful.
I love all these colors in here.
Sculpted on paint strokes.
I like that idea.
In this, the forms
are very, very stylized.
Very cartoony.
I don't understand
the apex of this thing.
All of the stuff
they jammed in here
makes it difficult
to interpret.
They must have had to repair
this with something.
All right, everyone.
It's time for you all
to get married.
- You ready?
- Yes!
Excellent.
Here we go!
We are gathered here today
to celebrate one of
life's great moments,
the union of two hearts
in marriage.
Let this ceremony
serve as recognition
of these couples' undying love
for one another
and their commitment
to a lifetime together.
Today, you are all witnesses
to the joining
of two souls as one.
Do you all promise to love,
honor, and cherish one another?
I do.
Do you promise to protect
your partner and forsake all others?
I do.
Then by the power vested in me,
I now pronounce you all married.
You may kiss.
Ah!
It's so hard to kiss.
I love you, baby.
Congratulations, guys.
You got me.
We're honored to have
taken part in this today
with you on
this most special day.
And thank you, again,
to our couples' friends
and family for being here.
We will celebrate
with all of you later.
However, we do have
some business to attend to.
Congratulations again,
everybody.
All right, guys, the judges
have scored your creations.
So let's find out
what they thought.
Ben and Jasmine.
Meg and Nora.
Jason and Missy.
Ricky and Jordan.
You are the best and the worst
this week,
and the judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Congratulations to the rest
of you.
That means you are safe
this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Okay, Jason and Missy.
You're up first.
Please step forward.
Tell me about your concept
for this bride and groom couple.
Mattie and Cassie
got engaged on a bridge.
They chose to be together
forever, so they jumped.
We wanted them to look like
they would be
in the waiting room
in Beetlejuice.
Tell me how you broke down
the duties
in creating these makeups.
I sculpted his face,
blocked out the chest.
I did the fish.
I did the rocks.
I sculpted her
face and his shoulder.
How do you feel
you did in this challenge?
I'd say eight or nine.
We just love what we did.
I couldn't disagree
with you more.
You got some decent
forms going,
then you went and colored shadow
over some of the highlight
and vice versa, so you've
completely obscured
all of the form that you managed
in your sculpture.
And the bone structure that
was sticking out of his arms--
completely removed
from real anatomy,
and that is very problematic.
All the characters in
the Beetlejuice waiting room
were all very bright,
pale colors.
Their silhouettes were great,
but the paint job
just killed you guys.
As his head was kind of lopped
off to one side,
the sagging was happening
on the other side of the face.
It read more like a paralysis.
I think that you both
fell very short.
Thank you. Will
you please step down?
Ricky and Jordan.
Please tell us
about your concept.
They're both into video games,
and at their beachside wedding,
they both fell into the water
and got electrocuted.
I worked on Serge,
and Jordan worked on Charlotte.
I absolutely love these guys.
They were like pop art zombies.
You really captured
the whimsical aspect
of this challenge.
Love the colors.
You did a great job.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
The woman was fantastic.
I think the forms on her
were the most whimsical.
On the male character--
anatomically, it felt real.
- The chest was so well done.
- Thanks.
I liked the guy.
His hair sticking up is one
of the things that works.
It looks goofy and disco
and electrocuted.
And the gag really sold
up close
in a Beetlejuice way.
- Good work.
- Thanks.
Ricky and Jordan,
please step back.
Meg and Nora,
please step forward.
Tell us the story about your
two characters.
There is this gothy chick,
and she draws this one guy
that she falls so head over
heels in love with
and becomes so distraught
that she can't be with,
that she takes her own life.
And her sacrifice actually
brings her drawing to life.
He takes his own life
so they can be together.
Who did what, exactly?
I sculpted the male
character's face,
as well as handled
the painting of it,
as well as his neck slit
appliance.
I did the female character.
I sculpted the chest appliance,
as well as the face.
We're, I think, both very aware
or our shortcomings this week.
We agree.
The idea of this living painting
is too subtle
to help carry the whimsy,
and the female character was
poorly executed drag makeup,
so I'm not quite
getting this one.
I love that you were swinging
for the fences,
but then you have to take
that idea and distill it
into something
that you can accomplish.
Do you know what the term
"whimsical" means?
That was the first thing
that you didn't accomplish.
And then we got up close and saw
these little paint strokes
that were sculpted in
that prosthetic.
Not in a million years would you
have seen that from back here,
or known what
we were looking at.
Thanks, guys.
Please step back.
Ben and Jasmine, if you'd please
come forward.
Tell me about your inspiration
for these crazy characters.
Tom, in life, is Liza's cat
and they both love
each other very much.
In death, they're able to spend
their afterlife together.
I worked on the female,
and Ben worked on the male.
This is exactly
what whimsy means.
First of all,
stellar form language.
In silhouette, before the light
comes on,
we're like, right, that's it.
Then the lights do come on,
and-- yarn horns?
Come on, what could be
more whimsical
than yarn beard and yarn horns?
I thought this was
such an amazing, colorful,
eventful collaboration.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
The paint job on the woman
was absolutely stunning.
I was very pleased
with both the characters,
and I thought they were both
really great.
- Thank you.
We see graphic breakup,
we get into materiality,
we've got other details
and storytelling going on.
This was a beautiful piece
of work.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
Ben and Jasmine,
you can step back.
All right, thanks, guys.
Would you please head back
to the makeup room
while the judges deliberate?
All right, judges,
why don't we talk
about your favorites tonight?
Let's start
with Ricky and Jordan.
I loved the
graphic design of it,
the bright colors,
the whimsical aspect of it.
Just all shone through for me.
It's very successful within
the challenge.
They did a lot of work
and both of them
really pushed themselves.
Yep.
It was one of the few
that really added the humor.
All right, let's move on
to Ben and Jasmine.
Nailed the whimsy.
You can see it as a silhouette
and know exactly
who the characters are.
They created characters
that lived within that world
so successfully.
Yeah.
But if Jasmine would have
painted Ben's face,
it would have knocked it out
of the park
because her paint job
was so fantastic.
Okay, let's move on
to the makeups
that didn't work
for you this week.
How about Jason and Missy?
This was another paint job
that Missy had her hand in
and made it really dark.
The male character's
wonky shoulder thing--
Ugh!
Which didn't look like
a broken shoulder.
They absolutely thought
they were top look.
That's alarming.
All right, let's move on
to Meg and Nora.
The story was lame.
The makeups were lamer.
I really like where
Nora was going with this--
the idea of the living painting.
But it was so timid.
Yeah.
A little brush stroke here,
a little brush stroke there.
It's like, hey, we get
the idea, but do it.
Right.
All right, judges.
Have you made your decisions?
Yes, we have.
Okay, let's bring them back out.
Welcome back, guys.
All right, go ahead and tell us
about tonight's top teams.
Ricky and Jordan,
you did some really cool
three-dimensional sculpting.
And we thought that
the vivid color
was a great way
to convey whimsy.
Ben and Jasmine,
we loved how detailed
these characters were.
Everywhere we looked,
there was something more
to take in and appreciate.
Okay, which team came out
on top?
The top team tonight is...
All right, Glenn.
Which team came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Ben and Jasmine.
Your characters were the epitome
of whimsical macabre,
and we love how you incorporated
your couple's personalities
into your work.
- Well done.
- Congratulations, guys.
Thank you.
Ben and Jasmine,
excellent work.
Thank you.
But as you know, we can only
have one winner.
Glenn?
The winner of tonight's
challenge is...
- Jasmine.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
We struggled a little
with this decision
because we really did enjoy
both characters so much,
but the beautiful painting
in the female character
is what put you over the edge.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you so much.
To hear my name right now
on the 100th episode
is literally breathtaking.
- I'm so happy.
- Jasmine, congratulations.
Thank you.
Now, there will be
an elimination later
but for now, I think it's time
for us to celebrate
our 100th episode
and, of course,
our newly married couples.
Ohh.
Come on, guys.
It's really cool to be
side-by-side
with McKenzie and Ve and Neville
and Glenn,
celebrating the union
of these seven couples.
It's definitely something
I'll never forget.
Okay, you guys ready
to cut the cake?
- Yes!
- All right, go for it.
Yay.
It is very surreal to see
all of these couples
get married,
plus to be a part of it
on the 100th episode.
It's just overwhelming.
Congratulations to you all.
Let's everybody raise a glass
and give a great toast
to our newly married couples.
Oh, my God!
It's one of those, like, once in
a lifetime opportunities
to be able to stand here on stage
and watch this all happen.
It's really cool
to be a part of this.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net