The winner of Face Off is...
Action.
The Critics' Choice Award winner
is better than ever.
Face Off is back.
Hell, yeah.
But if you
think you know Face Off,
I have something entirely new
in store for you.
Think again.
- Yay!
- This is so exciting!
- Oh, my God, this is real.
- We made it.
This season, the
competition gets turned on its head
with all new challenges...
Create a stunning short film
on location.
Ah, I'm so excited.
Massive stakes...
We like to call it
"The Gauntlet."
What?
And one epic milestone.
This is the 100th episode
of Face Off.
It's overwhelming.
In the end, our
legendary judges will decide
who wins a VIP trip from
Kryolan Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
an all new 2015 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
This is Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
This can't be real.
I'm at the Natural History
Museum.
I see this girl
walking towards me
and she looks
just as scared as I do.
Jason.
Brittany, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
You ready for this?
I'm so excited, I can't believe
we're on Face Off.
Chills is the best way
to put it.
I've worked so hard
to get here.
After I graduated
cinema makeup school,
I got involved
with the drag community
up in San Francisco.
I love doing beauty makeup
just as much as slapping blood
all over somebody,
so being on Face Off
is a dream.
As soon as I walk
in those doors,
my life's gonna change.
I have no idea what to expect.
Yeah, no idea.
Not at all.
I've been a professional makeup
artist for three years.
I graduated from Make-up
Designory in New York.
I grew up in theater
and you're always expected
to do your own makeup.
So at six years old, I was
putting on my own eyelashes.
I am ready to kick some butt
here on Face Off.
- Hey, what's up?
- Hey, I'm Missy Munster.
- I'm Meg, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
Growing up, I was bullied a lot
just because I'm a freak.
That led me
into the effects world.
I found a lot of people that
I had things in common with.
Now I'm a lot more social.
I've worked
in a few effects shops
so I know how to work
in a team, and that's
a good skill to have here.
Where are you from?
I am from the beautiful
Garden State.
I didn't go to school for this.
I learned it on the Internet.
That is very intimidating to me,
but I am tough.
I was diagnosed
with Hodgkin's lymphoma
about six years ago
and I showed cancer.
After my hair grew back,
I decided to shave half of it,
'cause it reminds me
of my tough days.
So if I just keep
believing in myself,
I could definitely
win Face Off.
- Oh, hey, I'm Ricky.
- Jasmine.
I've been in this field
for 13 years now.
I've worked on Cirque du Soleil,
Latin Grammys,
Billboard Music Awards,
so I'm really hoping
my experience takes me
far in this competition.
I'm so nervous.
I am pretty fucking
nervous too.
I started off my career path
as a kid,
chopping up foam furniture
to make all kinds
of different monsters.
That was before I found out
about Savini School,
and now I feel
like I'm definitely
on the fast track to success.
- Let's do it.
- Uh-huh.
This is so cool.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
Welcome to Face Off.
Now, I know that you're
a very talented bunch,
so that's why we're not going to
go easy on you this season.
- Ooh.
- Good.
We're just gonna launch
into your first
epic Spotlight Challenge
right now.
No foundation
challenge means no immunity,
so one of us is going home.
As you can tell, we are here
at the Natural History Museum
of Los Angeles County,
which houses
extensive collections
of animal and mineral artifacts
from every corner of the Earth,
but this challenge is
much bigger in scope
than just little old Earth.
It takes place
on a galactic level.
Tapping into one
of the hottest genres
out there right now,
science fiction.
Yes.
Now, while we're all blown away
by the super cool aliens
in these films,
sometimes the true stars
are the awe inspiring
and nightmare inducing
alien animals.
- Yes.
- Awesome.
For your first
spotlight challenge,
you'll work in teams of two
to create your very own
alien animal.
Yeah.
Now, I've brought
one of Hollywood's
most sought-after
creature designers
to help you out today.
He's worked with huge names
like JJ Abrams,
James Cameron, Ridley Scott,
and Stephen Spielberg.
Please give a warm welcome
to Face Off series judge,
Mr. Neville Page.
Hello.
This is awesome.
I am so excited
to be in Neville's presence.
He is just so good.
Yeah, good to see you.
- Hi, guys.
- Wow.
Thank you for helping me
to kick off
this season's first
Spotlight Challenge.
I am excited to be here.
All right, Neville has
hand-selected items
from all over the museum
that you will use as inspiration
for this challenge.
Today's challenge is all about
shifting your perspective
and thinking out of the box.
Don't think literally.
Look at your inspiration
as if you're seeing it
for the first time
to inspire design directions.
All right, the person
you walked up with
in the rose garden out front
is your teammate.
Hey.
Yes.
All right, now, Neville
mentioned wanting you guys
to think outside of the box
for this challenge.
I'm going to force you
out of your comfort zone
by knocking down the walls
of that box right now.
For this Spotlight Challenge,
you'll be working
with two models
in your final creations.
Guys, come on out.
Oh, my God.
How are we going to do this?
I have never taken two people
and put them into one creature.
It's insane.
On my go, you'll hit the museum
to choose
one of Neville's picks,
and your models will join you
once you've made
your selections.
Neville will come by to consult
on your creature designs
before you head
back to the lab.
You guys ready?
Yes.
- Let's do it.
- Go.
Is rounding the corner.
- Oh, my gosh, yeah.
- The turtle's perfect.
Where's mineral?
Yeah, all right.
Got it.
Yes, I love it.
My name is Sidney.
I'm from Pace, Florida,
and I actually model
for makeup.
After watching
what they're doing,
I decided I can do it myself.
Being self-taught
worries me a little bit,
but my teammate Evan
is on top of his game
so I think we can do this.
We got the Schorl Tourmaline
with Albite.
It's a black stone
wrapped with white mineral.
Instantly have an idea.
They share a brain.
The layout of the two models
is just like our mineral.
She's gonna be wrapped
around the male model
to make it one monster.
Basically, she's
your life force kind of thing.
In 2006, a friend of mine
inspired me
to go to the Tom Savini School
for Special Effects Makeup.
I found my passion.
The rest is history.
I love doing aliens,
but I'm super worried
'cause this is
a really hard challenge.
Hey, guys, so where are we at?
What do you got going?
We're going with a
six-legged, ape-like creature.
Okay, a six-limbed
creature?
Yeah.
That's gonna make it
feel alien,
but those limbs,
which are your arms--
Yay, she can animate--
maybe they're some kind
of sensory appendage?
And that's gonna change
your silhouette.
- Yeah.
- Got you.
So since we have a clam
and it's two models,
I think it's definitely
essential
that we utilize them
to make something open.
I've been doing makeup
for about eight years now.
I've worked for haunted houses
and independent films in Denver,
so I'm used to deadlines.
That's gonna be essential
in my performance on Face Off.
Omar and I like the idea
that the clam can open up.
So these can operate
big shells, little mouth.
I used to work here
in Los Angeles, California,
on films like Blade II,
Spider-man 2,
and The Last Samurai.
About 12 years ago,
I had a newborn baby
with a disability
so we had to move
back home
to be closer to family,
but now I'm here on Face Off
because I am ready to get
back into the special effects.
You've got four eyes?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yes, we'll decorate a face
that utilizes
their double eyes.
My only concern is
the reveal would
almost feel like you've got
two human heads.
That might kind of
kill the gag.
There are things here
that feel alien and organic,
and that's gonna be successful,
versus two people
inside of a creature.
Okay.
Azurite with malachite.
Yeah, I like the colors
on this.
Yeah, and then some of those
protruding rocks
that are coming off,
like, near the bottom there.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
I've always loved sculpting,
loved making creatures,
and then my senior year
in high school,
I entered
a mask making competition
and got a scholarship
for the art institute.
That's when I realized
I could actually
pursue this as a career.
I think it'd be cool
to have pieces of the stone
jutting out from the shoulders.
Shoulders, yeah, definitely.
I originally started
as a computer animator,
but sitting
in front of a computer
didn't really appeal to me.
Special effects makeup
is a lot more dynamic,
and I absolutely love it.
Maybe stand in front of here.
There's so much riding on this,
being the first challenge.
It's go big or go home.
- Hey.
- Hey, how's it going?
- Good, how are you?
- Good.
We'd like to actually put
one of the spikes on her head
so that it can move around.
Okay, but make sure that
what you're going to not do
is create a rock creature.
- Okay.
- It can have the surface
that mimics rock perhaps,
but it can't be made of rock.
Okay.
My name's Scott,
nice to meet you.
Jordan, nice to meet you,
Scott.
- I'm Nora, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
All right, we've
got the ram horn.
- Ram horn, all right.
- Yes.
I was not a person
that wore a lot of makeup
myself growing up,
always been a tomboy,
so makeup effects school
wasn't exactly
the obvious route for me.
I went to community college,
took philosophy and art courses,
and that's when I found out
about the Tom Savini
Special Makeup Effects program.
I actually just graduated
the day before I came out here.
No rest.
I went from one
high stressful situation
to the next.
What if it's a predator?
We need to have some sort of--
- Not necessarily a defensive...
- It's got to be quick-moving.
But an offensive system,
so what is that?
Claws? Teeth?
What?
Thinking we make this
into a claw.
My name is Scott.
I'm 43 years old.
Over the last 18 months,
I've had
several major life changes,
starting with losing 110 pounds.
Then I got a divorce,
moved to Florida, and started
to work at a special effects
materials supplier,
and as a result,
I fell back in love
with my childhood passion.
Now with my weight loss,
my newfound energy,
it's time for me to reboot
the rest of my life.
There's so much texture
and detail, which is great.
Just make sure you focus
on what we're gonna see.
Spend a lot less time
on the back, and try and get
some of those details
done in paint
versus sculpting scales
for example.
Absolutely.
All right, we got
the native silver.
It's the big one.
- It's that big one over there.
- Okay.
I started by working
at haunted houses.
I'm still new to it,
but in 2013,
entered competition
for Top Haunts Magazine.
I won best makeup artist.
Now I'm here to win Face Off,
and I'm gonna try my hardest.
Let's start back-to-back
just to see, like,
- proportions and stuff--
- Yeah, Lily's height could--
- Yeah.
- There we go.
I grew up behind the scenes
of the film industry.
My mother was
a casting director.
I remember going to sets
with her
and being in awe
of everything that was going on.
I only graduated
from Makeup Designory
a year and a half ago,
so I'm a little worried
because Stevie and I
are so new to this.
I just really hope that
we pull together as a team.
We got the native silver.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
And we're making
a being that could
use all of her subjects
as miners
to draw the silver
from the Earth.
That's good
for a different challenge.
This is about
the organic animal.
Not necessarily gonna have
culture, et cetera.
Just worry about making
- a really cool creature.
- Okay.
This is horrible.
It's just really bad.
Forgetting what
our challenge is about
is not the first impression that
I wanted to make on Neville.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Yeah, my pleasure.
We just wasted all of that time.
All righty, guys,
it's time to go.
Now we're gonna have
to come up with a new concept
in the lab without the models
and without Neville's advice.
If that doesn't get done,
we're screwed.
_
Holy crap.
- Oh, my God, look at all this.
- Whoo!
Wow.
We get into the
lab for the first time
and words can't describe
how awesome it is.
I'm blown away.
- Oh, my God. Vacuum forms.
- Ah!
- Nice.
- Wow.
- Oh, yes, this is my room.
- This is it.
It is like a playground
combined with a candy store,
and it is amazing.
Oh, my God.
All right, guys,
let's get to work!
Oh.
All right, all right.
My partner is
Ben and our creature
is a cave dweller
that hides from an alien race
that wants to harvest
formations
that are growing
out of their backs.
Are we still going
with a no eyes thing or?
I was gonna make a flap
right here,
so that he can
see though--
Nice.
Our plan is to make a face,
a cowl, four giant legs,
and fabricate a giant body.
It's a tall order.
I like where we're headed.
Cool.
Yeah, yeah.
The first thing
Libby and I have to do
is figure out our concept,
because we forgot
the animal part.
We have a head here and
something that looks like a head
- to kind of throw off the prey.
- Yeah.
The concept is
this bug-like creature.
The top half is alluring,
and the bottom half of it
will trap you
once you get too close.
All of the texture will be
these rock formations.
Okay, I'm gonna go grab clay.
Hey, guys, here with my dad
for the first walk-through
of the season.
- Oh, hey!
- Whoo-hoo!
Yeah!
There's Michael Westmore,
amazing,
Oscar-winning makeup artist.
I'm really freaking out.
We chose alligator skin,
and it has a giant jaw
that's able to snare
and catch things.
This is the roof of the mouth.
It looks like a girl
that's had injections.
It can't have human elements
to it at all.
Right.
So put this form down here
so this whole thing
looks like a ladder.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
We chose the herbivore jaw.
What's your color
scheme gonna be now?
Dark shades of brown
and then dry brush over it
with a little bit of a highlight
in a bone color.
If you get it muddy,
I'm going to kill you.
Start off very light
and build up.
Deal.
We chose the ram horn,
and it's gonna be this snake,
reptilian armored animal.
And you're gonna have horns
coming out of here?
Yes, that's where the first
set of horns would be,
maybe a smaller set
coming out of the cheek area.
You could probably get away
with making one mold
and just running it in urethane
a couple times.
Definitely.
So tell us what you chose
at the museum for inspiration.
We have tourmaline with albite.
What I'm seeing here
is the devil.
- Oh!
- Exactly, exactly.
- I knew it. I knew it.
- You know?
It really should be
asymmetrical
like you've done there.
- Okay.
- Yes.
We are doing one creature
with two heads.
If you have time,
do away with this human crease
by making a little piece
that would fill
all the way out there,
because this is a mask
with human eyes.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Good luck, everybody.
- Thank you!
- Bye, thank you.
- Bye!
I like that a lot.
If you're happy, I'm happy.
I am sculpting the two shells
and Kevon is sculpting
the inside of our clam,
but I'm a little worried
because of the size
of all these sculpts.
I have never attempted
anything close to this before.
I don't think
it hurts to go bigger.
Right, yeah.
I'm definitely nervous.
Time's up, everybody!
Oh, my God.
Holy cow, I'm here.
The Face Off house is unreal.
This place is huge.
- Wow, this is insane.
- Ho!
It's completely
surreal to be here.
We all can't believe it.
We're so excited.
Congratulations, everybody.
Today, Stevie and I
have a lot to work on,
and since we wasted
a whole bunch of time
coming up with a new concept,
Stevie suggests we combine
my face with my cowl
and make it a mask.
- Yeah, look at that.
- That's good enough.
Now we can do one mold,
rather than separate pieces.
Today I need to
get this face done,
so I put the final details
on it...
Evan.
And I get it to Sidney
for molding.
And then I get working
on finishing the back
and starting the arm.
We have a lot of work to do
and I just hope
that we can get it done.
_
Oh, it's happening.
I'm getting nervous about time.
We have a ton of molds
we have got to get done.
We should probably start
casting up as many as we can.
On top of that,
I have a really big priority,
and that is the mouth
of this clam,
and time is ticking.
I figure we do the buckets
or something,
- we'll mix a big batch.
- All right, cool,
can you start
without me at all?
Things are taking longer
than they should be,
and these are the biggest molds
I have ever had to make.
I'm freaking out a little bit.
Shit.
I am very nervous.
Get more...
This is a tall order to fill,
and I'm worried
that we bit off way too much.
Me and Kevin only have five
hours left.
and these are the biggest molds
I have ever had to make.
I'm gonna switch gears,
'cause I got to get
that other mold started.
We just got to divide
and conquer,
so Omar is doing
the mold of the heads
and the inner membrane
of the clam,
and I'm working
on the clam's mouth.
You guys have the biggest
shit I've ever seen.
I know.
It's frustrating.
This is hard.
We can do it, though.
I've been up against worse
deadlines than this.
I start working on
the wings for our alien animal.
It's taking this long to dry,
makes me a little nervous.
Yeah.
The slip latex
is not drying quick enough.
so I use some stretchy fabric,
cover that in slip latex.
That way, we'll only have to do
one layer of latex
but we'll still have
the stability we need
to lift it off the floor.
- It was a happy accident.
- Happy, happy accident.
It was, like,
completely happy accident.
So I' going
off of Neville's suggestion
and making feelers
out of a pipe insulation tube
and panty hose.
Hopefully, that'll give it
a real nice, loose feeling
when they move.
I also cut the end of the tube
to give it a hand look.
It's so long, though.
Well, I know, it's...
got to feel stuff.
I'm excited.
I am fabricating the
body for our massive creature,
so I grab
several sheets of L200
and start getting
the general shape,
and then I start
laying down tinfoil
so that it'll give it
that rocky texture.
Once all the textures
are on there,
I start painting latex,
forming a skin
around the entire thing,
and I couldn't be happier
with how it looks.
Hey, everybody,
that's 15 minutes left.
Careful with that.
My gosh, did this actually--
yes!
The molds are done.
We just need to open
and clean them out
as fast as we can.
Uh-oh.
Shit.
Oh, fuck.
There's a hole in my mold.
What's this?
I have no idea.
We're screwed.
I'm not really sure
what to do at this point.
This is the main thing
I worked on.
I have to fix it,
but I'm not gonna have time
to finish this today.
All right, everybody,
time's up!
So at this point,
I'm just, like, f-- s-- fucked.
I might not have a piece
to send out on stage.
Today, there's
a hell of a lot we have to do.
It's so thick
right here, but that's okay.
First thing's first, I'm running
the latex and poly foam cowl.
Jasmine is finishing up
the final touches
on the back spine
for the creature.
- You like this?
- Yeah.
I am in the zone,
'cause I have to get this done.
There is no other option.
The first thing we come in
and do is repair the mold,
and then we have to poly-foam
two big pieces,
and we also have to figure out
how to cover up
the rest of our model.
We got to get this done.
_
- Hey, what's going on?
- How you doing? How are you?
- Hey.
- Good to see you.
There you go.
When my models show up,
I start applying
the cowl and the face
while Jordan's
finishing up the body.
The amount of work is
just shy of soul-crushing.
So where is the monster's eyes?
It doesn't really have eyes.
- Okay, cool.
- Yeah.
Your face is right here.
You're gonna be terrifying.
I am very nervous.
Not only is this
the biggest challenge
Face Off has ever thrown
at anybody,
but we also made
a very risky decision,
because there is no way
we could stick those two actors
together and then send them
to Last Looks,
so we're not going to be able
to put anything on these models
until we get to the stage.
So just sit tight for now.
Okay.
Yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
All right!
This might not fit.
I take charge of the application
while Evan paints the tentacles
and works on all
the extra pieces
that we're gonna add
to this character.
Yeah, we're gonna have to
trim that out.
But I'm stressing out
because the cowl
doesn't fit properly
and I have to stuff pieces
of mattress foam in there
so that I can get the face
and everything lined up.
This is our first challenge.
It's so scary.
Everything's applied,
and now we have to get
this thing painted.
We decided to use
a cooler palate
with highlights
of browns and oranges,
and we're feeling good
with how everything is gelling.
Like, right here,
is this what you want?
For our paint scheme,
we're using Pax washes,
which is Pax paint with
a little bit of water in it,
just so the color's
not so monochromatic.
Just keep doing it the way
you're doing it.
I'm extremely stressed
about how long it's taking,
but it's easy
to muddy a paint job
when you're using
so much brown.
I just want it to have
a lot of texture.
All right, everybody,
ten minutes!
_
Not over till it's over.
Time just flies by
and we are so far behind.
You got everything?
No, I need sea sponges.
We've spent so much time
patching holes
and fixing things that now,
we have nothing painted.
Do you think I should take
some of this texture just down
- into her arm a little bit?
- They're fine.
I thought we were just
cutting them.
Time.
We just don't have
time to fabricate the pieces
that we had hoped
to cover the actor's body.
All right, guys, that's time!
We're gonna have
to do the entire paint job
in Last Looks.
We're just not gonna get
everything that we want done.
We only have one hour
of Last Looks.
Turn that way for me.
I'm trying
to finish this paint job,
but I'm nervous,
because a bad paint job
can send you home.
All right, this is
gonna have to do.
Where are those scissors at?
We are just slamming this
all together.
We're pinning, we're cutting,
we're hot-gluing.
This is my first chance
to make an impression.
I've got to make this good.
Right now, we're just
trying to paint, paint, paint
and try and cover,
cover, cover.
I've gotten out of my head
that we're going to go out
with a winning look, but
at least we'll have something.
We get the suit on Isabelle
and we position her with Matt,
and we realize that the front
is completely open,
so we look over
to our wardrobe,
we drape it over it,
start ripping it,
and it's looking great.
All right, everybody,
15 minutes!
I'm having trouble
seeing the vision, girl.
I'm starting to lose my cool.
I don't know how
I'm gonna conceal this one.
Just glue it together.
I have to conceal
this whole body.
Let me just do the eye
real quick.
This is supposed to be
when we're ready
to send it out, and
I feel like we've got nothing.
I can't-- I can't
put this on stage.
It was what it is.
Time's up!
- I've never done anything that
looks like this. - We're gonna be okay.
Our makeup's a piece of shit,
and I'm worried
I'm going to be in the bottom.
We got to go, okay?
We're gonna get ripped up.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
You know our illustrious
series judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve
Makeup Effects Studio,
Mr. Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening.
Oscar and Emmy award-winning
makeup artist, Ms. Ve Neill.
Welcome to Face Off, everybody.
Hi, Ve.
And of course, creature
and concept designer,
Mr. Neville Page.
All right, guys, for your first
Spotlight Challenge,
we definitely threw you
a huge curve ball there...
asking you to make
an alien animal
using two models.
So let's take a look
at your final creations.
From a distance, this
actually looks really amazing,
so I'm really hoping
that the judges
are really digging it.
It's just awesome.
When our creature
is moving around,
it looks like it is
one massive creature.
I am so pumped right now.
I do like the way the
inside of the clam turned out,
but I'm worried
that it doesn't look finished.
She looks fierce,
beautiful, deadly.
We did it.
I love how the tentacles hang
out of the back of the wardrobe.
They look great.
It's hard to look
at it because this is not
the caliber of work
that I like to put out.
My heart is dropping.
I knew we should've gotten
some cloth to cover that.
I see some good
points and some bad points.
I definitely see
the things we missed,
but I'm pretty happy
with my facial sculpts.
Okay, judges, why don't you
go ahead and take a closer look
at our alien animals.
Oh, I see,
this is supposed to be
the bottom of the mouth.
- Yeah.
- I got it.
Ah, that's so unusual.
Thank you.
There's a lot of interesting
shapes here.
I love the coloring on this.
It's kind of like
Little Shop of Horrors.
Yeah.
I can't understand if I'm
supposed to see a face in this.
Thank you.
I like the paint work on this.
They were smart to put
a little bit
of sparkle powder in there,
because it gives it life.
That use of the second
performer
to have these tentacles
is a good idea.
It's different from what
everybody else did,
and it makes great use
of that second person.
This one actually
got worse up close.
I'm losing my mind.
In my head,
I'm completely
ripping it apart...
It's buried in the paint.
So I feel like they're gonna
rip it apart too.
All right, guys, it's time
to get on Twitter and tell us
who made your favorite
alien animal using #FaceOff
I feel really,
really stressed out
because I have no idea
what they're saying.
They did a lot of sculpting.
It's buried in the paint,
but it's
some of the nice form language
happening up in these horns.
I don't see the synthesis.
I don't understand
how that's utilizing
the two performers.
I do love
the paint job, though.
Yeah.
Really elegant
form language happening.
His goes that way
and hers goes that way.
That's kind of interesting.
Okay, the judges have
scored your creations.
Let's find out
what they thought.
Jasmine and Ricky,
Brittany and Jason,
Missy and Meg,
Nora and Scott,
congratulations,
because you are all safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Nice work, guys.
Thank you, guys.
That means the rest of you
were the best
and the worst this week,
and the judges would like
to find out
more about your work.
so Sidney and Evan,
if you please, step up.
All righty.
Tell me about the concept behind
your alien animal creation.
Our reference was stone
with a mineral
wrapped around it,
and the white section of
the stone looks like it's a...
Parasite.
So this intelligent creature
merges with it
to protect itself.
I think you did an amazing job.
Tell me about the division
of labor.
I sculpted the cowl,
the back piece,
and Sidney blocked out the face,
and I fabricated the tentacles.
I absolutely loved
the tentacle movement
and I thought it was
very successful
combining the two performers
into one creature.
The eyes were the creepiest
part of the thing.
I did like your paint job,
and the back end was so great
when it was animated.
Cool idea.
Thank you.
The way you executed
the tourmaline was beautiful.
It felt authentic,
and as a consequence,
it's standout.
- Nice.
- Thank you.
Sidney and Evan,
if you please, step back.
Omar and Kevon.
Please tell us how your clam
inspired your character.
We wanted to create a clam,
so we thought we could have
the models each use an arm
to open and close
part of the shell
and then use their hands
as part of a jaw
that's in the center.
I tell you, it looked
like SpongeBob the Clam.
It was very cartoony, guys,
and it was confusing.
You have camouflage fabric
on the outside,
your colors were
all over the place.
It looked like something right
out of a little kid's TV show.
Okay.
When yours opened up,
it was just a mess visually,
and having a clam
as your reference,
definitely don't make
a clam creature.
It could be clam-inspired,
but just not a clam.
You myopically focused
on this hand gag
and lost your way,
trying to figure out
how to build things around it.
I think there's a great concept
underneath there,
but you didn't get there.
Omar and Kevon,
if you please, step down.
Thank you.
Libby and Stevie.
Tell us about the object
you chose
and how it inspired
your alien animal.
The object that we ended up
choosing was the native silver.
We decided to make this insect
where the top head
would draw prey
while the bottom head
would feed on it.
I made the top head.
For the bottom creature,
I did the cowl and the face.
I think the core concept
really fell apart.
You had this head on top,
which didn't feel
like an angler lure.
It felt like another person
in a body position that
wasn't very inventive.
There's no synthesis
of the two actors,
and that was a failure
in terms of succeeding
within the challenge.
If it's trying to lure
its prey in,
you want to give it something
recognizable to look at,
not down there where it's
gonna get eaten,
but up top where it might
be looking at it.
All of that being said,
I thought your paint job was
absolutely spectacular.
Thank you.
Libby and Stevie,
please step back.
Ben and Jordan.
So what is the overall concept
behind your alien animal?
This alien
creature is a cave dweller.
Part of its anatomy
uses camouflage.
Its main senses
are smell and vibration.
I love this thing.
Thank you.
In terms of the detail
that you accomplished,
it's extremely intelligently
designed.
Thank you.
Who did what?
I sculpted the face,
he sculpted the cowl,
and I applied the cowl and face
and did the painting
on both of those.
He fabricated the entire body
all by himself.
It's like a subterranean
dinosaur.
I mean, it has triceratops,
a rhino,
an elephant mixed
into this one creature.
It's so cool.
- That means so much, thank you.
- Yes, thank you.
The discreet graphic design
that lives within your mineral,
you used it
in such an organic way.
Beautiful work.
- Thank you.
- Thanks so much.
Ben and Jordan,
please step back.
Thanks, guys, please head
back to the makeup room
while the judges deliberate.
Thank you.
All right, judges,
let's start with your favorites.
How about Sidney and Evan?
The fact that they just
covered the second performer
with this parasitic thing
and allowed it to become
the mechanical element
made it
so visually interesting.
That just brought
that whole thing to life.
Absolutely.
That black rock element,
I thought they crafted it
quite well.
It looked authentic.
Okay, let's move on
to Jordan and Ben.
This is definitely the
hardest opening challenge
we've ever given, and these two
delivered on a level
that could not be expected
out of this challenge.
I love that they used
things that were familiar to us
like the rhino skin,
the elephant feet.
It was like an alien dinosaur,
which is cool,
and the color was beautiful.
It was a very resolved
head sculpt
and the paint job was so good.
All right, let's move on
to the looks
you liked the least.
Let's start with Omar and Kevon.
Biggest mistake
was to do a clam.
A clam.
And it was sloppy,
and it wasn't a very
creative clam.
They even sculpted
and molded the shell.
It might as well have been
a piece of L200
with some shapes carved in it.
I thought it was.
I did, too, until they told me
they sculpted it.
Yeah.
And finally, Libby and Stevie.
Great paint job, horrible ideas.
The two heads
was such a bad choice.
Why is the second performer
a second face.
they could have covered him
with a trash bag
and just had him holding wings
and it would've been
more successful.
All right, judges,
have you made up your mind?
I think so.
Let's bring 'em back out.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about tonight's top teams.
Sidney and Evan,
you guys made some
really smart decisions,
and the tentacles
gave your work
that special something
it needed to set it apart.
Jordan and Ben,
your creature is the epitome
of same-page teamwork
and the head was
the crowning achievement.
Okay, which team
came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Alright which team came out on
top?
The top team tonight is...
Jordan and Ben.
The varied textures,
the brilliant sculpting,
and the fantastic
graphic paint job
combined into something
pretty incredible.
- Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
Jordan and Ben, excellent work,
but as you know,
we can only have one winner.
Glenn?
The winner of tonight's
challenge is...
Ben.
Thank you very much.
Though Jordan did do
a massive amount of work,
my favorite things
about this creature
were the face and that
beautiful graphic paint job,
and that was all you.
Great job.
Thank you so much.
Wow.
Being the winner of the first
Spotlight Challenge
is pretty incredible.
It's a really awesome way
to start out in the competition.
_
Ben, congratulations.
Thank you.
You, Jordan, Sidney,
and Evan are all safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thanks, guys.
- Thank you, guys.
All right, guys, unfortunately,
that means one of you
will be going home tonight.
If you'd please step forward.
All right, Glenn,
tell us about the bottom teams.
Kevon and Omar,
the idea of the mouth gag
was great,
but it was your
straightforward concept
that was at the heart of what
went wrong for you this week.
Libby and Stevie,
your paint job captured
the essence
of your native silver,
but it was
the scope of the work
and poor use of models
that really did you in.
All right, Glenn,
so who is going home tonight?
No one is going home tonight.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
My God.
What?
We threw this incredibly
difficult challenge at you...
...because we wanted to see
what you were capable of.
Needless to say,
we learned a lot
about every single one of you
this week,
but you definitely have
a lot to prove next week,
so do not waste
this opportunity.
All right, guys, you can all
head back to the makeup room.
Thank you.
- See you next week.
- Good night.
Got all teary eyed.
Me too.
I can't believe
that this just happened.
I can't believe that
they are keeping us around.
It's all of us.
- You serious?
- What?
We're all staying.
Being given a second chance
is awesome.
I'm incredibly relieved,
and I have
so much more to show.
Oh.
And I'm ready to kick some ass.
Season nine! Season nine!
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net