Damn, you did a great job.
That's a lot of good decisions.
You've really done
a beautiful job this week.
Previously on Face Off...
Tyler's Whangdoodle brought him
a staggering third victory.
Thank you so much.
And Chloe was sent home.
Now, six artists remain,
and tonight they'll tackle
a challenge
of genetic transformation...
Oh, that's so cool.
I've been waiting
for a challenge like this.
...and draw one artist closer
to the finale.
If I don't get this done,
this is gonna send me home.
They're so important
to my design,
but they are taking me
so freaking long.
Oh, my God.
It's like constant pain.
This makeup
doesn't really work.
It's really quite beautiful.
You really have to turn
your game up
at this point, man.
In the end, only one
will win a VIP trip
from
Kryolan Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Face Off!
Welcome toFace Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
I need to step it up.
I was again
in the bottom looks.
But you don't know
what could happen,
you know?
The competition is getting
tighter though.
Much tighter.
It's the real deal now.
The challenges are getting
more extreme.
Competition's getting tight.
Everybody here is a threat.
And I just need to make sure
I stay
on top of my game
and keep coming up
with original things.
- All the girls are gone.
- Yep.
All the girls are gone,
except for Niko.
- Ooh.
- Look at this.
This is cool.
We end up at the Gnomon School
Of Visual Effects.
That is beautiful.
This is a very famous school.
They have top-notch students
here.
This is gonna be cool.
Ooh.
Oh, my goodness.
We get into
this freaking cool room.
All these computers,
and then there's McKenzie
and Neville.
It's like, "Oh, my God.
This is gonna be cool as hell."
Hey, guys.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Welcome to Gnomon School
Of Visual Effects.
This state-of-the-art facility
has produced some
of Hollywood's premier
digital effects artists,
like Neville here,
who is on the advisory board,
so I'm gonna let him
tell you a little bit
more about it.
Gnomon is widely considered
the MIT of visual effects.
Past students,
which include yours truly,
have contributed
to blockbuster films
such as The Avengers,
Prometheus,
and The Wolverine,
just to name a few.
Visual effects
are a really great tool.
Visual artists sketch out
the character
and then it comes to us
to actually build it,
so I'm really excited.
All right, so let's talk about
this week's challenge.
Films like Spider-Man
and The Hulk tap
into the hidden power
of genetics...
Sweet.
...where special genes
or mutated DNA
give extraordinary abilities
and sometimes radically alter
one's physical appearance.
Oh, my God.
Talking about mutants here.
We're doing mutants.
Everyone in the room,
we're like-- just, like,
"Oh, my God.
This is our challenge."
I think we're all,
like, mutant nerds.
On each of these monitors
is a special strand
of mutated DNA
representing
a unique trait or ability.
Your spotlight challenge
is to select one of them
and create an original mutant
who physically manifests
that trait.
- Oh, that's so cool.
- Thank you, thank you.
I've been waiting
for a challenge like this,
so I'm excited.
George, you're up first.
George, you have
impenetrable skin.
Niko, you have magnetism.
Rashaad, you have elasticity.
Tyler, you have wallcrawling.
Graham, you have tunneling.
Daran, you have
panoramic vision.
All right, so, what
are you gonna be looking for
in their final makeups?
We're gonna be looking for
these specific physical traits
manifested,
and I want to make sure
that you guys really
push yourselves creatively
because you got these wonderful
DNA strands to work with.
Now, in Hollywood,
makeup artists have to keep up
with the latest trends.
For many, that means
using digital technology
to help perfect
their designs before
they even begin sculpting.
Today, our friends at Pixologic,
makers of Zbrush Software,
have been kind enough
to bring us
some amazing
visual effects artists
who will help bring
your designs to the next level.
Oh, awesome.
That's pretty cool.
I've never seen Zbrush work,
and now we get to sit down
with a Zbrush artist
and start firing ideas out
and watch them appear,
which is incredible.
Now, you've each
been assigned to one
of these talented artists
and will have two hours
to collaborate with them
on your design.
So, go ahead and get started,
and I will see you later on
back at the lab.
Good luck.
Hello.
- I got tunneling.
- Tunneling.
- Okay, crazy.
- Yeah.
It needs to have
a strong head...
- Right.
- ...neck, shoulders, and arms
with more, like,
vermin-like features.
So, like, we'll pull the jaw
back a little bit maybe?
Yeah. Yeah.
That looks good.
That's already looking
kind of mole-like.
Something kind of like that?
Immediately I thought
sort of subterranean
mole-like man.
Also, he's wearing a helmet
to help him dig
as he's going through
all these tunnels.
I don't want to go
with something too, too big.
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
More, like, cool-looking,
you know?
I don't want to be, like,
a little animal, you know--
Yeah. Yeah.
No, no, no. Totally.
I get impenetrable skin.
The mutant is
a military officer
who is experimented on,
and he starts turning into
an armadillo kind of look.
Oh, dude.
That's so cool, man.
Like, even if you want
to incorporate
- the elastic things, like...
- Mm-hmm.
...perhaps, like, on the corner
of the nose, but really small.
My mutant gene is elasticity.
My concept is this octopi guy
who has the ability
to stretch and expand,
and he's got these tentacles
on his back,
and he's got
this elongated head.
So I'm explaining this
to Stefano
and he's working it into
the computer,
'cause as soon
as I tell him what I want,
he's already doing it
on the Zbrush.
So it's amazing.
I like the way it looks now,
'cause then that helps
break up
the human form somewhat.
Yeah. Yeah.
That is cool.
That's gonna look cool, man.
It does remind me of a bat
and a fly kind of--
because I got wall crawling,
my concept for my character
is this villain mutant
that's in mid-mutation
and very fly-like.
It has these big hands
that can propel him up a wall.
To me, that looks like that
can stick to something.
Metal doesn't attract so
he can actually push it back.
- Oh, push it back.
- Yeah.
Oh, that's great.
Thank you so much.
All right, guys.
It's time.
Let's head back to the lab.
It was absolutely awesome.
Good to meet you too.
- Good luck to you.
- Thanks.
All right, here we go.
It's day one
of the mutant challenge.
We have five hours
in the lab today.
My mutation
is panoramic vision,
and I'm gonna make
this protrusion
coming out of the head
out of gelatin
that you can see
from any angle,
which will be
an extension of her eye.
I've gotta get a piece of foam
and draw out
my design
for the gelatin piece,
cut that out,
and stick it to my clay,
which has gotta
be sculpted separately.
I just hope the judges
are gonna be able
to read this later on.
I get magnetism, and I'm like,
"That's super, super cool."
My concept
is this villain mutant
that transforms himself into
this power source of magnets,
so I want to do the muscles
all built in coils
and have some magnets
in the hands
so he can control his power.
The first thing I start
working is on the face,
but I need to make the cowl,
and I need to do a chest piece
and also work in the hands,
so I have a lot of work to do.
My creature has these big hands
and the little hairs that flies
use to climb up a wall.
Her chin ends here...
- Oh.
- ...'cause she's tiny.
My model's face
is very, very small
but my character's face
is very long.
- That longer--
- Yeah, that-- It's weird.
Oh, yeah.
She has, like, really small--
- I'm gonna have
to actually build clay
to get that elongated look.
Hello, guys.
- Hey.
- Hi, everybody.
- Here for a walkthrough.
There's gonna be a cowl
that is gonna integrate
with this,
which is gonna start here,
all around the back,
- up to here.
- Mm-hmm.
- So, right there?
- Yeah.
Edit yourself.
This whole first impression
is more important
than in the back.
If you're gonna have
to spend half a day...
- Yeah.
- ...sculpting and molding.
Okay. Got it.
All of this
is going to be eyeball.
It's really a story
that the judges need to know.
They would totally not
understand what's going on.
I would think if there
was anything else
that you could put in there,
like little veins or something.
Oh, okay.
Well, I got the mutation
of magnetism.
Okay.
His whole skin
is made in coils.
Be careful that you don't
get them too flat
so it looks like a wrinkle.
If you want to do
that second layer,
you just take your clay
and roll 'em out,
and then lay it
on top of there.
- All right.
- Okay?
- Thank you so much.
- Good luck.
I was trying to think
of an elastic animal
that can stretch and contract.
So I decided
to go with an octopus.
Accentuate the pulling
and the stretching
- in the face...
- Right.
...to sell the idea
as elasticity.
- Okay. Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
I got the tunneling mutation.
So, instantly
I thought mole rat.
You really need to paint
this well
to bring out
all the little details.
And this is also something
that can have
a lot of dirt on it.
Take a big sponge with
Kryolan brown or something
and give it a squirt
and give it
- a smear of paint.
- Okay.
I have wallcrawler.
So, I had that concept
of, like, a bat-fly
that can actually, like,
stick to the wall and climb up.
Mm-hmm.
You're pretty tight here.
You're not leaving yourself
much forehead here.
Mm-mm.
I would, just to allow
for shrinkage.
Okay.
All right, guys.
It's looking really good.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
- Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
So, to create this character,
I'm gonna need to make
a face and a cowl
to build out
the muscle structure.
I'm making the face so it's
scrunched into the design,
based on the idea
that he's just built out
so much that's kind of got,
like, this henchman-y look.
I am concerned that a mole
isn't that
interesting-looking,
so I hope I don't
get knocked down
for being too safe.
That's so you.
Like, the fun-- it's you.
The clock is ticking,
and I'm still working
on the detail
of the sculpture of the face.
That's a huge problem.
Doing these coils
like Mr. Westmore told me
is actually
time-consuming
because you have
to make sure that you make
those lines really perfect.
If not, the judges
will not get the concept.
I don't know if I'm going
to be able to do them all.
I'm like, "Oh, shit.
What do I do now?"
If I don't get this done,
this is gonna send me home.
Coming up...
Oh, fuck!
Ooh, George.
You all right?
Fuck, man.
My body hurts like crazy.
This is your weakest showing
to date.
Nobody's gonna get it.
This is really
quite exceptional.
It's the first day
of our challenge,
and I'm having some trouble
with the face piece.
My mutant has the ability
to control magnetism.
So he's all built in coils,
and it's taken me more time
than expected to make them.
I really want to focus
on having a really good piece,
so I want to take my time
to do this right.
I don't like it,
but it probably has
to be finished tomorrow.
I'm definitely taking
Mr. Westmore's advice to heart,
and to incorporate more
of the elasticity in the face,
I pull the corners
of the eyes out,
pull the corners
of the mouth out,
pull the corners of the nose.
Once I finish sculpting,
it's time to mold.
I need to get this ready to go
pretty quickly,
because when you get the face
done and run in foam,
you can line it up
with the cowl
and make sure everything
is perfect.
Is that supposed to be,
like, her bone?
No bone.
Like, an extension of the eye.
Nice.
I've got my face sculpted.
And my plan on this one
is to run
some strips
of LED lights underneath,
which will actually give
the gelatin a glowing feeling.
Mr. Westmore was not sure
if the judges
are gonna get the concept,
so I'm hoping this will help
this panoramic eye read better.
So, I finish sculpting the face
and I start blocking out
the cowl.
I hear you sighing.
What happened?
My shoulder's locked, dude.
Yeah.
What'd you do,
slap the clay on?
I think so.
Making this gigantic cowl
has taken a toll on me
physically,
and I'm not 20 anymore.
Oh, my God.
What the fuck?
This thing is slowing
me down, man.
So I'm a little worried
about it,
but we'll see how it goes.
You got 33 minutes!
All right, guys, that's time!
Right here.
At the end of day one,
I've got a face done,
I've got the nose molded
and done,
but there's still
a whole lot to do.
I got to make a cowl.
I need to figure out
how to pad out the arms.
And I definitely need to make
some cool mole talons.
I'm worried that I'm gonna
have a tough time
getting everything
sculpted right.
It's day two
of our mutant challenge,
and we have 9 1/2 hours today.
Because my character
is in mid-mutation,
I want to make sure
I get that round back
and the thick parts of the neck
and really make this character
look demonic and fly-like.
Because my model is so small,
instead of sculpting
separate pieces,
I'm doing
a pull-over bodysuit.
I think everybody
at this point's like,
"Okay, got to step it up."
So I got to get this out
because it's my main piece
that is gonna just make it
or break it at this point.
Day two is going
to be very important.
I need to finish the cowl,
so I start sculpting
out the muscle structure
for this thing.
I'm a little bit worried
because it might be too simple.
But since it seems
like it's gonna be
a lot of sculpting,
I'm trying
to go as fast as I can.
Today, I'm finishing
the detail on the face,
finishing the cowl,
and start sculpting the chest.
I got to do it at super speed.
My shoulder is,
like, hurting right here,
but I'm gonna keep going.
If I can lift my finger
to sculpt,
I'll freaking do it.
I'm trying to work as fast
as I can with the coils.
I'm bouncing back from the face
to the chest
so they can look cohesive.
And I want to mold them
almost at the same time.
First with the face,
and then as soon
as I finish the face,
I can start with the chest.
I've got both pieces sculpted
for the gelatin eye.
So at this point,
I am molding them together,
and I'll be pouring the gelatin
in before the end of day.
Feeling pretty crunched
for time right now.
I know this one's
going to take a lot to do.
There's a lot of pieces to this
and everything's got to line up
and look just right.
I finish the cowl,
so now I need to make
some big mole claws.
I find some pre-made horns
that kind of look like claws.
Anybody have
a little bit of extra plaster?
Yeah.
Absolutely.
And I realize, like,
I have to wait
for this stuff to set.
Great.
Now what the fuck
do I do with these?
I don't know what to do
with all this crap.
I'm sittin' around
with 'em like a jackass.
I finish sculpting
the chest piece,
the face, and the cowl.
And I'm trying to mold them
all at the same time.
Damn it.
Every time I do molds,
my body hurts like crazy.
The whole physical toll
of the competition
is getting to me.
Oh!
Ooh, George.
You all right?
- Fuck, man.
- You all right?
Fuck.
It's like constant pain
all the time.
It's hard to think, I'm tired.
And I'm like, "Oh, my God."
Shit.
I still have a lot of work
to do,
but this is gonna slow me down
and I know it.
I'm afraid I'm going home,
for sure.
Fucking shoulder.
Shit.
It's day two
of our mutant challenge.
I am very worried 'cause I need
to get three things molded
by the end of the day,
and it's actually hurting
my shoulder a little.
But I've dealed
with this pain all my life,
and I'm gonna keep going,
no matter what.
I sculpt out the tentacles
that are gonna go on the back.
And instead of sculpting
two tentacles,
you just sculpt one
and make a flat plaster mold
that can be used
for both sides.
They came out beautiful,
ready for application day,
and I am happy.
At this point,
everything's done
on my wallcrawling character.
But the biggest thing
are these little hairs,
and I find these foam noodles.
I can just use those
and melt 'em.
So I'm cutting them
in various sizes.
So the entire day,
I am melting and pinching
and they look great,
but I'm literally making
over 100 of these things
because they're so important
to my design,
but they are taking me
so freaking long.
I know it's gonna eat up
my application time tomorrow.
I'm doing all these molds
at the same time
and I'm looking at the clock,
and I'm almost done.
I'm like,
"Wow, I did it."
All right, guys.
That's time.
Time to go home.
It's been a very hard day
physically,
and tomorrow I got a lot to do.
A lot to do.
We'll see if I get it done.
Wow, dude.
What a day.
Definitely what a day.
I miss my wife
and my parents and my brother.
- Everybody, man.
- Yeah.
I really miss my wife.
I need that little boost
of confidence
that she brings to me.
I hope my wife is okay, man.
She's alone there
with her belly, our baby.
- In a month, dude!
- In a month?
I'm gonna be
a father in a month!
That's crazy.
I got a longer wait.
- You miss your family, dude?
- Oh, definitely.
Definitely.
I miss my family,
but I try to stay focused
because this is all for them.
Come on, I need--
Let's go get something
to eat, man.
I need something.
Let's get it. Whoo.
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab,
one hour in last looks.
I run in, check my pieces.
Yay, they came out.
All I really have to do
is cut the seams off,
make sure everything
is patched,
dried, and ready to go.
How are you?
Our models arrive.
- Ohh, I'm so excited.
- Are you ready?
You have no idea. Yes!
I am so ready.
And I start
getting everything on Megan.
I get the suit on her,
and of course, it's too big,
so I end up cutting the face
and pulling the cowl down
around her face with glue.
I put my appliance over that
and everything's
lining up right.
I'm like, "This is great."
Perfect.
You look so scary.
Let's put the head first.
I start applying the cowl,
and I'm noticing huge gaps
in the shoulders.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let go of that.
It's gonna be
a little problematic.
I end up cutting foam
to stuff into the cowl
to make the whole thing tight.
And it's perfect.
It works.
- Oof.
- You okay?
Okay.
Don't scare me, man.
"Here we go again."
"Time to make another tunnel."
I start comin' up
with this idea
for the tunneler
where he's kind of disgruntled
because everyone else
has a cool power
and his is tunneling.
"You think you're strong?
I'll tunnel right through
your house."
I'd be jealous if I were him.
You know, somebody has,
like, wallcrawling abilities
or impenetrable skin,
and I can tunnel.
But I tell the guy, you know,
"We're gonna make you
the coolest tunneler
you can be."
And he'll go--
he'll snap one day.
_
All right.
Let's try this.
Well, it's extremely important
that these strips of LED lights
line up perfectly to make
the translucent gelatin glow.
Perfect.
I manage to get everything
glued down all the way around.
So, I'm gonna stand you up now.
I'm gettin' ready to start
painting this thing,
and my model stands up
and the LEDs
get caught on the chair...
Shit, I just pulled that
all the way through.
And pulled out of the cowl.
Absolutely not good.
So, I try to run these LEDs
back up to the head,
but it's impossible
because my hand
won't fit up in there.
I'm gonna have to scrap
the LED idea.
Okay, we're movin' on.
The lights were a pretty
important part of my makeup,
so I'm gonna be in trouble.
Okay, I'm gonna
go under your chin.
I have the face piece,
arm pieces,
and the chest applied,
and I still have time to paint.
We're going to win this.
- Do it.
- Let's do this.
I start doing some dry brushes
with my copper Kryolan aquacolor
on top of every coil.
So it still looks shiny
through the makeup,
and I'm really happy about that.
Once I get my base color down
I go glue each individual hair
into every single hole
that I made on the cowl.
I can't have any empty holes.
Every one has to be filled.
But there is so many of them
that I'm gonna have
to make these hairs
in last looks, I think.
I'm gettin' worried
because I spent
a lot time in my application
trying to fix the LEDs,
so I still have
to finish my paint job.
We got six minutes.
All right, everybody.
That's it. Time.
I feel like I'm really
behind on this one.
I don't have
the gelatin pieces glued down.
I'm freakin' out a little bit,
but I'm hopin' that everything
works out in last looks.
- Coming up...
- You all right?
Yeah, it's my arm.
I can't go home on this.
This is ridiculous.
I'm fabricating in last looks.
That is superb.
It's not one
of my favorite makeups.
Whoo-hoo!
Same spot, different day.
I still have a lot of work
to do going into last looks.
Sit down, my friend.
We got a lot to do.
I'm just now startin'
to glue down the suction cups.
I need these to go on
because that's
what's gonna sell
my whole theme of elasticity.
You all right?
Yeah, it's my arm.
Sink or swim, George!
Sink or swim!
It's wearing out, dude.
I'm so sick of making
these things.
I have to make more
of these hairs.
This is ridiculous.
I can't believe
I'm fabricating in last looks,
but these hairs are so important
that I have no choice.
_
- Okay.
- Thank you.
At this point,
I'm gettin' worried
'cause I don't have the gelatin
pieces glued down
and I'm not sure
if they're gonna fit right.
I'm racin' through
to figure out
what's most important,
because this hour's
feeling like 15 minutes.
All right, everybody.
That's it.
Brushes down.
I think that
was the fastest hour yet.
That was the fast one.
Well, the paint job definitely
suffered on this one,
but I just hope the judges
can understand
- what I was goin' for.
- Yeah.
Welcome to
theFace Offreveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
First, let's say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve
Make-Up Effects Studio,
- Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
- Good evening, Glenn.
- Glenn.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
- Gentlemen.
- Ve.
- Hello, Ve.
- Hey, Ve.
Creature and concept designer,
Neville Page.
- Hello, guys.
- Hi, Neville.
And joining us tonight
is a member of
the Face Off family.
She's an Academy Award-winning
makeup artist
for Lemony Snicket's
A Series Of Unfortunate Events,
and she won the Bafta
for Tim Burton's
Alice In Wonderland.
Please welcome back
Valli O'Reilly.
Hi.
I am such a fan of her work.
So this is the woman
to impress here.
Valli, great to see you again.
Good to see you too.
I'm excited to see what you guys
have come up with.
All right, this week,
your spotlight challenge
was to select
a special genetic trait
and use it
to create an original mutant
who physically manifests it.
So, let's take a look
at your mutants
while the audience
at home tweets
about their favorites
using #FaceOff.
It's got a cool paint job.
He's got those
awesome, big claws.
So I'm really happy
with what I've done.
He's got a strong profile,
and it's going
with the background,
so I think
he's a strong character.
I'm loving the size
of this thing.
It's looking very impressive.
I can't go home on this.
This is-- this is good.
At this point,
I just hope that the judges
appreciate my originality.
I'm not sure
if they're gonna get
what I was goin' for,
so I'm definitely
worried on this one.
This makeup was stressful
in the beginning,
but I'm happy with it.
It looks so creepy.
There's something about it
that just tells a story,
and I hope the judges get that.
Judges, why don't you
take a closer look
at our mutants?
That's a nice claw.
Let's see how much
you can move your hands
- with those things.
- Wow.
That looks like
it's coming off.
One of these things looks like
it was coming off.
Oh, yeah.
That's startin' to fall apart.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Some really beautiful shapes.
The paint is tight, man.
He left himself a lot of time.
That must have been
the pre-paint.
- Yeah.
- Nice colors.
Thank you.
I don't get what this is.
Is it a hide or is--
it almost feels like
rock textures
being attempted in some places.
Do you think
there should have been
a little more definition
in the skin tone?
- For sure.
- You know, a little, uh--
It's very flat.
Thank you.
Wow.
It's like a blue turtle,
which is not a good thing.
Those are cool shapes.
They just need to be
emphasized with the color.
I'm worried about
what the judges are thinkin'.
I know there
are a lot of problems
and I could be going home.
Who made your favorite mutant?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
Wow.
It's like a blue turtle.
I didn't have a chance
to finish my paint job,
but hopefully the judges
will see what I was going for.
- Thank you.
This is reminiscent
of Geiger work.
Are those teeth?
- Feels like it.
- That's cool.
Look at that.
This is all foam, guys.
It would have been so easy
to make the mistake
of making it bronze,
and there's so much flecking
and stuff to break it up.
Thank you.
I like this one much better
close up.
There's really nice color
transitions.
There's a lot of colors
in there,
- blending them together.
- Yeah.
- The eyes are really creepy.
- You can see all that pink...
- Mm-hmm.
All throughout this paint job.
Yeah.
Beautiful.
Thank you.
The judges have scored
your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Rashaad...
George...
The two of you are safe
this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you.
The rest of you
are the best and the worst.
The judges would now
like to speak
with each of you to learn
more about your work.
Niko, please step forward.
Tell us about your concept
and how you worked
with your artist
to create this character.
The DNA that I got,
it was magnetism,
so we came up with this design
that he has all these coils
and generates all the magnetism.
It's gorgeous.
You went off
in your own direction
and integrated this coil idea.
I quite like that.
It's a very unique way to have
approached this challenge.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
I really like this character.
I love the metallic look of it.
You did a really magnificent
paint job.
Nicely done, Niko.
Thank you so much.
It's a bit more
of a costume design
than it is a makeup design,
but it doesn't change
my opinion about it
being a really
good-looking character.
Thank you so much.
I really see how much time
and how meticulous you were
with your applications.
You did a great job
with this challenge.
Thank you so much.
Niko, if you'd please
step back.
- Good job, brother.
- Thank you.
Graham, please step forward.
Tell us how you got
the inspiration
for your character.
I decided to play
with the naked mole rat look.
But at the same time,
I threw in, like,
the star-nosed mole just
to make it more interesting.
I got to tell you,
it's not one
of my favorite makeups.
I don't like the way
your cowl and your face piece,
they don't even blend together.
I don't think your hair work
was very well applied.
For me, this makeup
doesn't really work.
My biggest problem is
you did go with kind of
the most obvious choice,
and I just don't think
it actually
played out very well.
I wasn't sure it was a mole
when I first looked at it.
I thought it was
some kind of slug,
and the teeth pop out too much.
I might have chipped them
a little more
to make them not come apart
from the rest of the character.
I hear that.
Graham, thank you very much.
If you'd please step back.
Tyler, please step forward.
Tell us about
your genetic mutation
and how it inspired
this creation.
When I sat down with my artist,
we were thinking of
some sort of fly or insect
that can crawl up a wall.
I wanted to use
the little hairs
to make it look
like that's how this thing
could stick like a spider
on the wall or a fly.
It's really quite beautiful.
You've done such
a large-scale character,
and the thing that
I noted first
was just the beauty
in the face,
but particularly around
the nose and the mouth.
Congratulations.
It's really quite exceptional.
Thank you.
As soon as this thing
walked out,
I thought, "That is superb."
Immediately upon looking at it,
I can put together
its back-story
and that is so important
with a character like this.
It's exactly what I'm expecting
out of this challenge.
You nailed the quintessence
of mutation.
When I got up close,
I went, "Wow."
The paint job is
so well executed, so subtle.
I loved the really beautiful
layering
of all those really
great, subtle colors.
It's those nuances
that make a makeup
really successful,
which I believe
you have really done.
- Thank you.
- Tyler, please step back.
Daran, if you'd
please come forward.
Tell me about your concept.
I chose the panoramic vision.
Instead of going literal,
with a bunch of eyeballs
or one huge eyeball in the back
I wanted to make
a spread-out thing
that looked like the eye
without the pupil or the iris.
And this would, like, pop out
when she needed to see.
So, I guess the white parts
that you had
are supposed to be part
of the eyeball, right?
Yes, everything white
is supposed to be the eye.
I didn't get the message.
When I look
at what's presented,
panoramic vision,
it didn't tell me that.
Makeup-wise, this is
your weakest showing to date.
I think that the anatomy
is really wonky on this.
Make sure that however cool
your design is,
when it walks out here,
it tells us what it is
that it's supposed to be.
You really have to turn
your game up at this point, man.
Oh, yes.
I agree.
It doesn't look
like panoramic vision.
The ordinary person is not gonna
know what the heck you did.
You got to think
about that, honey.
You just can't just, like,
throw your weird ideas
out there
and hope that
they stick on the wall,
because, you know,
nobody's gonna really get it.
Okay.
Daran,
if you'd please head back.
All right, guys,
the judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
All right, judges.
Why don't we talk about
the looks
we like the most this week?
Let's start with Niko.
I dug that makeup.
I love the antiqued quality
of it.
It was
an organic-looking makeup.
He had a big idea,
and he chose to focus
only on that which he could do.
It's one of Niko's
strongest works, for sure.
There was so much detail
in that makeup.
He must work fast.
All right.
Let's move onto Tyler.
The subtlety of that paint job,
it was so well handled.
And that really soft pink
around the eyes
was mimicked throughout
the makeup.
There was just
a lot of great decisions.
The fact that the hands
are all stretched out
felt like it was still
transforming.
Tyler's got
a really good sense of form.
When you got up close,
it had really
elegant, beautiful
little details
in its form language.
He followed
the challenge perfectly.
- Mm-hmm.
- All right.
Let's move on to the looks
we liked the least.
How about Graham?
I thought that tunneling
was such a great mutation,
but going with a mole rat
was just
the lowest hanging fruit.
It's, like,
the obvious, go-to thing.
He didn't follow the challenge
to the fullest.
His has suffered massively,
in my opinion,
from the obliteration
of the human form.
I did not empathize
with his character.
I didn't want to know
more of its story
because I felt like
I knew its whole story.
It's a mole. It tunnels.
I get it.
And what about Daran?
It was so out of the box
conceptually
and it also wasn't
a beautiful makeup,
and this
is dangerous territory.
The question is, do we want
to see what he does next?
The notion of the sclera
creating this graphic mask
was kind of cool,
but just
the dark blue prosthetic--
- it was horrible.
- Yes.
It really was pretty,
pretty terrible.
Very pedestrian paint job.
It's so below
his normal skill level
that I'm kind of shocked
he brought it out.
So, judges.
Have you made your decisions?
- Yes, we have.
- Yeah.
Let's bring them back out.
Glenn, tell us
about the top looks.
Niko, we thought your sculpting
displayed
some impressive detail,
and the paint job
and the overall design
were really well handled.
Tyler, very cool idea to create
the character
mid-transformation,
and we thought that you
did an expert job
creating something
that evoked emotion.
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner of tonight's
challenge is...
All right, Glenn,
who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner of tonight's
challenge is...
Tyler.
It is rare that
a character strikes
such a fine balance
between villainous
and empathetic.
Astounding work tonight.
Thank you.
Holy cow, I won again.
I'm, like,
so honored and blessed.
Now it's getting close
and I'm in top five,
so for the first time
I'm thinking,
"Maybe I could win this."
Tyler, congratulations.
You and Niko can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you, guys.
- Thank you.
- Good job.
- You're a monster, dude.
Thank you.
Unfortunately,
that means you two
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Graham, though we did
like parts of your makeup,
your concept was clearly
the first thing
that came to mind,
and that is rarely
the right path.
Daran, your concept
was wildly interesting,
but what you had in your head
just didn't translate
into the makeup.
We didn't get it visually.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Graham.
As we get closer to the finale,
we're looking for truly
stand-out makeups.
Unfortunately, yours
was just too conventional.
That means Daran,
you are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
An absolute pleasure, brother.
- Likewise, man.
- Thank you, guys.
Graham, I'm confident
that we're gonna
get to see the best from you
in the future professionally.
I love the chance
that you guys gave me.
Thanks a lot.
Graham, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
It has been so great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- See you, guys.
- Thank you, Graham.
Good luck, honey.
Yeah!
I don't have one regret.
I've loved everything
that I've done
and I've had tons of fun
doing it all.
That's the end of Graham.
I got to create
some great makeups
and put them in front of
some really talented judges.
Yeah.
Okay.
I've proven to myself that
I know how to do this stuff,
and I not only
can technically achieve it,
but artistically as well.
I feel like I can do
almost anything at this point.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net