This is a beautiful piece.
I've never seen
anything like it before.
I dig it a lot.
It's creepy-licious.
Previously onFace Off...
Niko's menacing minotaur
brought him his first win...
- Thank you.
- And Tanner was sent home.
Now ten artists remain,
and tonight they will enter
the mysterious world
of the unknown.
Bring that cryptid to life.
We're like, "Oh, my gosh!"
But some teams
fail to see eye to eye.
Bring this crown
right down into the spine area.
How long is this gonna go on?
I'm not your assistant, Daran.
I'm not sure
that it looks like a dog.
For the first time
in this competition,
I'm really worried.
I really want to see
Captain Kirk fight this thing.
You made all that ridiculous
come together.
It's a beautiful piece.
In the end, only one
will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations...
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500...
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Face off!
Welcome toFace Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
I'm really,
really proud of you.
I want Niko to enjoy his win
and not worry
that I'm on the bottom.
It's at that point
in the competition
where you make one mistake
and you're out.
Parts of me think that
I should have been sent home.
But I want to prove
to the judges
and to all my competitors
that I can create something
that's gonna
take their breath away.
I'm happy that
I still have Cat here.
I like you both here.
Thanks, mama.
Yeah, I know.
Uh-oh.
What is this?
We're trying to figure out
where we're at
or what this challenge
could possibly be,
but nobody has any idea.
I see McKenzie.
Is that Howard Berger?
I'd recognize
that beard anywhere.
Howard Berger--
he's a respected,
award-winning makeup artist
and a huge inspiration.
Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Welcome to your
next foundation challenge.
Nice.
Before I tell you about it,
let me introduce you
to your judge today.
He's one of the most prolific
makeup artists of all time,
with a laundry list of
amazing credits, like Kill Bill,
Oz The Great And Powerful,
Breaking Bad,
and The Chronicles Of Narnia
The Lion, The Witch,
And The Wardrobe.
Please give a warm welcome
to Oscar-, Bafta-,
and Emmy award-winning
makeup artist Howard Berger.
Howard Berger
is a huge idol of mine.
I am so excited.
Thank you.
Howard, it is an honor
to have you here today.
It's my honor, and it's great
to be here with all of them.
All right, so fantasy films
are filled with stories
of mythical characters,
like elves, gnomes, and dwarves.
But there is none
more intimidating than the orc.
- Whoa.
- Nice.
Yes! Orcs!
We love orcs.
They have human features,
but they're scary and grotesque.
All right, Howard, what is it
that makes orcs so terrifying?
Orcs are aggressive.
They're brutal warriors.
But what makes them
really scary
is they never, ever
travel alone.
Wait a minute.
What does that mean?
- Of course.
- What is that?
That's a lot of people.
This horde comes down
the mountain,
and we're like,
"Oh, my gosh."
We have to do
all of these people.
Oh, man.
All right, so, as you know,
lead makeup artists
are responsible not only
for creating
the featured characters,
but also the myriad
of background characters.
Working together
in teams of two,
your foundation challenge
is to choose one
of these orc war banners
and use it to inspire
a featured orc warrior
and nine members of his clan.
Nine members--
oh, boy.
We have to do makeup
for ten people.
This is a lot of work.
My heart--
like dun-gun-gun-gun.
Your teams have been
randomly assigned.
They are Chloe and George...
Corinne and Matt...
- Graham and Tyler...
- Hmm.
Niko and Daran...
- Rashaad and Cat.
- Oh, yeah.
Please stand next
to your new teammate.
- Hello.
- What's up, team?
Let's choose your war banners.
Chloe and George,
you're up first.
Black.
Blue.
Orange.
Purple.
We'll take green.
So, Howard, what are you
gonna be looking for
in their final makeups?
I'm gonna look at the design,
and then, of course,
I want to see
what the execution is--
the detail aspect,
the paint work,
the application, how it's gonna
work with your banner.
You want it all
to tie in together.
Also, orcs are really scary.
They want to be really,
really menacing.
So keep those things in mind.
All right, guys, even though
you are working in teams today,
only one of you
can win immunity.
You have 2 1/2 hours
to complete your makeups.
Your time starts now.
Please sit down for now.
I'm just gonna start slapping
prosthetics on all of them.
You three, come see me.
I'm getting all
the background orcs organized
and getting them
through prosthetics...
Okay, other ear.
And Corinne's working
on the main hero orc.
To me, the most definitive
characteristic of an orc
are the pointed ears,
as well as an angry brow.
Matt and I looked
at the flag that we chose
and saw that it was,
like, a moon.
So we want to go
with nightwalkers
that attack at night.
- Daran.
- Yo.
I'm applying ears
and brow pieces.
We're really excited.
This is like working on set.
But this is a lot of work.
To make all of these orcs
seem like they came
from the same clan,
I'm gonna put this image
from the flag on my hero orc.
And then
for our other characters,
we're gonna put the image
on their chest.
Niko, how many appliances
you got on everybody?
Two people,
three appliances each.
This is a lot of work to do.
The winner gets immunity,
but it's gonna be
a tough one to win.
We're gonna take
the symbol from the banner
and put it on each of them.
The banner has an eye symbol,
so our concept for the orcs
is they believe they
have to take their eyes out
to give them vision
of the future.
This is an orc assembly line.
Okay, next.
We chose the green banner.
The main orc-- he's got
this class of orcs under him,
so we've got generals,
soldiers, and then pawns.
We're gonna put brow pieces
on all the generals,
noses on all of the army guys,
and ears on all of the pawns.
They're gonna be green
like the banner,
and that tribal sign
is gonna be on their faces.
We're in kind of ahurry.
Our main concern is to get
every one of these people
in some prosthetics.
When we saw the banner,
it looked like fire,
which made us think branding
and then metal,
and everybody needs some sort
of, like, armor in Middle-Earth,
so these are the orcs
that make it.
Hey, orcs, I got you guys
some hats.
_
That's one hour, everybody.
Holy moly.
- Time to move on.
- Next!
Each brown, blue--
heavier on the brown,
then do the blue.
We have five different
shades of colors
that we sponge paint on
in different layers.
I'm so not a sponge painter.
Bam.
- Whoo, team green.
- That's awesome, Chloe.
I'm gonna do
all of the orcs' hair red
because we have
some red leather
that's hanging from the banner.
I'm almost done with this guy.
We got to move a lot quicker.
Five minutes, guys!
All right, we need to get
black crap all over their hands.
This is awesome.
That's it, guys!
Time's up!
Brushes down!
- Whoo.
- Cool, brother.
So tell us about your orcs.
This is our leader over here.
He's the meanest.
He was actually branded
with a hot brander on his face,
which caused scarring,
and it's the symbol of the flag.
And everybody else
has tattoos on their chest.
The lead guy has that
big, nasty scar on his face,
and everybody else feels clean,
but they do feel
all very similar.
So, cool.
They're very nice.
- Thank you guys.
- Thank you.
We went with the green color
as their skin tone.
The mark that's on the flag,
as it goes down in rank,
it gets smaller and smaller.
I think the green's
a little overpowering.
I would rather have seen
a little more flesh tone
with green qualities to it.
But in the time frame, you made
sure that everybody is green
and got done,
which is important.
- Cool.
- Thank you.
We saw this as fire, so
they're all forgers and welders.
Well, I think there's
some paint opportunities
- that got missed...
- Oh, yeah.
Just going in
and punching things up
and make sure you always
paint inside the ear.
But everything looks very cool.
Thanks a lot.
They believe that
when they take the eyes
of their enemies,
they can foresee the future.
I think your concept
is working well.
I like the contrast
of the red hair a lot.
I was looking at everybody's
flag and wondering
if people were gonna use
any of the accoutrements,
and you certainly did.
Good job, guys.
These nocturnal orcs
come in the night,
and they attack and feed
on other orc camps
or elves or whoever.
They're very vampiric,
which is cool.
They feel cohesive.
I can tell that they're
all uniform within a tribe.
I like the fact
that some are splattered
with this dark blood,
and I think the concept is cool
and I think you certainly
pulled this off.
- Thanks, guys, really.
- Thank you.
So, Howard,
this was undoubtedly
the most difficult
foundation challenge
we've ever given
our contestants.
How do you think they did?
I think everybody did amazing.
I wouldn't want to do it,
that's all I know,
not in that time frame.
All right, well, which teams
had the best clans?
Chloe and George...
you're the only team
that went beyond the banner
and utilized the accoutrements
that were hanging off.
And, Corinne and Matt...
I felt everything
was very well executed
and your hero guy
was really spot-on.
Which team came out on top?
The top team is...
Coming up...
Come on, gentlemen, let's move.
I don't know
if I'm gonna finish this mold.
I was trying to give it
some angularness.
Daran doesn't trust me or think
that I know how to do anything.
- That really looks bad.
- That was a very smart move.
So disproportionate.
Which team came out on top?
The top team is...
Corinne and Matt.
Awesome.
The work that you guys did
was exceptional.
Everything worked together,
and I felt they
were actually film-quality.
So big thumbs-up.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
Congratulations,
Corinne and Matt.
But as you know,
we can only have one winner.
- So, Howard...
- The winner is...
Corinne.
Wow. Thank you. Awesome.
You designed the paint scheme,
and that really led the path
for the rest of the clan.
- So job well done.
- Thank you.
To know that I have immunity
is such a relief.
Congratulations, Corinne.
In the next spotlight challenge,
you cannot be eliminated.
Yay!
All right, guys,
you definitely created an army,
and I think
they're ready for war.
Oh...
Oh, my God.
Oh, they look angry.
Oh, my God,
let's get out of here.
I wonder where we are.
We're walking into this swamp
in the middle of nowhere.
It's super hot,
and I'm trying to figure out
what we're doing out here.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
All around the world,
sightings of mysterious
creatures are on the rise.
They include
the infamous Loch Ness Monster
in the Scottish Highlands
and Bigfoot
in the Pacific Northwest.
I'm talking about cryptids.
Excellent.
Cryptozoology is pretty wacky.
It is the study of possibly
real, possibly fake animals.
On each of these monitors
is a set of coordinates
that correlate to the location
of a cryptid sighting.
Working in teams of two,
your spotlight challenge
is to choose a set
of coordinates
and bring that location's
cryptid to life.
And today you'll be picking
your own teams.
So go ahead and stand
next your new teammate.
- Come on.
- Niko.
- Corinne?
- Sure, buddy.
I picked Corinne.
I loved working with her
on the foundation challenge,
and I'm hoping we can turn
that energy around
and win it again.
When I call your team,
select your coordinates.
Graham and Rashaad.
All right, let's take a look
at your cryptids.
That looks pretty cool.
Niko and George,
you chose Vodyanoy from Russia.
I just knew it.
Russia.
Corinne and Matt, the Jersey
Devil from New Jersey.
Excellent.
Chloe and Tyler, Mapinguari
from the Amazon in Brazil.
Daran and Cat,
Chupacabra from Mexico.
- Chupa.
- And, Rashaad and Graham,
you have the Bunyip
from Australia.
Right.
All right,
I would like you to meet
a very special guest.
He's Hollywood's most
sought-after creature actor.
He's currently featured
on Falling Skies
and blockbusters such
as Pan's Labyrinth,
Fantastic Four
Rise Of The Silver Surfer,
and the Hellboy franchise.
- Oh, my God.
- Yes, yes.
Please give a warm welcome
to Doug Jones.
Doug Jones!
Oh, hi!
- Yay!
- Thank you.
Doug Jones is one of
the best creature performers.
He knows how to bring
a character to life
through the makeup.
Thank you so much
for being here.
Thank you for having me.
This is a treat.
Well, you've elevated
so many films
with your amazing performances.
- Oh, now, stop it.
- No, it's true.
And you're gonna be joining us
- on the reveal stage...
- I am.
So what are you gonna be
looking for in the final makeup?
The word "Organic"
comes to mind.
When I'm wearing something,
I want to know
that I woke up that way.
You don't want to feel
like a guy in a suit.
Also, can an actor move
and perform in it?
That's always key to what I do.
Fantastic.
All right, guys, I want you
to grab your sketchbooks
and start working
on your designs.
Good luck.
It's just hard to draw
without any reference.
Chloe and I look at our tablets,
and we have information
on what our cryptid is.
I think we have to do
all of these elements
that it says here.
This is definitely
gonna be a challenge
because we don't have
any kind of reference material.
They've never
been photographed,
and there's no proof
cryptids even exist.
The Mapinguari
are ape-like creatures
covered in fur,
one eye,
a mouth on its stomach.
I'm just like, "What?"
_
We're doing two things that
the judges absolutely hate--
fun fur, which we're gonna cover
our creature in,
and mouths on the stomach,
which we're gonna do
a giant one.
But it is what this challenge
calls for.
Maybe he has doglike features
but he's not a dog.
Yeah, for sure.
Our cryptid
is the Jersey Devil.
It's part man, part kangaroo,
and it has bat wings,
horns, and hooved feet.
We definitely want to use
all of those elements.
All right, guys,
let's head back to the lab.
Let's go.
We have six hours at the lab.
George and I
picked the Vodyanoy.
I got an idea there.
He's a creature
that lives in swamps,
and so we want him
to have a frog face,
a barracuda type of mouth,
and a tail so it looks aquatic.
George starts
working on the face,
and I start working
on the cowl.
Awesome.
Cat and I end up
with Chupacabra.
I start sculpting the face.
Cat starts working on the cowl.
We want it to have
a very doglike face
with a snake-like tongue
and leathery, scaly skin.
Bring this crown right down
into the spine area.
One element that I'm pushing
for is the color choice.
The story specifically says
that the Chupacabra
has a green-gray skin,
but Daran wants to give it
orange-y, red,
burgundy skin tones.
It's not what the story says.
I don't have a problem
letting Daran
take creative lead on this,
but I'm trying really hard
to make this a partnership.
We want to kind of-- shoo--
slope it down just like that.
This silhouette
looks really nice.
I will be creating
the bat wings,
and Matt will be sculpting
the face and the stomach.
I'm building the wings
out of armature wire,
then I drape a netting fabric.
I'm really excited
about these wings.
I wish I could keep these.
This is a Bunyip.
I ain't ever seen one.
Just don't know what it is.
What we learn about the Bunyip
is that it's got tusks,
feathers, flippers,
and the body of a man.
So we're gonna force
all of these descriptions
into the creature.
Very animalistic, mate.
It's going to be
crocodile from the head,
have feathers like a mohawk,
and have the tusk of a walrus.
Graham sculpts the cowl.
I sculpt the face.
And we hope we can pull it off.
I will be doing the face
for our Mapinguari.
Tyler is going
to make the fur suit
and then block out the chest.
Your favorite stuff
in the world, Chloe.
I start building my forms
and then start
gluing foam cushion
to really form out
the structure of an ape.
It's about halfway
through the day,
and I'm working on the face.
But there's a lot of elements
of the Jersey Devil
that I'm not getting,
and I'm really starting
to get nervous.
I'm not sure
that it looks like a dog.
I'm not super well-versed
in sculpting animal forms,
and I don't feel very good.
You don't really need this.
I feel anxious,
and for the first time
in this competition,
I'm really worried.
She has immunity,
and if we're a bottom look,
I'm in trouble.
I need to fix my sculpture,
or I'm going home.
I'm not sure
that it looks like a dog.
Today is the first day
of our cryptid challenge,
and I feel like there's
a lot of elements
about the Jersey Devil
that I'm not getting.
My confidence level
has dropped.
Do you want to refine that,
and I can start putting
some clay on the belly?
Sure.
I ask Corinne
to take over the face
because I'm having
a difficult time,
but she has immunity.
So, if we're a bottom look,
I'm the one going home.
You picked me.
Remember that.
I did.
- Are you sculpting a tongue?
- Yes!
I'm in the middle
of sculpting the stomach piece
on our Mapinguari,
and I need a reference
of a tongue of some sort.
Okay.
I end up taking a reference
of Rashaad's mouth,
and it really helps.
I think it's hilarious.
Here's yours.
- Thanks, Rashaad.
- You're welcome.
It's time to mold.
We got to get
this face out today,
because since
we're doing the cowl,
we need to make sure
that it lines up correctly.
Then we can move on to
the other aspects of our Bunyip.
We don't need
to be adding more clay.
We need to take away, I think.
Daran takes over the cowl.
He doesn't trust me,
and I feel like
I might as well not even
be here, and that's frustrating.
I need to fight to put
a bit of me in the design
because I want
to impress the judges
with something that's mine.
- There you go.
- We only got seven minutes.
Can he do it in seven minutes?
We're gonna find out
over here on Face Off.
At the end of the day,
I'm still cleaning the mold.
- Time?
- 2:22.
I'm pushing it.
_
We've got minutes left
on the clock.
- A minute and 38 seconds.
- Go!
I've just got my fingers crossed
Graham can get it done
so we can run in foam.
You got 20 seconds, Graham!
Here comes the mold strap.
I'm spraying this mold out
with seconds left.
We get it done.
All right, everybody,
that's time!
By the end of the first day,
the face is already finished.
Tomorrow we're in a good spot.
So it's looking
pretty good for us.
Let's do this.
It's day 2
of our cryptid challenge,
and we have 9 1/2 hours
in the lab today.
Check that out.
The foam gods love us.
No, your molds love us.
Maybe make it, like,
a little more of a fish scale.
We have a lot of work to do.
George needs to finish
detailing the face and the cowl.
I need to start sculpting
the chest and back.
I'm trying to get this chest
molded today.
I hope we can do it.
- It's gonna be beautiful, dude.
- Yeah.
I'm just making sure
that, you know,
we don't put
all this time and effort
into veins you don't even see
until you're--
They'll see it.
Corinne is definitely
leading this team.
I want to do bigger, but Corinne
keeps wanting to go minimal.
It is really hard to see
from far away.
If we don't do enough
and we're a bottom look,
I'm gonna
take the brunt of that.
Come on, let's move,
gentlemen, let's move!
- George?
- Yes?
Can you bring me hemp?
I'm putting the last layer
of the mold, but it has to dry,
and we have to open it,
we have to clean it.
So I don't know, at this point,
if I'm going to get it done.
How much time?
- 32.
- 32 minutes.
- Let's take it outside.
- Come on, dry for me.
If we don't get this out,
we will have no chest
and no back,
no tail, no nothing.
We got to help 'em
open this mold.
We're attacking this thing
to get it open.
Oh, it's opening.
All right, come on, let's do it.
- Got it.
- Yeah!
Put it on the floor.
With one minute left,
there's just so much chaos.
All right, let's go, guys.
- Got it.
- Got it, got it, let's go.
Oh, my God.
We do it in the nick of time.
All right, guys, that's time!
I'm really grateful
that I have, like,
good people that help us.
We couldn't do it without them.
We got it.
It's application day.
We got four hours in the lab,
one hour at last looks.
We're just ready to apply
this thing and get going.
We just need a bucket of water
and a bucket of thinner.
- How's the face?
- It's good.
I'm gonna grab some clay
real quick
and just make a quick hoof.
I think that we've gone
way too subtle,
so I'm working on getting
some hooves made up.
It's an additional piece
that might punch it up.
- Hey, man, good to see you.
- Good to see you too.
Ours is more
like a frog-fish.
Ooh, you got
a good bald cap head.
Ready to be a Bunyip?
There you go.
Okay, thinner right here.
Glue here.
Daran pours up some glue
and says,
"Hey, Cat, stand here."
- Glue.
- And I'm standing there like,
"How long is this
gonna go on?"
Fill me up
a little more glue, please.
I'm not your assistant, Daran.
Do you want to have him
hold the cups?
I think it would be
a better use of our time
for me not to stand here
and hold cups.
We've got a lot to do,
so I kind of
just move on really fast.
We need to start painting
and applying our model.
You're good.
- We got to get painting going.
- Start.
We have all the pieces
applied on him
and start applying paint.
I'm going with this
minty-green color.
It looks unreal,
which it would make sense to me
for a creature like this.
This is, like, a perfect blend
of these two colors.
Just like you and me.
We decide on
an overall paint scheme,
which needs to transition all
of these different animal parts.
That's a Bunyip.
Everybody,
that's 15 minutes left.
That's time, everybody.
Everyone's concepts
are so great,
and I'm looking at ours
and it's not looking good,
but it's what we have,
and we have to go with it.
It sucks because I let Daran
make so many
of the important decisions,
and I don't want to go home
for something
that I know wasn't my design.
Coming up...
This is the fastest hour
of my life.
- Look at in there.
- Oh, boy.
One of us could be going home.
Wow.
That's impressive.
Dudes, you got
the kitchen-sink boogeyman.
All right.
It's last looks, and we know
we have a lot of work to do.
I need to glue the tail.
We need to finish
all the paint job.
We're trying to work
as fast as we can.
- I got to lay all this hair.
- It's looking really good.
At this point,
we got to make sure
every element
is on our character,
because at the end of the day,
one of us could be going home.
You want to hot-glue
this to here?
This is the fastest hour
of my life.
You want to leave this hair
long like this?
- I was thinking.
- We should, uh...
maybe cut some of this down.
I like 'em kind of flaring off.
I'm not happy
with the hair at all.
Daran doesn't listen
to anything I say.
15 minutes, guys!
15 minutes.
Where's his teeth?
All right, guys, that's it.
That's time.
- Yay!
- High fives.
I'm sorry, but it looks good.
I'm not feeling very confident,
and I really don't want to go
home because of this makeup.
I'd rather go home
on an individual challenge,
knowing that it was my fault
rather than someone else's
poor decisions.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
Say hello
to our talented judges...
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick...
- Good evening.
- Hey, Glenn.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill...
- Hello, everybody.
- Hey, Ve.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page...
- Hi, guys.
- Hi.
And joining us again is famed
creature actor Doug Jones.
Hey-- Oh, thank you.
Thank you for having me back.
I can't wait
to see what happened
over the last couple days.
All right, guys, this week
your spotlight challenge
was to choose a set
of coordinates
and create the fabled cryptid
found at that location.
Let's take a look
at your creations.
I'm not happy
with this creature.
I definitely regret
not pushing the ideas
that I wanted in this makeup.
There are a lot
of risky things we did
that the judges
might absolutely hate.
But I hope they notice
that we really did try do it
in a way that did make sense.
I think we did
bring the folklore to life.
It's creepy,
and I'm proud of it.
It just looks so cool.
I'm happy to show Doug Jones
what we've made.
Maybe it's something
he might want to wear.
I know she's not quite
as stunning and striking
as the other cryptids.
I'm just hoping, at this point,
that we're safe.
Judges, it's time to take
a closer look at our cryptids.
What happened here?
Dude,
this is a speckle-fest.
And as we go
into the face, mud.
It's so sloppy.
Turn all the way around,
please.
- Is the spine off-center too?
- Yeah, looks like it.
All right, thank you.
I like how this fur has been
all treated from head to toe.
Look how beautiful
the paint is on the tongue.
Look, that's a lot of movement
out of that thing.
Yeah. That's got to hurt.
Thanks.
Turn sideways.
This line here is really cool.
- Matches this one back here.
- Mm-hmm.
So he's balanced.
- Good.
- Thank you.
Excellent.
This dude's
got it all going on.
Turn all the way around.
Wow.
You wouldn't have put feathers
and reptilian together,
would you?
It works.
Thanks.
I think that's
the kangaroo belly.
- I guess.
- The skirt hides it.
Everybody else
got so much done,
and all they have is the wings
and this facial sculpt.
Yeah.
I know that the judges
are thinking,
"It's just not as good
as everyone else's."
So, if we're a bottom look,
I'm probably
going to be going home,
because Corinne has immunity.
Who made your favorite cryptid?
Tell us on Twitter,
using #FaceOff.
Everybody else
got so much done,
and all they have is the wings
and this facial sculpt.
Yeah.
I'm starting to feel like this
may be my last day here.
It's just not as good
as everyone else's.
Can you move
your eyebrows at all?
- Mm-mm.
- No?
All right.
Thank you.
So, Doug, you gave these guys
some great advice the other day.
What do you think
of the final creations?
I think that everybody
listened really well.
You all have elements that
move well, each one of you.
- They did a great job.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Okay, the judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Tyler and Chloe,
you're up first.
Tell us about
your design, guys.
This is a Mapinguari,
a creature that has one eye,
a mouth on the stomach,
and lots of mudded red fur.
Chloe sculpted the face.
I fabricated the suit.
I sculpted the mouth,
and we both painted together.
I really want to see
Captain Kirk fight this thing.
I think that
your greatest triumph
is taking all those
extremely ridiculous things
and combining it in a way
that's not so ridiculous.
- Yeah.
- Wonderfully done.
Thank you.
I think you did
a really great job
not using red fur
but using the semi-gingerish,
warm coloring.
And the fact that
you matted it all down--
that was a very smart move
on your part.
Thank you.
I particularly love the forms
on the chest
imply, with the nipples,
a set of eyes.
Your character
has character within it.
It's so good on so many levels,
so congratulations.
Thank you.
The mouth in the middle
of that belly
is the centerpiece for me,
especially from
a performance level as well.
It's a beautiful piece.
Thank you.
Tyler and Chloe,
please step back.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, guys.
Matt and Corinne.
Tell us about your character
and who did what on the project.
We got the New Jersey Devil.
It had features of dogs
in its face.
It had devil-like horns
and tails, bat-like wings,
and a kangaroo body.
I made the wings and the horns.
Matt sculpted the face,
did the hooves and the tail.
I think you just didn't do
enough this week, guys.
Everybody else
did so much more,
and you guys just had
fabric wings and this face,
and the wings look
like draperies, unfortunately.
So I'm a little bit
disappointed in that.
If it's gonna be minimal,
it's just got to be so precise.
But I don't think that you've
executed a high-end makeup.
We should want
to shrink in terror
from the horrible visage
of the Jersey Devil,
and instead, you chuckle
at the curtain-wing demon.
You made some tough decisions
this week, guys, sorry.
Matt and Corinne,
please step back.
I'm sorry.
Let's talk to Niko and George.
Tell us about your creation.
Our creature's name
is Vodyanoy.
He's known
to have a frog-fish body.
This is mostly frog,
and for fish, a barracuda,
and then fish scales
going through the body.
There are some really
good things in this.
What I like the most about it
is that there are details
that look physically
purposeful,
like the elements
on his forearm.
They feel like
they're hydrodynamically
meant to be there.
I like seeing things that feel
like they have a reason.
What I like specifically
about this one
is the consistency
of your fin-like attributes,
from the head, the shoulders,
all the way down
to the sides of his arms,
the back of the tail.
There's a balance to him.
Great job.
Thank you.
Niko and George,
please step back.
Yeah, buddy.
Rashaad and Graham,
please come forward.
So tell us about
the inspiration of this design
and who did what on what.
This is called a Bunyip.
It has the tusks of a walrus,
feathers like a bird,
crocodile-type head,
flippers, and a horse tail.
I sculpted the face.
Graham sculpted the cowl.
And we broke down
the paint job.
I actually like this one a lot.
The description was ridiculous,
and you made
all that ridiculous
come together
in a cohesive being.
I love the two rows
of teeth placed willy-nilly
as though it really just--
kahh!--
came out of somewhere
and-- ahh!
- I like this one a lot.
- Thank you.
One sculpted the face,
one sculpted the cowl?
Yeah, I sculpted the face.
Graham sculpted the cowl.
Wow. That's impressive,
because the face and the cowl
look like they were sculpted
by one person.
Well done.
That's really tight.
Dudes, you got stuck
with the kitchen-sink boogeyman.
I can't even remember
all the stuff
that it said it had on it.
I love the colors
on the paint job.
And his profile is amazing.
- Thank you.
Rashaad and Graham,
please step back.
Daran and Cat, please step up.
Thank you, sir.
Hi, guys. Tell us
about your cryptid design today.
We chose the Chupacabra.
It's like a reptile,
emaciated dog-type creature.
I sculpted the face.
Cat sculpted the chest.
And I detailed the rest
of everything out.
Things have gone off the tracks
in terms of anatomy for you.
Yeah.
The head is so big
compared to the rib cage.
That puts it in a really bad
place for me this week, guys.
- Okay.
- A bigger issue, though,
is the structure
in the face sculpturally,
especially around his mouth.
That really looks bad.
From an actor's point of view,
when an expression like that
is carved into you,
there's very little
the actor can do.
So you've limited what
his performance can be in this,
but overall, I would pet him.
Daran and Cat,
please step back.
Thanks, buddy.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
Thank you.
All right, judges, so let's
talk about tonight's looks.
Why don't we start
with Tyler and Chloe?
That's probably one
of the best uses of fun fur
we've had on the show.
I mean, they treated it.
They gummed it all up.
The sculpture
was pretty incredible.
The paint job on the tongue
and the interior of the mouth
up into the teeth
is one of the finest paint jobs
we've seen on the show of any
single element, ever, period.
And the fact that it moved--
oh, gosh, that was hilarious.
All right, let's move on
to Rashaad and Graham.
This is a cool exercise
in picking and choosing
what you're going to take
from your direction.
And they pick and chose
everything.
Everything.
This is the paint job
that I love so much.
The profile was amazing.
That crocodile side view
was unbelievable.
All right, let's move on
to Niko and George.
There were some
absolutely gorgeous shapes
coming off of the head.
I love that pinched, curvy line
that came off the side
of his head.
- Yes.
- I thought it was gorgeous.
And the consistency of it,
from all the elements--
arms, head, shoulders,
and that tail.
All right, let's move on
to Matt and Corinne,
and I do want to remind you
that Corinne does have immunity.
Good for her.
My first comment is,
"Is that all there is?"
Because they did
just this face appliance.
They fabricated the wings,
and they could've been
so much better.
It didn't read "Dog" to me.
I don't know if it should have.
They could've done
a beautiful makeup,
and they missed
that opportunity.
All right, let's finish up
with Daran and Cat.
This makeup was profoundly
uninteresting and uncreative.
My problem with this
is that the bone structure
is not straight, and it's
not purposely asymmetrical.
It looks like the skull itself
has a raised eyebrow.
It was like Silly Putty.
As a performer,
when you're given an expression
that you can't
express out of...
- Right.
- ...that's death to an actor.
All right, judges.
Have you made your decision?
- Yeah.
- Yep.
Okay, let's bring 'em back out.
Glenn, tell us
about the top teams.
Tyler and Chloe...
We love that this character
was funny but believable
and amazingly well-balanced
throughout.
Rashaad and Graham...
There were some
tremendously well-done parts
of the head and the cowl,
and the multiple rows of teeth
were super cool.
Okay, which team
came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Okay, which team
came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Tyler and Chloe.
Good job.
We were quite impressed with
how well you brought together
all of the outrageous elements
of your cryptid tonight.
- Great work.
- Thank you.
Tyler and Chloe, great job.
But as you know,
we can only have one winner.
Glenn?
The winner tonight is...
Tyler.
Wow.
Your belly mouth and tongue
were just fantastic.
Thank you.
Second win--
I'm feeling pretty ecstatic.
This is awesome!
Tyler, congratulations.
Thank you.
You, Chloe, Rashaad,
and Graham are safe.
Niko and George,
you are also safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you, guys.
- Thank you.
Unfortunately,
that means the rest of you
are on the bottom this week
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Now, Corinne,
you do have immunity,
so you are safe this week.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room.
The rest of you,
please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom teams.
Matt, the scope
of your creature
simply paled in comparison
to everything else tonight.
Daran and Cat, there were
many divergent design aspects
in terms of the anatomy,
and the paint job
was inconsistent throughout.
So who's going home tonight?
The person
going home tonight is...
Matt.
You knew that Corinne
had immunity,
so you had to step up
and include some signature
element in this makeup.
Unfortunately,
that didn't happen.
That means, Daran and Cat,
you both are safe this week.
Please head back
to the makeup room.
Matt, I really love
how you think,
and I'm hoping we get a chance
to see your creativity
- out there in the real world.
- Thank you.
Matt, I am so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
It's really been great
having you here with us,
but if you would please
head back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- Good luck.
Good luck, Matt.
This sucks,
because it was a makeup
that I knew
I could've done better on.
Oh, man.
My mistake was not standing up
for some of the things I thought
should've been in my makeup.
I came here to learn and grow,
and I did that,
and I'm gonna take this momentum
and make some crazy creatures
when I get out of here.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net