Fantastic job.
He's amazing.
I'm not really a big fan.
Previously on Face Off...
Rashaad's robot earned him
his first win...
Thank you.
...and Daran was sent home.
Now only four artists remain,
and tonight their challenge
will be legendary.
The most famous movie monster
of all time...
How cool is that, man?
But with the finale looming,
a single mistake can cost
one artist everything.
What the fuck, man?
I don't think that
I can use this piece.
It's very serious.
All of a sudden, I realize
I made a big mistake.
Fucking shit, George.
They looked awful.
It looks beautiful.
It's fantastic.
It really doesn't look
like the top half
goes with the bottom half.
It could be responsible
for sending you home.
In the end, only one will win
a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Face Off!
Welcome toFace Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
All right, Mr. Winner,
- finally.
- Yeah.
- Took a while.
- Catching up to me.
But on a sadder note,
we did lose Daran.
I know. Daran--
Daran's awesome.
To see Daran knocked
out of the competition is crazy.
Now that there's only four
of us left,
every challenge
is getting more real,
and you can't slip,
and you can't make any mistakes.
- How do you guys feel?
- Good.
Wondering what today's
gonna be.
Pretty much our last challenge
and then the big one.
To be this close to the finale
is, like, a dream come true.
Final four, let's see
what we got for today.
- Let's see.
- All right.
- Let's see. Let's see.
- Let's go.
Let's see.
- What in the world?
- Nice.
I don't know, guys.
We're walking up
to this mausoleum,
and it's a beautiful building,
lots of cool patterns going on.
- I like the colors.
- Yeah.
We're all just trying to think
of what our next challenge
could be.
Whoa.
It's kind of creepy.
Yeah.
There's dead people
in here, you know.
We don't want to start messing
around with any spirits here.
So let's all behave.
Let's behave.
Oh, my God.
I see McKenzie with somebody.
It's frickin'
Patrick Tatopoulos.
What is this?
And where the hell are we?
'Cause this place
creeps me out.
Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- Hello.
Welcome
to the Angeles Abbey Mausoleum.
This beautiful building
was inspired
by the iconic Taj Mahal.
Now, we've come to this house
of the dead
to talk about your
next spotlight challenge.
Before I tell you more,
please welcome back
our very own Patrick Tatopoulos.
- Hey, Patrick.
- Good to be back, guys.
Good to see you.
Now, I know
you've been busy at work
on the new
Superman-Batman project.
So thank you for taking
the time to be here today.
I wouldn't miss it
for anything.
Now, your next challenge
taps into what many consider
the most famous movie monster
of all time.
Vampires.
We're all like, "Yes."
You know, finally, vampires--
we get to do something
that we've wanted to do.
And I think across the board,
everybody wanted
to do a vampire.
Awesome.
Of course, you know
it can never be that simple.
You'll each need something
before we can go any further.
Down this hall
are four coffins.
Ooh.
When I call your name,
I want you to head down there,
open one,
and take what you find inside.
George...
you're up first.
Good luck.
Oh, my God.
I have to go through
this hallway
that's got dead people
in the walls.
There's four coffins.
And I see this
very old, rusty one.
There's a stake with
a name on it.
Whoa.
On your stakes
is the name
of a legendary vampire
from a different part
of the world.
Nice.
But these vampires
are not the type
we're used to seeing today.
Instead, each has
a very specific characteristic.
Like green fungus-covered skin
and fingers that drain the blood
of their victims.
Your spotlight challenge
is to create
a vampire inspired
by the blood-sucking legends
that you've chosen.
Ooh.
But...
your final creations
must introduce
a new extreme ability
not typically associated
with vampires.
Now, Patrick, you created
some pretty extreme vampires
for the Underworld franchise
that stood out
from the typical Dracula look.
How can these artists create
something unique?
Pay attention to their
culture, their backstories,
and I think you'll find
something very interesting
and original, in that case.
Thank you, Patrick.
I believe you have
a surprise for everyone.
My great friend Len Wiseman,
writer and director
of Underworld
and Underworld Evolution
will be at the reveal stage
this week to look
at your vampires.
- Nice.
- Awesome.
How cool is that, man?
Len Wiseman--
I'm a big fan.
I can't wait to present him
my work.
We're gonna leave you here
to start working
on your designs.
When you're finished,
head back to the lab
and get to work.
Bye, guys.
Good luck in here.
Thank you.
We immediately grab
our tablets,
looking up the characteristics
of our vampires.
I have Sasabonsam, which is
a vampire legend from Ghana.
It says that he lives
in the forest.
It's known to have horns,
iron teeth,
and it's bat-like
with 20-foot wings.
Whoa.
20-foot wings in three days?
Yeah, don't think so.
But it also says he has
these short, stubby arms.
So I'm thinking I could make
short, stubby arms
and use the model's arms
as the wings
and just add a second set
of fangs as my extreme ability.
So, if this thing were to wrap
around a person,
it can kind of get them
also right here.
My character, Yara-Ma-Yha-Who,
is a vampire creature
from the Aboriginals
of Australia.
And he has no teeth.
His teeth to suck blood
are in the ends of the fingers.
And it has a very large head
and a big mouth,
red skin and lots of hair.
And then his extreme ability
is gonna be stingers
that come out from the back
to grab the victim.
I got Jiang Shi,
which is a Chinese version
of the vampire.
It's actually
more like a reanimated zombie.
This fungus plant has taken
over his body,
and vines shoot out
from his palms
to grab his victims.
But instead of sucking blood,
he absorbs the person's chi,
or life force,
through his chest.
His extreme ability is gonna be
a Venus flytrap mouth
on his chest.
That's where the chi enters
his body.
Aswang is a vampire
from the Philippine folklore
that can change itself
into different shapes.
In the day,
she's a beautiful woman.
And in the night,
she becomes this vampire
with a giant tongue
for sucking blood.
But I'm having a lot of trouble
coming up with an extreme
ability to incorporate.
Hopefully, I can figure
something out.
All right, guys,
let's head back to the lab.
Back.
We get back to the lab,
and we have six hours
to work on our vampires.
The first thing I have
to figure out is the face.
Australian folklore says
that Yara-Ma-Yha-Who
has a very big mouth
without teeth
and that,
after he sucks the blood
through his fingers,
he swallows his victims whole.
So I'm definitely gonna go
with a gigantic jaw.
That's cool.
My face sculpture is coming
along really good.
But I still don't know
what to do
for the extreme ability
of my vampire.
As soon as I think of that,
I'm gonna incorporate it
into my design.
Right now I just want to focus
on having a really good piece.
I really want to get my face
done by the end of the day,
so I can be running foam.
Then I can just finish
doing my cowl,
do all the last-minute details
tomorrow.
- Hello, gentlemen.
- Hello.
- We're here for a walk-through.
- Hey, how are you?
Hi.
My vampire is Aswang.
He's from the Philippines.
And he has a big tongue.
The tongue is gonna be
on the chin.
Are you making
a second piece that's gonna--
Yes, I'm gonna make
a second piece.
Okay.
This is all gonna be
inside of the mouth,
and the tongue is just gonna
be right here.
I think it's a good idea.
What are you gonna do
for your extreme?
What are you gonna add
to this that isn't
in your description?
Um, well, I was thinking that
maybe he can survive underwater
or something like that.
Those are words.
I mean something that maybe
is visual.
At this point, I'm confused
about what extreme ability
to incorporate.
You're supposed to add
an element to it
that isn't in the description
that adds to your vampire.
I don't know what to do,
and I'm really worried,
because if I don't have
this extreme ability,
I'm not gonna make it
to the finale.
Coming up...
All of the sudden, I realize
I made a big mistake.
What the fuck?
I don't think
that I can use this piece.
He just looks so menacing.
It could be responsible
for sending you home.
You're supposed to add
an element to it
that isn't in the description
that adds to your vampire.
It is day one
of the vampire challenge,
and Mr. Westmore tells me
that my concept needs to have
this extreme ability.
I still don't know
how I'm gonna figure it out.
But I need to do it fast,
because it has to be part
of my design.
- Good luck.
- Okay.
- And you think of that.
- All right.
- Good luck, Niko.
- Thank you.
I got the Jiang Shi--
vampire from China.
He's more like a zombie.
When he died,
the plants around him
grew into him
and made him alive.
In your drawing,
you're seeing a lot of neck.
Are you gonna have
a lot of neck showing?
Oh, yeah.
So you can take your sculpture,
and you come all the way
out here like that.
- Hmm.
- You cover all this up.
And you've got
so much wrinkling going on.
I would say just take
and stretch
- and stipple the mouth...
- Mm-hmm.
...and pull those eyelids
and stretch and stipple those.
Otherwise, you're still
gonna have
a young person
underneath there.
Unless you have thought
of that already.
No, I didn't even think
of that, but thank you.
I got Yara-Ma-Yha-Who.
He's a vampire from
the Aboriginals from Australia.
He sucks the blood
with his finger.
He has a very big head,
and he's all red, like a demon.
The skin tone needs
to be mottled red,
not just one tone.
It means you're gonna have
to get in there
- with the airbrush...
- Airbrush.
...maybe even do
some spattering.
- Oh, yeah, that's cool.
- You know, if you have time.
For sure.
I'll experiment with that.
- Good luck.
- Awesome.
- Thank you so much.
- Good luck.
Thank you, McKenzie.
Okay, remind us what
you've got on your stake.
Sasabonsam.
- Where is it from?
- Africa.
The wings are, like, 20 feet
long in their description.
And I'm like, "Oh, boy."
And they have little mini arms.
Okay, now, what are you adding
as the extreme ability?
The fangs
at the tip of the wings.
Someone comes--
chh!
And that's
what sucks the blood?
Yeah.
So how are you going to melt
that into this?
I love doing a lot of things
with textures and wrinkles.
And I want this to have
a leathery-skin feel.
So I'm thinking
of a dark skin tone
with definitely
a lot of speckling
- of other colors.
- Mm-hmm.
You got to be careful
with that,
because you're gonna lose
all your detail.
- Okay.
- You can make it tan.
But if you go too dark,
you can't go back...
- Okay.
- ...because you're not gonna see
all this wonderful sculpting
that you've done.
All right, gentlemen,
we are heading out.
- But it's looking really good.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Almost ready to mold this puppy.
My goal for today is to finish
this face piece,
because I have to mold it,
but I have to also make
a snap mold of the sculpture
on this area.
Niko.
Here comes Niko.
Finally.
- Two hours, I think--
- Yeah, two hours.
So a snap mold is a replica
of a specific area
that you want to sculpt.
So I can have just
a separate piece of the lip.
So, as soon as it's done,
I take it
and pour some plaster on it.
After it's ready,
I take it out.
And now I have a replica
of the mouth piece.
I think it will work.
♪ bum, bum, bum, bu-- ♪
Nice.
- Good job, buddy,
- Thank you.
Now that I have my face
molded, ready for foam,
I start blocking out my chest.
The Chinese legend states
that Jiang Shi
has fungus all over his body
and doesn't drink blood.
He absorbs the person's chi.
So I decided to incorporate
a Venus flytrap mouth
on his chest
for his extreme ability.
It has big teeth and can open
really wide to engulf the chi.
- Rashaad, what time?
- You got 19 minutes.
What's going on, man?
That's time, guys.
Let's go.
So, at the end of day one,
I got my face molded
and ready for foam.
Tomorrow I have to do the cowl
and the extreme ability,
which are
the vampire's stingers,
bone protrusions that grab
the victims.
I also have to make
the fingers,
which I don't know yet
how I'm gonna do.
Ow!
It's a lot to do.
And the stakes
are humongously high.
Whoosh!
So it's day two
for our vampire challenge.
- We have 9 1/2 hours today.
- Back to work.
The first thing I do
is go to the mold room
and start opening my face mold.
It actually opened really fast.
So I started cleaning
out the clay
to get it ready for foam.
This challenge is pushing us
out of our comfort zones
because our vampires
have specific traits
from different parts
of the world.
Plus, we have to create
some kind of extreme ability
for these vampires.
And it's very interesting to me
how we interpret this stuff.
I still have to sculpt
the tongue.
I want it to look perfect
because it's the main feature
of my vampire.
It doesn't look that bad.
Yeah, that looks cool.
Make it more pointy.
- More pointy?
- Yeah.
I want it to look as creepy
and realistic as possible.
We're almost down
to the finale,
and I want to make sure
that I can go to that finale.
Nice.
I'm making it a little bit
more pointy.
I really got to finish
sculpting
my vampire's upper-body suit,
because it's gonna be
a very big mold.
The stress is extreme.
I have a lot
of detail to cover.
Most importantly, I still have
to make these huge wings.
They're not only essential
to the Sasabonsam legend,
the extreme ability
is a second set of fangs
on the wings.
So I need to mold this
as fast as I can.
Sweet, dude.
What do you think of mine?
It looks, like, puppy--
Tell me the truth, please.
Ooh, I love that.
- I'm so getting bat out of it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- That's cool.
- Thanks.
So I'm busy working on my cowl,
when I finally notice
my face prosthetic.
What the fuck?
Damn.
My face has, like,
a huge tear in it.
Come on.
Look at that.
It has a tear in the corner
of the mouth.
Two huge tears in it.
And a tear by the eye.
_
I'm frustrated.
My paint job is gonna be
what sells it.
Now there's less time to paint.
So I need to figure out
what I'm gonna do and quickly.
Two huge tears in it.
It's day two
of our vampire challenge.
And my foam has a tear
in the corner of the mouth
and also a tear by the eye,
going towards the nose.
Can you fix that, Rashaad?
I'm gonna run it again,
but I'm gonna keep that one.
- I'm just mad it came out ripped.
- Yeah, I know.
I'm running my face again.
But just in case
it doesn't come out better,
I'm gonna patch this one.
So a lot of work.
But it means everything
to get to the finale.
Everything has to be perfect.
My Aswang is a vampire
that is from
the Philippine folklore.
And I decided to place two claws
on the tip of the ears,
maybe to make it
a little bit more original.
And I also decided to use
the claws
as a type of horns or hair.
And then it just goes
all the way down to the spine.
- It's cool, man.
- Really?
Yeah.
It's a good start.
I finally came up
with an extreme ability--
a tail that has fangs.
That's the way my vampire,
Aswang, feeds off his victims.
I hope I can impress
our guest judge, Len Wiseman.
My vampire's mold has probably
well over 200 pounds of clay,
and that weighs more than I do.
So, at this point,
the mold is so big,
it's taking too long.
Unfortunately,
I just don't think
I'm gonna have time to do
these big wings.
And that kind of sucks,
because that's a big part
of my design.
Hey, Niko,
what do you think of this?
My vampire sucks the blood
of his victims
through the fingers.
So I find these foam tubes.
They're hollow.
So I can fit the finger inside.
- It will be like a tentacle.
- And you don't have to...
Sculpt the whole thing.
I'm gonna shape them out.
And I'm putting some tissue
and latex on them,
so it looks kind
of textured and organic.
My cowl is molded.
My chest is molded.
And I mold this hand piece,
which looks like a little mouth
where vines shoot out
from the vampire's palm
to grab his victim,
so their chi can be absorbed.
And I think it's looking good.
I don't know what to do,
because
the 20-foot wingspan
is the most distinctive
characteristic
in the Sasabonsam legend.
It has to be part of my makeup.
So I find these spandex gloves,
and I put them
on mannequin arms.
I'm thinking, "All right,
what if I create the illusion
that this thing has big wings
that are just all folded up?"
All right, everybody,
that's time. Brushes down.
Unfortunately, I have
no choice-- I have to go with it.
I'm still bummed that
I can't complete these wings
exactly how I wanted them.
But I just really got to focus
on detailing tomorrow
because it's gonna be
a very big application day.
Another day.
We're feeling it at this point.
We're all exhausted.
I think we all pushed ourselves.
- Come on, Georgie.
- Coming.
All of our designs
are so strong.
And most importantly,
they're all different.
- What a day, man.
- What a day.
We're doing things
that usually take a team
of people to do.
And I really want to make it
to the end.
It's just that, mentally,
it's very, very exhausting.
Oh, my God, I was, like,
running around all the time.
I have a lot of pieces
to apply tomorrow.
The face, did the cowl,
did the tongue.
There's some pressure,
because this is it.
With this, the judges
decide if you're gonna be
on the finals or not.
And you, you did that big mold.
I can't wait to put it
together tomorrow.
Oh, yeah.
That's the best part.
You got all of these
little pieces.
And you're just excited
to see what they look like
all together,
then you're like, "Oh, crap."
Yeah.
The four of us--
we become brothers here, man.
Knowing that tomorrow
we're losing one of us,
it hurts a lot.
- Let's see what we got.
- Let's do this.
It's application day.
We got four hours in the lab
and one hour in last looks.
- Tyler, it didn't rip this time.
- Yay.
My new vampire face
is amazing-- no splits.
It's the right thickness.
It just looks great.
Nice.
But I start to get worried
because there's so many pieces.
I just hope I have the time
to apply it all.
How are you?
The teeth are gonna be
in the fingers.
So these things go
on your fingers.
You're gonna have
a couple appliances.
This is, like, the face piece.
And it's gonna have
this big tongue.
We have a lot
of work ahead of us.
Yes.
So the models arrive.
And the first thing that I start
applying is the tongue.
I put a strap with a velcro
and put the cowl
on top of that.
So it can all hold it together.
There you go.
So, immediately, I have to get
this creature suit
off this mannequin
and apply it to my model.
I start putting the pieces on.
And it's coming together
really, really well.
So, finally,
I get all my pieces applied.
But I got to make sure that
I have time to paint everything,
because I basically have to do
a whole-body paint.
Turn around.
I'm using different
techniques of modeling,
speckling--
blue, some purple--
to do the whole body.
That was easy enough.
I put the cowl on and the face,
and they're looking great.
I'm loving it.
I'm painting the whole body red.
And all of the sudden,
I realize...
I made a big mistake.
Fucking shit, George.
The finger extensions--
one side is very thin.
It can blend to the skin.
But I put the nails on
the wrong side.
So now I have these
huge, thick edges right here,
where it's supposed
to blend to the skin.
And it's like, "Oh, my God.
They look stupid."
It's too late to change
anything right now.
So I have to use them like this.
We got 20 minutes, guys.
We got 20 minutes left.
All right, guys, it's time.
Brushes down.
I'm looking around.
Everyone's look so different.
And, like, I just feel
so behind
because I have to finish
painting
this massive, huge
creature suit.
And some people just have
a face piece and a chest piece.
I honestly bit off a lot
to push me into the finale.
I just hope I can finish
this makeup.
Coming up...
Ah, it doesn't matter.
Fuck it.
They look awful.
I don't know if I'm gonna
have time
to finish everything.
You gave us something
that we've never seen before.
- Thank God.
- It looks beautiful.
You've done some really
great things thus far.
But this is not one of them.
Good luck, guys.
We get to last looks,
and we have one hour left.
I still need to finish
painting the tail.
And I still need to work
on the inside of the mouth.
I don't know if I'm gonna
have time to do everything.
_
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
I love it.
I still have to work on
the hands,
get the vines in there,
get the moss on him.
Still a lot of work to do,
but I'm feeling very confident
I'm gonna get it done.
Leave that like that.
This one goes here.
All right?
Ah, it doesn't matter.
Fuck it.
I'm putting the fingers on,
and they look awful.
So I'm hoping that I can cover
the seams with hair.
Maybe the judges won't notice.
Now let's paint the horns.
_
All I want to focus on
is last-minute details,
folding the wings up
and positioning my model,
so she can give me
that crouched, birdlike feel.
Like, neck up, like--
Exactly.
I'm worried.
The time is going
really, really fast.
So I decide to scrap the wings
so I can concentrate
on the mouth and giant tongue.
All right, everybody,
we got ten minutes.
You can do this.
That's time!
What a run.
One of us is not gonna make it
to the finale.
So, at this point,
it could be anyone.
Welcome
to theFace Offreveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
First, say hello
to our talented judges--
owner of Optic Nerve Make-Up
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick...
- Good evening, guys.
- Hey, Glenn.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill...
- Hello, chaps.
- Hi, Ve.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page...
- Hi, guys.
- Hi, Neville.
And joining our panel tonight
is a highly acclaimed writer,
producer, and director,
whose work includes
the Bruce Willis action flick
Live Free Or Die Hard
and, of course,
the epic film franchise
he helped create--
Underworld.
Please welcome Len Wiseman.
Hey, guys.
I'm really looking forward to
seeing what you guys have done.
- Cool.
- Awesome.
Underworldis one
of my favorite vampire movies
of all time.
So, if I can impress this guy,
that's another personal
achievement for me.
All right, guys, so this week
your spotlight challenge
was to select a storied vampire,
each from a different part
of the world,
and use it as inspiration
for your very own
vampiric creations.
So let's take a look
at your bloodsuckers
while the audience at home
tweets about their favorites,
using #FaceOff.
It looks really creepy
with that big tongue.
I think it's pretty cool.
I'm worried.
Those fingers look clunky,
like a cheap costume.
And they take away from
the presence of the sculpture.
This is one
of my best makeup jobs.
He emotes really well
through it.
I'm just excited.
She looks like
some crazy vampire demon,
and I really like
how the makeup looks.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look at our vampires?
Wow. This is just,
like, fabricated--
- Looks like he's got a goiter.
- It's broken up right there.
Yeah.
Can you breathe okay?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, oh.
There you are.
I wish that the placement
of the implied jaw
felt correct.
I couldn't agree with you more.
Can we see you from the side?
The head shape's not awful.
- I like these things here.
- Yes.
Turn around
a little bit more-- right there.
Like, if they continued down
- a little bit more into here...
- Yeah.
So it's not just
the back of his head.
Oh, boy.
I'd like to see you emote.
Push your forehead.
Wrinkle it.
Open your eyes and mouth
as wide as they go.
- That's interesting.
- It is.
I actually think
this is a good touch here,
putting a little bit
of hair on there.
- Hmm.
- Really?
Oh, my God, those fingers.
That looks like
a bad, bad choice.
I may be screwed on this one,
just because
of those awful fingers.
Who made your favorite vampire?
Tell us on Twitter,
using #FaceOff.
Yeah, these hands-- that looks
like a bad, bad choice.
I may be screwed on this one,
just because of the fingers.
I bet this was
the last-minute thing here.
The only choice is to just
leave those on the table.
Just take it off.
I'm hoping the judges consider
the good sculpture,
and they will ignore
the fingers.
Thank you.
The paint's even better
up close than it is far away.
Oh, that's cool when you open
your eyes really wide.
That's a good-looking face.
That hair is hiding a lot
of what's actually there.
Thanks.
There's something about this
that looks so flat,
in terms of the paint job.
If he was on set, I would squirt
him down with a hose.
I really like this thing,
the way that comes out.
And then we have this internal
piece of the nose exposed.
- Can you turn around?
- Yeah, turn around for us.
- Oh, my God, he did so much.
- That's a lot.
- That's a big mold too.
- Boy, oh, boy.
Nicely painted on the face,
I think.
Yeah, the paint job
on the face is great.
Thank you.
So, Len, did they
successfully reenvision
the classic vampire?
There was a lot
of very imaginative choices
that I wouldn't have expected.
So I'm very interested to see
some of the reasons
behind the choices
and what that character means
to you guys as well.
Okay.
The judges would now like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Niko, please step up.
Tell us about the concept
behind your vampire
and what unique ability
you included.
My vampire is originally
from the Philippines.
I wanted to incorporate
the big tongue with poison.
So, if he licks you,
he hurts you.
And then he sucks
the blood from the tail.
I think there's
so many design opportunities
that you simply missed.
It would've been
more vampy to me
if the teeth protruded
from the upper jaw,
making it a little more scary
and intimidating.
Man, is that nasty.
I do appreciate the fact
that you took the chance
on making that big,
giant tongue.
You gave us something
that we've really never
seen before. Thank God.
I still don't get the tail,
because that is not
a special ability, really.
It's just an added appendage.
I don't think I can address
any other choice
that you made
beyond the tongue.
My concern is the way
you've sculpted it.
It's just this flaccid tongue.
So it doesn't look menacing
or scary.
It's a very, very loose sketch
of a good idea.
Okay.
Yeah.
The vampire quality
in being a vampire theme
wasn't immediate.
I think it looks like
an evil clown.
The red, the tongue
has a little bit
of a comedic element to it.
But I will say that the story
behind the design of it
I do really like.
- Thank you.
- Niko, please step back.
Thank you, guys.
Rashaad, please step forward.
Tell us about your vampire
and what extra-special ability
this guy has.
I got the Jiang Shi.
It's a Chinese version
of the vampire.
When he died,
his blood went into the ground
to make this vampiric plant
that grew onto him
and brought him back to life.
He has these vines
that come out
of his palms to grab
his victims.
I really like this guy.
I love the paint job on him.
He just looks
so menacing and creepy.
I do wish, however,
you would've, like,
kind of ratted up
his hair a little bit.
But I think you did
a really nice job.
He's really cool-looking.
Thank you.
The face is so well crafted.
And your actor is able
to emote through it,
which is great.
Hate the palms.
The way you executed that
is counter to how
you executed the face.
If this character was
to step on set,
I'd say the makeup's done.
The face is really scary.
- And the color design is great.
- Thank you.
I think this is incredibly
visually articulate,
in that it conveys not only what
the character's supposed to be,
but also
the cultural reference.
I do wish that we could see
the ears a bit more.
It's the most vampy aspect
of the whole thing.
Look at that.
I mean, that's a huge
improvement right there.
You also managed to make sure
that your paint job
is accentuating your sculpture.
And you leave a lot
of light surfaces
for us to just see
the highlight and the form.
And then where
you do put color,
you didn't go overboard
with it.
- Thank you.
- Rashaad, step back.
Thanks.
Great job, brother.
Thank you.
Tyler, please step
to the center.
Tell us about your concept
and the unique ability.
Well, this is
the Sasabonsam of Ghana.
I made the short, little arms
and used her natural arms
as the wings.
His special ability is fangs
on the end of his wings,
and that's what he uses
to grab his victims in.
My biggest bone of contention
is how you're sculpting
the anatomy.
From basically the necklace
down to the waist,
it's just so active and busy
with folds of skin
and shapes
that don't make much sense.
It's really visually muddy.
It feels like a costume
that is three sizes too big
for the subject.
The head, there's something
about the horns.
Because they are sculpted
into it,
it reads almost as a hairdo
rather than horns.
Okay.
Thank you.
My main focus is
the proportion.
It doesn't look like
the top half of this body
goes with
the bottom half at all.
You put all of your time
and effort
in the paint job into his face.
That was really well done.
Unfortunately, you didn't have
quite enough time
to do that to the entire body.
So he looks like
a big, brown tree trunk.
You definitely did
a massive amount of work.
I get that.
The sculpt has to be rough.
That's necessitated by
the amount of time that you had,
but you could've saved it
with paint.
You've done some really
great things thus far.
This is definitely
not one of them.
It could be responsible
for sending you home.
Tyler, thank you.
You can head back.
Thank you.
George, you're up next.
Hey, buddy.
- Hello, George.
- Hi.
Tell us the story
behind your character.
The name of the vampire is
Yara-Ma-Yha-Who.
He's originally from Australia.
He feeds through these guys.
He stabs the victim and sucks
the blood through the holes.
From a director's perspective,
it has a menacing presence.
The face looks real.
It looks like a creature.
It doesn't look like a man
with prosthetics on.
Really, really great job.
Thank you.
I think the head
is absolutely gorgeous,
but you've surrounded it
with a buffet
of bad decisions, man.
Like, you couldn't take
a prettier sculpture
and then make more piss-poor
choices to present it with.
I think this guy is terrific,
but the fingers...
- Yeah, I know.
- They really do suck.
I want to see what this thing
looks like without that sash.
Look how bitchin'
this thing is!
Oh, dude, take the fingers off.
Hurry up. Hurry.
Let's do it.
This is so beautiful.
Why cover it up?
Put that in the trash.
I will, absolutely.
It looks beautiful.
It's fantastic.
You create elegant lines
within something
that is beastly.
This is a very beautiful
character.
Thank you.
Thank you, Neville.
George, please step back.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you would please head
back to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
- Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
All right, judges, let's talk
about tonight's looks.
Why don't we start
with Rashaad?
It's so well crafted,
both from
a sculptural standpoint
and, I think, also
from a paint standpoint.
There's so much work
and detail.
It does have
that Asian influence,
and you recognize that.
I especially love the way
the neck flowed from the ears.
I love the charcoal
around the eyes
and all the little bits
around the nose.
In that paint job,
there's so many great details.
And to do it that fast
is quite astounding.
All right,
let's move on to George.
I loved how regal
this thing was,
keeping everything sucked in.
And then just making the face
as majestic as he did
it was very, very intelligent.
The color palette
is so different,
but it reads as a vampire,
and it looks real.
I think he was concerned
about getting the suckers
on the fingers
because this particular vampire
does not have fangs.
I still think he could've done
it in a much smaller way.
He didn't need to use
those big fingers.
All right, judges,
let's move on to Niko.
The tongue's very distracting.
It makes it comedic.
It looked like he got punched
in the face,
and his tongue
just sort of fell out.
I do think it was an extremely
appropriate color decision.
But this paint job
was really sloppy.
Yeah, it was just
a spattery mess.
Okay, let's move on to Tyler.
Wow. I don't know
what the heck
he was thinking
about this week.
That thing is dreadful.
It looked like a tree trunk
stuck on top
of a little person's body.
It got so complex
in the midsection.
His torso looked like
it was spray-painted brown.
It looked flat.
I wish the detail on the back
existed in the front.
You go to the back,
and he knows what he's doing.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
Yes, we have.
Let's bring them back out.
Glenn, tell us
about the top looks.
Rashaad,
we loved the sculpting
and the movement of the face.
And your color choices
and paint
did a great job
showcasing that.
George, there were some
brilliant sculptural decisions
in your character's face
and head.
That made
for a very convincing character.
So, Glenn, who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
So, Glenn, who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
Rashaad.
You did a great job
melding disparate elements,
from hallmark
vampire characteristics
to traditional zombie ideas.
Well done, man.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Second win,
and I'm just stoked.
I'm shocked.
I can't stop smiling.
I'm just very excited.
Finally, they're recognizing
my talents.
- Rashaad, congratulations.
- Thank you.
Now this is where
I would normally send you
and George back
to the makeup room.
But I can't do that tonight.
I'm completely bewildered
at this point.
Like, "Oh, my God.
Am I going home?"
We're about to do something
that we have never done before.
This is actually
a two-part challenge.
And the second half starts
right now.
Okay.
This means no one
is going home tonight.
Oh, my gosh!
Second chance!
Holy cow!
Now I'm really excited
that I have one more chance
to prove myself.
So I just want to know
what the other part
of the challenge is.
Next week the judges
will be putting
three of you through
to the finale
based on both characters
that you have created
for this two-part challenge.
This is very nerve-racking.
Even though I did well
in the vampire,
the next creature
we're gonna make
could send me home.
I have a van waiting outside
to take you
to meet a special guest
and find out what's next.
I don't know what we have
in store,
but I want to make sure
that I do everything I have to
to make it to the finale.
There's no point
in going home now.
Thank you, guys.
See you.
Bye.
What's happening?
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net