Face Off is back
and more extreme than ever.
This season the artists
will face bold new challenges.
This will be a season
of extremes.
How can it get
any more bold and extreme
than it has been?
I have another surprise
for you.
And their quest to become
the next great name
in movie magic will take them
to the far reaches
of the globe.
I'm taking you all to Japan.
What?
Are you kidding me?
In this
no-holds-barred season,
artists will bare their souls
and push themselves
to the breaking point.
I have really messed up.
Coached by makeup effects
legend Michael Westmore,
they'll work
through creative obstacles
and impossible deadlines.
- Oh, my God.
- But ultimately,
their fate will rest
with our award-winning panel
of judges.
In the end, only one will win
a VIP trip from Kryolan
Professional Makeup
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Face Off!
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
My name is George.
I'm from Puerto Rico
originally,
and I have my own company.
I'm gonna be a father.
So, if I win Face Off,
that money's gonna be for her.
- Hi.
- Hey.
My name is Chloe.
I enjoy doing fantasy work.
Being a woman
in special effects makeup,
I really have to prove myself
every time.
- Hey, how are you?
- Hey!
My name is Tyler Green,
and I just quit my job
as a dental lab technician.
So I'm taking a huge risk,
and I'm gonna really push myself
to make it to the end.
- Wow.
- As soon as I walk in,
I see this huge runway,
and I'm thinking,
"Here we go."
This is crazy.
I'm Rashaad.
Right now I can only work
on special effects part-time
because I'm trying to support
my fiancee and my son
by working
at a fast-food restaurant.
So winning Face Off would
definitely change our lives.
Dan Phillips.
I'm from Detroit, Michigan,
and I own
a special makeup effects
studio.
And I've been very fortunate
to work
on some really good projects.
Hopefully, being a little
older and experienced
will really help
in this competition.
- Hey, how you doing?
- Hi.
- I'm Dan.
- Hi, Dan. I'm Cat.
My dad was very disappointed
when I told him
that I didn't want to go
to law school
and was even more disappointed
when I said,
"Hey, I'm gonna go
to makeup school instead."
Winning Face Off
would definitely show him
that this is
a legitimate career for me.
My name's Matt.
I've been working in special
makeup effects professionally
since I was 18 years old.
I feel like my drive
and my passion
is gonna give me an edge.
- How's it going? Matt.
- Bethany.
I went to school
for video game design,
and halfway through,
I switched to special effects.
So now, instead of sculpting
on a computer,
I'm sculpting in real life.
- Bethany.
- Tanner. Nice to meet you.
I work for a company that
contracts for the military.
We make suits to simulate trauma
in the battlefield.
Hey, guys.
- I'm Cat.
- Hi, Cat. I'm Tess.
In Denver, there's not a lot
of opportunities
in special effects,
so I make molds
of mannequin sculptures,
and create the perfect casting
so that they can reproduce it
over and over.
Whoa.
What's happening?
- Hey, guys.
- Oh, my gosh.
Whoo!
Welcome to Face Off.
- Whoo!
Oh, God.
I'm actually doing this.
This is going to be
a season of extremes.
Now, in addition
to some huge surprises
that we have in store for you,
the judges will also be looking
for bolder and more extreme
makeups than ever before.
My heart drops,
and I'm like, ugh.
How can it get any more bold
an extreme
than it has been?
So take a look at this.
Oh, boy.
- Oh, shit.
- Oh.
Wow.
All of these models walk out
wearing these huge, weird wigs.
My heart is in my throat.
It's very exciting.
All right, for your first
foundation challenge,
you're going to choose
one of these over-the-top wigs
and create an extreme character
that represents you
as an artist.
The winner
will receive immunity
and cannot be eliminated
this week.
Immunity in this first
challenge is very important.
Nobody wants to go home first.
All right, I brought
a special guest
who knows all about creating
incredible characters.
She's an Academy award-winning
makeup artist
for her work
in The Chronicles Of Narnia,
The Lion, The Witch,
And The Wardrobe,
and was nominated again
for The Hobbit,
An Unexpected Journey.
Please welcome Tami Lane.
Wow.
I'm freaking out immediately
because I'm a fan
of The Hobbit.
She did an amazing job.
Thank you so much
for being here.
Well, thank you very much
for inviting me.
What advice can you give
these guys
about today's challenge?
In order to create
a cohesive character,
you have to have good makeup
as well as good hair.
They both work together.
You will destroy a character
if the makeup is bad
and the hair is great
or vice-versa.
So I'm looking forward to seeing
how you bring your wigs
into your makeup.
Okay.
Models, if you'd please
head down.
All right, now, on my go,
I want you each to select
a model.
Grab some wardrobe and create
your extreme characters.
You have two hours,
and your time starts...
now!
- You're with me.
- Okay.
- What's your name?
- Tyler. Nice to meet you.
I'm Niko.
I'm from Puerto Rico.
I live with my girlfriend, Cat.
She's also competing.
If either of us win,
it's gonna be great
for the both of us.
_
My name is Margaret.
I've been doing special effects
for nine years.
I'm trying to grow a business
out of it in the Bay area.
If you look at my wig,
it's a very haunted
earth goddess.
I am starting my prosthetic,
and I have an idea
for what I want to do
for the colors.
I want it, like,
sort of fashion on this side,
kind of creepy on this side.
I'm Graham.
I'm a freelance
makeup artist/instructor.
My concept is this model
tried to transform herself
by drilling holes into her face
to resemble
her circular hairdo.
It should represent me
and the fact that I have style,
I'm creepy and weird.
My name's Corinne.
I'm a co-owner
of Synapse FX,
and we recently headed
special effects
on Sharknado for SyFy.
She's going to be
a forest witch doctor.
I applied this brow
to give her a unique look.
My character is a princess
that lives in a fantasy land.
Three weeks before coming here,
I fractured my hand.
It hurts, but I'll do
whatever it takes to win.
My name is Daran.
I'm originally
from Kansas City.
For most of my life,
I've been a regular joe
doing regular jobs,
9:00 to 5:00,
but my passion was always makeup
and monsters.
Now I make monsters,
and I sell 'em online.
My concept
is a futuristic club girl
who's got purple hair
with lights in it.
I figured that'd be
pretty bold and extreme.
Ten minutes, everybody!
Shit.
_
Time's up, everybody!
Brushes down!
Phew.
- Hi, Bethany.
- Hey.
Tell us
about your makeup today.
This was the fairest lady
of the land.
One of the suitors
attacked her,
and this is the aftermath.
- Wow.
- I tried to keep her
still beautiful, yet grotesque.
You've achieved that,
because it's a beautiful makeup
on that side
and the contrast on this side.
- Thank you.
- Very nice.
I really loved how natural
the wig was,
so I wanted to go
with sorceress.
Good use of some
very subtle speckling.
It's very excellent, simple,
very well applied.
Thank you.
She's a queen,
but she has something
inside her body
that is precious.
They were trying to make
an incision there.
Well, I love
your color choices.
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
And it goes very well
with the costume,
and I like the fact
that you put
the wound on her chest.
- It was very well executed.
- Thank you.
Well, when I seen the wig,
I automatically thought
about a bird.
The top part of the beak is
an old-age throat piece.
- Huh.
- And then the bottom piece
was actually a large brow.
You've done a great job
incorporating the face
with the wig to make
a full creature.
Thank you.
I'm looking around the room
and noticing
that there are
some really strong concepts.
I realize the competition
is going to be intense.
For a two-hour makeup
with a brand-new kit,
I think everybody
did a great job.
All right, Tami,
which of the makeups
were your favorite looks?
Bethany, you combined
the beautiful
as well as the horror
in a very cohesive way,
and, George, I love
the prosthetic on the chest.
You didn't do the typical
bleeding red.
That was thinking
outside the box.
All right, Tami,
who is the winner
of today's challenge?
The winner of today's
challenge is...
Coming up...
There's no way to get
this mold off
without cracking it.
We didn't have a face.
I'm just absolutely devastated.
I love it.
It looks like a big blob
of Silly Putty.
All right, Tami,
who is the winner
of today's challenge?
The winner
of today's challenge is...
George.
You created a bold
and extreme character
with an incredible attention
to detail.
Thank you so much.
- Well, George, congratulations.
- Thank you.
You have won immunity
and cannot be eliminated
in this week's
spotlight challenge.
Yeah. That's a good start.
Yes!
All right, and I will see
you tomorrow
for your first
spotlight challenge.
- Bye, guys.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Oh, my God!
- No!
This is where we're gonna live
for the next ten weeks?
I see a living room,
a ping-pong table,
a pool, a hot tub.
I am blown away
being in this house.
Face off!
All right.
It's the morning of our first
spotlight challenge,
and we're walking
through this huge metal gate,
and we see
this beautiful castle.
It feels
like I'm in a fairy tale.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
Welcome to Castle Knoll.
We're here today
because your spotlight challenge
is based
on a timeless fairy tale,
Beauty And The Beast.
- Yes.
- Yay.
These trumpeters come out,
and these gorgeous princesses
start filing down one by one,
and I am stoked.
These are our belles
from Beauty And The Beast.
Each of them is holding
an amazing castle
which you will use
to inspire your makeups.
So, working together
in teams of two,
your spotlight challenge is
to choose one of the belles
and create the huge beast
that would live
in the castle with her.
Yes.
Your randomly assigned
teams are...
Rashaad and Chloe...
Daran and Graham...
Bethany and Tyler...
Margaret and Matt...
Tanner and Corinne...
Cat and Daniel...
Tess and Niko...
Okay, go stand
beside your new teammates.
And, George, as the winner
of the first
foundation challenge,
you actually get to select
which team you'd like to join.
I think I'm gonna go
with Daran and Graham.
- Excellent.
- Nice.
All right, now, keep in mind,
when choosing your castles,
the judges will be looking
to see how they've inspired
your designs.
All right, Rashaad and Chloe,
you're up first.
- Underwater?
- Yeah.
All right, I've brought in
a special guest
to give you some advice.
He's a writer, producer,
and director
whose films have grossed
over $2 billion worldwide,
including Van Helsing,
GI Joe, and The Mummy films.
Please give a warm welcome
to Stephen Sommers.
I'm excited.
Stephen Sommers has created
some great creatures,
so his advice is
gonna be very helpful.
We are very lucky
to have you joining us
on the reveal stage this week.
What are you gonna be
looking for
in their final designs?
The real trick, I think,
to the beast is
you have to scare us
in the first half
but by the end,
he has to be sexy.
So, when belle kisses him
at the end,
we can't be repulsed.
All right, guys,
we're going to leave you here
to work on your designs.
When you're done,
go check out the lab
and get to work.
- Good luck.
- Good luck, guys.
Bye.
We decided to go
with a whitish look,
like the Marble Palace.
We're taking some
of the structure from the castle
into his horns.
Our inspiration is a little bit
classic monster Creature
From The Black Lagoon.
We're making his face
very fishlike,
giving him gills and this fin
that goes down his back,
but he is also gonna be having
a nice physique.
We have a lot of interesting
shapes here with geometry,
and we're trying to find ways
to incorporate that into
the anatomy of our character.
Since he's alien-like,
we're gonna bump out the jaw
and stuff, make it strong.
We're trying to make sure
that he's defined and sharp.
I'm thinking we go with, like,
- a hardened castle-like back.
- Yeah.
This is all gloomy
and kind of foggy.
We're incorporating
the stone as well.
There's three of us,
so they're gonna expect
a little bit more from us,
I'm sure.
We are working
on a dragon kind of character.
We have these type
of horns in the palace.
We want to add it
in the crown piece.
All right, guys.
Let's go check out the lab.
- All right.
- Whoo!
- Wow.
- This is awesome.
- Oh, my God.
- Holy moly, dude.
This is heaven.
Oh.
I've never worked
in a lab like this before.
We have five hours to work,
and the first thing we do is
we select our model,
and we start sculpting.
I get paired with Cat.
All right, let's do this.
Our castle's very traditional,
and our belle is very regal,
a lot of jewels.
So I really want more
of a traditional, regal beast.
You want me to start
on blocking?
I'm gonna say face.
Corinne and I picked
the ice fort.
We want to make our beast
abominable snowman-ish
with this mane-type hair.
Is that what you were thinking?
Our character has
a face, a torso,
and a cowl,
so I'm constantly checking in
with Chloe,
making sure that we make
one cohesive piece.
- Like this?
- Mm-hmm.
- Kind of?
- I like that a lot.
Focus.
I'm working on the face,
and Matt is working on the cowl.
The face is
really important to me,
and there's some things
that aren't correct--
the symmetry and anatomy.
I'm just gonna work as hard
as I can to correct that.
30 minutes left.
My goal was to get
the face piece sculpted,
molded, and ran in foam
by the end of the day.
As I'm molding my face sculpt
I notice that I'm
the only one in the room,
and no one else
is molding their face.
All right, guys, that's time!
Getting the face piece
molded is really gonna help
Bethany and I get
ahead of the game,
'cause tomorrow we can focus
on the cowl
and the accessories
and the paint scheme
to bring this character
to life.
Let's do this, guys!
Let's do this.
Let's do it.
I like it.
I like it a lot.
It's day two in the lab,
and Rashaad and I
are going to start
tightening up all the pieces,
getting them
ready to be molded.
I will be responsible
for molding the face...
It's game time.
And Rashaad assured me
that he can pull off
the chest piece,
as well as the cowl.
Look what I've got!
I trust he'll get these
out on time.
- Hey, guys.
- Hello. Hi.
We're here
for a first walkthrough.
Hi.
McKenzie and Mr. Westmore
come in,
and it's amazing.
I am a huge
Michael Westmore fan.
We're gonna go with, like,
more of whites and grays
for the hair
to have it within the theme
of being in the snow.
You've got
something very unique,
and that's ice.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
When you put the face together,
take advantage of icicles.
It'll be very effective.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
We chose The Sultan's Palace.
We wanted to keep the face
more humanist a little bit,
but also kind of have
that beast flair to it.
Up close, I can see
all the hard work,
but when you paint this,
make sure you don't lose it...
- Okay.
- ...by doing a wash on it.
By picking The Lunar Tower,
we were able to play
with the hard elements
of what we know as the Moon
and also the vagueness
of extraterrestrial life.
Your face and this
look awfully close,
so I would bring this down
a little bit more
on the forehead,
because once you turn this
out in the foam,
you could get up to 5%
to 10% shrinkage.
Okay.
So we got The Golden Keep.
Our beast is a dragon.
With the scales,
you don't want to make them
so subtle
they totally disappear.
It has to show up,
so you need to,
at least when you're painting,
make sure you take advantage
of shading
to pop the scales
into your design.
All right, we're leaving,
- but good luck tomorrow.
- Thank you very much.
- Bye.
- Good-bye, everybody.
- Bye-bye.
Bye!
I go to check on Rashaad.
_
Rashaad told me that he knew
how to do molds really well,
so I thought
it was all taken care of.
There's no burlap down here.
There's not?
I'm starting to panic
a little bit.
There's no way to get
this mold off this head
without cracking it in half.
_
If we crack this mold,
we'll lose the entire piece
and have to start from scratch.
I may not have a cowl tomorrow.
This is the beginning
of the end.
The cowl mold is not coming
off the mannequin
because the mannequin has
undercuts,
which is a curve
that the plaster seals around,
which means you have to chip
away at your mold
in order to get it off.
So make sure you do, like,
really thick burlap
on all these edges
so we have, like, a really good
spot to pop it off.
Okay.
I'm feeling guilty.
This is not a mistake
I normally make.
The cowl is a crucial element
to our character.
It's coming.
We have to get this thing free.
Oh!
We finally crack it open
on the floor.
Thank God.
We have enough of the mold
so we can get our cowl piece.
- Next time...
- I got you.
...maybe we should make it
a little thicker.
Yeah, a lot thicker.
You know what
would be a big help?
If you spent, like,
five or ten minutes
just cutting burlap for me,
it would make this go
so much faster.
Daniel's adamant
about doing the wig.
He's only concerned
about his stuff, so fine.
I'm gonna go mold.
We have the prop,
the two hand molds,
his face,
and my huge cowl,
which is a two-part mold.
We're a team,
and unless he wants to end up
in bottom looks,
then he needs to help me.
_
We open up the cowl mold,
and the clay is sticking to it.
Niko and I only have
five minutes left.
So I'm outside cleaning
up this thing,
and I'm feeling
absolutely anxious.
We have, like,
the important scales done.
Two minutes left--
We're starting to put
things together.
I'm like, holy shit,
we're gonna get this mold done
in time.
And that's when my heart sinks.
Niko, we don't have the face!
All right, everybody,
time's up!
I was so hyper-focused
on the cowl,
we forgot to pour foam latex
in the face piece.
I'm absolutely devastated.
What do we do about the face?
Tomorrow we're gonna have to do
a latex and polyfoam face.
Fuck.
Latex and polyfoam is stiffer
than foam latex.
How is the actor going
to be able to emote?
I'm really worried.
Let's do this.
It's application day.
There's four hours in the lab,
and Matt's looking
at our piece,
and it has this huge ridge
of foam
on the perimeter.
So Matt starts to patch that,
and we're just gonna make
the best of it.
The face piece
wasn't ready before time's up,
so I decided to go with gelatin
instead of the polyfoam,
because gelatin
will have better movement.
I'm worried that
a transparent gelatin face
is not going to match
an opaque foam cowl,
but I am gonna hope
for the best.
- Hi, guys.
- How you doing?
You're, like, a wolf guy.
Give us 45 minutes.
Our plan for application day
is to open our chest mold,
fill it with poly foam,
and pull our pieces
out of that.
I can't do anything
until we have the chest piece,
because it has to be
the chest piece first
and then the cowl
and then the face.
All right, we're gonna try
to put this on you here.
There's a lot to do.
I have to finish the staff,
finish painting, dress him,
put the wig
and all of his hair on.
But I'm feeling a lot better
at this point.
We're actually vibing
very well as a team right now,
but we still have to pull
this character together.
I'm looking
at all these pieces,
and I'm thinking, "All right,
all these edges are very nice,
and we're ready
to start painting."
So we're basing everything
out in white
to make sure that
all the stone texture
is really gonna pop,
and we're gonna get all
those cracks to show off.
Going over your face.
I just ripped it in half.
When I pull the cowl
over the head,
it completely rips
in the center.
I'm just gonna have to fix it.
It's a "Oh, fuck" moment
for me,
but our creature is gonna be
kind of a warrior king,
so I'm just gonna create
some scarring
so he's battle-damaged
and make a negative
into a positive
and just keep moving forward.
We can just put latex
on top of it.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
I got it.
We're getting that
blue on there,
but I'm thinking we need
another bold color,
and I remember that our belle
has a red dress.
So I find a color I can pop
into the chest
to match her
the best that we can.
- How many minutes do we have?
- 15.
I need a white acrylic.
- Empty bottle.
- All right, I'll go get one.
All right, guys, time's up!
- Let's go.
- Good job, buddy.
You're gonna kick ass.
- Do-do-do!
- Time is up,
and Margaret and I are gonna
have to hit
the ground running as soon
as we get into last looks.
We've got to finish
the paint job,
and we got to finish
bondo'ing some of his edges.
I think that we're in trouble,
and I'm really starting
to get nervous.
Coming up...
Yeah, that's too much.
We got to fix all that.
There's a new twist
that I need to tell you about.
Your technical ability is
very, very evident.
I think this is really cool.
This is one
of the kookiest choices
I have ever seen on this show.
It's last looks.
There's only one hour left.
And we're just gonna paint
the living shit
out of our character.
I need hair on the other ear.
Everything is applied.
Now I need to lay
all of the hair
as fast as humanly possible.
We got held up
having to fix all the patches
and the appliances,
so Margaret and I have to skip
some of the stuff
we wanted to do.
We got to fix all that.
That's time!
I can't believe it.
I'm really anxious, but it's
time to stop worrying about it.
We did our best,
and I'm hoping the judges
are gonna see that.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
Let's say hello
to our talented judges--
Owner of Optic Nerve
Makeup Effects Studio
Glenn Hetrick...
- Good evening, guys.
- Hi.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill...
- Hello, everybody.
- Hi.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page...
- Hello.
- Hi.
And rejoining us tonight
is writer, producer,
and director Stephen Sommers.
Hey, guys.
Good to be back.
Now, before we see
your makeups,
there's a new twist
that I need to tell you about.
This season the judges
will be able to issue
a one-time special immunity.
They will be able to save
an artist who's had a tough week
and would have
otherwise been eliminated,
so this will be
at their discretion,
and you won't know
when it's coming.
The judges are gonna grant
immunity to one of us.
How cool is that?
All right, so this week
your spotlight challenge
was to choose
one of the castles
our belles were holding
and create the huge beast
that would live in it with her.
So let's take a look at
your creations and their belles.
The gold against the black
looks awesome,
and I want to give Niko
the biggest hug in the world
and be like,
"We did it, buddy."
He's beautiful, sexy,
and terrifying.
I'm really proud of everything
me and Daniel did together.
He looks like he came
from that castle.
He looks like he's part
of that castle.
He looks like a beast,
and he looks like the belle
might be able to kiss him.
Looking at our beast,
I'm totally bummed.
It doesn't look real.
It's just not what
I wanted it to be.
Our character has
the brightest-looking elements
out of everybody else's.
I'm nervous, because
I don't know what to expect.
We're happy with what we did,
and we know what we did wrong,
and we're gonna do better
next time.
But we're so proud
of what we've done today.
I'm very proud of what
me and Chloe have done
in the limited time
that we had.
That's our baby.
Judges, it's time to take
a closer look at our beasts.
These nails are cool.
Try to emote
through the makeup.
Growl. Grimace.
Cool. Thank you.
The blood throws me.
It's more horror.
It should be scary,
but not gory.
Thank you.
Up close, there's
some nice detailing happening
up through here.
If they pulled
the eyelids back,
I think it wouldn't be
as hard to light.
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
The judges are going
for a closer look,
and I'm really nervous,
because I know
what all the flaws are.
I'm very curious
as to the choice of sculpting
around the nose.
Can you turn your head?
_
The ears are laughable.
I knew as soon as the judges
noticed them,
we were going to be in trouble.
I'm really scared
that I'm going home.
I like that there's snow in it and frost,
but I thought it made him look old.
Judges going for the closer look,
and I know this isn't the greatest makeup.
The sculpting around the nose
almost feels diseased.
- Okay, thanks.
- Well done.
I want to know the story
behind this makeup.
- This is not a pretty look.
- Thank you.
How would you kiss those lips?
That's an odd nose.
- It's an odd everything.
- Yeah.
Wow.
This is a lot of detail.
It looks so professional to me.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, thanks.
Okay, the judges have scored
your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Tess and Niko...
Cat and Daniel...
Tanner and Corinne...
Congratulations, because
you guys are safe this week
and can head back...
- Oh, my God.
- ...to the makeup room.
We did it!
Now, the rest of you
were the best and the worst.
The judges would now like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Daran, Graham, and George,
if you'd please step forward.
Start by telling me
about the idea
and also who did what.
He's been trapped
in this castle
with a 100-year curse.
The longer he's in the castle,
the more he becomes part of it.
Daran sculpted the face.
George did the chest.
I blocked out the cowl.
I think this is really cool.
One of my favorite things
about the makeup
is you can't actually follow
those shapes into his chest.
He'd be bulked out super huge.
But you just suggest that,
and it goes away
under the robe,
and that's really cool.
Is the pink color supposed
to resemble a fleshy tone?
It's around his heart,
so it's just keeping
that area warm,
to show that there's still
a man in there.
I think it should have been
a little bit warmer.
- Mm-hmm.
- It just looks
a little pink-y to me.
The execution of the sculpt
is at a high level.
There's some really nice detail
when you get up close.
I am excited about what
the three of you have to offer.
Thank you.
I love the backstory,
and, also, I like
that I can see his eyes.
Belle I could see
kissing him at the end.
- Awesome, thank you.
- Thank you.
Please step back.
Matt and Margaret.
What is his backstory?
A human prince of this
castle had come upon a stone,
not realizing that this was
an object
that was slowly turning him
into this beast.
I got to tell you guys,
he looks like a big blob
of Silly Putty
with some divots in it.
There's not enough texture
in it.
This shape is very odd.
I'm just not real fond
of this particular design.
I said to make it
terrifying and sexy,
and this one in particular,
especially with the lips,
I don't know how belle
kisses this creature.
Okay.
Who put the initial shape
on the front of the face?
- I did.
- Okay.
The abrupt disruption
of the cheeks
and the nasolabial folds here
in the face
is a very strange decision--
beyond unacceptable.
Okay, you can head back.
Rashaad and Chloe.
So tell us about your design.
I've been very inspired
by the Gill-man.
That's the oldest
"Beauty And The Beast" story.
Chloe sculpted
the wonderful face,
and I did the cowl and torso.
You've got a beautiful piece.
The face has a lot of detailing
going on there.
The sculpt on the chest
and the back--
there's some
beautiful stuff there.
It's a very complete makeup.
- Thank you.
I can't believe what you did
in a day and a half.
- It looks amazing.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I think it is stellar.
The sculpture
is so well designed.
It's scary,
but you could sell it
to little kids as a doll.
Thank you.
You can step down.
Thanks, Omar.
Tyler and Bethany,
please step forward.
- Go first.
- Thanks.
What's your character's
backstory?
He was chosen to be
a human sacrifice,
and that's why he's chained up.
Bringing in cultural aspects
of the palace
was something
we really wanted to do,
so the orbs are the structural
part of the building.
He doesn't seem scary,
and he doesn't seem sexy.
The face, especially
with a black nose,
it's very mousy.
It doesn't quite gel
for me there.
Okay.
I don't see the monster in him.
He seems like a teddy bear
or a clown.
He looks like a Persian cat
that got mixed up
with a blueberry
ice cream cone.
I'm not really even sure what
you guys were thinking of
when you jammed
this guy's head with balls
with spikes coming out of 'em.
This is one
of the kookiest choices
I have ever seen on this show.
Thank you very much.
If you'd please step back.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
All right, judges,
why don't we start
with the looks
you like the most?
Let's begin with Daran, Graham,
and George's team.
The way that the chest flowed
into the wardrobe--
it was a pretty clever way
to integrate
the bulk of the beast.
It was almost like
a ruffly shirt coming up
that was part of his body.
Daran's face sculpt
was particularly good.
All right, let's move on
to Chloe and Rashaad.
Wow, did they get a lot done.
I mean, there was so much detail
in that face,
it was pretty much astounding.
That is one of the most complex
and complete first-week makeups
we have ever seen.
I was completely and absolutely
impressed with this.
All right, let's move on
to the looks
you liked the least.
Let's start
with Bethany and Tyler.
It really did look like
a kitty cat
and some ice cream cones
got into a brawl.
We asked huge--
Not there.
Terrifying-- Not at all there.
Sexy-- It wasn't there.
So what we were asking
wasn't there at all.
Okay, let's move on
to Margaret and Matt.
He wasn't scary or sexy.
Even though he was a big model,
they didn't take advantage
of it.
My biggest complaint
is the face.
There was no elegance
to the sculpture,
but there was also no reference
to any strong anatomy.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- I think so.
- Yes, we have.
Let's bring them back out.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about the top teams.
Chloe and Rashaad,
we were really wowed
by how much work
you did this week
and how detailed it was.
Daran, Graham, and George,
we really liked the way
that you integrated
your castle elements,
and your decision to retain
some of those human skin tones
was a wise one.
Okay, which team
came out on top?
The winning team tonight is...
Okay, which team
came out on top?
The winning team tonight is...
Chloe and Rashaad.
We were really wowed
by how detailed it was.
- Thank you.
Great job.
But we can only have
one winner.
All right, Glenn,
who is the winner
of this challenge?
Tonight's winner is...
Chloe.
Awesome overall character,
but the face and the paint
were the standouts
of this makeup.
Thank you.
This is incredible.
Winning the first spotlight
challenge
is a confidence booster.
Chloe, congratulations.
Thank you.
You, Rashaad,
George, Daran, Graham,
are all safe and can head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you, guys.
Unfortunately, that means
the rest of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom teams.
Bethany and Tyler,
there were some really good
techniques employed
in your makeup,
but a faulty concept
and poor design choices
ultimately led you astray.
Margaret and Matt,
your sculpting lacked
in detail--
a problem which was
further exacerbated
by a bland paint scheme.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Margaret.
We had several issues
with this makeup,
but the face was filled
with sculptural shapes
and anatomy
that just didn't make sense
to us.
Yeah.
That means,
Tyler, Bethany, Matt,
you are safe.
If you'd please head
back to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Margaret, go home
with your head held high.
That makeup in another season
might have gotten you
at least through
to the next week.
Margaret, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
It's been great
having you with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
- Take care, Margaret.
Good luck, Margaret.
I am disappointed to go out
in the first round.
_
Aw.
Meeting all these
different artists,
it's been inspiring.
Come on.
For me, makeup
has been amazing.
It's done a lot for me.
I'm looking forward to seeing
what happens next.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net