It's a black hole
of original thought.
It's an awesome makeup.
It's kind of
like bondage Rambo.
Previously on Face Off...
Daran's multiple-faced victim
brought him his third win...
Thank you,
thank you, thank you.
...and Corinne was sent home.
Now, seven artists remain.
Tonight they dive into a world
of whimsical beasts.
- Never-seen-before characters.
- Cool.
I'm ready to embrace anything
that's on the immature side.
But some struggle to bring
their creations to life.
If you have the time,
do a cowl.
- It could only help you.
- That's fucking risky, dude.
Everything we do is risky.
I think your character needs
a little more power to it.
I keep looking at it
and I'm like,
"Oh, shit, he's right."
Head to toe, you've
really done a beautiful job.
It doesn't
feel like a predator.
It feels more like it would
be subject to gang beatings.
In the end, only one will win
a VIP trip
from Kryolan Professional Makeup
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new
2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Face Off!
Welcome toFace Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
I can't believe
that you and Corinne
were on the bottom.
I didn't want
either one of you guys goin'.
Being on the bottom
for the first time
and just seeing the red lights,
it was weird and not a position
I want to be in again.
Corinne's an awesome artist,
and I thought
I was gonna go home.
It was very frightening,
and it's not a place
I want to be at again.
There's less than half of us.
- We started with 15 people.
- Mm-hmm.
This far in a competition
means you have to dig deep
because any little mistake
can send you home.
What do we got now?
- Hm, Kidspace.
- Kidspace.
I love kids.
We're walkin' up
to the Kidspace Museum.
Ooh.
What is this?
There's all sorts
of cool learning contraptions.
- Nice.
- Oh, cool.
Oh.
Oh, there she is.
There's McKenzie standin'
next to a giant box of crayons.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
And I'm ready
to embrace anything
that's on the immature side.
Welcome to Kidspace Museum
in Pasadena,
it's a place for children
to explore their creativity
and learn
in a fun, hands-on way.
I brought you here because
like your next challenge,
it was designed
to inspire the imagination.
Good.
Today, we'll be entering
the whimsical world
- of children's books...
- Ooh.
Which have been
the source of some
of Hollywood's most
successful films,
like Charlie
And The Chocolate Factory,
The Fantastic Mr. Fox,
and James And The Giant Peach.
Oh, nice.
All of these
sprang from the mind
of best-selling
children's author Roald Dahl.
- Wow, nice.
- Oh.
It touches me in a way
'cause I've opened my creativity
so much reading
Roald Dahl's books as a kid.
We are lucky enough
to have someone
here with us today
who's very close to the source.
Please welcome author,
screenwriter,
and Roald Dahl's daughter,
Lucy Dahl.
- Cool.
- Amazing.
It's really an honor
to have a daughter
of the guy
that we all loved as a kid.
- Lucy, hello.
- Hi.
Thank you so much
for being here with us.
Thank you for having me.
Well, this year
is the 50th anniversary
of Charlie
And The Chocolate Factory.
Yes.
Why do you think
this has resonated
so profoundly with people?
Chocolate.
Being able to go into a world
that you don't really think
that you can ever
normally go into,
like a chocolate factory
with chocolate rivers.
Actually,
one of my first memories
was going into
the real chocolate room
in the first film,
which was amazing.
Oh, awesome.
While we will
never forget characters
like Willy Wonka,
Miss Trunchbull,
and the Oompa Loompas,
not all of Dahl's creations
have come to life
on the silver screen.
The Oompa Loompa-eating
Whangdoodle,
Hornswogglers, Vermicious Knids,
and Snozzwangers
have fascinated
my father's fan base for years,
but they've never
been seen on-screen.
He only described them
as living
in the thickest of jungles
and the most dangerous beasts
in the world.
Each crayon
in this box contains
the name of one
of these unseen beasts.
Your spotlight challenge
is to select one of them
and use its name to inspire
a wild and whimsical beast
that would feel
right at home
in the world of Roald Dahl.
Oh, yes.
- Nice.
- All right.
Graham, you're up first.
Snozzwanger.
Hornswogglers.
Vermicious Knids?
Vermicious Knids.
Hornswogglers.
Whangdoodle.
We're both Whangdoodles.
And I'm very happy to report
that Lucy will be joining us
on the reveal stage this week.
What should these guys
keep in mind
while working on their designs?
Exaggeration of the truth.
If you're nice,
you're really nice.
If you're horrible,
you're really horrible.
If you're spoiled,
you're really spoiled.
Just imagine what would eat
an Oompa Loompa.
All right, guys,
you have the extraordinary
opportunity to give fans
all over the world
a first glimpse of these
never-seen-before characters.
I'm going to leave you here
while you work on your designs.
When you're done,
you can head back
to the lab and get started.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
- Good-bye.
- Bye.
Ooh.
This place is awesome.
I feel like a little kid.
There's all
these really cool bugs
and oversized game pieces.
It's crazy.
Working on this Whangdoodle
definitely brings out
the child in me
because Willy Wonka
And The Chocolate Factory
was one of
my favorite movies growing up.
For years, I wondered what
these creatures looked like.
And now, I'm actually
gettin' the chance
to design one of 'em.
I'm thinkin' Whangdoodles
has got to have some kind
of split personality.
Very yin and yang.
Whang would be
the serious side.
Hard-edged, straight lines.
And the Doodle
has to be the silly side,
swirly lines and circles.
If he catches an Oompa Loompa
and they sing a song
that he likes,
he'll let 'em go,
and if they don't,
he'll eat 'em.
Designing this character
is a real honor
because nobody
has seen these guys before.
There's no images of this,
no reference,
and I'm nervous because
I want to do it justice.
So I start
drawing a rabbit creature,
but it has this horrific mouth
with teeth
coming out of his chest.
He lures the Oompa Loompas in
and then eats 'em up.
Snozz sounded like "Schnoz,"
so I thought big elephant nose
and a huge,
scary monster mouth.
It lays traps
filled with Snozzberries
for the Oompa Loompas,
and then uses
its huge nose
to sniff them out.
The first thing
that comes to me
is a Venus flytrap.
I'm thinking
this little creature
that's like--
It's a very whimsical plant.
It's gonna be brightly colored
with a lot of teeth,
and it pops out of the forest
to eat these little orange men.
I got Whangdoodle.
Doodle, noodle,
worms, insect, and then bam.
These giant earth worm things
that would come out
and snatch the Oompa Loompas
and suck 'em back in.
I can't wait to get in the lab.
- I gotta make this thing.
- All right, guys.
Let's go back to the lab.
So soon?
We get to the lab.
We have six hours.
First, we choose our model.
I start sculpting
my Hornswoggler's face.
So at first,
he's not gonna look scary.
He's just cute and silly.
He's gonna have
really big horns in the back
and big eyes on the side,
and a big smile with big teeth.
But if he sees an Oompa Loompa,
he becomes this vicious,
evil monster eater.
I'm not actually used to doin'
whimsical-type characters,
sometimes when I get in a little bit
of a jam or get stuck,
I just scribble
on a piece of paper
and try to get images
out of whatever I'm scribblin'.
Since it's a Hornswoggler,
it needs to have horns
and a big mouth so it
can eat the Oompa Loompas.
For some reason, it's comin' out
lizard-y or froggy,
and I know kids love both,
so I'm gonna go with it.
I'm lookin'
at my Snozzwanger design,
and I'm thinking,
this thing is so silly-looking.
It'll probably be the weirdest
makeup that I've ever done.
The way that
this prosthetic is designed,
the nose is
actually on the forehead,
so it needs
to have an armature inside
to help the clay
to stay where I want it.
And the armature
has to be removable
so that I can cut off
the end of the nose,
remove that,
and then mold that separately.
So the model will be looking
through the nostrils
of the nose.
I would like
to win this challenge
to show the judges,
"Hey, like, you kept me around.
I'll show you somethin' else
that's really cool."
I'm sculpting my Whangdoodle,
and I'm tryin' to think of
how I'm gonna make these teeth.
So I end up grabbing 32 claws
that we have in the lab,
and I'm poppin' 'em in.
I'm like, "All right.
This is awesome."
These look cool.
So I'm sculpting
this Vermicious Knid,
and I'm realizing
as I'm doing it
that it's just not working.
I'm just kind of
pushing around clay.
I'm just not sure what
I want on this Loompa-eater,
so I wipe out what I have and start
sculpting more of a flytrap this way
with leaves behind it.
Hopefully, this works.
Hey, guys.
We're here to check on you.
- Hello.
- How are ya?
Hey.
And so, he's gonna
have some big eyes
over here on the side,
and then I've got
some horns that are gonna
go up the center.
I think you're catchin' it.
- I really do.
- Am I on track?
This character
could be salivating
thinking of Oompa Loompas.
Put a little K-Y jelly
or something in there
to really juicy-up
that lip and even--
- Keep Ve from touchin' it?
- Yeah.
I'm not sure what I want to do
with the mouth yet.
I would do somethin'--
like something round.
Like, so if you were lookin'--
actually looking
into a flower,
'cause then that could all
- be painted one color...
- Right.
...and-- and washed
over the top of it.
So when you look into there,
you're looking
into the inside of a flower.
Okay.
I'm thinking
of yellowish-orange tones.
If it's comin' up
out of the ground,
you shoot it
with a little water first,
hit it with brown hairspray,
and it just starts to drip,
'cause then it would look like
he's comin' up
out of the ground--
and he's been wet,
and dirty, and--
Perfect.
Whang is more
like the serious side,
and Doodle is
more of the silly side.
What are you doing for color?
I want to play
on a day and night theme,
this side be brighter
and then this side darker.
- And a really good transition.
- Oh, yeah, of course.
Paint be-- be--
between the two.
I didn't want
to do a cowl separate,
and a chest, and a back,
so it's gonna be a whole suit.
With something this big,
you can let your imagination
go wild on a skin texture,
either with polka dot
or striped even,
because that becomes part
of this fantasy camouflage.
Is this gonna
be able to move at all?
Or is this
gonna stay stationary?
This part
is gonna move up and down,
so that'll be kind of neat.
Clever idea too, coming off
the top of the head with it.
It's calling out for scoring
from the inside here,
and just cutting through it,
not pulling any out,
so it will kind of accordion.
Oh, that's a good idea.
I like that.
Great.
He's gonna be kind of friendly,
like, "How are you?
I'm beautiful," you know?
And all of a sudden, like--
For what the challenge is,
I think your character
needs a little more power
to it.
You know, whimsical
can't be subtle.
You need to exaggerate
as opposed to making it
too human-like.
Mr. Westmore
says I need to go
with something bigger than life,
something exaggerated.
I keep looking at it,
and I'm like,
"Oh, shit, he's right."
I gotta come up with something.
Otherwise, I'm gonna
be in big trouble.
- Coming up...
- Go, daddy, go.
If I don't finish this,
I'm not gonna have anything.
Fuck.
There is this much clay
in the top of the mold.
Damn, you did a great job.
It's almost freaky
how you channeled my father.
You're better
than what I see here.
Your character needs
a little more power to it.
It's day one
of our Roald Dahl challenge.
Mr. Westmore
thinks my sculpture
doesn't feel big enough
for a character like this.
Whimsical can't be subtle.
You need to exaggerate
as opposed to making it
too human-like.
I agree with Mr. Westmore.
I need to go with something
that is bigger than life,
so I have to resculpt
this whole thing.
But I gotta speed this up
'cause I don't have
much time to finish this.
All right, guys.
Have fun with this.
- All right.
- See you soon.
Thank you, guys.
For my Snozzwanger,
I have to do two molds
because the nose
curves in such a way
that I wouldn't
be able to clean it out.
So I remove most of it,
and I'll mold
that separately in silicone.
I know the judges
are gonna hate it
because it has
no anatomical function.
It's just this wacky,
childlike monster,
but I think it looks so cool
that you can't help
but like it.
That's gonna be creepy as hell.
The only thing I'm
worried about is the profile.
If I just leave it like this,
it's just
gonna look unfinished.
I mean, if you have
the time, do a cowl
'cause it could only help you.
No, that's fucking risky, dude.
Everything we do is risky.
Just gotta make sure
you do it and you do it good.
I'm feeling a little bit uneasy
because I'm not doing a lot.
So tomorrow,
I'll sculpt the cowl.
And hopefully,
I'll have a good piece.
You should
have two static arms.
Maybe I'll put
like five on there.
I'm really
trying to go all out,
having this character
really act like a worm
and kind of doing
all these crazy movements.
So I'm sculpting two arms
just to give it more motion
and the sense
of something that can come up
and snatch something
and bring it back.
It's comin' along.
That's time, guys.
I definitely wish that things
would have gone
a little bit faster today...
Opa.
...but I've
nailed down my concept,
and I'm ready
to go forward on it.
It's day two,
we got 9 1/2 hours.
And for my Snozzwanger,
the cowl needs to be real big
'cause it's
this huge elephant head
with giant ears,
fat rolls around its neck,
and the eyes are gonna
be coming off of the head.
Yeah, big, goofy ears, right?
Yeah, dude.
Today, I need
to focus on these giant worms
coming off this cowl piece.
And they need
to be lightweight,
so instead
of sculpting out of clay,
I feed little foam rings
onto a wire and I bend it.
I'm like, "This is it.
This is the shape I need."
That is so cool.
Even though I still
need to sculpt the cowl,
I'm worried,
because Lucy Dahl said
that in her father's books,
everything is
an exaggeration of the truth.
So I'm adding some more leaves,
adding all of my detail.
I think it's an opportunity
to sculpt something crazy
and take a lot of risks.
And I'm also taking quills
into the middle of the face
to create Venus flytrap teeth
so it can eat an Oompa Loompa.
Overall, I'm really excited
with the way
that this is turning out.
I'm making this Hornswoggler,
and I would like to add,
like, some really big horns
in the back
because he's a killer monster
that lives in the jungle.
So I cut L200, and I just start
placing some pieces
on the bodysuit
and it looks like
a vicious, evil monster eater.
I hope the judges will see that
just from Roald Dahl's world.
Today, I'm sculpting the chest.
The chest piece
is very important
because if it doesn't
have that horrific mouth
that is gonna
eat the Oompa Loompas,
it's just the face of a bunny.
And a bunny
eating the Oompa Loompas
is not whimsical or scary.
It's just a bunny.
Time is flying,
and I'm not getting this done.
I want to make
more detail on the cowl,
but I have to let it go
and just go mold it
because otherwise
I won't finish this.
Let's go.
I'm trying to give myself
at least four hours
to mold my bodysuit.
I'm really pushing
the limits on this a lot
because it's big, so I'm taking
a lot of risks doing this,
but I think
it's gonna come out great.
I have
a lot of confidence in me.
I think I can
do this mold very good.
So on this Hornswoggler,
I'll be fabricatin' a cowl.
And I think I'm gonna
go with some blue feathers
just to add a little
more whimsical to it.
I'll try to lay these things
to where it looks like hair.
I've never tried
the feather trick before,
and I'm--
I'm really diggin' it.
All I can do is hope the judges
like my idea
for feathered hair.
I decided to fabricate my torso
because I know
I can do it a lot faster
than sculpting,
molding, running it in foam.
I start blocking out
the shape I need.
And then I begin
cutting out pieces of L200,
pieces of upholstery foam,
shapes that match with the face.
The left side
is the Doodle side,
right side
being the Whang side.
So I make sure I work that
into the torso as well.
- You crazy, dude.
- I'm crazy!
I'm really pushing
the limits on this mold.
It's so big
that I actually have
to get on a step stool
to get the top part.
But somehow, I get it done.
And now, I need
to open and clean it out.
This mold is 200 pounds.
All right.
I don't know how
I'm gonna open this by myself.
Go, daddy, go!
If I make one little mistake,
it can actually
ruin the whole mold.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
That man is crazy.
I just hope
that this doesn't break.
I'm starting to
get really nervous.
I cannot lift this.
The mold is too heavy,
and it's starting to crack.
Fuck.
If the mold cracks,
I'm not gonna
have anything for tomorrow.
It is day two
for this Roald Dahl challenge
making this Oompa Loompa
monster eater.
_
This mold is 200 pounds.
I still have
to open it and clean it
or I'm not gonna have anything.
Mr. Rashaad?
Can you help me one last time?
One, two, three.
So we put this on the floor,
and start like trying
to crack it and open it
and just hope
that this doesn't break.
There you go.
Thank God for Rashaad.
Now I have to clean it out
before the end of the day.
You and your big molds, man.
I have all my pieces,
and I'm like,
"All right, let me
just start painting everything."
I remember Mr. Westmore's advice
on taking brown hairspray
to create this muddying,
dripping effect.
Mr. Westmore was right.
It looks like-- like muddy dirt.
- He's always right.
- Yay.
It just drips,
and it looks amazing.
It looks like wet mud.
- Give me that.
- Don't break my shit.
I'm not gonna break it, Tyler.
It needs to go
through a stress test.
Get it going.
- It works.
- It's pretty creepy.
The paint job on this
is very important.
I'm going with black and white
because they're good colors
to put against each other.
This is the Whang,
and this is the Doodle side.
- Ooh, nice.
- He catches Oompa Loompas.
And if they don't
sing a song that he likes,
he eats them.
This is
a two-tone paint job,
but you can't
just have black and white.
All the colors
in between have to show as well.
Oh, yes.
I've just sculpted this cowl
faster than I've sculpted
anything in my entire life,
and it's not terrible.
But now, I have to mold it
and clean it out
before the end of the day.
- Time?
- 21 minutes.
If I don't get this cowl done,
I'm gonna have
to run it in poly foam,
which is not
a very good option.
All right, guys.
It's time!
Fuck.
Time is called,
and there is still
this much clay
stuck in the top of the mold.
Shit.
I'm not happy with the situation
that I've put myself in.
I have a lot to do tomorrow,
and I think my only
saving grace right now
would be a good face piece.
- Whoo!
- Mm, mm, mm.
All right.
Okay.
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab.
The first thing
I do is make sure
all of my pieces
are free of seams,
fix anything
that needs to be patched.
Get on down.
This is the difference between
great makeup or goin' home.
I can do this.
After I clean the mold,
the first thing
that I need to do
is create a latex skin
in my cowl mold.
And then,
I will pour poly foam into it.
I just need everything to work.
Hey, what's up, bro?
- What's goin' on?
- There you are.
Thank you.
A little patching to do.
I look at my bodysuit,
and there's a lot
of seaming and patching to do.
And that takes
a huge chunk of your time,
so I hope
I can get everything done.
What we've got here is a bunch
of monsters from Loompaland.
I'm workin' on the safari hat
because I need
these eyes to come up
out of the brill of the hat,
and I dremel out
some nice-sized holes.
And then I give the hat, like,
a little bit of wear and tear
just so it looks like
it's been through the jungle.
Sweet.
What's great
about this spandex cowl
is that I did
coat it with latex.
So now, it's pretty much
like a ball cap.
This is great.
It's like a wig.
Yeah, it's like a giant,
custom-made wig for this.
This competition
is getting stiff,
so I think these little details
and these little tricks
are extremely important.
Holy shit.
I go to check on my mold,
and I see that the poly foam
has not cured at all.
This is pretty bad.
At this point, I've wasted
2 1/2 hours on this cowl.
I can't try it again.
I don't have time.
I gotta let it go.
All right,
I'm gonna wash my hands,
and then we're gonna start.
I immediately
start applying the face.
I've decided
to completely scrap the cowl.
I'm gonna pull the hood up
and glue moss around it,
and I just start painting
as quickly as possible.
Perfect.
At this point,
I'm applying everything,
but I'm still taking
a lot of time
to seam
and patch all those sides,
so I'm getting
a little bit worried
because I'm not gonna have
enough time to paint everything.
Ten minutes, guys!
I'm moving as fast as I can.
I don't know if I'm gonna
have time to finish everything.
But at this point,
there's no turning back.
I made the decision
to make this bodysuit,
so I have to keep painting.
That's time, everybody.
Brushes down.
I need to keep focused
and try to do as much
as I can in last looks.
If I don't get this done,
this is gonna send me home.
Coming up...
Nice.
I made a full bodysuit,
but it looks like a chicken.
I hope this isn't
a complete mess.
You knocked it
out of the park, well done.
I feel like it would be subject
to gang beatings
by the Oompa Loompas
rather than being
able to hunt them.
Whoo-hoo.
- I'm gonna go over here.
- So we get to last looks.
We have one hour to finish
our Oompa Loompa monster eaters.
I still need to add the eyes,
I still need to add the horns
and finish my paint job.
Speed makeup.
I'm goin' from one arm.
Then I do a leg,
and it's really comin' together.
This is probably the most fun
that I've had painting
one of these creatures.
Nice.
I love it.
It's like a dance routine.
I start
gluing in all of the quills
inside of the Venus flytrap
to add detail
so I don't
have a complete mess.
- Time?
- That's ten more minutes, guys.
Holy cow.
That's scary.
That's it, everybody.
Time's up.
Brushes down.
Boo.
Bummer, man.
It might not
be enough this time.
Welcome to
theFace Offreveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
First, let's say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
- Hey, Glenn.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
Hi, fabulous makeup artists.
Hello, Ve.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
- Hi, guys.
- Hey, Neville.
And joining us again tonight
is author, screenwriter,
and Roald Dahl's daughter,
- Lucy Dahl.
- Hi, Lucy.
Great to have you back.
Thank you.
It's a pleasure to be back.
All right, this week,
your spotlight challenge
was to select
one of the unseen creatures
from the world of Roald Dahl
and use its name to inspire
a wild and whimsical beast.
So let's take
a look at your creations
while the audience
at home tweets
about their favorites
using #FaceOff.
Pretty excited about this.
I just hope
it's whimsical enough
and scary enough
for the judges to like it.
Oh, my gosh, this looks great.
It has a lot of movement,
and it really does look
like an Oompa Loompa-killer.
It's not what I wanted.
It's not what I envisioned.
It just fell apart.
I'm looking
at this Snozzwanger,
and it looks so awesome.
I couldn't be more happy
with this character.
I'm loving the character.
I love the way he looks,
the way he moves.
If I go home,
I'm happy about it
because this is a great makeup.
It doesn't look evil.
He just looks like a chicken.
I'm actually really worried
at this point.
He looks amazing in profile.
He looks amazing
from the front.
I'm-- I'm excited.
I'm happy.
Judges, why don't
you take a closer look
at these Oompa Loompa-eating
beasts?
Nice eyebrows.
I like the blue feathers too.
The horns are a good idea.
I wish
they were different sizes,
like this one
being a bit smaller.
Oh, that's
beautiful right there.
Very expressive
for something that thick.
How's that Oompa Loompa
tasting?
- Delicious.
- Yeah.
Great answer.
Thank you.
There's not
much here, is there?
What is that supposed to be?
It's a bit
like a sea urchin's face.
It's so minimal
compared to the scope
of what other people have done.
I do like the paint work
that's going on there.
Thank you.
Can you wiggle
your head around?
Look, he's got
Oompa Loompa skulls,
and what's in there?
Snozzberry Oompa bait.
- Oh.
- Genius.
It's the skinned bunny.
This transition
from these grays into the pink
is a really cool idea.
Give us some expression.
Oh, very nice.
Thank you.
Oh, boy.
Talk about biting off
more than you could chew.
It's the lack of precision.
I'm not satisfied
with this makeup,
and I know I'm gonna
be in bottom looks.
I really think the judges
are gonna send me home.
Who made
your favorite whimsical beast?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
It feels like
he's just poking around at ideas
for lack of anything
solid in terms of direction.
I made a full bodysuit,
but it looks like a chicken.
This just feels
like a waste of time.
There's nothing
there as a design.
- I'm baffled.
- Thank you.
Let's see your hands here.
That looks like that could
slit an Oompa Loompa's throat.
To address all
of these forms in the time?
Really, really difficult.
Definitely a lot of hard work.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Lucy, you asked these guys
to really use
their imagination this week.
How'd they do?
I think you did
an extraordinary job.
I'm blown away by your talent.
Thank you.
Okay, the judges
have scored your creations.
Let's find out
what they thought.
Rashaad...
Daran...
George...
Congratulations,
because you are all safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you.
The rest of you are the best
and the worst this week.
The judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Tyler, please step up.
All right.
Here he comes.
Tell us
about your thought process
and how it fits
into this week's challenge.
I had the Whangdoodle,
and my concept
is this earthworm,
cockroach-type beast
that lives under the jungle.
And when Oompa Loompas come by,
it grabs 'em and snatches 'em.
This is
a very successful makeup.
Thank you.
What I like the most about it,
your color denotes
an evil character.
And then you were
cautiously playful
and cartoonish with it.
That's a lot of good decisions
that resulted
in a really impressive makeup.
Thank you.
He's scary right down
to the little touch of
Oompa Loompa hair in his mouth.
Yes.
It's very successful,
and on top of that,
- your paint job is just beautiful.
- Thank you.
The character is so complete
from an aesthetic quality
and from a performance quality.
You've really done
a beautiful job this week.
Thank you.
I really felt that's
a monster in Loompaland,
and my dad would love that.
- That's great.
- Tyler, thank you very much.
Hey, man, thank you.
Niko, please step up.
Where did you
get your inspiration
for your Hornswoggler?
I wanted to make it silly,
and wacky, and funny,
but he can turn himself
really evil if you tempt him.
It seems to me like you wasted
a whole bunch of time
trying to create this body
for absolutely no reason
at all.
I think your time management
went someplace funny this week,
honey, 'cause I-I don't
really see the point
to have built these whole arms,
which just didn't work for you.
How you're applying it,
how you're sculpting the chest,
the belly,
there's so little here.
Yeah.
All right.
Its goofy,
static gaze makes it feel
like it would be
subject to gang beatings
by the Oompa Loompas
rather than being able
to successfully hunt them,
and the paint job has
all the finesse of an easter
egg coloring gone awry.
- Niko, please step back.
- Thank you.
Chloe.
So tell us about your concept.
I have a Vermicious Knid.
I thought
of these little plants
that the Oompa Loompas
are curious about,
and they have
this beauty to 'em,
but they just snatch 'em up.
I did the cowl this morning,
spent most of the morning
trying to run it,
and I couldn't make it work.
I know that you're better
than what I see here,
but what we're left with
does feel hurried
and incomplete.
That's why I spent so much time
trying to get the cowl.
Oh, it breaks my heart
when stuff like that happens.
I can't imagine
how disappointing
that must have been for you,
but I want you to know
that an Oompa Loompa would--
would step on it, and that
would be the end of him.
If you would have highlighted
and shadowed everything,
and-- and showed me
some of the layers,
it would pop out,
but you camouflaged the work
behind the moss,
and muddled the colors.
Chloe, thank you.
If you'd please step back.
Thank you.
Graham, please step up.
Graham, can you please tell us
about the concept
of your Snozzwanger?
Immediately, in the name,
I thought schnoz,
but I imagined
this sort of safari hunter
who hunts and traps
Oompa Loompas.
It's almost freaky to me
how you channeled my father
in this.
I wish my dad was here
because he would be delighted.
You knocked it out of the park.
- Well done.
- That means a lot.
Thank you.
The way that you've managed
to capture the essence
of the challenge makes me think
that we made the right decision
in saving you a few weeks ago.
- Thank you.
- On top of that,
the fact that you used
bits and pieces
to give the character a history
was a brilliant decision.
Thank you.
He's scary, and bizarre,
and he's like
a kid's nightmare.
Your mouth is like the opening
of one of those fun houses
where you go in
through the thing--
You get scared to death.
Thank you.
Graham, please step back.
Great job.
The judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you'd please
head back to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
Thank you.
All right, judges,
let's talk about
the looks
we like the most tonight.
Let's start with Tyler.
Head to toe,
it was really stellar.
On top of looking cool,
it worked really cool.
It came out
and performed excessively well
through a very thick piece,
which is not
the easiest thing to do.
And the Oompa Loompa hair,
he was very obedient
with his challenge,
so that's what won me over.
All right,
let's move on to Graham.
Looked like it could
eat the Oompa Loompas,
and it was playful,
and it really
fit the challenge.
I do like the fact
that it is childlike
and it is whimsy.
He was obviously
a big fan of my father's book
'cause he knew
about Snozzberry bait.
Now you see someone
who really knows
the source material
takes advantage of it.
I love that.
All right, let's talk about
the looks we like the least.
Let's start with Niko.
He saw how badly
these body appliances came out,
and he just kept goin' with it?
That's just dreadful.
He didn't know
when to say "When" and stop.
And this deep in the game,
very concerned about bad
decision-making on that level.
He was leaning
towards an alien,
more like an ET.
To me, that doesn't belong
in a jungle.
All right,
let's talk about Chloe.
It lacked
a sense of familiarity.
It was so unique
as a design choice
that I didn't understand
what I was supposed
to think that that was.
Design-wise, it still
looks like the prostitute cousin
of Madame Marjory Trash Heap
from Fraggle Rock.
Like, it's not
a working concept.
I can't imagine how
devastating that must have been
for her to have
every single thing she did
completely flop this week.
Okay, judges.
Have you made your decisions?
- Yes.
- Let's bring them back out.
Glenn, tell us
about the top looks.
Tyler, your sculpting
and paint job
were both right on,
and we were impressed
with the overall high level
of execution.
Graham,
this was a great example
of embracing the childlike
and whimsical nature
of this challenge.
It is great to see you
back on top tonight.
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
Tonight's winner is...
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
Tonight's winner is...
Tyler.
We were wowed by this beast.
It was so well done,
it almost seemed like you had
a day more than everyone else.
Thank you so much.
Holy cow.
This is amazing.
That means
a third win on a makeup
that I absolutely love,
so I want
to keep pushin' myself
to the finale.
Tyler, congratulations.
You and Graham can head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Unfortunately,
that means the two of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Niko, your concept
felt unfinished,
and your decision
to spend so much time
on the body instead of the head
was detrimental
to your character overall.
Chloe, we appreciate
that you intended
something more
with this creature,
but what little makeup
that you did manage
to put in front of us
was rough and unfinished.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Chloe.
We know you're talented,
but the other artists put out
some great work this week,
and what you gave us
just wasn't enough.
That means Niko,
you are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Chloe, all the best of luck.
You'll do really well.
You're a really good
makeup artist.
- Thank you.
- Chloe, I am so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
It's really been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you
for all the opportunities.
It's been amazing.
Good luck, Chloe.
I know I have talent.
Today just wasn't my day.
- Aw, man.
- Oh.
I live and breathe makeup.
Just it wasn't enough.
You're a good artist,
and this is not
the end of the road for you.
I'm proud of myself.
I have no words to explain
how inspired I've been
by the people that
I've been surrounded with.
This has been
a once-in-a-lifetime experience.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net