I couldn't be more pleased
with this makeup.
I think it was
a really huge mistake.
It's killer.
Previously onFace Off...
13 talented makeup artists
competed
in a monstrous challenge.
Tyler's icy dragon soared
to the top for the win,
and Daniel was sent home.
Now, 12 artists remain,
and tonight they face their
most electric challenge yet.
- Rock and roll.
- Oh, yeah.
But some will crash and burn.
I'm not seeing goat.
- It's like a smiling kitty cat.
- Okay.
I am having, like, the worst
panic attack in the world.
Cat and Niko's mold
is going to weigh
more than both of them combined.
We're really taking
our chances on this.
_
If we don't
have a full bodysuit,
what are we gonna have?
Just a face?
This character is a vision.
This thing would never last
through a day of shooting.
Rock and Roll, Hoochie Coo.
In the end, only one
will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan Professional
Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Face off!
Welcome toFace Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- Hey, Tess.
- Hey, Niko.
- How do you feel?
- You know.
The last one was pretty hard
for the both of us.
I'm definitely confused.
I feel like
I'm second-guessing everything.
It doesn't feel good
being in the bottom.
Next time it's the top.
Yeah.
Next time.
I've been off my game
a little bit,
so if I can really pull it
together this challenge,
I'll be able to prove myself.
Ladies.
Thank you, sir.
Ooh.
- Holy...
- Not too bad.
- That's a cool idea.
- Holy crap.
We walk in the lab today,
and we see these amazingly
crazy motorcycles,
and Patrick Tatopoulos
is standing right there.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Well, as you can see,
today's foundation challenge
is inspired by motorcycles,
so who better to judge
than Face Off's resident
bike expert Patrick Tatopoulos?
- Hello, guys.
- Hey.
I'm extremely excited.
I'm a huge fan of his work,
and I think he's just amazing.
It's great to have you
back on the show.
- Thank you.
- All right, let's get to this.
Some of Hollywood's most
memorable characters
look great on a motorcycle,
whether it's
comic book hero Batman
or even supernatural creatures
like Ghost Rider.
So with that in mind,
your foundation challenge is to
choose one of these motorcycles
and create the badass character
that rides it.
- Yeah.
- Nice.
So, Patrick, as the judge
of today's challenge,
what will you be looking for
in their final makeups?
You're gonna create creatures
but never forget
what they're sitting on.
The bikes are your clue to
the world the riders come from.
Look at them
in detail, color, shapes.
Make something
people will remember.
We have an important prize
on the line.
The winner of today's challenge
will earn immunity
and cannot be eliminated
this week.
On my go, I want you to choose
a bike and get to work.
You have two hours,
and your time...
starts... now.
- Whoo.
- Mine, mine, mine, mine, mine.
- Got it.
- You.
My character
is a female road warrior
in a postapocalyptic society.
You know,
after looking at the bike,
I'm going to keep it
kind of dingy and gritty.
I'm totally going
with a Mad Max theme.
I got the yellow
almost Vespa-looking bike.
I'm gonna try and do,
like, a graphic-looking
Bumblebee fairy kind of thing.
I've given her a bald cap.
So I want it to be like
she paints on her head
to emulate the bike.
I picked
the fluorescent green bike.
I feel like I could do
a really neat body paint
using the colors of the bike,
so it would be very black,
very green, so she'll be like an
alien-esque, sexy, badass biker.
I ended up
with a vintage road bike.
He's been riding it
for a long time
and doesn't
really stop riding it.
I'm a big fan of aqua colors.
I like to sponge paint and model
with them and really layer 'em.
I think I was the last one to
choose the big train over there.
I'm going for a crazy conductor
who lures passengers on
and takes them away
to some crazy place
that no one wants to be.
You got five minutes left.
Time's up, everybody.
Brushes down.
- Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
- Hey, Tyler.
- Hello.
All right, tell us
about your character today.
So this bike
is like a giant train,
so it kind of inspired me
to do this,
- like, crazy conductor character.
- What is she holding there?
She's holding a ticket to hell.
Oh, a ticket to hell.
Fantastic.
- Wanna jump on?
- Look, a prop.
The character is great.
The idea of a train
is really fantastic.
My character
is an alien humanoid.
She had this bike custom-made
based on her natural
alien markings.
It feels very ghostly,
- and I love that.
- Yeah.
I think
it's a beautiful execution.
It's very slick.
The paint job is really cool.
Thank you.
He was a demon
who fell in love with the bike.
Because it's
his prized possession,
the bike stays clean,
and he just lets himself go.
Your character is
very realistic, very dark,
and the bike is almost silly,
but you know what?
- It's a beautiful piece.
- Thank you.
I wanted to make a badass queen
- that would go with my bike.
- Mm-hmm.
I wanted to bring in
some elements of the copper
in the fingernails
to match the motorcycle.
The motorcycle feels
very tribal to me,
and you brought at lot of that
in the character as well,
like the mix of colors
through the copper tones.
It marries
really well together.
My character--
she's taken on this persona
of, like, the Bumblebee Racer.
You didn't
put hair on her head.
There is something very simple
and slick about the motorcycle,
which translated by that.
That to me is the best thing.
I would even have pushed it
a little sleeker even.
Looking around,
it's again anybody's game.
Everybody has amazing talent
and interesting concepts.
Getting immunity would let me
create an amazing character
without the stress
of the competition,
which would be really awesome.
All right, Patrick,
what did you think
of the creations today?
I loved them all, seriously.
Thank you.
All right, who created
your favorite looks today?
Tanner, great job
for the paint.
Absolutely bold and strong
and stark lines.
Thank you very much.
Daran, you brought the road
warrior to another level.
That tribal look
really works for me.
Thank you.
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of this challenge is...
Daran.
- Nice.
- Awesome.
Thank you.
I love your choice of color,
and the whole character together
was very much in symbiosis
with the bike.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
That's awesome.
Daran, congratulations.
You have earned immunity
in the next spotlight challenge.
The immunity
gives me the chance
to go a little more bold
and extreme,
which is what
this season is about.
All right, Patrick,
thank you so much
- for being here with us.
- It was great.
I'm glad I was here today
with you guys.
You guys are amazing.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
All right, guys,
I will see you tomorrow
for your next
spotlight challenge.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
Thank you.
Oh, wow.
I like this already.
We're walking into the lab,
and I see McKenzie and Glenn
and all of these really amazing
guitars, and I'm so excited.
This looks like it's gonna
be an awesome challenge.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
Some say that there is no
bigger influence to pop culture
than rock and roll.
- Oh, yeah.
Legends like Chuck Berry
and Elvis Presley,
bands like the Beatles and U2
have used music to inspire,
unite, and shape society.
And none of it
would have been possible
- without an electric guitar.
- None of it.
Which brings us to
your next spotlight challenge.
The best guitar players
in the world are so good,
it's almost as if they're
one with their instrument.
So working in teams of two,
your spotlight challenge
is to select
one of these amazing guitars
and create an extreme
rock star character
that has literally fused
with their guitar.
- Nice.
- That's cool.
This is awesome.
I love music, so I'm stoked.
All right, now, Glenn,
you're a musician.
You've even designed
a custom guitar for Lady Gaga.
What will you be looking for
in the final makeups?
I'm going to focus on just
how clever each of you are
at integrating your instrument
with your model.
Take advantage
of the extremely unique designs
of these instruments
and incorporate their shapes,
colors, and even their
personalities into your designs.
All right, you will be working
together in teams of two,
but this time, you get to decide
who you're going to work with.
Oh.
So go ahead
and choose your new bandmate.
Instantly,
everyone couples off real fast.
Tess and I are the last ones,
and we don't have a partner,
so we're together.
It's me and Matt.
We don't really know
how each other work,
so it's gonna be interesting.
All right, guys, it's time
to select your guitars.
Cat and Niko, you're up first.
- The first red one?
- Yeah.
Okay.
All right, guys,
get started on your designs.
I'm gonna stop by later on with
my dad to see how you're doing.
Good luck, guys.
Thank you.
We just
make these more angular.
I'm feeling good
about this challenge
because Tanner and I have really
wanted to work together.
Our concept for this rock star
is a red and black queen
of shredding.
We want to hide these shapes all
throughout this makeup,
so we're gonna do this mohawk
with vacuform pieces that are
the shape of the guitar,
and Tanner's gonna
sculpt out the cowl.
In that will be more hidden Vs
and then guitar picks
for the nails.
I love that idea.
- Standard grain pattern.
- This part here.
George knows
that I have immunity.
I'm not sure
if he's nervous or scared,
but I'm not gonna let him down.
I'm a little confused
how we're going to integrate
the clear guitar
into our character.
I've always wanted
to do a makeup
where the face is actually
on the neck area,
so we're gonna get rid
of the model's face
and make our own face
down under the chin.
Can you picture
her lips right here?
- Yeah.
- This is her head.
This is cool.
Our concept
is a heavy metal goddess.
It's a complete transformation
kind of thing.
The wood and the crystals
are trying
to take this character over.
Let's get clay.
Our concept for our character
is a punk rock kid
that makes a deal
with the devil,
and the devil
ends up turning him
into this demonic
guitar rock god.
All right,
we've got this, Niko.
We decided to sculpt
a full bodysuit,
so she start working
on the face.
I start working on the cowl,
chest, and back piece.
Niko and I are boyfriend
and girlfriend,
but we also work together a lot.
To be able to share
this whole experience with Niko,
it's priceless.
You know on my team
who's in charge.
Cat.
Cat, yes.
I was gonna say Cat.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Here to do our walkthrough.
So remind us again
which guitar you picked.
We picked this guitar.
The guitar makes me
think of Rockabilly,
and Tess thought it would
be fun to do a rocker billy.
- Billy goat.
- So we're doing a goat man
rocker who's starting
to fuse into his guitar.
I'm not seeing goat right away.
Okay.
There's a jowl on the goat
which you don't have here.
It's like you have
a very human form.
What about the nose?
To me it's like
a smiling kitty cat.
Okay.
Our design is risky,
and I don't want to be
on the bottom again.
Dude, I don't know what to do.
That's okay.
We'll figure it out.
He said that it
looks like a cat.
- It'll be all right.
- Oh.
I have never had
so much anxiety in my life.
Shit! Shit!
Tess has been having
a really hard time emotionally.
She's letting
the stress get to her.
Matt, I'm so sorry.
I'm having, like,
the worst panic attack
- in the world right now.
- Just calm down.
It's overwhelming me.
I can't really breathe,
and there's no time
to take a break,
but I kind of need
to take a break
before I just
absolutely lose it.
I'm having, like, the worst
panic attack in the world.
Coming up...
_
What are we gonna have,
just a face?
We're really taking a big
chance with Daran's design.
I am very worried.
- It is genuinely unique.
- Wow.
Rock And Roll, Hoochie Coo.
Our challenge
is to pick a guitar
and create the rocker
that is literally
becoming fused with it.
We want to do
a rocker billy goat.
Tess is upset about the advice
from Mr. Westmore.
Mr. Westmore tells us
that the face that I'm making
isn't very goatlike.
It's much more catlike.
I'm having, like, the worst
panic attack in the world.
I feel really bad
that I'm having this meltdown
in the middle of us
needing to finish our sculpt.
I don't know
what's going on with Tess,
but right now
we're not looking so good.
Yeah, we sort of have
this psychedelic style guitar.
- Interesting.
- Almost a paisley, isn't it?
- It's got paisley.
- Yeah.
So we're thinking of, like,
psychedelic acid trip.
Our concept is a trippy hippie,
where as he's jamming out
on his guitar,
he's becoming one with it,
and it's also distorting
his features.
And then we're just gonna try
to have this paisley design
trail down one of the arms.
That's a great idea
incorporating
the paisley into it.
How are you planning
on painting this?
Are you gonna cut a stencil?
I think cutting
a stencil's a good idea.
- Yeah.
- Wow.
Look at that coloring in there.
- The detail.
- Oh, yeah.
Our character
is a demon rock star.
He is literally
becoming his guitar,
so I'm incorporating
that crackle texture
that's in our guitar
onto the face.
The detail that you're doing,
do it deeper than that.
Oh, yeah.
This is an ideal place
- to put your base color on.
- Okay.
Put your red over the top,
and it'll pick up
- just like the guitar is.
- Oh, yeah.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
We also are gonna incorporate
those clear plastic pieces
as kind of, like,
the pectoral muscles and--
And using that little hint
of silver around it.
- Great.
- Good luck to you.
- Good luck, guys.
Thank you.
All right, guys,
we're heading out.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
The competition
is just weighing down on me,
and I just wish
that I could get it together.
Matt and I
are running out of time.
_
No.
What do you need me to do?
- Just focus on the guitar stuff?
- Yeah.
After Tess comes back in,
I tell her to take some time
cleaning up on the chest piece.
I'm gonna work on getting
the face a little more goatlike
and then get it ready
for molding.
We can make it rock.
Don't worry.
Matt's being really supportive.
He gives me
my time to calm down.
I think it's done.
It looks friggin' beautiful.
Let's mold it.
We're getting down
to the end of the day.
Let's mold this thing.
Having the face on early
means tomorrow I can focus
on getting that cowl done.
After I take over the face, I
sculpted the chin, the lip area,
and some of the sides
of the face
to try to bring in more
of the goat elements.
All right, I'm gonna
go get this molded them.
- Hey.
- Where'd it go?
High five.
Come on.
- Gonna get it done on time?
- I don't know.
Oh, we only have 21 minutes.
Yeah, I'm just gonna get
another coat on it.
I know we're not gonna
get these ready for foam today.
At least if we can get
these both molded tonight,
they'll be ready to go
in the morning.
After you get another layer
on this, can you come help me?
Yep.
Totally.
Tess is a little worried,
but I think as long
as I stay calm
and keep a positive attitude,
we'll be okay.
That's time, people.
We're just gonna do
what we have time to do.
There's no time to stress out
about what ifs.
Day two of the challenge,
I want to get these molds done
so that we have time
to get enough paisley out
to cover an arm.
I run back to open up
the face mold.
Cool, thanks.
And Tanner is cleaning up
the cowl sculpture
so that we can start
molding it.
I'm really excited
at the way it's looking.
I think that's cool.
I like it.
Niko and I give ourselves
two hours to finish sculpting
before we start
molding that thing.
It's a lot to mold
because everything is connected.
Graham, do you think
we should chop the horns?
It would make your mold
a lot easier.
I know in a perfect world,
I would cut the horns off
and do a two-piece mold,
but we don't have time for that.
Holy fuck.
Cat and Niko's mold
is going to weigh
more than both of them combined.
Like, I hope
that they can get this done.
_
We're really taking
our chances on this.
We didn't want to take time
molding the horns,
molding the bodysuit,
and we decided
let's just trust ourself
and do this.
Are you doing the single layer
on the body, a double layer?
- Double layer and that's it.
- Okay.
And the parts were gonna
be here or on this one?
The clear plastic parts.
They're gonna be on this one.
- On this one?
- Yeah.
In this makeup, we're going to
make a dome from clear elements
to cover up the model's face.
How many clear parts are there?
- Just this one?
- Six.
Six clear parts.
Where is she looking out of?
- The top part.
- The dome.
As I'm sculpting,
I put the plastic into the clay
and sculpt around it,
and then I've got to
pull the plastic out later,
so we can mold this thing.
- This piece goes here.
- Yep.
I don't see any shapes
of the guitar on Daran's design,
and I'm a little worried.
We really have to make sure
that the vacuform pieces
fit into the foam
because that's
the guitar element.
It has to work.
We'll make it work.
This one here.
Nice, dude.
Cat and I--
we're working great,
going as fast as we can,
but we still have to open
the mold and then clean it.
We're trying to open it,
trying to go as slow as we can.
- You got it.
- Is that the--
- the front's coming off?
- Yeah.
Or is it the back?
The whole thing's
coming out with it.
- There she goes.
- Boom.
It just opens really easy,
really fast.
Beautiful.
Oh, like butter.
_
We're starting
to open the other side.
_
We were risking ourself
when we decided to mold it
with the horn.
If the mold locks, we'll really
have problems with this.
_
If we don't
have a full bodysuit,
what are we gonna have,
just a face?
_
I think it's one of the biggest molds
that we have done together.
We were risking ourself
when we decided
to mold it with the horns.
If it locks, we can really have
problem with this,
so we're really
taking our chances.
_
All right.
All right. Got it.
So it's a miracle.
We end up cleaning out
and finishing
our molds early.
I think everyone in the shop was
kind of holding their breath,
waiting to see if we could
really pull it off.
- Oh, yeah.
- Whoo!
And we did it.
Biggest mold in the house.
Originally, our character was
just gonna have a clear plate
on his chest, but I figured
that's going too simple.
I'm pretty sure the judges
are gonna want to see
something else under there.
- Take some L200 for ribs...
- Okay.
...and then put this over.
I begin to fabricate
his clear heart,
some other internal organs,
which look mechanical
like our guitar,
which I can put together all
under that plastic sheet,
which will make it
look amazing.
Liking this already.
Yep.
Hey, what are you guys
doing over here?
It looks pretty interesting.
I'm trying to make
some paisley.
- Okay.
- And I'm trying to just
make it look, like, you know--
like I can sculpt.
Corinne traces the design of the
paisley onto a piece of paper,
so we're able to trace
those drawings with the clay,
which is making creating these
patterns a little bit easier.
I'm looking at our design,
and I'm like,
if this doesn't read right,
it is gonna look like
a big mess of nothing.
Come with me, children.
Girl!
Tess has been working on
the horns most of the morning,
but she's just about ready
to get molding.
Hey, looking pretty cool.
Do you like how it, like,
is a horn that turns
into the fret bars?
- Yeah.
- Cool.
Now that I have these forms
sculpted, I find poster board,
and I make a box mold
out of that,
and I pour it up
out of silicone,
and I've just got to wait
for it to set up now.
Graham, what time is it?
It's 23 to the end
of the world.
Once it's finished,
I pour rigid foam into my mold.
In about ten minutes,
I have a horn.
There you go.
I am a little worried
'cause I think that our design
is starting to go
way too simple.
Time.
Brushes down!
But I think once
all the pieces come together,
it's going to look really fun.
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab
and one hour for last looks.
Close.
It's a big prosthetic piece.
Niko has to spend a lot of time
seaming and patching
this monster.
But because everything
is in one piece,
we don't have any edges
that are gonna show.
- Where are the horns?
- In the bucket.
Oh, yeah.
Matt and I only have
two pieces to do today--
a face and a chest piece--
so they need to be flawless.
We want our application
to be really solid
and a good paint scheme going
for the judges.
- Are you excited?
- I am.
Me too.
- Hello, how are you?
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi, how's it going?
- Good.
First with our model,
we apply a bald cap,
and we place the cowl and
make sure everything lines up
with his neck and he can move.
***
Me and Tyler are
like the dynamic duo.
We just know what we want,
and we get things done.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
Like a glove.
Like a head glove.
We really, really, really got
to get that face stuck down.
So our trick is to put a plastic
bag over the model's head,
so we can slip the cowl on.
It goes on a lot easier,
so there's no tension.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
- We got the mouth perfect.
George and I are trying to judge
our time wisely.
We've got the dome pieces
and all these plastic pieces
that have to go on the model.
We want to make sure she can
breathe and have an open view.
So I have these vacuform pieces
that I made for the mohawk,
and I have to paint them
and get them ready
to be applied onto our cowl.
And it's an integral part
of our makeup
because that V-shape
is our guitar.
Niko and I have a lot to do.
We have a lot more painting, and
we need to get him in wardrobe
and get his nails on.
We've really got to move it
if we want to get
this character together.
I'm a little bit worried
because we're definitely
not as "Rock and Roll"
as everything else is looking,
but George and Daran,
I don't even know what that is.
It looks like a mushroom
with a fishbowl on it.
25 minutes.
This is not working at all,
man.
I am very worried
because it's way different
from everybody else.
It's like, oh, my God.
We're, like, so different.
All right, guys, it's time.
We're really taking a big
chance with Daran's design,
and Daran has immunity,
I don't,
so if the judges don't like it,
I'm going home for sure.
It sucks to be
in that position.
Coming up...
I'm out of options.
All I can do at this point is
hope to God they don't come off.
This character
as a whole is a vision.
I mean, the thing would never
last through a day of shooting.
Let's do it.
Here's the glue.
We get to last looks.
We've got to get
the LEDs glued in,
glue in the vacuform pieces.
That's gonna
take a while to stick.
And if these things
don't stay or fit right,
that's gonna
ruin the whole makeup.
Okay, here we go.
You think she's good on black?
Maybe shade
the in-between areas.
We definitely need to hammer
home this paint job
because right now
she's pretty much red.
Chloe and I
are scrambling around,
I'm gluing like crazy,
everything's a blur.
- Right there, yeah.
- Turn it on now.
Yeah.
String's not sticking?
It's 'cause I keep
pushing on him.
_
It already fell off once.
The horn pops off,
and it's got me really worried.
I'm out of options.
All I can do at this point
is hope to God
they don't come off again.
15 minutes, guys.
Okay, guys.
Time's up.
Mission accomplished.
For the first time,
I'm not really afraid
of anything.
They asked for a rock star,
and we're gonna give it to them.
Welcome to theFace Off
reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
But first let's say hello
to your talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Make-Up
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening, guys.
- Hey, Glenn.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
Rock out, guys.
Creature and concept designer,
Neville Page.
- Hello, everyone.
- Hi, Neville.
This week
your spotlight challenge
was to choose a guitar
and create
the extreme rock star character
that has literally
fused with it.
So let's take a look
at your rock stars.
There is nothing else I could
think to put in that thing.
We're both feeling good because
we both love the character.
Ours is the only one
where we decided
to go whimsical and silly.
I just don't know
if the judges are gonna love
how literal we took it.
I think
she's very rock and roll.
There's no way the judges
can't see the V-shaped guitar
everywhere in that makeup.
Everything looks awesome.
I'm so happy.
I'm hallucinating looking at it,
so if that's happening for me,
I'm hoping it's gonna happen
for the judges.
This is the biggest thing Niko
and I have ever made together.
It's exactly what I envisioned
as soon as I saw the guitar.
This is my demonic
punk rock guitar god.
She looks great, but I'm
a little nervous about it
'cause Daran has immunity, so if
anything goes wrong with this,
it's not gonna be him,
it's gonna be me.
Judges, time to take
a closer look at our rockers.
Wow.
Lot of stuff going on.
- Yeah.
- I like this.
Like, seeing through a chest
shape into instrumentation
that's just integrated
to the inside.
- That's cool in there.
- Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
- This is gorgeous.
- Uh-huh.
All the tones they picked
are exactly the right balance
to get this skin tone.
These are kind of wonky,
aren't they?
Do me a favor,
shake your head around.
- Go yes and no.
- Yep.
- Oh, boy.
- Whoop.
- Oh!
- Fuck! Damn.
I don't even want to look
at the judges right now.
If it can't hold up to simply
saying yes or no with his head,
that's a serious problem.
Those damn horns.
They're gonna
kill me in the end.
Who made your favorite
guitar-infused rock star tonight?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
- Go yes and no.
- Yep.
- Oh, boy.
- Fuck! Damn.
That's a serious problem.
I don't even want to look
at the judges right now.
*** that shape.
It just doesn't feel
very integrated.
- Do you think they like that?
- I don't know.
- I think this is bitchin'.
- Yeah, it's great.
- Thanks.
- Wonderful.
Thanks.
From the front view,
all we have really is a demon.
Yeah.
Could you turn
all the way around, please?
Oh, that's cool.
This is where
it comes together.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
- This is freaky.
- Yeah.
I don't understand
what this is.
I think there's a lot that we have
to hear about the story of this.
- Thank you.
- Cool. Thanks.
Okay, the judges
have scored your creations.
Let's find out
what they thought.
Niko, Cat,
Graham, and Corinne,
you guys are safe this week.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you.
The rest of you were the best
and the worst this week.
Now, the judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Tyler and Rashaad,
please step up.
Tell me about your concept
and how you integrated
your guitar
into your character.
We picked the guitar
with the crackle design.
He wanted to join a band,
so he sold his soul
to the devil.
And he became
part of the guitar.
I like your aesthetic approach
very much.
The thing I like the most
is your taking elements
from the guitar
and making them internal.
- Thank you.
I think this
is a really cool makeup.
Very impressive.
Beautiful sculpting work
on that face piece.
The paint job is beautiful.
I took a close look
at the guitar,
and it looks like
it is the same textures.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Tyler and Rashaad,
please step back.
- Thank you.
Matt and Tess.
Please tell us the concept
and whose basic design this was.
I came up with the concept
of the Rockabilly Goat.
I sculpted the face
and the horns.
Matt sculpted the body.
I painted
pretty much everything,
and then Tess helped me in
last looks to finish up stuff.
It looks like a cross between
Gary Busey and Ron Perlman.
Just a little silly.
You did a really nice paint job
on the arms.
You should have done that on
the face too and on the chest.
I happen to like what you did
with the character conceptually,
but it feels like
you're sticking this stuff on
in the most obvious of ways.
It's a guitar
painted onto a guy,
and it lacks the complexity
and cleverness
that I was looking for,
but none of that bothers me
so much as the instability
of the horns.
Thing would never last
through a day of shooting.
Matt and Tess,
you can head back.
Thanks, man.
Tanner and Chloe, you're up.
Tell us about the concept
and how the guitar
influenced your design.
She's the dark lord
of shredding.
'Cause our guitar shape was very
simple and angular and powerful,
we wanted to make sure
that all of her features
were very sharp and angular.
The body of the guitar
is what creates her mohawk.
Chloe sculpted the face.
I sculpted the cowl, and then
we painted everything together.
It's a real striking image,
but it's the idea that I like.
It's not the execution.
By widening the head so much
and having the black makeup
around her eyes,
it really makes her look like
a small head
inside of a big frame.
My problem with this is
in the angularity on the face.
They're just such hard lines
on the guitar.
It's very angular,
and we were trying
to keep our lines the same.
Once you try to start doing
hard surfaces in flesh,
they've got to make sense.
They have to be scales
or plating or armor
or a helmet.
For me, this makeup is just
a little boxy and a little busy.
I'm just not thrilled
with this one.
Tanner and Chloe,
please step down.
Thank you.
_
George and Daran,
please step up.
Can't wait to hear this story.
This is our heavy metal
goddess of rock and roll.
Upon her journey,
she comes across this guitar
with no known origin.
The guitar is
a mystical element
and will assume any soul
that lays their fingers upon it.
I am thoroughly impressed
with this makeup design.
It is genuinely unique.
Where is
your instrument integrated?
We didn't want to go literal,
so we wanted to implement
the elements of the guitar
like the crystal and the wood,
so it blends into the character.
This is the vines coming up,
and then, this is part
of the metal guitar.
Wow.
Rock And Roll, Hoochie Coo.
Who did what on this makeup?
Daran did the design
on the face up to the skull.
In my design, I integrated
the vines, like, wrap around.
And then, I did all
of the blue and pearl paint,
and George did the wood paint.
Integrating that blue
in the eyes
and the blue glowing
in the chest,
really beautifully done.
She is bitchin', awesome,
and totally groovy.
- Thank you.
- The eyes that are glowing,
is that this character's face?
- Basically, yes.
- A beautiful piece, guys.
- Thank you.
Daran and George,
please step back.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you would please head back
to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
All right, judges,
let's start with the looks
you liked the most this week.
How about Rashaad and Tyler?
Integration-wise,
it was probably the best
out of all the makeups.
Using guitar components
internally
for the finished character
was just genius.
And the fact
that they replicated
the face of the guitar so well,
the texture and the colors.
And the facial piece
was beautifully crafted.
Let's move on
to Daran and George.
Truly a very unique aesthetic.
And I love that there's
no conspicuous guitar elements
just jammed in,
sticking out at an angle,
and the idea of the element
and the character
in a stage of metamorphosis--
it's so high concept.
All right, let's move on
to the looks we liked the least.
Let's start with Tess and Matt.
The Rockabilly Goat
was a goofy idea.
If they're gonna go there,
it better be a damn good goat.
It just seems like an excuse
to not do something really good.
Matt did a majority of the
paint, which was inconsistent,
but Tess was in charge
of the horns,
and they were so poorly done.
That's why I asked him
to say yes and no
and shake his head
side to side.
If it can't get through that,
it's a completely
nonfunctioning makeup.
All right, let's move on
to Tanner and Chloe.
At a glance,
theirs was very strong,
but they overdid the sculpt,
and the paint job made it look
synthetic and plastic.
It was too red,
too graphic, too busy,
and it was poorly done
all around the ears.
They didn't try
to cover up the seams.
All right, judges,
have you made your decision?
- Yeah.
- Let's bring 'em back out.
Glenn, tell us
about the top teams.
Rashaad and Tyler, we love
the '70s vibe of this makeup,
and we think
you made a great choice
integrating
the see-through panel.
Daran and George,
this was an eye-catching makeup,
just filled
with interesting ideas,
and it is unlike anything
we've ever seen before.
Okay, which team
came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Okay, which team
came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Daran and George.
Nice.
The way that you managed to
blend so many different elements
into a single makeup
is almost unfathomable.
An impressive display, guys.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
Great job,
but we can only have one winner.
Glenn?
The winner tonight is...
- Daran.
- Awesome!
The head was fascinating.
We could not
take our eyes off of it.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
That means a lot.
I feel like I'm on Cloud Nine.
It's a pretty good place to be.
I'm here to win
this whole competition,
so I'm just gonna
keep doing what I do.
- Daran, congratulations.
- Thank you very much.
You, George, Rashaad,
and Tyler are all safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you, guys.
Unfortunately,
that means the rest of you
are on the bottom this week, and
one of you will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom teams.
Tess and Matt, though we did
like parts of your character,
overall it lacked complexity
and therefore missed the mark.
Tanner and Chloe,
we liked the graphic statement
of your makeup, but you made
some design decisions
that just did not add up
for us.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Tess.
We thought that the biggest miss
was your concept.
It was just a mismatch
for the challenge.
That means,
Matt, Tanner, Chloe,
you guys are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Tess, you have a lot of talent,
but the competition
this season is so tough.
Tess, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
It's been so great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- Bye, sweetie, good luck.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
- Good luck, Tess.
I had a tough time
with this challenge,
but I'm proud of what Matt
and I came up with.
- It's me.
- Oh.
I've learned to be
more confident in myself.
I'm gonna miss you.
So when I get back home,
I'm gonna make
some amazing creatures.
I think now
that I've experienced this,
I can tackle the world.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net