This makeup
doesn't really work.
It's really quite beautiful.
You have to turn your game
up at this point.
Previously, onFace Off...
Tyler's wall-crawling mutant
brought him
an astounding fourth victory.
Oh, my God.
And Graham was sent home.
With only five artists
remaining,
tonight, they face a challenge
of bionic extremes.
It's the future
that brings us here today.
This is right up my alley.
And the competition explodes
with a dramatic fight
to the finish.
- It's gonna come apart.
- Fuck.
I'm really worried,
because if I don't have this,
I'm not gonna have anything.
I'm looking around, everybody
seems to be going larger.
This challenge
is so far out of my league.
- You have blown me away.
- I'm not really a big fan.
This is the best thing
that you have showed us.
In the end, only one
will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who'll be the next great name
in movie magic?
Face Off!
Welcome toFace Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- Five of us, man.
- Final five.
You can almost taste the final.
We're that much closer
to the finale,
and everyone remaining has wins,
and I don't.
So I just need to get into
that zone and focus on the goal.
All right, guys, let's see
what our next challenge is.
Everybody's on their A game,
so I can't make anymore mistakes
because that'll be
my ticket home.
Where are we today?
- Union Station.
- Oh, nice.
Whoa.
Oh, this is big.
We are at Union Station,
and it's just beautiful.
I can smell the old furniture
and the wood.
It's like history.
I'm smelling history here.
Hey, guys.
Welcome to Union Station
in downtown Los Angeles,
known as the last
of the great railway stations.
This historic transportation hub
continues to serve
over 60,000 passengers a day.
- Mm.
- It's also been
a popular filming location
for movies like Drag Me To Hell,
The Dark Knight Rises,
and the futuristic sci-fi
thriller, Blade Runner.
And it is the future
that brings us here today.
- Nice.
- Okay.
This is the old ticketing room,
and once upon a time,
it was the station's
bustling nerve center,
but its ticketing agents
have since been replaced
with machines.
Now, with the onslaught
of machines handling tasks
that were once
exclusively done by humans,
one can't help but wonder,
how long
until we're all replaced?
Now, next to me are props
representing
various occupations.
We have a surgeon, photographer,
hairdresser,
firefighter, chef,
and construction worker.
You're spotlight challenge
is to select one of them
and create the robot that has
taken that professional's place
- in the workforce.
- Nice.
Awesome.
We get to do futuristic robots.
This is right up my alley.
Tyler, you're up first.
Surgeon.
Photographer.
Firefighter.
The construction worker.
Hairdresser.
Before you begin your designs,
there's just one more thing
I need to tell you.
Each of your robots must display
an extreme functional advantage
over their human counterparts.
_
I'm slightly terrified,
because I know
a robot that has
multiple functions
is gonna be a lot of work,
and this is not my thing.
It's time to start
working on your designs,
and I want to remind you,
do not go for the obvious.
Make bold choices that will
surprise and impress our judges.
Good luck.
- Thank you.
- See you later.
I have firefighter.
It's actually something I
thought about being
for a long time.
I want this character
to be very big
and be able to save the day.
I also want to incorporate
the eagle on the helmet.
There's no truck,
because this robot
can put out a fire by himself.
I'll be taking a chance
on doing
a lot of fabrication
and hardly any makeup.
I plan on making the head
a camera, fabricated chest,
which is gonna be
a huge light on the front
because it needs to shine light
on whatever subject
that the camera's gonna be
taking a picture of.
You need a lot of time
to fabricate a robot,
and I'm not a big fabricator,
so I'm gonna sculpt everything.
I want to make
my hairdresser robot
very cool and elegant and
something pleasant to the eye.
So the concept
for my hairdresser
is a female robot.
She's gonna be stylish
and modern looking and hip.
The special feature
that my robot is gonna have
is two blowers coming
out of her breasts,
and her hands are gonna have
different fingers
with the scissors
and the nose clipper.
Each hand will have utility.
All right, guys,
let's head back to the lab.
- This is gonna be fun.
- Oh, yeah.
It's day one
of our robot challenge.
We get six hours in the lab.
We have an extra day
for this challenge.
That means I get more time
to work with the fabrication,
which tends to take
a little extra time anyway,
but the first thing I do
is sculpt the face.
I decided to cover one eye
with wires,
put two lenses in the forehead
and one over the nose
so it looks like
it has three eyes
that can rotate
and see different things.
Holy fuck, man.
What the fuck is that?
Nice.
My robot can see
the structure of a building
as well as things that might
be harmful to people.
That way,
he could replace a human.
I've worked
in a hospital setting before,
so the surgeon one
kind of screamed to me.
This surgical robot
has these little arms
that come out on both sides,
and I want it to have
a human-looking face.
So I vacuformed my model's life
cast to create a face shield.
So when it talks to people,
they're not looking
at a creepy-looking machine.
I selected
a construction worker,
and I know that I have to do
something big.
This robot is from the future,
but it's the first generation
of this kind of machine,
but he can still do the work.
I want it to have
all the cables and everything
coming on the face,
and then everything else
is just gonna
be fabricated around it.
I immediately get to work
building a face
for my futuristic
photographer robot.
I'm basically sculpting
with wood instead of clay,
and I'll be using a router
and a dremel and a hand saw
and everything else to make
this face look like a camera.
I've been a carpenter
since I've been 16.
I'm used to working with wood,
but I've never actually
used wood to do a makeup
or make a robot.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- Here for a walkthrough.
- How are you?
You left this lower jaw open,
and so it's gonna look
like a human who's wearing it.
- Mm-hmm.
- You're gonna have to keep
adding pieces to cover anything
that is skin.
Mm-hmm.
This is gonna be the face here.
- Okay.
- Is it gonna be
all basically gadgets?
Or are you working any type
of makeup in there with it?
I was playing with the idea
of a silicone face
that goes over my model.
If you do that,
I would make sure
you kind of square things off
a bit
as opposed to making it flow
like a human in there
or something.
Right, right.
How are you gonna incorporate
the aspects of hairdressing?
Her boobies
are gonna be like hairdryers,
and they suck also the hairs
that fall from the person.
- It goes--
- Okay.
Sucks it in and throws it
out in the back.
You know, the thing is,
I don't know
if this is going to sell
as a hairdryer.
You might rethink that design
a little bit.
Might be able to combine this
all into one
or something
so it comes down--
Like a blow dryer
or something--
And actually maybe take
a piece of plastic,
and then mount it in there
so you know that's a dryer.
You need to do something to--
And it's similar to a dryer
of our time, exactly.
Exactly.
Are you planning on covering
it all with this type of wiring?
No, the wire is gonna be
in this bottom part
and around the eyes.
To me, it looks like a face
that you put worms over the top
of it in these areas here.
I think you need to be
a little bit more powerful
in your bridge across here
and in your nose.
What you want to do
is make planes
as opposed to rounding off.
Otherwise, I'm afraid
it's gonna look like a person.
What you can do to maybe
get away from this human look
with the eyes and the mouth
is do a lower lip
in a separate piece, just so you
get a whole mechanical mouth,
or that's
gonna look like a person.
Okay.
All right, gentlemen,
we're heading out.
- Good luck to everybody.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
I take Mr. Westmore's advice
by taking away human form.
I distort the face.
I make it look very mechanical.
And I'm back on track.
Now it's time to mold.
I always try
to get the face first
because that's the most
important element in a makeup.
At this point,
everyone is in the mold room,
but I'm gonna spend more time
working on the changes
that Mr. Westmore told me to do.
But after I finish,
I only have a less than an hour,
and I still have to mold it.
I'm molding as fast as I can,
but I don't think
I'm gonna be able to open
and clean this
by the end of the day.
Since we have an extra day,
I think it will be worth it
to just open it tomorrow.
All right, everyone.
That's time.
My sculpture is ready
for opening tomorrow.
I feel pretty good with my face,
and I'm excited
to start working
on the other pieces.
Whoo!
Ah!
It's day two.
We have nine hours
in the lab today.
The first thing I need to do
is check the silicone
to make sure it set up so I
can pull the wood out of that
and then pour resin into it
for the face
on the robotic camera.
But right now, I need
to get sculpting on a face
so I can have a base
to attach all this stuff to.
As soon as my face piece
is ready for foam latex,
I start sculpting
the chest piece
for my construction worker.
I'm taking my time
to do a really good sculpture
so it doesn't look too similar
as last challenge.
And because we have
an extra day, maybe tomorrow
I can spend my whole day
just working on the robot suit.
I'm sculpting this chest piece
that I'm gonna incorporate
these little helping hands
coming out
that spread open the tissue
during surgery.
I'm gonna vacuform it,
so I can use this same piece
as my back.
This challenge is all about
the really smart,
quick decision, and this
is gonna help me save time.
I'm following Mr. Westmore's
advice, and my robot
is gonna have a hair blower
coming out from her chest.
Everybody's doing
all this L200 and gluing,
but the last time
I fabricated pieces,
I almost got eliminated.
At the same time,
it's kind of hard to make foam
look like metal, and I would
hate to go home now.
At least, I want to go
to the finale.
So I'm afraid sculpting
this robot is a big mistake.
Coming up...
This is so far
out of my league.
Maybe I didn't do enough.
He won't be able to move.
It's gonna come apart.
I don't have time
to do another bodysuit.
I think you really missed the mark
on this one.
You hit the right notes.
It's the second day
of the robot challenge,
and I'm sculpting
the chest piece and the cowl.
My strength is sculpting,
not really fabrication.
But foam moves like foam.
It doesn't move like metals.
So there's a big risk, but
I'll have to do what I do best.
It's got a blow dryer
on the front.
Oh, you got a blow dryer.
I hope I made
a good decision on doing this,
so hopefully, the judges
won't send me home.
With this fireman suit,
I'm using L200,
a very flexible material.
It can also be very rigid.
This fireman has vents
on his chest
that are gonna be taking
in the smoke
and putting out fresh oxygen
through the back,
and a water tank on his back
with an arm that goes over
the shoulder with a hose on it.
I really want to get
my two arms and chest done
so that all I really have
to focus on the third day
is the legs.
So to create these extremities
coming off of my robot
and the headpiece with
the vacuform face in the front,
I take PVC pipe, cut several
different sections,
and I velcro every piece
to a black spandex suit.
It's gonna be so much easier
in application, where the models
can just slip into the suits
and pull everything on.
I'm hoping the bright, white
pieces will help your eye
get rid of that black suit,
and all you see
is the form of the robot.
I'm creating, for
my robot construction worker,
an arm piece that will hold
a lot of different tools.
There you go.
So I got this idea
to fabricate quick slots
for each one of the tools.
I vacuform all these tools.
I have a drill,
a wrench, screwdrivers.
It's starting to look
really cool.
I finished the mold,
and honestly
I think it looks beautiful.
It's gonna be foam.
It's not fabricating a robot.
But I'm liking the way
it's looking.
The only thing that's
worrying me is that tomorrow
I've got to fabricate
some arms,
and I'm not sure
how they'll come out.
By end of day two, I have
all these pieces laid out
and everything pretty much
is almost covered.
And then I realize that
the mannequin I'm using
is 6' tall, and my model's 5'.
All right, guys, that's time.
I hope I didn't waste
all this time doing this suit
because I don't even know
if it's gonna fit my model.
Robot.
I don't know what to do.
I know a mistake like this
can send you home.
Yeah!
It's the third day
of the robot challenge,
and I'm gonna concentrate now
on the arm pieces and the hands.
The tools that I got
for my hairdresser,
they're very stylized combs
and scissors,
and they're actually
very cool tools.
I'm taking all the tools,
and I'm casting them in resin,
which is plastic
that's gonna be lighter
so that it won't weigh down
my model's fingers.
- Oh, nice.
- Really lightweight.
As soon as I get to the lab,
I start working
with my full-bodysuit robot.
Where is that paper that you
said that you used?
I get some advice from Rashaad
because he's the king
of fabrication.
You draw it, you cut it,
and then you put it--
- draw two.
- Okay.
It's gonna be
a little bit challenging
because it's the first
fabrication that I do
for a whole suit,
so it's very important for me
to take my time and make sure
that I can put all
the pieces together in a way
that looks cool
and it has movement.
And I want to make it
really big.
What you makin'?
I'm makin' a robot!
I'm taking advantage
of this extra day
because I have a lot to do.
I start getting everything
on the spandex suit,
start to tie in tubing
and wires
to really give the robot feel.
And I want to give the sense
that this thing
has a functioning brain,
so to create this illusion,
I glue LED light strips
to the top of the spandex cap.
So it almost looks like
a circuit board computer
on the inside,
and it looks cool.
Today, I've got to get
a helmet made for this robot,
and I've also got
to get a chest piece made,
which will reflect light
on whatever the camera's
gonna be taking pictures of.
The first thing I do is
I vacuform over a styrofoam head
so I can get a shape
of a helmet.
I cut that out, and now I need
to move on to the chest piece.
I hope I can just get it right.
Today, I need to finish
the legs, the feet,
and an arm that goes over
the shoulder.
- Is that like a hose?
- Yeah, for--
to feed the water through.
My time management
is where I need it to be,
and I need to get this armor
latexed down so I can paint it.
I'm gluing L200
onto the bodysuit.
Is that gonna be able to bend?
- Yeah.
- You sure?
- I think so.
- But you glued it all together.
So now he won't be able
to move his arms.
And Rashaad's telling me
that I kind of, like,
screwed myself.
- It's gonna come apart.
- You think so?
Yeah because
you glued it all straight.
I left some spaces
so he can move,
but I glued
the joints together.
I put a screw and a washer
so it could bend.
But you glued it all straight,
so it's not gonna be able
to bend now.
I don't have time
to do another bodysuit.
You got to leave that open,
and then I hope
you do the same thing
for the legs.
I'm really worried because, if
I don't get this bodysuit
done the right way,
I'm gonna be in trouble.
I need to fix this
or I'm going home.
Fuck.
It's day three
from our robot challenge.
He won't be able
to move his arms.
Okay.
I mistakenly glued
the robot's joints together.
Don't glue nothing there.
Don't glue nothing in the back.
Leave this all open.
And Rashaad starts
giving really good advice,
so I make sure that I unglue
all these parts
and make sure that all
his joints are free of glue
so he can actually
have some movement.
I need to fix this
so I can move on
to fabricating the helmet.
I'm making vacuform pieces
for the robot arms.
The arms are not perfect.
They're not super pristine
like I wanted it to be.
It's kind of rough
on the edges.
They're looking
like vacuform pieces,
but with a good paint job,
I'll make it work.
I'll make it happen.
A lot of times in doing armor,
people make it
bright and shiny,
but a firefighter
breaking through buildings
and knocking down doors
and having smoke
constantly on them,
it's going to be dirty.
It's gonna have scratches
where you can see
the silver metallic paint
under it.
Exactly how I was as
a little kid playing with toys,
this is how I feel
doing this robot.
So I'm in a good place.
Feeling very good today.
I've got everything done
that I wanted to do.
I've got all of the lenses
and plastic parts
and metal pieces for
my futuristic robotic camera.
Everybody else seems
to be going really large,
but all I'm doing
is a robot face,
and I'm okay with that.
This is so far
out of my league.
I don't do robots,
so we'll see what happens.
All right, guys, it's time.
I feel pretty good
about application day tomorrow.
All's I need to do is get
these things glued to the foam
and start putting
everything together.
Maybe I didn't do enough.
I could be going home
or I could be a winner.
I just don't know.
That's right.
So we get back to the house.
We're all completely worn out.
Oh, my God.
How do you guys feel?
- Worn out.
- Me too.
I'm tired.
With the stress of the
challenge and the competition,
I'm feeling mentally tired.
I'm definitely missing
my motorcycle, my girlfriend.
Daran, happy birthday.
Hey, buddy!
Happy birthday to you!
Red velvet.
Thank you, thank you.
To my surprise, my roommates
know it's my birthday.
I basically forgot
about it myself,
and they bring out my favorite,
red velvet cupcakes.
- Thank you, gents.
- Whoo-hoo!
- Final five.
We made it this far.
There's only five of us left.
So the pressure is really
on now to get to the finale,
and I'm hopin' I can make it.
- Good luck.
- Oh, definitely good luck.
So it's application day.
We have four hours in the lab,
and one hour at last looks.
I start taking the robot apart,
knowing that it's all
gonna go back on really well
if everything fits.
But I'm also nervous
that this thing
may not fit my model.
I obviously do not know
how everything's gonna turn out
until my model
tries this thing on.
So on this application,
I really need to make sure
the face piece is
glued down perfectly
because it will be holding
a lot of weight.
So I'm gonna have to put
some latex in it,
which will help the bond
of the glue,
and this should work out great.
Here they come.
You're gonna be a hairdresser
from the future.
Okay.
I'm nervous that
it's not gonna fit you
'cause it's so tall,
but we'll have to see.
So this is what you got.
I try all the armor on my model
to make sure everything fits.
Little kid's dreams.
That's exactly how I design.
Every time I design a character,
I always think to myself,
"Would my son
want to play with it?"
And I think this robot
looks like a superhero.
He looks amazing.
Oh, yeah.
This is gonna have a light.
For my construction worker,
the first thing
that I want to do
is finish that helmet.
Almost there.
I need to work as fast as I can
so I can start painting
the whole robot suit.
It's big, so it's gonna
take me a little bit of time.
Oh, that's a big gap here.
Let me see.
I don't want the judges
to be seeing any human form.
Otherwise,
it won't sell as a robot.
So I'm taking
this windshield tint,
put it on the surface
of the face.
Perfect.
And you just see
metallic reflection,
but my model
can actually see through it.
It's very good stuff.
I start zipping everything up,
popping everything on,
and everything
actually fits great.
Ah!
This thing looks like it
can actually operate.
It's amazing.
Yeah, it's perfect.
Ten minutes, guys, ten minutes!
Coming around.
I'm looking around the room
and noticing
that there are some
really strong makeups.
Beautiful.
Everybody's robots
is just lookin' amazing.
All right, guys.
It's time.
Brushes down.
There's only five of us left,
and everybody else has wins,
and I don't.
I really have to get a win,
or else there's no way
I can make it to the finale.
Coming up...
Paint job is still not there.
It's gonna look
like a silver spoon.
I don't have a clue
where I stand.
He's amazing.
I couldn't believe it
when he walked out.
He's clumsy.
His proportions
are a little wacky.
That is one of the strangest
shapes I've ever seen.
Yay, I get my corner!
We get to last looks.
We have one hour left.
The most important thing is
getting this mouthpiece glued on
and gettin' all of these lenses
and plastic parts put on
so this can look like a camera.
I've got a hot glue gun.
I've got some five-minute epoxy,
and it's just all about
attaching things now.
This little piece I found
attaches right
to the top of that.
The paint job
is still not there,
and everything's gonna look
like a silver spoon.
So I decided to go
with a faint gold wash.
I think it's working.
It's looking very stylish.
I'm getting the face shield on,
getting everything adjusted.
I'm building this thing
not knowing
how it's gonna turn out.
I really hope it's enough
for the judges.
It's pretty intense.
I'm trying to apply everything
as fast as I can,
but I'm worried if I can get
all the pieces painted and done.
I forgot the box cutter.
I got one.
Here.
I've pre-painted so much,
all I have to do
is touch up some weathering
and yellow highlights
on his back,
and he's ready to go.
Ten minutes, guys!
That's it, everybody.
That's time.
I've been pretty steady
throughout
this whole competition,
but I really have to get a win
because I definitely
want to be in the finale.
Welcome to theFace Off
reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
First, let's say hello
to our talented panel of judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
- Hello.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
- Hi, guys.
- Hi, Ve.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
- Hello.
All right, this week,
your spotlight challenge
was to select a professional
and create a robot
that has replaced them
in the workforce.
Now, I also asked
that your robots display
an extreme functional
or articulating advantage
over their human counterparts.
So let's take a look
at your creations.
From a distance, all you see
is this exoskeleton,
and it just looks like this
thing is really operating
in front of my eyes.
It looks so cool.
Everything I envisioned
has come to life.
This is my first robot that
I've ever attempted to make.
Kept it nice and clean
and robotic looking.
I'm very satisfied with it.
She's looking very slick
and beautiful.
She's looking like a freaking
robot from The Jetsons.
It looks pretty cool.
He has a good presence.
It's looking really big
and massive,
and I just want to hear
what the judges have to say.
Judges, why don't you
take a closer look
at the robotic replacements?
It makes sense functionally.
Smart thing too about
just doing the spandex bodysuit.
Just let it disappear.
Love the layers.
This is really cool.
And it's cool that he put work
under it for us to see too.
- Yeah.
- Good. Thank you.
This dude is killer.
It's actually
even better close up, huh?
Yeah.
Look at all this detail.
- Yeah.
- Wow.
I absolutely love
this flourish,
just to break it up
a little bit.
Can you turn to the side?
Look at how tight
that profile is on his head.
Can you turn
all the way around?
Plus his choice of weathering,
it gives it history.
Okay.
Thank you.
I think heartbeeps have more
complexity in the chest piece
than this thing does.
Like a lampshade.
Is it possible that something
didn't come out?
I don't have a clue
where I stand.
I'm still feeling like I didn't
do enough on this makeup,
so I'm really worried about what
the judges are gonna say.
I mean, we really
have just this face.
- This is so minimal.
- It is.
I don't do robots, so it could
very well be me going home.
Who made your favorite robot?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
This is so minimal.
We really have just this face.
Maybe I didn't do enough.
It could very well
be me going home.
This is wood.
Hmm.
Thanks.
It feels so retro accurate,
it could step off of original
Battlestar Galactica--
- Biddy, biddy, biddy.
- Mm-hmm.
It's an interesting choice.
I kind of like it there.
I think it's an attachment
for her hand.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
There's a ton of work.
All scruffy, mind you,
but every single region
has been addressed.
I love whatever this is.
I just wish he would've
explored this more.
- Thank you.
Okay, the judges would now
like to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
- Tyler, step forward.
- Okay.
Tyler, tell us how
the profession that you selected
inspired your robot design
this week.
I wanted to do something
like the surgeon of the future,
a robot that can really take on
the job of several surgeons
at once.
I think you
did a fantastic job,
particularly the construction
out of very rudimentary
elements,
of the harness that holds
that face piece
out from the face.
I think that's your
great triumph this week.
It's really cool,
and it's fun to look at.
Thank you.
She doesn't seem
to be too futuristic,
which is kind of a nice thing
in a weird kind of way
because it makes her look
a little bit more familiar.
I think she's pretty sweet,
honey.
- Nice job.
- Thank you.
What's great is you've hit
all the right notes
of what implies this
being a medical product,
and it all kind of stacks up
to being a nice,
solid character.
Thank you.
Tyler, thank you very much.
Please step back.
Daran, if you'd please
step to the center.
Can you tell us how your
profession inspired your robot?
I chose the futuristic
photographer.
I wanted to make a robotic head
that was nothing but a camera.
Definitely out of my element.
I don't make robots.
I can tell.
I'm disappointed in this.
It just doesn't have the vavoom
that all the rest of them have.
This looks like a guy
with just, like,
a little rubber vest on with
a big plate in the middle of it.
I think you really missed
the mark on this one this week.
Yeah, I don't do robots.
I'm sorry.
That right there
is your main problem this week.
Even though the robot thing
is not your bag,
focusing on the fundamental
ideas of proportion
and functionality
would've helped go a long way.
What I struggle with
is the overall silhouette
and the codpiece thing.
It turns it from a potentially
sophisticated concept
into a cartoon-like
character.
Yeah.
Daran, thank you very much.
Please step back.
Rashaad, you're up.
So tell us about the profession
and how it inspired this guy.
I always think of a firefighter
as heroic and cool,
so that's what inspired
my design.
Definitely heroic.
You sculpted and fabricated
an entire costume,
which is astonishing.
Thank you.
I think this is the best thing
that you have showed us
so far this season.
- Thank you.
- It's all about function,
what the thing does.
And that's exciting, because
that makes you really believe
that the thing was built
for a specific task,
which is exactly
what we asked you to do.
Thank you.
- He's amazing.
- Thank you.
I couldn't believe it
when he walked out.
He looks like
he's been through hell.
He looks like he's been through
a blowtorch about 40 times.
And the fact that you
spray-painted
that yellow is awesome.
You have blown me away
this week.
Thank you.
Rashaad, you can step back.
You were lookin' for that win.
You got it.
Finally.
I hope so.
Niko, please step
to the center.
Niko, tell us how your
profession inspired your robot.
I think about construction
workers, like, big and bulky,
and I wanted to create
a big machine
that is in the future, but
it's, like, the first series.
You certainly did a lot
of work this week,
but it's a bit clunky,
isn't it?
Yeah.
Could've been proportioned
a little bit more elegantly
and still looked
rough industrial.
Okay.
He does have
that kind of clunky feel,
but he's kind of fun.
I particularly like those--
what are they called, Neville?
- Hydraulic cylinders?
- Yes.
- Oh, this?
- Yes, the hydraulic cylinders.
It's a really neat little touch
that you put on him,
and I think he's kind of sweet.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
His proportions
are a little wacky.
He's got this big beluga head.
He's clumsy.
There's, like, all sorts of
weird stuff goin' on with this.
I'm not really a big fan of it,
but it's cohesive.
Okay.
Niko, thank you.
George, please step forward.
Oh, there you go.
All right, can you tell us
how your profession
inspired your robot?
Her name is V-3000.
It stands for Venus,
for the goddess of beauty.
I got inspired by high fashion.
I would go to this salon
in a minute.
- I think she's quite beautiful.
- Thank you.
I think she does
a little crossover,
'cause I see she also
has some makeup tools
on the end of her fingers.
- Oh, yeah.
- Very well done, George.
Thanks.
There's some
very elegant line work
that divides up the planes
either for access panels
or just for the sake
of making it pretty.
It's a beautiful piece.
That is one of the strangest
and most bizarre chest shapes
I've ever seen.
Using those planes
to create something
that suggests female,
that's the high point for me.
The form ideas
are near perfection.
Thanks, man.
George, thank you very much.
If you'd please step back.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
- Thank you, guys.
- Thank you.
All right, judges, let's talk
about tonight's looks.
Why don't we start with Tyler?
Tyler did an excellent job
with the colors and the shapes
conveying a piece
of medical equipment.
It feels very much
like a logical progression
from conventional
robotic attempts
that we're working with now
into the future
where it actually works
and walks around like a person,
and I think that's
a really intelligent way
to have approached this.
Yeah, and I liked the way
that he had
the human facial piece
over the top so the patient
would have something
to refer to.
All right,
let's move on to Rashaad.
This is awesome.
I couldn't believe
all the detail.
You could put that thing
in a movie right now.
There are some really
gorgeous design choices,
and as a character,
all those layers of paint
gives us a sense of history.
It's an impressive amount
of work.
All right,
let's move on to George.
George's is very well done.
For me, this was
an exercise in form.
Even though he had
the utility in the hand,
our focus was on the head
and the chest,
and it ended up
being beautiful.
I like that he used
different techniques
for the metal process.
There's silver
and gold bronzes.
There's hammered,
there's smooth,
and he made them all
go together.
What did you think
of the name V-3000?
Ah, he named it after me,
of course.
All right,
let's move on to Niko.
It felt disproportionate.
It looked like an old
boxing helmet on top of a face
that made no sense to me.
It's so clunky,
particularly
the proportion of the head
and the proportion
of the legs and pelvis.
But I loved the chest
and the detail--
those little wires that
were embedded in the design.
I think it was very successful.
Do I think it's as successful
as the other makeups this week?
I-- I don't.
I like this robot.
I don't know.
You guys are bein'
really hard on him.
You know what
was a cool detail?
He made animated
hydraulic actuators.
That was the one element
that really did say
construction equipment.
All right,
let's move on to Daran.
So disappointing.
He decides to just focus
on the head,
throw, like, a sheet of foam
over the body,
and even the head
wasn't stellar.
It's convoluted.
It's huge.
It's massive.
It makes no sense.
Even when he was defending it,
if you want to call it that,
he kind of just kept repeating
a simple sentence--
"I don't do robots."
Maybe he's not interested
in doing anything
other than what he feels
comfortable doing.
That makes you
very unemployable.
Yeah, exactly.
All right, judges.
Have you made your decisions?
- Yeah, we have.
- We have.
Okay.
Let's bring 'em back out.
Glenn, tell us
about tonight's top looks.
Tyler, there were
such cool and clever solutions
in your design that it
was really hard to believe
that this is the first time
you've tackled
this level of fabrication.
Rashaad,
your robotic firefighter
really felt like a hero,
and we loved the decision
to place that crest
around his neck.
And, George, your robot's
flowing lines and gold paint job
really made her quite elegant.
All right, Glenn, who
is the winner of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
Glenn, who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner of tonight's
challenge is...
Rashaad.
Your choices were all
so spot on this week.
This is the perfect time
to raise your game.
Thank you guys so much.
Finally got a W.
I can join the winners' circle.
And gettin' a win now definitely
gives me that extra push
and lets me know
that I do have what it takes.
- Rashaad, congratulations.
- Thank you.
You, Tyler, and George can
head back to the makeup room.
Thank you, guys.
Glenn, tell us
about tonight's bottom looks.
Actually, there was only
one bottom look
for us this week.
Daran.
It was really obvious that you
were out of your element,
and you were a bit resigned
because, as you put it,
you don't do robots.
That sentiment really worked
against you this week.
That means Niko,
you are safe and can head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you, guys.
All right, brother.
It's been fun.
Daran, it is obvious that you
are truly a huge talent.
You've shown us some beautiful
and unique designs.
We all look forward very much
to seeing what you do next.
I appreciate it.
Daran, I'm so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
It's really been great
having you here with us,
but please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- Thank you, guys.
- Good luck, Daran.
I'm a little bit sad
I didn't make it to the end.
I was right there.
I definitely wanted to go on
and win this competition.
What do you think, boys?
What do you think?
- Don't do that.
- Don't do that, bro.
- It's you, Daran?
- Yeah.
- What?
- Aw, dude.
Ah, brother.
This competition is no joke,
and I'm truly amazed
at the stuff I came up with
in the amount of time I did.
- Whoo!
- Fierce hug. Fierce hug.
Bein' here was a blast, and
if this is feelin' like a loser,
then I'm very confused
'cause I feel like a winner.
I'll always be a makeup artist.
I'm definitely
gonna design more.
I've got a lot of ideas.
This is not the end for me,
of course.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net