This is really cool.
It looks like a big blob
of Silly Putty.
You've got a beautiful piece.
Previously on Face Off...
In a season of new extremes,
15 talented makeup artists
competed in a classic
fairy-tale challenge.
Chloe's undersea beast
earned her a victory...
and Margaret was sent home.
Now 14 artists remain,
and tonight they'll face
a challenge
- of interplanetary intrigue.
- Yes!
I want to make something
that nobody's ever seen.
But some will crack
under the pressure.
I am kind of having
a hard time.
_
Please, just make a decision
and get it done.
I'm afraid that
I'm gonna make a mistake.
I need to not look at it
for a second.
- Okay.
- We don't have time
to play around.
This whole thing was
so impressive.
- You guys did some weird stuff.
- Here's the bad part--
- I'm thinking,
"I'm going home."
In the end,
only one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Face off!
Welcome toFace Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- How you doing?
- So-so.
I feel bad about Margaret
that left, you know?
Yeah, it sucked last night,
for sure.
I feel guilty,
like I'm responsible.
I took full responsibility,
but the judges made
their final decision,
and it was Margaret.
So, you know, what happened
is in the past now,
but I'm gonna try to do my best
on the next makeup
to make sure that I don't end up
on the bottom again.
- Right on.
- Thanks.
Instead of squandering
this opportunity,
I'm just gonna keep doing
what I think is right.
- Oh, my God.
- We're at this farm,
and we're walking down
this dirt road...
You first.
- ...and we walk into a cornfield.
- Whoa-ho-ho.
And this is pretty cool.
Where are we?
Oh, man.
There's this blank space
in the cornfield,
and there's McKenzie
in the middle
of all these briefcases.
I'm like, "Hmm."
- Awesome.
- Hey, guys!
Hi!
I'm sure glad you found me
out here.
So, whether it's UFO sightings,
abductions, or even
the remarkable construction
of Stonehenge and the pyramids,
humans have long sought
the answer to one
of life's greatest mysteries--
are we alone in the universe?
- I don't know.
- Oh, yeah!
In case you haven't noticed,
you're currently standing in
the middle of what many believe
to be one of the telltale signs
of life on other planets--
a crop circle.
Oh, yeah.
- Yes!
- Oh, yeah.
I'm pretty familiar
with crop circles.
I love UFO conspiracies,
so I'm very, very stoked.
So, in the last 30 years,
over 10,000 crop circles
have appeared around the world.
Now, while government agencies
like the CIA and Interpol
officially consider
these hoaxes,
conspiracy theorists believe
that they're actually
intergalactic distress signals
from alien civilizations.
And that, my friends,
is the basis
for this week's
spotlight challenge.
- Oh, yes.
- Whoo!
I love aliens.
There are so many different ways
this could go,
and my creative juices
are really starting to flow.
Inside each of these briefcases
is an aerial photo
of a crop circle,
along with a dire message that
the aliens may have been trying
- to communicate to us.
- Sweet.
So, working in teams of two,
your spotlight challenge is
to choose a briefcase
and create the life-form that
could have sent the message.
- Oh, yeah.
- Nice, nice.
Your randomly selected
teams are Niko and Corinne,
Chloe and Graham,
George, Bethany,
Tess and Daniel...
Cat and Matt,
Daran and Tanner...
All right.
Of course,
then Rashaad and Tyler.
Yes!
Please stand
next to your new teammate.
Now it's time to choose
your briefcases.
Niko and Corinne,
you're up first.
"We need water."
"Gravity changing."
"Polluted,
toxic environment."
"Our sun is dying."
We have
"Ice caps melting."
"Overcome with disease."
"Global famine."
Make sure the judges see
evidence of your aliens'
dire circumstances
in the final makeup.
All right, time to get started.
Good luck.
Bye.
- "Toaders."
- "Toaders"!
Rashaad and I come up
with a name,
"The Toaders,"
from planet Toad.
When they eat,
they could fill up.
- Mm-hmm.
- These guys are gluttons,
and they send out
this false message
to other planets that,
"We're hungry.
We need food."
When those civilizations give
them the okay to come in,
they just take over
and consume everything.
So they're a greedy,
greedy race.
One of the greediest.
I'd want it to look like
an alien sore.
Maybe, like, fungus
was growing on them
instead of just, like,
a big boil.
Our concept is, a team of aliens
have crash-landed on our planet,
and the fungus on our planet
takes them over.
Cool alien with cool skin?
- That's really gonna sell it.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're gonna do
some melting face, right?
With the skin peeled off,
you know?
Mm-hmm.
I think it will be pretty veiny.
We have "Polluted
and toxic environment,"
and our character is a gatherer
who goes out
into the wastelands
and gets things she can
to bring back to her people.
And the respirator...
Will at least be married
into the neck.
- We can do a cowl.
- Mm-hmm.
Um, maybe not a full cowl
into the shoulders?
Our alien
looks really sunken in
because he's
from a really dry planet.
So we're going to incorporate
a cracking in the back
of the cowl to make it appear
that the alien is dry.
Um, so we have the possibility
of goggles, tribal tattoos,
dried mud to help
keep them cool.
We have dry skin texture.
What do you think?
Uh, I'm not in love
with the goggle idea.
Matt's so iffy
about the design,
and we spent
so much time talking,
we didn't get
a clear concept drawn.
So I know when we get
to the lab,
it's gonna be a little hard.
All right, everyone,
let's go back to the lab!
So we get back to the lab.
We got five hours
of work today.
We pick our models
and start figuring
this thing out.
Tanner and I hit it off
right out of the gate.
We're feeling pretty good about
partnering up with each other.
You'll have to see if you can
just keep up here with me.
I want to try to make something
that nobody's ever seen.
So our alien eats through
the fingers,
and because our message is
the "Ice caps are melting,"
their land is getting flooded,
and therefore their food
and nutrients are being
flooded over.
So I figure there's
a filtering system
that would kill any bacteria
through their fingers.
Get some water handy.
Dump it.
Since the hands are gonna be
such an important part,
we just started mixing up
this huge batch of alginate,
and I dip my hands in there
and just keep them really still
so we can get a positive
of my hands
so that I can sculpt on
so that we can make gloves.
- You ready to break free?
- Once it's finally done,
I just wiggle and slip
my hands out.
We just mix up
a little batch of 1630,
dump it in each hand, and then
we just wait till it cures.
And we got hands.
And then I can finally start
sculpting my hands.
So they go
in the same direction,
let's give it a feeling.
The whole thing's looking good.
I'm sculpting the face
and the gross skin texture,
and George
is blocking out the cowl.
We're gonna show
that it's a toxic environment
by putting boils and burns
on her skin.
We are synchronized.
So we're still sticking
with the big ear?
Are we pronouncing the brow
a little bit more
kind of thing or...?
Because me and Matt
didn't decide
on a clear-cut design
before we got to the lab,
we're both kind of figuring it
out in the clay.
Their skin has evolved darker
because of the sun.
I agree.
So we decide to go
with an expanding sun
for the "Sun is dying" theme.
So we want a tribal,
African creature
with ears really big
as a way to cool them off.
I dig on science fiction,
and I'm teamed up with Chloe,
who won the last challenge,
so I'm at ease.
For our alien,
we get "Gravity's changing."
I'm thinking,
the gravity is expanding,
so this alien's features
should be stretched out.
Just try to push
all those forms.
Graham really wants to get
the face ready to run in foam
so that we can match it up
to the cowl.
I'm gonna try for that,
but I want to make the face
as perfect as possible
because it is the focal point.
Rashaad is sculpting the face,
and I'm sculpting
the whole cowl,
and we got to get that face
piece molded immediately.
If we get it out today,
tomorrow it's one less thing
I have to worry about.
- I love that. Love that.
- Thank you.
_
You need to tell me those
things sooner than later...
- Okay.
- Because you're only hurting
both of us by keeping
your mouth shut.
We both keep kind of trying
to change things,
figure it out as we go,
but we're losing so much time,
and I'm starting to get
a little worried
that our concept is reading
way too animal.
_
There's aspects
of the cowl, ears, and face
that Cat's not happy about.
I don't want to get too far
into this and be like,
"It's-- it's crap."
It's obvious
that we haven't talked enough
about what we want
out of this whole creature.
I'm just trying to see
where you're going with it.
I'm still really, really uneasy
about our concept.
I really don't want to go home,
not this early in the game.
Coming up...
Her indecisiveness
is making me nervous.
_
This is not good.
I'm going home.
This is an impressive makeup.
Who did all the painting?
I didn't agree
with some of the decisions.
_
Today is the first day
of our alien challenge,
and I'm not feeling
very confident on our alien.
I'm starting to get
a little worried
that our concept
is reading way too animal.
Cat's not happy
about our design,
so we're hoping
that Michael Westmore
will have some good advice
on how to keep it alien.
- Hey, guys!
- Hey.
We're here
for a walk-through.
- How are you?
- Hey!
- Hey, Tess, Daniel.
- Hi.
So tell us
what crop circle you got
and what the message was.
That's our crop circle,
and our message was
"Overcome with disease."
Okay.
Our alien is going to have
a disease from mold.
We're actually going to have
some mushrooms and stuff
coming out as mold.
I think the painting would
be very important with that,
otherwise it's gonna look
like tumors or growths...
- Right.
- And different sizes.
Make sure you have some,
you know, some Portobellos...
- Sure, sure. Yeah, yeah.
- And, uh, some Shiitakes...
- Yeah.
- That's what we plan on doing.
Our biggest worry is that
you're gonna think we made an
animal hybrid and not an alien.
Like, right now it is reading
pretty much animal hybrid.
What could they do?
I think you're being
too subtle.
Maybe bigger cheekbones
or change
your ear configuration.
Like a conical shape?
- Yeah.
- Great.
And we were thinking of going
with a darker-skin base.
Uh, don't get black.
All of a sudden,
it becomes a silhouette.
- You lose the detail.
- Yeah.
Awesome.
These guys
are basically gluttons.
They go to different planets
and take over
and eat all the food
that's there,
and then they have to move on.
Make sure you stay away
from flesh tones.
Yeah.
I mean, you can
be creative with this,
like even cutting stencils
and airbrushing spots on it.
- Oh, yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
So many frogs have those spots
on them and everything.
I think you've got
a great start.
Thank you.
He's going through dehydration?
Yes.
I don't think you're really
selling the concept,
having it so smooth.
Your character looks hydrated.
This crackling you're doing
along here
needs to be much deeper, okay?
- All right.
- Okay.
Color-wise,
are you going to metallize?
So this is all gonna
be gunmetal,
and then these lines between
are gonna be dark red.
Areas down in here, you could,
even with a little silver,
- just dry-brush some areas.
- Oh, yeah.
And it'll make
your metal pop out.
- Mm-hmm.
- Great. Thank you.
All right, guys,
we're heading out. Good luck.
- Thank you. Bye.
- Bye. Thank you.
Around the eyes,
what do you want me to do?
- Just a little black?
- Black, yes, sir.
Rashaad is finished
with the face,
so I decide to mold it.
And Rashaad can start putting
some details
into the cowl
just like his face,
so we can have
more of a cohesive feel.
- It's exactly how I pictured it.
- Cool.
I'm sculpting the cowl,
and it's looking great.
I'm actually getting
pretty impressed
by the way I'm able to elongate
all this anatomy.
I'm thinking the vertebrae
starts getting stretched
- up into the skull.
- That would be really cool.
I would prefer to get
this face molded today,
but I'd rather Chloe be happy
with her design
than to rush her through this.
Six minutes.
By the end of the day,
I still haven't finished
sculpting the face piece.
Time!
Tomorrow I'll look more
at what Graham's got going on
and try and kind of
match it up,
but I definitely need
to move faster
so it's ready in time for foam.
It's day two, and we have
9 1/2 hours in the lab.
We just got to hit
the ground running.
Time is flying, no time.
Daran needs to finish
fine-tuning the face,
and I need to get
these hands done.
We need to get
these things molded
and then start on the cowl.
I like it!
It's looking sweet.
After we speak
with Mr. Westmore,
we're seeing
the alien aspects come out.
I say, "I'll paint it,"
but I mean,
"We'll talk about it."
We're pretty sure
that if we paint this properly,
the alien forms will pop out.
I'm gonna start prepping
my station for the mold.
Cool.
I finally finish sculpting
the face.
Graham's going to do
all of the molding.
I'm glad I got extra time
to make it better.
Do you feel like
we're ahead of schedule?
No.
Our character has these weights
on her wrists and her ankles
to keep her from floating away.
So I'm working on them.
Vacuforming
doesn't really work out,
so now I'm gonna mess
with some L200
and see if that will work.
Chloe keeps changing
her decision,
so it's making me worry.
Are we gonna get these done?
So, as soon as I finish
the cowl, I start molding,
and Bethany starts doing props.
We want to create a respirator
to show that she can't breathe
the air outside.
So, for the respirator piece,
we use this stuff
called epoxy putty,
and it's a plumber's putty.
The only thing with that is
you have to work really fast
because it sets very quickly.
All we have to figure out
from there
is how she can breathe in it.
I think I've kind of
just lost my, uh...
my sight for doing this ear.
Matt's having
a really hard time
figuring out
how to mold our cowl
because it has
these really huge ears.
You don't think this is gonna
be sturdy enough to do this?
- No.
- There's-- there's--
- The angle's really scary too,
you know?
Finding the right place
to put the dividing wall
is very crucial.
If you mess that up, it can
totally mess up your mold.
You won't be able to open it.
Do you mind just taking over
for a minute?
I need to not look at it
for a second.
Okay, totally fine.
Yeah.
I'm getting a little flustered
with it,
and I'm afraid
that if I keep looking at it,
I'm gonna make a mistake.
Matt is just a nervous wreck.
Oh, well, we don't have time
to play around.
As I'm making these weights,
I'm realizing
that the L200 isn't working.
It's just kind of messy.
I feel like I can't figure out
what I'm gonna do about this
to make it work.
It's looking more like jewelry.
They need to look like
they're contraptions
rather than jewelry.
It's not really going
the way that I was hoping
that it would go.
Chloe is really struggling
with her design.
Please, just make a decision
and get it done.
_
Okay, sculpt them.
I have a picture in my head,
but for whatever reason,
I can't get it out.
I have to have these weights,
because without it,
my makeup isn't going to make
any sense.
_
Okay, sculpt them.
It's day two
of the alien challenge,
and Chloe is supposed
to be making gravity weights,
but her indecisiveness
is making me nervous.
_
Please, just make a decision
and get it done.
The weights are
an important part of our design
because they keep her
from floating away.
But I'm just not sure
what I want,
and we're starting
to run out of time.
So I'm just trying to get
this done at this point.
Rashaad is fabricating
some armor,
some plates,
and things like that
to make our alien
look gargantuan and nasty.
And I come up
with these little arms
to help our Toader
eat and eat and eat.
- Lookit, lookit, look at that.
- Look at how perfect, yo.
Fuck yeah!
You make the mushrooms.
I make the kit.
Daniel and I have our sculptures
molded and ready for foam.
Now he has to hop
on the mushrooms,
and I got to get
that medipack done.
Daniel molds the mushrooms
in silicone
so that we can run them
in a rigid foam tomorrow.
That way, we're gonna be able
to have the mushrooms
sprouting out from all over.
That'll look cool.
I finish sculpting plate molds
with the texture
of the weights in them.
Now I'm gonna bring them over
to Graham for the molding.
- Oh, those are cool.
- Sorry that took so long.
I look at the sculpts,
and I think,
"This probably could have been
done in five minutes in L200."
But, hey,
at least we have something.
I'm molding it.
We're gonna use it,
so I'm happy.
I'm gonna keep cleaning out
that mold.
- Okay.
- You jump on those hands
- and finish them up?
- Yeah.
So cool, dude.
It looks cool.
So it's almost the end
of the day,
and I notice Rashaad and Tyler's
really awesome alien,
and it's gonna be quite big.
And I'm like, "I don't think
we're gonna be in top votes."
Are you thinking any lights
for this character?
Lights?
Niko is questioning
if we're going big enough,
and I tell him to,
"Just stop judging yourself
based on what other people
are doing,
and let's trust our ideas."
All right, everyone,
that's time!
I know our alien
will not be very big.
So I hope Corinne and I will not
look bad for the judges.
Let's check it out, check it out,
check it out, check it out.
Today is application day,
and we got four hours to apply
and one hour for last looks.
The first thing we do
is check out our foam pieces.
- Oh, my God.
- All right?
Look, it's all ripped.
The whole cowl-- it's totally
ripped in the middle,
all the way to the chin.
And that's actually
my responsibility, my piece.
- Fuck, man.
- Yeah, "Fuck, man."
That's right.
I'm going home.
That's it.
'Cause we're not doing
something very big.
So, on top of that,
having it ripped,
- it's like, "Come on."
- How's the rest of it?
The back is okay.
We have to figure out
how to save this.
It's okay.
- How we doing? How we doing?
- All right.
- Matt?
- Yeah.
- I'm Dan. How are you?
- Nice to meet you.
You're gonna be
the mighty Toader.
The Toaders are coming.
Ooh, I like the ears on it.
All right, all right,
all right!
Before I can apply, I have
to fabricate the mushrooms.
I pour rigid foam into my mold,
and I wait for that to set up
in about ten minutes,
and then I have the mushrooms,
which are pretty awesome
at this point.
There we go.
I make these protrusions
on the outside of the face.
They're made out of gelatin,
to give a different feel
to the alien.
I've never put gelatin
and foam together,
so it's a little bit scary,
but we're supposed to be going
bold and extreme,
so I'm gonna try
something new here
and see if gelatin
will stick to foam.
Perfection!
Release the Toad.
Can you just turn
your head towards me?
Corinne is doing a really good
job with the painting,
and I'm actually really excited
over what I'm looking.
- Oh, man.
- Yeah, this is ugly.
I'm really sweating it here.
You know what?
I'm making a wound here, okay?
Just like a huge crack
happened here.
Maybe some toxic liquid
jump into it
and melted the helmet here,
and she's all wounded
and melted skin and everything.
Let's make that wound with a--
- Third degree?
- Yeah.
I think that'll be faster
than applying.
- Yeah.
- Stand up for me.
Matt's really confident in his
ability to paint dark skin tone.
Okay, chin up for me,
like that.
I look up, and I'm like, "Whoa.
This is looking
a little bit muddy."
His head gets a dark color
over top of everything
I just did.
Is it supposed to be like that?
Mr. Westmore warned us
against going too dark,
but I don't think
we're taking his advice.
I'm a little worried right now.
Cat's not happy
with the paint job,
and there's lots of things
I really want to change,
but it's too late, so I'm gonna
do my best to move forward.
How much time we got?
- 19 minutes.
- 19 minutes?
♪ madness,
madness, madness, madness ♪
So I'm a little nervous.
We still have to do a lot
of painting on the face,
and we got only one hour
to finish this in last looks.
We need some more sickness
in the eyes.
We have to go in it
with the color too.
That looks awful.
George is nervous
because of the rips,
but you never know
what the judges are thinking.
That's time, people!
Brushes down!
That's time!
George and I are feeling
pretty stressed now.
This is not where we wanted
to be before last looks.
Coming up.
I'm gonna push it up a little
bit more into your gums.
Oh, no, they're gonna know
that it's a ripped cowl.
I'm going home.
This whole thing
was so impressive.
You're pushing the envelope.
I didn't agree
with some of the painting.
Here's the bad part--
It's not gonna cut it.
Let's make it happen!
It's last looks,
and we have one hour,
and I am freaking out a lot
because we still have
so much painting to do.
She just has a base coat
and some light highlights,
so we both attack the face
as hard as we can.
We need to be in, like,
super final details
in the next 20 minutes.
We have to fix this paint job.
I feel like the paint
is a little too far gone,
but I do my best.
We got 30 minutes, guys!
I'm gonna push it up a little
bit more into your gums.
Can you get some shadow colors?
That's time, everybody!
Good job!
She's gorgeous.
Thank you.
You were a trouper, man.
He looks really good up close.
It's not as bold and extreme
as it probably should be,
but it's not
a solid brown color,
so I'm happy with what it is.
I feel good.
Welcome to theFace Off
reveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
First, let's say hello to our
talented panel of judges--
owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick...
- Good evening.
- Hey.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill...
- Hello.
- Hi.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page...
- Hi, guys.
- Hello.
And joining our panel tonight
is a writer, producer,
and director
whose work includes
Priest, Dark Skies, Legion,
and SyFy's Defiance,
returning this spring.
Please give a warm welcome
to Scott Stewart.
Thank you.
Scott, thank you so much
for joining us tonight.
It's my pleasure.
Looking forward to seeing
what you guys come up with.
Scott has done amazing work.
And if anybody knows aliens,
it's definitely gonna be
this guy.
All right, guys, this week
your spotlight challenge
was to use a crop circle
and its decoded distress signal
to inspire
an original alien creation.
Let's take a look
at your new life-forms.
She looks awesome.
It's retro.
It's female.
It's also kind of eerie-looking,
but also kind of sexy, I'd say.
We think
she's absolutely beautiful--
completely different
than everybody else's,
so we're very happy.
He looks amazing.
We're thinking we're tops,
even possible in the run
for a win.
I'm pretty amazed
at what we were able to do
in the last hour,
and I'm pretty happy
with the overall look.
I'm really happy
with everything.
Tess-- she's happy.
She's smiling.
And I think that all in all,
we pulled it together
and did a really good job.
I'm feeling
a little bit better.
I think my biggest worry
is that our concept's
not that original,
but it came together.
I love the way he looks.
Not like a big, huge monster--
he looks like a piece of art.
Judges, it's time to have
a closer look at our aliens.
Oh, interesting.
- Can you move your fingers?
- Very clever.
_
I like the way
they've integrated
the silver tones in there.
Yeah, it gives it texture
and depth.
This is
a very advanced concept,
using gelatin
integrated with foam latex.
It's creepy.
- Yeah.
- It freaks me out.
Hey--
Oh, little lights in there.
Thanks.
Just really nice forms.
This is separating pretty bad
on his chest here, these edges.
Thank you.
That paint work feels like
a bad watercolor painting.
Tilt your head back.
Oh, no, they're gonna know
that it's a ripped cowl.
These guys are expert,
so they know.
This is not good.
I'm thinking, "I'm going home."
Who made your favorite
crop-circle-inspired alien
tonight?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
That paint work feels like
a bad watercolor painting.
The judges go up close
to the makeups,
and honestly, I'm thinking,
"I'm going home."
I wonder about the decision
to leave all of these
huge surfaces devoid of paint.
It seems like the beginnings
of a really cool idea.
Cool.
Thank you.
This is another one
of those makeups
where they didn't do
a good paint job,
so you can't even highlight
the work that they did do.
Thanks.
Look at this beautiful
paint job.
Could have done
with a little bit
more skin texture, wrinkles,
I think.
- Very interesting.
- The nails are fantastic.
- The nails.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
So, Scott, what did you think
of tonight's aliens?
I have to say, guys,
the quality of the work
is excellent,
especially considering
the amount of time
you guys had to do it.
Thank you.
Okay, the judges have scored
your creations.
Let's find out
what they thought.
Tess and Daniel...
Graham and Chloe...
Rashaad and Tyler...
Congratulations,
because you are all safe
and can head
back to the makeup room.
The rest of you were the best
and the worst this week.
The judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Niko and Corinne,
please step forward.
Begin by telling me
about your concept
and about who did what
on this makeup.
Our crop circle was,
"We need water."
So we wanted to go
for a very dehydrated type
of a feel.
Corinne sculpted the face
and the neck piece,
and she did most of the paint.
And I sculpted the cowl,
the chest, and the hands.
In last look, we went together
and finished all the paint work.
That's extremely impressive,
because I wouldn't have guessed
that two people
were painting on him.
These color notes
that you've brought down
along the side of his face
and on to his neck,
from afar, it gives a shade
and counter-shade,
but up close, they're actually
really nice details.
That's really advanced
painting technique.
- Thank you.
- Really well done.
This is definitely
an impressive makeup.
It's beautiful, color-wise.
The palette is fantastic.
Can you turn around?
I want to see
the back of him as well.
All of this breaking up,
explosion in the back
of his head,
is really a cool idea.
You can turn around.
Not to mention,
the fabulous green fingernails.
They are awesome.
- Very well done, you guys.
- Thank you.
I just think
the overall presentation
feels very strong and cohesive.
So great work.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
Niko and Corinne,
please step back.
George and Bethany.
Tell me the concept
for your alien
and how you divided up
the work.
She's a gatherer that goes out
into the wastelands
and gets whatever she can
and brings it
back to her people.
Bethany did the face.
I did the cowl.
Okay, and who did all
the painting?
I did the cowl, mostly,
and she did the face.
From afar, this makeup
was so impressive
and then when we got up close,
I was really
kind of disappointed.
You fell down
in the facial sculpture.
It's really kind of rough.
Underneath the chin,
it's broken apart,
and there's this big reveal
of her throat.
What is that about?
Actually, that was an accident.
It came out ripped in the--
right here.
That's a good case of turning
lemons to lemonade,
but the face doesn't really
evoke any kind of sympathy.
You've talked about
a few story elements to us.
She was gathering stuff.
We should see
the effects of that.
So I think
it's about taking more time
to think these things through.
George and Bethany,
please step back.
Daran and Tanner.
So tell us about your concept.
Ice caps are melting
and covering over their food.
They don't eat anything solid,
so everything is through
the fingertips.
I sculpted the face
and the protrusions.
Tanner sculpted the hands.
Some big concepts here,
and I actually love that you're
really pushing the envelope.
And part of it is because
there's some freaky things
going on
with these special glands.
You guys did some weird stuff.
- Yeah.
- We're pretty weird.
The use of soft color,
I think, is really wonderful.
It's really weird,
in a good way.
Thank you.
It looks alien, but it
looks reasonable. It looks rational.
You managed to capture
this organic look
that I really, really,
really enjoyed.
- Thank you. Thank you so much.
- Awesome. Thank you.
Daran and Tanner,
- you can head back.
- Thank you.
Good job, brother.
Cat and Matt,
please step forward.
Tell me about how
you approached the concept.
Also, who did what?
Our decoded phrase was
"Our sun is dying."
We decided to go with a planet
that was getting hotter
and hotter
and a species of alien
that had to,
over time, adapt to the heat.
Matt started the face.
I started blocking out the cowl.
Matt blocked out the chest.
The first impression is strong,
but when you get close,
particularly up in the head,
it feels like one color.
There was just
a missed opportunity there
to take it to another level.
I didn't agree
with some
of the painting decisions.
I just think that it
kind of got lost in the paint.
Okay, it's got
this conical shape,
but you didn't develop the rest
of the facial features.
And here's the bad part--
the "Swamp thing" nose,
which looks great
on swamp thing.
Anyone else, not so much.
I really think
a little bit more
groovy paint job on the face
would have made this thing
really spectacular.
We don't want to just see, like,
a muddy, brown face.
So you have to think about this
when you're painting it.
Cat and Matt,
you can step down.
Thank you.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you had to say.
Will you please head
back to the makeup room
while they deliberate?
Thank you.
All right, judges, why don't
we talk about the looks
you liked the most this week?
Let's start
wi Niko and Corinne.
It's a really cohesive
head-to-toe character.
They put a little bit
of luminescent paint
on the crop-circle design
so the whole thing wasn't flat.
It felt organic
to the character.
The exact amount of darkness
they achieved around the eyes.
It's not so dark-- they didn't
just blacken it, you know?
It feels like Corinne led
the paint job.
Then again, Niko sculpted
that great cowl--
- beautifully done.
- Beautifully done.
All right, let's move on
to Daran and Tanner.
I thought that it was
extremely uncomfortable.
An alien shouldn't be
comfortable to look at.
So I think they won in that
category-- that's for sure.
They made such good use
of gelatin being translucent,
and they didn't overpaint it,
so it stuck out
against the foam.
The ideas are so adventurous.
The one struggle I had was
telling the story in the design,
but it's so winning
in all the other ways
in which it needs to be.
All right, let's move on
to the looks we liked the least.
Let's start
with George and Bethany.
When she walked out,
she had a great profile,
and then she took off
the respirator
and it fell apart.
And to skip the quality
on the face
and deliver a nice cowl,
it's just not gonna cut it.
You have to do that first.
It seems like Bethany is
very responsible for the face.
All right, let's move on
to Cat and Matt.
There's just not really
an interesting alien design
in there.
Yeah. It sounded like
there was a lot of conflict
between them about it too.
At some point,
I thought somebody was about
to throw somebody under the bus
and then kind of stopped.
I'm not sure the chest that
they did was worth the work
that they put into it.
I'm not really sure
what that accomplished.
They did think about things
from the story point of view.
I appreciated
what they were doing.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
We have.
Let's bring them back out.
All right, Glenn,
tell us about the top teams.
Niko and Corinne,
your character
made a strong impression
due largely in part
to your excellent sculpture
and your beautiful paint job.
Daran and Tanner,
you had an adventurous concept
that resulted in a fascinating
and well-executed makeup.
All right,
which team came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Glenn, which team
came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Niko and Corinne.
You worked
extremely well together,
creating a cohesive makeup
and one of the nicest paint jobs
that we have seen.
- Thank you.
- Niko and Corinne, great job.
But as you know,
we can only have one winner.
Glenn?
Our winner tonight is...
Corinne.
Thank you.
We felt
that you were the driving force
behind your very successful
alien character.
Thank you very much.
I'm really excited.
It gives me confidence to know
that I have the ability
to continue to compete
in this competition.
- Corinne, congratulations.
- Thank you.
You, Niko, Daran, Tanner,
you guys are all safe.
Please head
back to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Good job, buddy.
Unfortunately,
that means the rest of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom teams.
George and Bethany,
from a distance, your makeup
made a great impression.
But up close,
the details were unrefined.
Cat and Matt,
your makeup had a solid concept,
but the sculptural detail
and the paint job
just didn't do it justice.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Bethany.
Our biggest issue
with your makeup,
unfortunately,
was the sculpture of the face.
That means, George, Cat, Matt,
you are safe this week.
You can head
back to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Bethany, thank you
for bringing your artistry
and passionate makeup
to Face Off,
and we wish you
all the best of luck.
Thank you guys so much.
Bethany, I am so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
Will you please head
back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit?
- Thanks, guys.
- Good luck.
It's just frustrating
to not be able to show
everything that I can do.
Aw.
This is definitely not the end.
This has just made my passion
grow even stronger.
I'm gonna miss you guys.
I've learned so much
about myself--
just what I can do.
I'm not done
with makeup at all.
I would really like to keep
kicking ass.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net