Absolutely stunning.
So well handled.
You did one hell of a job.
Previously on Face Off...
George's wizard
earned him his first win.
Finally!
And Cat was sent home.
But the biggest surprise of all
was revealed backstage.
I'm taking you all to Japan.
Are you kidding me? Japan?
Konnichiwa!
Now eight artists remain,
and they'll journey
across the globe
for extreme inspiration.
Being in Tokyo
is absolutely amazing.
Please welcome Kazuhiro Tsuji.
Kazu is one
of the greatest makeup artists
in the whole world.
You must create
an anime character of your own.
I love anime.
You know
it's not gonna be that simple.
- This is it.
- Some much color.
The anime district.
Oh!
The whole thing
is exquisitely executed.
It's really nice.
I think you've done
a great job.
In the end,
only one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Face Off!
Welcome toFace Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
We're getting ready
to go to Japan.
I wish I could share
all this with Cat.
One of her dreams
is to go to Japan,
and I want to make her proud
of whatever
we have to do there.
This is, like,
the biggest thing
they've ever done on Face Off.
And we're part of it.
This is my first trip
out of the country.
I'm so excited.
- We're going to Japan!
- Konnichiwa.
Being in Tokyo,
the sights, the smells.
Everything feels like
a different world,
and it's absolutely amazing.
We arrive
at this world-class fish market.
It's a very hectic,
amazing environment.
- Oh!
- Ah!
It's a ritual thing--
before they cut the fish,
you give it a kiss.
Tyler, right here.
All right, fine.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
That is so good.
And the sushi
is absolutely amazing.
- So great.
- So good.
This is just absolutely crazy.
Here we are in Tokyo
in the middle
of Shibuya Crossing.
It feels like
Japanese Times Square--
so many different billboards
and colors
and people and personalities.
McKenzie really wanted us
to be inspired by Japan,
and I'm like a kid
in a candy store.
I just collect reference photos
of the architecture,
the colors, textures,
even the outfits.
I'm here to be inspired
to do more art.
This is, like, the coolest gift
I've ever been given.
It's just nonstop incredible.
Tokyo!
Oh, this is a really nice view.
This Japanese garden--
everything's so beautiful,
so peaceful.
- What do you got over there?
- This thing's pretty cool.
This is definitely
a very powerful experience
for us.
It's all hitting me--
everything, from being
in this competition
to being so blessed.
Honestly, I want to stay
for a while.
I just can't believe
we're here.
We probably won't be able
to sleep tonight
because we're trying to take in
as much as possible.
I wouldn't mind living here.
Unbelievable.
We're walking through
this quiet, little street,
and we approach
this temple gate
that looks like it's been there
for hundreds of years.
So cool.
The gate opens
to this beautiful lake.
- Check out the turtle!
- Wow, dude.
Then we get to the top
of the bridge,
and all of a sudden--
You guys hear that?
- Oh, man.
- So cool.
This is so cool.
What do you think, Georgie?
This is amazing, dude.
- Nice.
- Wow.
So cool.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Welcome to Shomyoji Temple.
This stunning structure
was built nearly 1,000 years ago
to represent
the land of perfect bliss.
Now, it is here,
surrounded by the haunting sound
of the cicadas,
that your next
foundation challenge
will take place.
Now, let me introduce you
to today's special guest judge.
Industry insiders
have called him
the best makeup-effects artist
in the world,
and he has a long list
of impressive credits,
including Men In Black,
The Grinch,
Planet Of The Apes, and Looper.
Please welcome two-time
Academy Award-nominated
makeup artist Kazuhiro Tsuji.
_
Kazu is one
of the greatest makeup artists
in the whole world.
I am so excited.
Thank you so much
for being here.
Thank you.
Today's foundation challenge
is inspired
by one of the most
iconic characters
in Japanese folklore--
the oni.
_
The masks you see
on the models are examples
of traditional Japanese oni.
Now, since they come
from the spirit world,
these colorful entities
don't always have
normal human features.
Oftentimes they are depicted
with extra eyes,
claws, fingers, even toes,
so, in this
foundation challenge,
you must create an original take
on a Japanese oni.
I'm really excited.
At the same time,
I'm really nervous.
Kazu is such a perfectionist.
This is really gonna have
to be a clean makeup
in order to impress him.
So, Kazu, what will you
be looking for
in today's final makeup?
_
All right, guys,
you have two hours
to create your oni characters.
The winner of today's challenge
will earn immunity.
Good luck,
because your time starts now.
I see this white
and purple kimono
and think of a character
who waits for samurais
when they die.
That's kind of like
their last battle,
to either go to heaven
or to go to hell,
and they have to fight her.
My concept is a demon
who captures people
and drowns them,
so my character's
gonna be very dark, gloomy,
and gray and wet.
I'm very excited
for this challenge.
We've got Kazu here,
so it's time to impress him.
My plan is to use
some of the architecture
and structure around me
as an influence.
I'm using seven prosthetics
on this makeup.
Hopefully I can get 'em all
applied in time
to get them painted--
a weathered bronze look
to match the buildings there
in the background behind me.
The oni is a Japanese demon,
so I'm gonna try and throw in
a little bit of extra everything
to dehumanize her.
I'm thinking, "How many horns
can I fit on this thing's head?
How many ears
can this thing have?"
But at the same time,
I want this to look like
it came out of a painting--
kind of like it's a statue
that's come alive.
I really want to bring out
the shape of the Japanese oni--
defined brows,
cheeks, and nose.
And I want to use blacks
and reds and golds
to help pull in the culture
around us.
It's kind of strange
to do something horrible,
when this is so beautiful.
My oni feeds on the sorrow
of their victims.
I'm using forehead prosthetic,
a chin piece, making her pale.
Somehow it's coming.
It's coming to me, you know?
- Okay, yeah, that's hot.
- Five minutes, everybody!
Anybody know how to tie
a kimono around here?
Time's up!
Everybody, brushes down!
Whoo.
- Hey, George.
- Hello.
- How are you?
- Good.
- Tell us about your oni.
She attacks by sorrow,
by making you cry to death.
I like the color
you used on the eyebrow
and the red on the eyelid,
but the way you painted
those tear stains--
it doesn't look like
it fall down from the eyes.
Yeah.
I chose to make
two different noses--
one's reversed--
and then six different eyes.
I love the paint job you did.
I was actually looking
at the roof over here
on the structure.
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah.
I wanted to create a character
who is in the death realm,
waiting for samurais,
and if they have the courage
to beat her,
then they go to heaven,
and if they lose,
they go to hell.
I think the color coordination
looks good,
but I see too much
of a brushstroke.
Oh, okay.
I immediately wanted
to grab the robe
so I could use that
as inspiration--
reds and blacks
being really dominant
and golds
being an awesome accent.
This is a nice paint job.
It fits really well,
and it has a lot of shape
going on around the face.
It looks nice.
Just to be able to do
makeup in Japan
is so cool.
And I'd like to get immunity
so I can step
out of my comfort zone
for the next
spotlight challenge.
So, Kazu, who created
your favorite looks today?
Daran...
Your makeup is quite unique
and different from others,
but I still can tell
it's an oni character.
Thank you.
Corinne, I love your paint job,
and application
was well finished.
Thank you.
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of today's challenge is...
Coming up...
You know
it's not gonna be that simple.
Ooh.
Chloe's design
is similar to mine.
I'm really worried.
Fuck!
I expect much better from you.
We have no idea where
you come up with this stuff.
It looks so cheesy.
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of today's challenge is...
Daran.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Overall, it was
a great original concept.
Coming from you,
that's absolutely amazing.
Congratulations, Daran.
As the winner
of today's challenge,
you have won immunity
in the next
spotlight challenge.
Just to impress Kazu
was incredible--
not only that,
but winning the immunity
here in Japan,
it's just mind-blowing to me.
Kazu, thank you so much
for being here with us today.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
All right, now let's talk
about this week's
spotlight challenge.
- Ooh.
- The impact of Tokyo
on today's pop culture
is undeniable.
Films like Pacific Rim,
The Matrix, Kill Bill,
and 2001 A Space Odyssey
have tapped into one of Tokyo's
biggest exploits-- anime.
With that in mind,
your spotlight challenge
is to create
a hyper-stylized anime character
of your own.
- Whoa.
- I'm really excited.
I'm not sure how to make anime
into a makeup,
but I love anime.
But you know
it's not gonna be that simple.
Your anime characters
must also be
an alter-ego version
of yourself.
Ooh.
An anime
alter ego of ourselves--
it's just insane.
This gets cooler and cooler.
I want you to make sure
that you source something unique
about yourself to incorporate
into your makeups.
Now, tomorrow I'm sending you
to Akihabara,
the anime capital of the world.
You'll have an opportunity
to consult
with genius anime artist
Hidetaka Tenjin.
He's worked on anime series
like the ever popular
Macross franchise.
All right, well, good luck,
and I will see you all
back in Hollywood.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
This is it.
- The anime district.
- So much colors.
Awesome.
So we get to Akihabara,
and I'm, like,
jumping up and down.
I can't wait to go explore.
I'm just seeing
all these different characters,
and my mind
is just going crazy with,
"What am I gonna do?"
- Oh, look, you--
- Chloe's right there.
- Look at that.
- This is so cool.
I've pictured myself
as a cartoon character
plenty of times,
so I think this challenge
is gonna suit me just fine.
Immediately
I know what I want to do.
It's a mad scientist turning
into a big plant monster.
There's my hair.
That's a Graham hair
right there.
My wife
is gonna love this makeup.
Alyssa's so
into this whole world.
She would be freaking out.
So I got to win this time.
I got to win, please.
- There you go.
- Oh, thank God.
I am super excited
to be here in Akihabara.
I want to do something
Halloween-inspired,
'cause I love Halloween.
Part of the challenge
of making an anime makeup
is really gonna be the eyes.
They have a lot of
their expression in their eyes.
They got oversized eyes...
- Yeah.
- Small noses.
Let's keep looking.
- That's anime.
- Awesome.
- Yeah.
- Oh, man, let me see.
Ooh, look,
it looks exactly like you.
- This is the right inspiration.
- Ooh!
You know where
we're going, right?
Yes.
- We go to @home cafe...
- Yay.
Which is a cosplay cafe.
This place
is straight out of an anime.
Check this out.
Oh, yeah.
_
- Princess?
We get 30 minutes to sketch,
and then Tenjin walks in...
- Hi.
- ...which is super exciting.
_
My alter ego
is a Robin Hood character
who takes from the rich
and gives to the poor.
I love that whole idea.
_
I wanted to make it
kind of like a gun and a sword
in one weapon.
_
- Make it bigger?
- Yes.
- The same size as him?
- Yeah.
That's cool.
I didn't even think of that.
I'm definitely gonna go
for making the weapon
twice the size.
This is anime.
They always got
oversized weapons.
_
Thank you.
My alter ego
would have to involve
some sense of freedom.
Fish have freedom
to roam the open seas,
so I'm gonna wrap koi fish
around the head of my character
and give the model
an actual fish face as well.
_
- Water?
- Water.
You're trying to get me
in trouble, man.
You're trying to get me to do
more than I can do.
In order to show
that the koi fish
are jumping out of the water,
I'm going to incorporate waves
into the cowl.
So I'm very happy
that we had the opportunity
to get Tenjin's advice.
Yeah, I like that.
He was very helpful
to everybody.
_
Thank you.
All right, guys,
time to go back to LA.
Let's pack it up.
The whole trip has been
just amazing,
and we want to stay
a little longer.
But there's a lot of work to do,
so let's get to it.
Bye!
See you!
- Bye!
- Arigato!
This experience
has made me realize
where my talent can take me.
The world opens up.
We're definitely
leaving Japan inspired,
but also more focused
and more driven,
just knowing that it's gonna
take that much more effort
to make it into the finale.
So it's our first day
in the lab.
We get to choose our model.
And I want to incorporate
my knowledge
in martial arts
in this character.
My concept is a samurai
that's just a normal kid
in the day,
and in the night,
he's like a superhero.
So the first thing that I want
to work on is my face.
My character's name
is Soulstice.
She is
a soul-sucking vigilante.
It's kind of a play on words,
'cause she's a soul sucker,
but also, I was born
on the summer solstice.
She's still gonna be sexy
and definitely have red hair.
That's frickin' close.
- Cool.
- Thank you.
It's gonna have,
like, a helmet.
My alter ego has,
like, an armor suit
that's gonna enable him to fly.
I always wanted to be
like superman,
and this guy's
gonna let me do that.
I got to do a face, cowl,
and a suit.
It's just crazy.
I got so much to do.
I block out the face
so I can start creating
the shape of the eyes.
I vacuform the eyes
and then use the vacuform pieces
to complete my sculpture.
That looks good.
My concept
is a super-fast version of me
who can handle
a lot of projects at once,
and I want to give
my character multiple arms.
Instead of sculpting arms,
I just figured,
"Why don't I just mold
my own arms
and I'll have them
be holding something?"
I'm pouring alginate in this
paper tubing that I made--
it's a molding compound
that's safe to use on skin--
and putting my arm in
and letting it set up.
Fill it with stone
and repeat the process
for my other arm.
Oh, he did his hands.
Looking around the lab,
I notice that Chloe's design
looks similar to mine.
Yeah, Corinne's got something
like that too.
It's really nerve-racking
because we've heard again
and again from the judges,
"Make sure that you're doing
something different
from each other."
Since Chloe and I
are the only two females left,
our characters
are already gonna have
some of the same elements,
so I'm really scared
at this point.
It's day one of our anime
alter-ego challenge,
and Chloe's design is looking
really similar to mine.
It's cool.
Yeah, Corinne's got something
like that too.
Even though our makeups
kind of look the same,
Corinne and I
paint differently,
and I think
they'll look different enough.
We've heard again
and again from the judges,
"If you see someone
doing similar
that you make sure that
you're doing the better job."
So I've taken the time
to really get the eyes right,
'cause I'm not changing
my design.
It's only fueled me
to show them that I'm better.
I'm making this sculpture
of my hair,
like, really, really big.
- Rashaad.
- Yeah?
Is that a whole block of clay?
- Yeah.
- That's so cool.
Hey, guys, that's time.
Now that the sculpture is done,
I have another big mold
to make,
and I still have
to fabricate my weapons,
so hopefully
I can finish it all tomorrow.
Here we go again.
So it's day two.
We have 9 1/2 hours in the lab.
I've got to get
this cowl sculpted,
get the fish detailed,
and sculpt the waves
that Tenjin thought
I should add.
It's kind of scary to be trying
to make a cowl this big
and with this much detail,
so I'm not sure
if I'm gonna be able
to pull this off or not.
- Tyler.
- Scary.
I have a wig.
Tyler, on the other hand,
is doing, like, a hard plastic
mannequin-style hair.
I think it's hilarious.
- You just put it on like a cap.
- Fantastic.
Apparently I look good in it.
Back to you, Graham.
That's hilarious.
Right now
I'm trying to figure out
the arm prosthetics.
First I start to make
the shell of it
out of L200 foam.
- Where's your hand, right there?
- Yep.
I then work
on the shoulder harness.
Then I have to make
a skin of latex on top of that
and create textures
with plastic wrap.
It's taking forever,
and I'm realizing
how much painting's
actually going to be necessary,
and it's a lot.
So I hand-painted
vacuform the eyes.
I think they look very different
from Corinne's makeup.
She was a little bit concerned,
but I'm happy
that they look different.
This dude is tired, man.
I got the face
and the cowl done,
but I still have a lot to do.
I have to do the suit,
rockets, and wings,
and I don't think
I'm gonna have enough time
to make all that.
Damn, I made
the same mistake again.
It's hard to think.
I'm tired.
What's wrong with me, man?
It's not coming along
like I wanted.
- Fuck.
- We got 15 minutes, guys!
Rashaad.
All right, guys, it's time.
So time's up,
and I'm only halfway
with my suit.
So I have to finish it tomorrow
on application day.
So, if anything goes wrong,
I'm gonna be in big trouble.
- Let's go.
- It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab
and one more hour
at last looks.
The arm still looks like
it needs a couple more coats
of latex,
but I'm really thinking
about all that painting
that's gonna have to go on,
and that's making me worried.
- What's going on?
- Hey, man.
I'm gonna turn you
into a superhero version of me.
I got, like, a ton of stuff
to do with your hair.
My plan for application day
is to finish the wig,
and then I'll start application
and painting.
Okay, squish it on your face.
The first thing I need to do
is make sure that the eyes
are really well set
into this appliance
and the model
has good enough vision
to act with these pieces on.
Is it still lined up
with your eye?
Yeah.
You look just like me.
Might have to help me out here.
Painting time.
So I start painting the pieces.
I've got to get
a base color put down,
which I need to keep light
and then build up dark
on top of that.
One koi is gonna be
a yellow-orange,
and the other one-- I'm gonna do
a white with some red.
We took a lot of pictures
in Japan of the koi,
so I'm referencing that.
So this is definitely
a challenge for me.
I've never tried
to paint like this.
Pretty badass.
Much better.
The cowl and the face
and everything's on,
but I have
to finish the suit now.
So I'm putting it on a model
to see if it fits correctly,
and I have to cut
and paint all these things,
but it's looking sloppy.
I mean, it's not the kind
of thing that I like to do.
15 minutes, everybody.
Is that too tight?
We have, like,
two minutes left,
and I'm starting to panic
about everything
that I have to do.
Fuck!
I slam into Graham's face.
I can feel my lip get cut
on the inside.
You all right?
I know that we only have,
like, seconds at this point.
Sorry about that.
That's time, guys.
My face is bleeding.
My model is not
all the way painted.
It's just-- it's a mess.
Coming up...
Ah, crap.
A lot is going wrong
in this last hour.
Hold it in place.
I'm gonna tape it, okay?
I'm applying like crazy,
but it's looking so crappy.
The execution is subpar.
It looks like
you didn't have enough time.
I think
you've done a great job.
It's last looks.
We have one hour, and I still have
to put the whole armor.
Hold it in place.
I'm gonna tape it, okay?
I'm applying like crazy.
Please hold there.
Finally I get it to a point
where he's at least not naked,
but it's looking so crappy.
Shit.
Close your eyes.
Ah, crap.
A lot is going wrong
in this last hour.
Leaves are coming off.
Oh, broken airbrush-- great.
And now the airbrush
doesn't work.
This is not ideal here.
I can't hand-paint
a whole tree,
not with all the other things
that I've got to do.
I don't like the paint job.
And one last time.
It's definitely
better than it was,
but I've never done
a paint job like this,
so I'm nervous.
All right, everyone,
that's time!
- Brushes down!
- Whoo!
I'm really disappointed,
especially when I tried
really hard
to do something for my wife.
It's just lame.
Welcome to theFace Off
reveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
First let's say hello
to our talented panel of judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve
Make-Up Effects Studio,
Glenn Hetrick...
- Hey, guys.
- Hello, again.
Three-time Oscar winning
makeup artist Ve Neill...
Hi, all you jet-lagged kids.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
- Konnichiwa.
- Hey, Neville.
And joining us again tonight
is two-time
Academy Award-nominated
makeup artist Kazuhiro Tsuji.
It's great to have you
back again.
Great seeing you again
and looking forward to see
what you come up with.
Thank you.
This week
your spotlight challenge
was to create
an original anime character
that is your own alter ego.
So let's take a look
at your anime creations.
This isn't the cleanest
application I've done,
but I hope
the judges will appreciate
the character as a whole.
I actually love the makeup,
'cause it's something different,
something
I've never tried before,
so I'm very excited
about this one.
I'm feeling very good
about this makeup.
I even think he looks better
than my sketch.
This is my favorite makeup
I've done.
She looks just like
I want her to look,
and I love it.
I see myself
a little bit there.
The hair looks wacky
and big like mine.
I just hope the judges like it.
I think
it's really, really funny.
It's definitely me,
but in anime form.
I'm not feeling good
about this, honestly.
The face is okay,
but the armature looks ugly.
It's not the way
I wanted to paint it,
but it definitely looks like
what I had sketched out.
I still like it.
Judges, it's time
to take a closer look
at our anime characters.
- Did a good job on the wig.
- Mm-hmm.
They should spend more time
on the eyes.
It just looks like
a sharpie painted...
Yeah.
Wow.
It's all one piece.
Can you turn around for us?
That's a lot of scales.
In such a short amount of time,
he did lots
of complicated detail.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
This isn't wardrobe.
This is all stuff that he did.
Yeah, that's a lot of work too.
- That's a neat prop.
- Yes.
She really tried to get
that reflectivity--
the way they draw anime.
I get it.
The eyes are pretty accurate.
It looks like Niko.
He really hits
this counter-shading,
the way that they blend
the paint in the anime.
I wish he would have brought
it up on the face a little.
Yeah, it's not good contrast
on the face.
- Yeah.
This thing
looks like Waldo on LSD.
Is this vacuform?
- Yeah, it's a vac--
- That's a good idea.
All right.
Thank you.
I think the face
is the best part of it.
Yeah.
Up close, far rougher
than far away.
The suit is falling apart.
It's just horrible.
I'm very worried
that I could be going home.
Shit.
We want to know what you think
of tonight's transformations.
Tell us on Twitter,
using #FaceOff.
Up close, far rougher
than far away.
The suit is just horrible.
It looks like it's falling apart
in front of the judges,
so, for me,
it's not looking good.
The colors blend together.
It's hard to see the form.
I like what he did
with the hair.
Okay.
Thank you.
The judges have scored
your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Daran, Corinne,
George, and Graham.
You are the best
and the worst this week.
The rest of you are safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
The judges will now like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Daran, please step forward.
Tell us about your concept
and what inspired it.
My alter ego is a person
who wants to break free
of society.
For me,
that's either birds or fish.
Because of Japan
and I love koi,
I decided to go with the fish
on this one.
The attention to detail
is quite impressive.
The scaling on the fish,
in particular, is gorgeous.
Also, working with
an animal form as an alter ego
is very prevalent
in anime fantasy.
So I think
you've done a great job.
Awesome.
Thank you.
The transition
from the water up on to the fish
is quite beautiful.
The whole thing
is exquisitely executed.
- It's a beautiful makeup.
- Thank you.
I am a fan of not using
the actor's eyes,
and I think you've done
a very good job
making it even more discreet.
It feels like
it's a nasal opening.
That's what I was going for.
Thank you.
You have a great sense
of proportion,
and you create
something totally different
from other people.
- It's really nice.
- That means a lot to me.
- Thank you very much.
- Daran, please step back.
Graham, please step forward.
Tell us the concept
behind your anime character.
I spend a lot of time
in a lab making monsters,
and I love plants.
This was a scientist
who turned himself
into a plant monster.
It looks like a reject
from Poison Ivy's Lab.
The plant-life arm
and the whole thing--
I don't get that part of it.
Yeah, I really wish
I could have done
a lot more painting.
The painting
would not have helped.
I expect much better from you.
Was this as an image
in your head when you started?
This is pretty close
to what I had illustrated.
I really just bit off
a little more than I could chew.
It looks like
you didn't have enough time.
I don't understand
the big googly eyes
as part of the lenses.
The hair feels anime to me,
but a little shock of hair
on the top of this thing's
not gonna save it.
Graham, please step back.
Corinne, please step forward.
Tell us
about your alter ego here.
I love Halloween,
and she's a giver of tricks
and treats,
depending on what's deserved.
I think you've done a great job
capturing the essence
of what anime is.
There's subtle sculpting
that feels anime,
particularly around the eyes.
It's very delicate.
I love that you drew
on the reflectivity.
That's very much in line with
the stylized drawing of eyes
and the way that they teach
anime eye drawing.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
I think this character
is the most anime character.
What you did proportion-wise
is pretty nice.
Thank you.
Corinne, you can step back.
Good job, little lady.
George, please step up.
Tell me about your concept.
Well, this blue crystal
is a meteorite,
and it's transforming me
into a mechanical superhero.
And he's a peacemaker.
If I look at just the head,
it's good,
but that whole thing--
it looks so cheesy.
This thing read, as soon
as it walked out, anime to me,
but there are
some horrible decisions
that set you back.
Why all the hard angles
on the face?
'Cause the crystal
is trying to transform my body
by making me
part of the whole suit.
But it's not sculpted that way,
and it sure as hell
is not painted that way.
- It's all one color.
- I agree.
I actually like
the sculpt of the face,
but it just doesn't go
with anything else.
The overall execution
is so subpar
and particularly subpar
for you.
George, please step back.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
- while they deliberate.
- Thank you.
All right, judges,
why don't we talk
about the looks
you liked the most this week?
Let's start with Daran.
Just to sculpt a koi--
the form itself is one thing.
Then to sculpt those scales
with such specificity
was really impressive.
I think the paint job
is really beautiful.
How he put the layers over it
is really nicely done.
The way it was kinetic
in the fact
that the fish
were swimming around his head--
I thought it was gorgeous.
All right,
let's move on to Corinne.
I thought
this was pretty fantastic.
the character was adorable.
She looked like
a cartoon to me.
Since it's anime,
the whole silhouette
is really important,
and the way she put the hair
around the head
and the balance with the face
and the size of the eyes,
that's a great thing
about that makeup,
is the proportion.
Let's move on to the looks
you liked the least.
- Let's start with Graham.
- This was a mess.
That big tree trunk tube
of an arm,
and those big old goggles
took up most of the face.
You couldn't even see
an expression,
even if the thing was trying
to make an expression.
It's probably his least
successful makeup he's done.
I did not see anything
that resembles
Japanese influence at all
in that makeup.
This feels like
he had some wonky idea
about doing a half-plant,
half-person,
jammed it into this challenge,
and it went horribly wrong.
He is definitely better
than this.
All right,
let's move on to George.
Here's another one
who's better than this.
I love George's design sense.
It was just buried
under terrible fabrication
and terrible paint.
His attempt at weathering
looked like he literally had
paint on his hands
and just smeared it
on the white surface.
With George and Graham,
I see the lack of planning
to carry to the end.
So, judges,
you have your special immunity.
Is that something you would like
to consider giving away tonight?
We have people on the bottom
that have really showed skills
in the past.
Both are better
than what they've done tonight.
You could say that about anyone
as we get deeper
into the competition.
Judges, have you made
your decisions?
Okay.
Let's bring them back out.
Glenn, tell us
about the top looks.
Daran, you gave us
a bizarrely beautiful creation,
and we were truly impressed
with the level of detail
in that sculpture.
Corinne, we thought
that you did an excellent job
capturing the spirit
of this challenge,
and your character was fun,
as well
as quintessentially anime.
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
Daran.
We have no idea where
you come up with this stuff,
but this was
an outrageously great makeup.
- Well done.
- Thank you very much.
I appreciate that.
Winning the foundation challenge
with kazu as the judge
and then winning
the spotlight challenge,
it's pretty damn exciting.
Daran, congratulations.
You and Corinne can head back
to the makeup room.
Unfortunately,
that means the two of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Graham...
You started
with some interesting ideas,
but somewhere along the way,
you went way off course.
George,
your technical execution
is well below
what you're capable of.
So who is going home tonight?
The person
going home tonight is...
Graham.
We didn't see
the anime inspiration,
and the execution
was way off as well.
That means, George,
you are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Sorry, bro.
Graham, it is a real shame
to see you go
because you showed such promise
in earlier challenges,
so much so that I thought
you might have made it
to the finale,
which is exactly why
we've decided to use
our special immunity tonight
and save you from elimination.
Wow.
Make sure we didn't waste
this one opportunity
we have this season.
Thank you
for this awesome chance,
and I think
this is a great catalyst
- for my next challenge.
- I hope so.
All right, Graham,
that means you are also safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you very much.
- Make it count.
You won't be sorry.
Holy moly.
I didn't expect
the judges to use that on me.
It's almost like a win.
Guess who they saved.
Shut up!
This special immunity
that they've never awarded
anybody ever
in the history of Face Off--
they gave it to me.
You deserve it, my friend.
- They believe in you.
- Me!
This second chance
is giving me a push
to do even better.
So I'm ready
for the next challenge.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net