The detail is impressive.
There's real subtle sculpting.
Your paint job is beautiful.
Previously on Face Off...
The artists flew
halfway around the world
for inspiration.
Tokyo is absolutely amazing.
Daran's anime koi character
earned him his second victory...
Wow.
And Graham was spared
from elimination
by the judges'
one-time wild card immunity.
Wow.
Holy moly.
And tonight, the artists
are faced with
a maddening challenge.
This is going to take you
to a very dark place.
I'm so excited.
But with stakes this high,
some will break.
What's wrong?
- Fuck.
- Call the medic.
I feel this stab in my back.
I can't move.
I don't have a solid concept.
I have to get on the ball
or I'm gonna go home.
It is a brilliant idea.
It feels alive.
Beautiful work.
It looks like she has
just something
stuck on her face.
In the end,
only one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan Professional
Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who'll be the next great name
in movie magic?
Face Off!
Welcome toFace Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
The judges gave
this special immunity to me.
I did not expect that.
It's a cool feeling that
they're just keeping me around.
- What's up, buddy?
- What up, y'all?
Good morning,
Mr. Graham.
The immunity card is gone.
You're here, buddy.
- I know.
- That's awesome.
They used it
on the right person,
and that's all that matters.
The pressure's on me,
'cause they were like,
"Make sure
we didn't waste this."
So I got to make sure
that the next thing I make
is awesome-looking, you know,
well-constructed,
and fits the challenge.
I can't be on bottom again.
No way.
Let's go to work.
Uh-oh.
We walk through the door...
Ooh.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, boy.
And the entire lab
has been changed
into this torture chamber.
What the hell?
This is creepy.
I'm so excited.
Wow.
Yes.
There are vials
with these different creatures
in them,
medical instruments
I've never seen before,
never even heard of.
- Oh.
- Ah, man.
- So cool.
- Yeah.
It's just insane.
Hey, guys,
how do you like the new lab?
Awesome.
Somehow I had
a feeling you'd like it.
In Hollywood,
makeup effects artists
are often asked
to create something
truly horrific or vile.
That leads us
to our next challenge,
which will take you
to a very dark place.
We're gonna do something dark.
We're gonna
do something haunting.
We're gonna do something real.
And I cannot wait.
Silence Of The Lambs,
The Island Of Dr. Moreau,
and American Horror Story
all feature scientists
who've gone mad and used
their scientific knowledge
to wreak havoc
on innocent victims.
And these demented doctors
won't stop
until they have satisfied
their bloodlust.
So in this spotlight challenge,
you are going to play
the role of mad scientist.
Whoa.
Oh, my God.
That's so cool.
And you're gonna create
a victim,
or perhaps more precisely,
a human guinea pig
that falls prey to your madness.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
I finally get to do something
organic and grotesque,
and I am so excited.
Of course, a mad scientist
is only as good
as his twisted tools,
so when I call your name,
I want you to select
one of these medical devices
to help inspire your victim.
Graham, you're up first.
I'm looking through
these bizarre medical devices
thinking, let's do something
I haven't done before,
something with electricity
running through it.
Electroshock machine.
Some cool stuff up there.
Antique amputation saw.
Leeches.
Embalming pump.
Rib cage opener.
Pneumatic bone auger.
Antique hand drill.
Trephine.
All right, I can already
see that evil look
in some of your eyes.
Go ahead and pick your models
and get started
on your designs.
I'll be back later on
with my dad
to check in
and see how you're doing.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Bye.
We choose our models
and start our designs.
My tool is
the antique amputation saw,
and I already see
the concept in my head,
because for the longest time
I have wanted to do, like,
a classic Frankenstein-inspired
makeup
that looks like it stepped out
of a black-and-white movie.
Does it get any more
perfect than this?
I don't think so.
My tool is
the electroshock machine,
and my concept is
an electronically reanimated
corpse.
There's all this light wire
and cool LED lights
that we have in the lab
that I haven't even played
with yet,
so I'm going to do
a really clean, cool makeup
and get these lights
going in there.
The trephine is used
for creating
circular incisions
in the skull.
What am I gonna do with that?
I'm a little stumped
on this one.
I'm not a huge fan of horror.
I'm more of
a sci-fi creature guy.
Everyone else is getting
their characters
sketched out, ready to go.
I'm just drawing a blank.
My victim has a conjoined twin.
The sculpture is gonna
have some pulling to it
that's gonna fade into the back
where the other head
is gonna start.
And the embalming pump
is going to preserve the tissue,
so as a mad scientist,
I can further operate on them.
The first thing I need to do
is sculpt out the face.
There's a twisting motion
to my character,
so I start working the clay
to give the illusion
that something is pulling
the face from the back.
I chose the antique hand drill.
_
I get this sick idea.
This pregnant woman got
kidnapped by this mad scientist,
and the mad scientist
wants to steal the baby
that she has inside of her.
That is sick.
I'm actually sculpting
three faces,
and I'm going to use
the pneumatic bone auger
to split them down the middle.
I've been waiting
for a realism challenge,
and I'm super excited
about this one.
I select the leeches.
I think they're really gross.
So I decided to put the leeches
in, like, different,
uncomfortable places
on the body.
I start thinking about
small silicon pieces
that I can
attach the leeches to.
An eye piece,
a really simple nose piece.
They're all separate elements,
and I'm going to be molding
them all at the same time.
That is vile.
Is that an ear?
Does it not look like an ear?
No, it does.
I have the rib cage opener.
So my concept
is this mad scientist
opens his victims up
and stretches the skin.
I got to create
a couple prosthetics,
and then each one has to be
hooked and stretched.
And both parts will be
connected with hooks and thread.
It's a lot of work to do,
so we'll see.
I'm making
some out-of-mouth teeth
that are supposed to attach
to the lips.
To do that, I need to create
a snap of her life cast,
and a snap is a small impression
of a singled-out area.
Once this sets up, I can
sculpt the teeth that I want.
I sculpt the teeth
on top of that little snap,
and it's looking pretty creepy.
_
What are you doing?
Come on, are you really?
It turns out Tyler and I
have similar concepts,
but I'm not gonna
change my designs
'cause this is something
I always wanted to do.
Hopefully,
Tyler's two-head thing
doesn't turn out
to look like mine.
Tyler's copying.
Oh, yeah.
I'm not copying anything.
Mine's completely different.
He's doing
a man and a woman face,
and I'm doing a parasitic twin.
It's nowhere--
nowhere near the same.
This is definitely
not a good position to be in.
I don't even
have a solid concept.
Every other challenge,
I've gotten concepts fast.
I've got them sketched out,
ready to go.
And this one is a struggle.
I'm here for a reason.
I'm here to show what I have.
There's still
so much I want to do.
But everybody else is sculpting
and I have nothing,
so I have to get on the ball
or I'm gonna go home.
Coming up...
I feel this stab in my back.
Let's call the medic.
I'm worried
my concept's too disturbing.
I think it's one
of your finest makeups.
It's really quite ingenious.
This is less than riveting.
It's the first day
of the mad scientist challenge,
and we have to take inspiration
from a medical instrument.
I picked the trephine
because it looks cool,
but all I have on my sketch pad
is a face
with some holes in the head.
Everybody else is sculpting,
and I'm just drawing a blank.
Let's get some clay,
start playing.
I decided
to just grab some clay
and start putting it
on the face,
hoping I get an idea.
As I'm sculpting the leeches,
I realize that everything
I know leeches to be used for
is actually a good thing.
So coming up with something
that could be evil or twisted
is much more difficult
than I thought.
I finally think of a concept.
Thank God.
The back story
that I come up with
while I'm sculpting
the face--
there's this plastic surgeon,
and he went mad.
So he takes females
and instead of making them
prettier,
he makes them grotesque.
I think it's a great idea.
Hey, guys,
here for the walk-through.
How are you?
I got
the antique amputation saw,
so what I'm doing is
a Frankenstein-inspired makeup.
So I'll--
Is this an ear right here?
Yeah.
Oh, I see it.
So you--
- Wow.
- Okay.
As long as you're moving
these body parts around,
you're gonna have
to be very careful.
These pieces are really
gonna have to look real.
Many years ago, I had
to sculpt up a pair of ears
for a special project.
Took me one day
just to do the ears.
You have to really capture
an ear
for that to read like an ear.
I chose leeches.
Placement of the leeches
is important.
Maybe there's a half a leech
burrowing into the skin
as opposed to just
gluing them onto the skin.
Right.
You want to make it as gross
as you possibly can too,
I think.
Right.
The purpose of my bone saw
is to split this thing in half,
and I'm gonna put
three faces on my model.
I'm gonna do male, female,
and then
some weird deformed thing,
like, down here
under the neck or chin.
You think I'm making a mistake
going with
a third face down below or--
It may get too confusing,
because when I see it,
right away,
there is something else
going on here...
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
And you're actually
putting a fourth down there.
You want to concentrate on this,
really getting that perfect.
All right, thank you.
I picked the trephine.
It's used for making
circular cuts in the skull.
My scientist finds women
who want plastic surgery.
And he's gonna use that thing
to drill holes in their head
and apply skin to their face
from other victims.
Whatever flesh tone
you pick out
as your medium one,
have lighter patches.
And the patch--
it's a little darker,
so it really looks like
a patchwork.
Oh, yeah.
All right, guys.
It's looking pretty creepy.
Good luck to everybody.
Thank you.
I've got the face finished,
and I want to mold it
as fast as I can.
Once the face is molded,
I can move on to figuring out
the appliances
that'll hold each one
of the electrodes
that are going into her legs
and into her arms.
This makeup has to be perfect
because the judges saved me
and I just don't want
to be on the bottom again.
At the end of day one,
I feel like I've really
gotten the face sculpt
to a good place.
I notice that a lot of people
are already molding,
but I'm trying to stay calm
and remember
this is a piece that
I want to be well-sculpted,
and it is important
to take the time.
- Time?
- Seven.
I'm gonna clean that mold in,
like, five minutes.
I don't know if this face
is gonna be done
by the end of the day
because I still have
to open it and clean it.
I'm trying to go
as fast as I can.
Time is running out,
but I want to go for it.
I only have one minute left
to clean the mold.
It's time, guys.
Nice job.
Thank you, Rashaad.
- Any time, bro.
- Thank you.
By the time I close it,
time is up
and my mold is ready.
I got it.
You got it?
I probably need to stop
doing molds at last minute.
So it's day two
of our mad scientist challenge.
We have 9 1/2 hours in the lab.
We have a face.
Look at how twisted
and demented this looks.
I asked Mr. Westmore
about the third face,
and he told me it might
get too busy,
so we came together
on the decision
that I should not be putting
a third face on this.
Can not even tell that
there's a person down there.
Cool.
That's what I'm going for.
I get my face piece,
and it looks gorgeous.
And I line it up with the cowl,
and there is the whole concept
I had in my head.
I can see the flow,
and I am just so stoked.
I think you got a winner there.
Isn't it neat?
I'm sculpting a simple cowl.
It's not gonna go
full down the neck.
It's just a cap
because I needed to show
incisions into the head
and I can't do that
with a regular bald cap.
And so I want it
to be thick enough to do that
but also thin enough
to look like a bald head.
I have two box molds that
I need to pour gelatin into
to create the leeches,
but I'm nervous
because everyone else
has a much bigger
and broader design.
I'm really worried
I'm not doing enough.
Okay, I'm making
a spine in the back
that's gonna be ripped open.
Tool goes like this
and then rips open
the chest and the back.
I'm gonna mold these
and run them in foam latex.
I want to wait
until I have everything here.
And when I have
all the molds ready,
then I'll open them
all at once.
My mad scientist
is bringing back dead bodies
through
the electroshock machine.
This stuff is called El wire.
I want this wire
to sort of connect everything
like she's sort of
being powered by it.
I'm trying to do some R&D
to figure out
how to get them to work right,
which--
I've shocked myself
a couple times.
You got you a pregnant girl?
Yep.
My character is pregnant,
and I'm trying to make it
really natural-looking.
So I do a test
using the hand drill.
And then I'm gonna
slice it open
like if the baby got out
of the belly.
I can't really open the--
I don't know.
There you go.
What, you never pulled
a baby out before?
Come on.
I'm holding the chest piece
and I'm washing the plaster
out of a bucket.
Ooh, you all right?
Oh.
What's wrong?
Fuck.
And all of a sudden,
I feel this stab in my back.
Let's call the medic over here.
I'm familiar with that pain,
and I know exactly what it is.
I have two herniated discs.
I can't move.
I mean, it's like
I'm totally freezed.
- Is it right in here?
- Yes. Yeah.
I'm actually worried
that this is gonna escalate.
So if that happens,
I'm out of the competition.
It's day two
of the mad scientist challenge,
and I have
this huge pain in my back.
I have two herniated discs,
and I'm actually worried
that this is gonna escalate.
So if that happens,
I'm out of the competition.
I start sewing into the foam
because it's supposed to look
like patchwork.
Started sewing mine,
but that's gonna take
too long to do all that.
Yes.
I have to cut down
on the amount of sew work
I'm gonna have to do.
You can't paint those on
with a little bitty brush?
That would go faster,
but it won't look as good.
I'd save that for last looks.
Yeah, I think I might.
Make sure you do
everything else.
- Is it right in here?
- Yes. Yeah.
The medic helps me
with a ice pack.
It still hurts.
Got it?
Yeah.
But I still have to do a lot.
So I have to just get up
and keep working.
I'm hoping that I can finish
what I started.
I find myself
with one hour left,
and I still need to sculpt
a blender piece over the knee
so it looks like
he's missing a leg.
I'm just gonna do it.
- Time?
- 28 minutes.
I have to get this thing
molded by the end of today.
One minute.
That's time, people.
Time.
Brushes down.
I get it molded.
I need to clean it out
first thing in the morning
and run it in poly foam.
So I have a lot to do tomorrow.
Hopefully I can focus
and just do art.
It's application day,
and we got four hours
in the lab
and one hour in last looks.
My back hurts like crazy,
and, like, I'm limping,
but I don't have time for pain.
Let's keep going.
Let's get to
the important stuff, like you.
The first thing I do
is open up and clean out
my leg stump prosthetic.
My only issue now is that
I have an immense amount
of painting that I have to do.
I just hope
there's time to do it.
♪ ah ♪
Where's my baby?
Wahh!
Good to meet you.
I'm Daran.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
- How are-- Ooh, a baby.
- Yeah.
You¡re being tortured...
I'm ready to just get
through application today,
and I immediately take
the time to make sure
that these edges are well done.
You can't do
a minimalistic makeup
and have edges everywhere.
All right, sir,
are you ready for this?
My cowl is attached to a shirt,
so there's no rippage involved.
Right turn.
It's just great to see something
that just popped in your head
starting to come to life
before your eyes.
Yep, it wor--
It works.
All right, good.
I start applying
the belly piece.
It fits her really well,
but I'm nervous about my concept
being too disturbing
for the judges.
I love babies, so...
The last thing that I want to do
is offend anyone.
All right, let's position this.
I'm applying the chest piece.
It's taking me forever
'cause my back
is slowing me down, man.
Let's turn you this way.
I hope I have enough time
to get this paint job done.
We'll see how it goes.
It's all about
the paint job on this challenge.
I go with a dark blood color,
which is an under-color,
and I think
I'm gonna end up using
about eight to ten colors
to get this paint job
just right.
- Ready?
- Mm-hmm.
At this point in the game,
I'm just worried
that the judges
are gonna call us out
on application.
Let me get them edges
laid down.
I also need to get hair
on this thing perfectly,
or it just won't come together.
All right, you feeling
pretty stuck in there?
Oh, yeah.
Would you hold this for me?
Thank you.
Before I put the face on,
I angle the lights
right next to her mouth,
but I need to make sure
that they're not touching
her skin,
because if they get too hot,
that can start
to cause discomfort.
Your face.
There is the chance that
the lights won't even work.
That electricity
needs to show through.
That's the only nervous part.
Oh, poop.
Physically and mentally,
I'm feeling a little numb.
I'm at a hard place
at this point.
I know I didn't do enough,
but all I can do
is push forward
with what I have.
I just start painting
on a grey scale
by paxing a light grey
over everything.
I want this to be
the cleanest makeup
that I've done
this whole competition.
So if I don't have the time
to do the leg piece,
I hope that they at least
see the time
that was put into
the face sculpt.
Whether or not
they will appreciate that
is really up in the air
at this point.
How much time, five minutes?
Like, seven.
I'm running out of time,
and right now,
it's not looking impressive.
I still have to do
a lot of paint job,
the whole back,
the whole front.
All right,
everybody, that's time.
Brushes down.
I got to stay here
for my family,
my baby girl that's coming.
If I win this money,
it's for her,
so I'll do my best.
Coming up...
Let's finish this, man.
Let's finish this.
It's not looking like
I really envisioned it.
- I'm really nervous.
- Brilliant idea.
It looks like she has
something stuck on her face.
Beautiful work.
Zip-a-dee-doo-da.
We get to last looks.
We got one hour,
and it's gonna be so intense
because I have a lot to paint.
Let's finish this, man.
Let's finish this up.
My back is hurting,
but I'm not paying attention
to that.
I'm just doing the job
that I have to do.
I really need to focus on
getting the eyebrows on
and making them look
really sweaty,
really tying the wardrobe
and everything together.
_
- Yep.
- Nice.
I have to hand stitch
all of these stitches
in last looks.
I had budgeted ten minutes
to do that,
and now I'm realizing that
it's gonna take a lot longer.
So I've decided
to just sew half of it.
- Fuck.
- How should I walk?
Like each movement is
electrocuting you a little bit.
Yeah.
- You okay with it?
- Yeah.
That's it, everybody.
Time's up.
Brushes down.
I'm really nervous.
It's not looking
like I really envisioned it.
I don't know where I'll stand.
We'll see.
Welcome to
theFace Offreveal stage.
Tonight,
one of you will be eliminated.
Let's say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening.
- Hey.
- Hi, Glenn.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
Hi, everybody.
- Hello, Ve.
- Hi, Ve.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
- Hello, guys.
- Hi, Neville.
This week,
your spotlight challenge
was to play the role
of mad scientist
and create a human guinea pig
who has fallen prey
to your madness.
I also asked each of you
to choose a medical device
to inspire your creations.
So let's take a look
at your victims.
I'm still a little bit nervous
that she's offensive.
I hope the judges
understand it.
I hope at least I can be safe.
I absolutely executed
my vision on this one.
This is exactly
what I wanted to do.
I'm loving this makeup.
I'm thrilled.
He looks like he belongs
in that era.
It really looks
pretty disturbing,
and I'm just really happy
with the character.
I love it.
I'm so happy
I got this second chance.
You can still see
all the lights
through the bright light
that they shine on her,
and it looks fantastic.
Everything I wanted
to bring across, you can see.
She's bloody, amazing.
I'm excited.
As I'm looking at
everybody's and seeing mine,
I know I didn't
quite push the envelope
enough on this one.
My character walks out,
and I'm really liking it.
I mean, it's impactful,
and that chest looks gnarly.
And he looks dead
and looks abused.
Judges, why don't you
take a closer look
at these poor souls?
I think he did
a pretty great job painting it.
I don't understand what
it has to do with the drill.
Yeah, and this is
really poor taste, I gotta say.
Let's have you open
your mouth as wide as you can.
That's so wild.
So important having
that little additional detail
at the sutures.
Mm-hmm.
Just elevates it so much.
Thanks.
Where are the stitches?
Got them started.
Yeah.
Really looks cool.
Let's see your hand.
- Wow.
- Okay, good enough.
Open your mouth all the way.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
What's interesting is,
both profiles work.
When you look
at this side of this head,
it still looks like a head.
Come around.
- Stop there.
- Yeah.
I mean, that just looks like
he's turning this way.
Yeah.
Come back around please.
The paint job
on this is really nice.
- I agree.
- Thank you.
Go ahead and open your mouth.
Oh.
Oh, all right.
It looked better than
you thought it was going to.
This is a lot better
up close than from afar.
Yeah, it is.
Most of these light gags
don't really work
when they come out
on stage in full light.
This one does.
- It tells a story.
- Thank you.
Do you think
this is a skin transplant?
The jaw just doesn't
make sense there.
Turn.
He did some nice hair laying,
finally.
Back around, please.
Thanks.
- Okay.
- Ew.
I am confused.
Is there a whole nose tip
on here?
Yeah, I can see-- yeah.
So we've changed
the profile of the nose.
- What is this?
- Those are leeches.
No, I know, but they don't
look like leeches, do they?
No, they don't.
And what an odd decision,
when you could do
really crazy surgical stuff,
to spend time putting
a nose and the chin on
when we don't know what the guy
looks like to begin with.
I've made some really
poor decisions,
and I'm really worried
'cause I know I'm on the bottom.
What do you think
of tonight's designs?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
What an odd decision,
when you could do
really crazy surgical stuff,
to spend time putting
a nose and the chin on
when we don't know what the guy
looks like to begin with.
I've made some really
poor decisions,
and I'm really worried
'cause I know I'm on the bottom.
All this nice staining
on the skin,
that's really cool.
Turn around.
He's covering up
some of the best stuff.
- This is really nice.
- Yeah.
Yeah, the paint job's
really nice.
Thank you.
Well, the judges
have scored your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Tyler,
Graham,
Niko,
George,
congratulations.
You are all safe and can
head back to the makeup room.
The rest of you were the best
and the worst this week.
The judges would now like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Chloe, you're up.
Chloe, I'd love to hear
the backstory of your character
and how you took inspiration
from your surgical implement.
The backstory is,
the mad scientist
was trying to be a surgeon.
The saw was her mechanism
of choice.
And I wanted to make
this character
look like it stepped out
of a black-and-white film.
I think it's a brilliant idea.
Super cool makeup.
Your choice to create
something that looks
as if it stepped off
of the silver screen
is indeed a laudable one.
I did
a black-and-white movie.
It was called Ed Wood.
Oh, I know.
And I found that
when you just use black,
there's so much blue in it,
which is what has happened
to your makeup.
It's kind of gone
to the blue side.
You have to put in
some dark browns to make it
actually look like
a black-and-white movie,
but it's an awesome makeup.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You had a concept
that was unique.
I think it's one
of your finest makeups.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Chloe, you can head back.
Nice job.
Rashaad.
Tell us
what medical instrument you had
and the story behind
this young lady.
The instrument is called
a trephine,
and my idea was a surgeon
who wanted
to make people
his own weird kind of dolls.
He would use pieces
of other people's skin
on their faces.
I don't know.
I'm not very happy
with this one, Rashaad.
The thing on the jaw
is just wrong.
It looks like she has something
stuck on her face,
and you have this poor
patchwork skin thing
going on that isn't defined.
Mm-hmm.
I have a love-hate
with this one.
Could you mind just turning
a little bit so I can see that?
That's the love part.
And if you don't mind
turning the opposite direction.
Ah, there's the hate.
It's that jaw.
- It's senseless.
- Mm-hmm.
This is less than riveting,
to be sure.
It doesn't feel like you had it
straight in your head.
It's just not
a fully realized concept.
Rashaad, thank you very much.
Please step back.
Thanks anyways.
Corinne, please step forward.
So tell us about your concept
and what medical device
you got.
Medical device I got
were leeches,
and it was just the thought
of being tied down
and having them on you
is just really gross.
It feels like bondage Rambo
with some stuff stuck to him.
It's just so devoid
of visual interest.
I wish there was more here.
I know.
I do, too.
There's nothing
about this makeup that is
in any way, shape, or form
expressive of you
as an artist
or something we haven't seen.
The work itself
isn't horribly done,
but it's a virtual black hole
of original thought.
You have done
some really cool stuff for us,
but this is not one of them.
I got to say, though,
you did a great job
with the appliances
that you put on him,
but we don't see them.
I'm really disappointed
in you this week.
Corinne, thank you.
Please step back.
Daran, you're up.
Daran, tell us how
the surgical instrument
inspired this.
I chose the pneumatic bone saw.
This is an experiment
that was born and raised.
The mad scientist
decided he wasn't happy
with the male and female,
so he started splitting it,
kind of messing around
with things.
The time that you had
to have pulled this off
at this level
is beyond impressive.
This well-trodden
two-head,
I've seen it done horribly.
This is stellar.
It's so creepy that
the faces are a bit too big.
I'm thrilled
with this thing, man.
Thank you very much.
I appreciate that.
I love this guy.
It's almost like
the two people are trying
to get away from each other,
which is a really cool idea.
It's really quite ingenious.
That's awesome.
Thank you.
I think there's some
really gorgeous stuff
happening in the face.
There's nothing better than
when you satisfy the challenge,
but it doesn't feel
like it's just a concept.
This character feels alive.
So, beautiful work.
Very cool.
Thank you.
Daran, thank you very much.
- Please step back.
- You're awesome.
All right, guys,
the judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you'd please
head back to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
All right, judges,
so let's talk about the looks
you liked the most tonight.
How about Chloe?
She did such
a great job of coming up
with an original idea.
She pushed the bounds.
She thought out of the box.
Being in
that black-and-white genre,
I think it worked
really well for her.
All right,
let's move on to Daran.
That was really well done.
That mouth should really
bother us,
but he manages
to move our eye across
from one face to the other
without tripping us up
with that mouth.
All right, judges,
let's move on to the looks
you liked the least.
Let's start with Rashaad.
Oy, the teeth
out in the middle of its jaw.
It just reads like a mistake.
We don't know if
we're supposed to be seeing
torn skin exposing the jaw
or if it's somebody else's jaw.
If he would have
actually done, like,
a patchwork face, like a doll,
that would have been cool,
with different colored skin.
It was not good.
There was just nothing there.
All right,
let's move on to Corinne.
Poor girl.
She was palpably uninspired.
I find it an extremely
odd choice to have spent
so much time changing
the guy's jawline and nose.
It didn't contribute
to the idea of the surgery.
It wasn't like she was
putting them under the skin
or doing anything
interesting with them.
You know, she could have
done all kinds of cool stuff.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
We certainly have.
Let's bring them back out.
Glenn, tell us about
tonight's top looks.
Chloe, we love that
you delivered
such a clean application,
but it was the risk you took
on such a bold concept
that really set you apart.
Daran, super impressed
with the sculpture
again this week.
The anatomical choices
in the face flowed beautifully.
All right, Glenn,
who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of this challenge is...
So Glenn, who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of this challenge is...
Daran.
We thought that your creation
was conceptually sound,
and the execution
was outrageously good.
I don't know what to say
other than
thank you, thank you,
thank you.
The judges seem
to like what I'm doing.
Hopefully I can keep it up
and keep doing what
I love doing.
Daran, congratulations.
You and Chloe can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, guys.
Unfortunately,
that means the two of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us about
tonight's bottom looks.
Rashaad, your work this week
smacked of a concept
that simply was not
fully realized.
It just didn't work.
Corinne, your lack of concept
was quite disconcerting to us
and left us feeling very
underwhelmed with this makeup.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Corinne.
Your concept and makeup
were so simple,
and at this point
in the competition,
it's just not enough.
Thank you for the opportunity.
That means, Rashaad,
you are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Corinne, you have delivered
some really amazing makeups.
You're gonna do really well
in this business.
Thank you.
Corinne, I'm so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
It's really been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- Thank you.
- Good luck, honey.
I'm disappointed.
Concept is something
I struggled with
throughout the competition.
I wish I'd been able to show
a bigger and better
kind of idea.
What?
I didn't put
nearly as much effort
into this particular challenge
as I should have.
But being here has been
such a great push as an artist.
I love makeup.
I love effects.
I love doing this for a living,
and I'm really excited
about the possibilities
for the future.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net