It looks beautiful, it's fantastic.
I think this guy's terrific.
You simply missed.
Previously on Face Off...
Rashaad's plant-inspired vampire
earned him his second win.
But instead of elimination...
This is actually a two-part challenge.
And the second half starts right now.
Oh, my gosh. Second chance.
And tonight...
You guys already created the vampire.
For the second part of your challenge,
you will have to create its greatest enemy.
- Yes.
- Whoa.
This is great.
But with the impending finale,
any setback could mean the end.
I really want to win tonight.
At least, I want to be in the last three.
But my wrist is giving me intense pain.
It just slows me down.
Who's gonna see that from 20 feet away?
This is a beautiful paint job.
You did something I haven't seen before.
The overall look is an issue for me.
In the end, only one will
win a VIP trip from
Kryolan professional make-up
to one of their 85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500, and $100,000.
Who will be the next
great name in movie magic?
Face off!
Welcome to Face Off.
So this is, like, the
craziest elimination, uh, ever,
'cause no one's going home.
And all of a sudden, we're
just driving somewhere.
And it's like, bring it on.
- Whoa.
- Oh, my God.
Look at this place.
It's dark, scary. We're tired.
And it's like, where are we?
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Welcome to the court of miracles
on the Universal Studios backlot.
This historic set has inspired filmmakers
since the early 1900s.
And you might actually recognize it
from House of Dracula,
The Mummy, Frankenstein,
and The Wolf Man.
This is where, like, the villagers run out,
and you feel like you're in the movie.
You feel like you're
standing in a part of history.
And it... it's so cool.
Now I mentioned a special guest.
He's here to tell you
about your last challenge
before the finale.
Please welcome back production designer
and director Patrick Tatopoulos.
- There he is.
- Hello.
Hello.
Well, I know these guys are dying
to know more about their next challenge.
So why don't you fill 'em in?
Well, you guys have already created
one of the most popular movie villains,
the vampire.
For the second part of your challenge,
you will have to create its greatest enemy,
the werewolf.
Yeah!
Since I was an eight-year-old,
I've been obsessed with werewolves.
It's, like, crazy.
I watched the Wolf Man with my father,
like, I don't know how many times.
So this is great.
That's right, your spotlight challenge
is to create a werewolf nemesis
that comes from the same
world as your vampires.
Wow.
Patrick, we're very excited to have you
joining us this week on the reveal stage.
What are you gonna be looking for
in their final creations?
I'm looking for a very uncommon design.
Do not forget that this werewolf
will have to belong to the same world
your vampire comes from.
That's very, very important.
Now there is just one more thing.
Your werewolves must incorporate
a newly evolved feature
specifically designed
to take their vampire rivals down.
Now remember, this is your last
spotlight challenge before the finale.
Only three of you will make it through.
The judges will be considering both
your vampires and your werewolves
when choosing this season's final three.
Well, we're gonna leave you here
to get started on your sketches.
Good luck.
- Thank you.
- Good luck, guys.
- Good night.
- Thank you.
♪ Do it, do it, do it, do it ♪
My vampire was Yara-ma-yha-who
from Australia.
My concept is, my vampires evolve
into werewolves over time.
And that kind of blend
is gonna be kind of cool.
My special weapon is gonna be
bone protrusions that come out
of their index finger, like a blade.
And it can jump at him and stab him.
My vampire has this big tongue that has,
like, acid and poison.
So I'm thinking... the
concept for my werewolf is,
he has all these spikes that protects him
from the acid tongue of the vampire.
And the spikes turn into stakes
he can attack the vampire with.
Yesterday was kind of like,
uh-oh, wake-up call, you know?
I focused too much on covering the vampire
and forgot about the simplest things,
like proportions and things like that.
Now it's almost like a second chance.
Now I know what I need to work on.
So my werewolf's ability is this extension
of his bone that comes out, like a spike.
I really want to push myself,
do as much work as I can
to prove that I deserve
to be in the finale.
I gave my vampire an Asian theme,
and I know I want to do
that again with the werewolf.
So I'm giving him a paisley brow
with an armored nose and tufts of fur
almost like their dragons have.
My vampire has plants
that have taken over his body,
and one way to kill them is with fire.
So I want to incorporate
that into my werewolf.
All right, guys, let's go home.
After doing a full day of make up
and finding out what our next challenge is,
we definitely need to
recharge for tomorrow.
All right.
I'm gonna redeem myself this time.
- Werewolves.
- This is it, guys.
It's very surreal to know
that we started with 15.
Now it's only four.
- Congratulations to you...
- Thank you.
- Yeah, man.
- That win.
It took me a while.
It took a couple challenges,
but now I'm starting
to get my point across.
Just hoping to make it to the finale.
Yeah, I think we want to go big on concept,
but not on making something super big,
because you can make the same with less.
And I have learned that.
I'm really excited that I have
one more chance to prove myself.
This has never happened
in the history of Face Off.
This time, I really want to focus
on the simplest things, getting those down
before I even start the make up.
Last challenge, I really didn't focus
on getting my ideas together,
and the judges didn't like it.
I'm gonna have to step it up.
All right, guys, let's
go make some werewolves.
- Let's do it.
- Of course, yes.
So we finally get to the lab.
We were super excited.
And we've got six hours today.
The first thing I got to
do is get that face done
and get it out for foam.
I don't want to do classic werewolf.
We have to do something original.
And I don't want to do a total big snout.
I want something in the middle.
It's not gonna be a static snout.
It's gonna growl and roar, you know.
And I think it might work very well.
Werewolves are all, like,
different from each movie.
There's werewolves that look like dogs.
There's werewolves that
have, like, big snouts.
There are werewolves that
even look more feline.
I think everyone is going
for different directions,
because we're trying to follow
the same world of the vampire.
Oh, okay.
Today I really want to focus on the face.
I love when werewolves are transforming.
And I always hate that
look of a big muzzle,
'cause it just reads fake to me.
So I kind of want to keep my werewolf
more on the human side,
just to kind of show that this thing's
in mid-transformation.
Because this is an Asian werewolf,
I want to sculpt Asian elements into it.
So I'm giving it the paisley brow,
a strong, dragon-like nose.
And because fire is gold in
traditional Asian culture,
I want the hands and face gold
to tie the whole look together.
Wow, that's [Bleep] gorgeous, dude.
Hey, guys.
We're here for a walk-through.
- Hey.
- How are you?
So tell us about your werewolf.
I want it to have these
spikes in the whole body
that protects him from
the vampire's tongue.
The mouth should be a little bigger.
It ought to come back
into here a little more
to get away from the reptilian look
and get it more into the werewolf.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
I want my werewolf to
have the ability of fire.
These tufts of hair almost give it
the look of fire.
And then paint it with the orange,
just to bring that across.
With all the sculpting you have going on,
- don't get too dark.
- Okay.
Your vampire read so well.
You don't want this to totally disappear.
Okay.
I'm trying to keep
some elements of human, right?
I would work on the nose a little bit more.
In most of the canines,
there's a split in here.
And you could take this
nostril down to here,
maybe close that up a little teeny bit.
Yeah, I get what you're saying.
My werewolf has this extremity coming off,
and that's what he uses
to kill the vampire.
Mm-hmm.
I'm just wondering, in your mind,
what makes this a werewolf?
The nose and there's this zone.
Yeah, but who's gonna see
that from 20 feet away?
Uh-oh.
You've got human lips on there.
There's really no muzzle.
It's gonna look like a vampire.
Mr. Westmore is not
liking what he's seeing.
This is, like, the worst
time to not impress him.
That canine look is in the muzzle.
- Okay.
- That's what's gonna sell your werewolf.
This is getting too close to the end
to not really keep on your "A" game.
For the first time, I
feel stumped at this point.
I'm standing back, going, "this sucks,
is this thing gonna send me home?"
Coming up...
My finger extensions
just broke and crumbled.
It's not like I sculpted it.
This is a beautiful paint job.
Thank you.
You did something I haven't seen before.
It's gonna look like a vampire,
as opposed to werewolf.
It's day one of our werewolf challenge,
and I feel stumped at this point.
Mr. Westmore thinks my
face sculpt reads vampire,
but I'm making a werewolf.
This sucks.
I go in the back room.
I just want to really clear my head.
I don't want to see anybody's sculpt.
I just want to focus on mine.
All right, guys, we're heading out.
- Good luck.
- Bye.
Thank you.
Time's up.
My face is sculpted the way I want it.
So now it's time to mold this thing
and get it ready for foam.
I mold as fast as possible.
While that's setting up,
I get to work on my cowl.
I'm in the back room,
trying to figure this out.
- And all of a sudden...
- Okay, Tyler,
we want to come back and talk to you.
I feel like you got a little scared
because the judges didn't
receive you very well last night.
- Yeah.
- And it's showing in your...
'cause you're such a good artist.
Don't forget that.
Don't let this challenge scare you
into doing something
that could send you home.
You're cutting back.
And you need to, you know, go for it.
Your drawing has it,
with all the stuff in it that's great.
- Yeah.
- Translate it to here.
- All right, thank you.
- Don't be scared.
- You can do this, come on.
- Thank you so much.
- Good luck.
- All right, thanks.
I'm going to take Mr. Westmore's advice.
I have my sketchbook.
And my werewolf drawing is exactly
what I pictured in my head.
So I think I'm finally heading
in the right direction.
It really means a lot that they came back.
They really gave me a boost and also
gave me advice that could help me win.
The game is on.
My cowl piece is very important,
because it's gonna separate
my werewolf from the vampire.
Since they come from the same world,
I have to do something to make him
stand out as a different species.
So I'm going with a very
massive head and neck.
And the ears have to look wolfy,
but not that wolfy.
So it's gonna be tricky.
That's cool, man.
It's getting there now.
I'm thinking, what could make this
a much cooler werewolf?
Let me change the forehead a little bit,
adding bits of Clay to extend the eyebrows
to follow a curvature.
I think that's gonna be a cool feature,
'cause it's gonna bring
you right up the face
and have your eyes follow to the skull.
What's our time over there?
Our time is 2:27.
But I just feel so behind.
My face is molded,
so I want to start blocking out the cowl,
so I can have a starting
point for tomorrow.
There's a little bit more
pressure for this challenge,
because the judges didn't like my vampire.
And that makes me really scared,
because three of us is
gonna go to the finale,
and one of us won't.
31 more minutes.
I am zooming with my face,
and I'm molding this in crazy, record time.
And the scene is chaotic.
Everyone is really scrambling
to get everything out.
Let's make some noise.
Go, Niko.
No time, no time.
That's time, guys. Let's go.
That is time.
- All right.
- Whoo!
This day is going so much better.
After having this big setback,
I'm gonna forget it, move forward.
I'm completely a new, new guy right now.
So it's day two of our werewolf challenge.
We have 9 1/2 hours today.
My face looks gorgeous.
Now it reads very dog, wolf like.
If everything turns out great,
this make up is gonna help me
get into the finale for sure.
I gotta finish the cowl,
so I can start molding it.
But it's gonna take a while
to create this whole big piece.
And I got to make sure that I have time
to start working on the spikes.
I think I can get it done.
I just have to work really, really fast.
I want to sculpt extensions,
just to make the hands look bigger,
like, if they conjure fire.
First, I cast both of my hands in alginate,
and then I pour in polyurethane resin.
Once those are cured, I release them
from the mold...
Yay.
Screw them into a board,
so I have a base to sculpt off of,
and start sculpting my
finger extensions on them.
So the bone extensions, I'm thinking,
"all right, what if I take a foam noodle
and carve it into this long spike?"
to give them a bone feel,
I coat them with epoxy.
The epoxy gives it a sheen
but also makes it hard as a rock.
I just sand it down.
And it's starting to look like bone.
Nice, how'd you do those?
Rock-ass hard.
- What'd you put on this?
- Stuff.
I know what you put on
that. I'm not an idiot.
As I'm trying to pop my hand mold open...
No.
It just breaks and
crumbles and comes apart.
My mistake was, I went just with ultracal.
I didn't use any backing,
like burlap or hemp,
because I wanted to save time.
So the mold was really weak and frail.
My werewolf is supposed
to kill vampires with fire.
This hand piece was going
to accentuate that look.
Even though I did win the last challenge,
all it would take is one mistake,
and I can still go home.
That was a complete waste.
No.
So it's day two of our werewolf challenge.
My finger extensions
just broke and crumbled.
So now I'm just trying to figure out
what I can use instead
to make my concept work.
And it sucks, because
we have no time to waste.
So I just have to very quickly
figure out what I'm gonna do.
Take more than a broken mold to stop me.
My cowl has to be done
by the end of the day.
I'm running out of time.
It's heavy as hell.
And my wrist is giving me intense pain.
It's slowing me down,
because it really hurts
when I pick up very heavy stuff.
You got it?
Yeah, it's just my fractured wrist.
The pain is there, but I just have
to power through it and keep going.
Yeah, I'm gonna finish this.
Thank you, bro.
So my werewolf has all these spikes
that protects him
from the acid tongue of my vampire.
I'm using different sizes of foam.
And I'm using the sander to make a point.
And then I'm using the heat gun,
so the spikes will have
really interesting form.
We got 40 minutes.
I can do this, I can do this.
Since my sculpted hands didn't work,
my plan "B" is aluminum foil fingertips
with latex wrapped around them.
I fabricate the fingers
with paper towels and latex.
Hot glue gives the aluminum foil backing,
so it doesn't bend or crease.
Then I take latex and paper towels
and wrap that around each finger,
so all the fingers will
go on like a glove piece.
How'd you make all the claws?
- Latex and hot glue.
- Cool.
Going through these setbacks
and having things not work that
are essential to your
design is always a bummer.
But that means I have to be
even more driven to make it out on top.
I'm pre-painting the face,
and I think it's really
starting to come together.
And I even have time to
make the nose look wet,
using a gloss medium.
All right, guys, that's time.
Brushes down.
At the end of day two, I have
a beautiful face set up for tomorrow.
Still debating on whether
or not I should use it
only because I really want to make sure
I match the cowl perfectly with the face,
so I can do everything as a whole.
I wish all of us luck.
We've been working hard.
And we all deserve it.
But we have to do this for our loved ones.
I'm doing this for my child
and my wife and my parents.
So I'll do whatever it takes.
You should do it for your baby girl.
She's gonna be so cute.
I can't wait. I don't know, George.
She's gonna be beautiful, dude.
You see my wife?
That's it. Yeah, but you got
to take your genes into consideration.
Oh, well, hopefully it
will take all of hers.
I'm just messing with you.
There's a lot riding on this one challenge.
So it feels good to relax together.
These guys are like a family.
Here's to, uh, great application.
- Whoo!
- Let's go, let's go.
Let's see what we got.
So it's application day.
We have four hours in the
lab, one hour at last looks.
And it's definitely
the most important application day of all,
because this is gonna determine
who's in the finale.
So I get the new face, and it actually
came out much cleaner than the last one.
So I'm looking at
the beautifully pre-painted piece,
and I'm like, "nope,
let's start from scratch."
I need to put these pieces all on
and start the entire recipe
of painting this guy from the beginning.
- Oh, yeah.
- Go have a seat, brother.
- Yeah.
- My model got sick.
So I got a change of model.
You're a werewolf from Australia.
I'm a little concerned.
My original model has very thick lips.
And my new model has very thin lips.
So that's gonna make a
huge gap in the prosthetics.
And it might look funky.
So I'm just hoping that it works out.
Let's see.
All right. It's like-
there's some issues here.
I have some trouble with the cowl.
The cowl has some ripped pieces
in both of the ears.
So I need to glue them down and patch.
That's gonna take time.
Let's see where your eyes are at.
I'm putting the face on my new model.
And I'm seeing a huge gap here.
I just have to glue teeth in
as best as possible.
The teeth are actually
distorting the jaw a little bit.
It's making the whole
face kind of squish down.
It's looking decent,
but it's not like I sculpted it.
Open your mouth, like...
So this paint job is a pretty long process,
and I have to make it look like it has hair
but not actually lay on the hair.
So that means I have to
airbrush strands of
hair all over this thing.
This is it, last make up
right before the finale.
I want to make sure that
everything is perfect.
Everything's going really quickly.
The paint looks even better
than the pre-painted piece.
I'm glad I made the decision
to go with this face.
And it looks great.
I want the paint scheme to be related
to my aswang vampire from the Philippines,
to have that light palette
but in a different way.
So I'm going more with
grays and some purple tones.
- How many minutes?
- Eight.
Eight minutes, okay.
So all these adjustments that I made
for the face took me too much time.
I'm worried, 'cause I only
have a base coat on it,
and I have a lot to do
to finish this paint job.
All right, guys, it's time.
Brushes down.
You know, I really want to win tonight.
At least, I want to be in the last three.
So I have a lot to do.
This is not the challenge
that I want to go home.
Coming up...
This is the one that's
gonna take us to the finale.
So it's a lot of pressure.
He looks like he could
kick everybody's ass.
The last person that will be joining us
in the finale is...
Aah!
We get to last looks. We have one hour.
And the first thing I
do is attach the spikes.
It's time-consuming,
because I have to put glue
in all of them and hold
them until they dry.
Because if I don't do
that, they'll come out.
There's definitely a
lot riding on this hour.
So I'm making sure
everything is glued down,
everything is seen.
There's so many things I have to
take into consideration.
All I have to focus on
is touch-ups and hair.
I have hair coming out
of the chest and hands.
And it looks great.
I got a lot of paint to do.
I have to also epoxy
all those protrusions on
the whole frickin' body.
So I'm worried about time.
This is the one that's
gonna take us to the finale.
One of us is gonna be sent home,
so it's a lot of pressure.
All right, guys, we got 15 minutes left.
Time's up.
Looks good.
I think it looks decent for the time I had
and all the situation with
the model and everything,
so I'm happy with it.
I hope the judges like it as well.
Welcome to the Face Off reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you will be eliminated,
and three of you will
move on to our finale.
First, let's say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of optic nerve make up effects studio
Glenn Hetrick. Good evening.
Hi, Glenn.
Three-time Oscar-winning
make up artist Ve Neill.
Good evening, gentlemen.
- Hey, Ve.
- Hi, Ve.
Creature and concept designer Neville Page.
- Hello, guys.
- Hi, Neville.
And joining us again tonight
is production designer, creature designer,
and director Patrick Tatopoulos.
Good to see you.
Great to see you again.
I'm sure you're anxious to see
what these guys have created.
We've got four great artists here.
I'm very anxious to see their work.
All right, this week I surprised you
with our first-ever two-part challenge.
Your second spotlight challenge
was to create a werewolf
Nemesis for the vampires
you created last week.
Now I also asked that you incorporate
a newly evolved feature in your werewolves
specifically designed to take
their vampire rivals down.
As a reminder, the judges will be taking
both characters into consideration
when choosing which of you
will make it to the finale.
Let's take a look at your creations.
My werewolf walks out onstage.
He's acting. He's roaring.
And he looks great. I'm loving him.
My werewolf comes out, and he looks strong,
cocky, confident.
And he looks like he can
definitely kick some butt.
My werewolf comes out.
He actually has a great profile.
He looks really good on the side.
He's awesome.
I'm feeling great about my make up.
My father will be super thrilled about it.
I can't wait for him to see it.
Judges, why don't you take a closer look
at our werewolves?
The shapes are nice.
I kind of like the classic nature of this.
It's a shame he didn't bring color
down into the chest, because it
almost reads like a t-shirt... It does.
Even though there's all this
awesome texture and shape to it.
The shape is cool.
It's a little thick here.
It's a detail, but scalloping that out
I think would've helped.
Even just some spots and mottling
would've helped, especially from far away.
Give us some facial expression.
It moves really well.
I like the lower lip
black, like the dogs have.
I'm not seeing this everywhere.
- It's kind of cool.
- Thank you.
I think it's vastly improved
from last week's sculpt.
These features are handled a lot better.
This is all just padded out,
which is a smart, quick
way to get his proportion.
And it blends nicely with the neck.
It does, it does.
I like the fact that
he was smart enough to,
like, wet up the nose and give it
some nice, shiny highlights.
He put some grays in there
to break it up a little bit, which is nice.
I like the subtle expression he's doing.
Let's see you do some really extreme faces,
and see how well it...
Really well done.
It's definitely original,
I'll give it that.
Can you turn around?
So what's happening on the back here
is intriguing for a werewolf.
So these are the growths.
- Are these the weapons?
- Yeah, they are.
One of my biggest concerns here is,
this is so flat and one-dimensional.
It doesn't feel like a functioning ear.
It would've been easy to carve deeper.
Yeah, it wouldn't have taken any more time.
- I agree.
- I feel really worried.
I don't know if the judges
like my concept or not.
Last challenge, they
didn't like my vampire.
So they're gonna have to
really love this make up
if I'm gonna make it
all the way to the end.
Who made your favorite werewolf?
Tell us on Twitter, using #FaceOff.
Can you turn around for a second?
He put his energy into the big concept,
certainly not the... the finish.
I don't know if the judges
are liking my werewolf.
But I know they're gonna have to really
love this make up if I'm
gonna get to the finale.
Thank you.
The paint job, from far away,
looks really great.
It looks a little rough up close.
But for the broad picture,
- it looks really terrific.
- Yeah.
Can we get a little
movement on the mouth a bit?
That's cool.
Can you... can you turn to the side?
That is one impressive shape.
It has ripped skin.
- That's a nice detail.
- Yeah.
There's so much stuff going on there,
even in the dark areas.
Thank you.
The judges would now like to speak
with each of you to learn
more about your work.
- Tyler, you're up first.
- Okay.
Tell us about your
concept for your werewolf
and how he fits in to
the world of your vampire.
My werewolf is a vampire hunter.
And he spends his days searching out
these legendary vampires
from around the world.
He uses a extension of his bone
to jab into the vampire and kill them.
It reminds me of several
traditional different werewolf designs...
- Okay.
- Which I love.
The way that you worked that angle,
coming down off of the enlarged skull
and transitioned to the human aspects
that remain, is beautifully handled.
You made this very organic and very real.
Thank you.
This is a beautiful paint job tonight.
Your hair work, superb.
Yes.
He's the smallest guy out there,
and he looks like he could kick
everybody in this room's ass.
Yes.
You've improved upon the aesthetic
that you established before.
And it's really nice to
see that you've enhanced
this world that you've established.
Congratulations. Thank you.
That thing is a werewolf.
There's no question about it.
The proportion of the chest,
the narrow waist, it feels very real.
Great work.
Thank you very much.
Tyler, please step back.
- Good job, man.
- Good job.
Niko, please step forward.
Tell us how your werewolf
fits into the world of your vampire.
And what is his special ability
for hunting and killing them?
My werewolf is a warrior-hunter.
He has this DNA that
grows all these spikes,
which he uses as stakes to attack vampires.
I think that's a really good idea, Niko.
Can you turn him around for me?
I love the profile, and I love
all the spikes coming off the back.
And I think this idea
of the spikes pulling off
is really very clever.
Thank you.
It's just on the hairy edge
of not looking like it's
of the canine family.
But there's just enough data there visually
that makes it feel like it is a wolf man.
You did something I haven't seen before.
You are very original.
You're a great designer.
That's very important for me,
and I'm gonna credit you for that.
- Good stuff, Niko.
- Thank you.
Your color scheme across both the vampire
and the werewolf is far too limited.
You'd want to keep the colour schemes
distinct from one another.
However, this character
has a captivating profile,
and I am very impressed.
Niko, thank you very much.
If you'd please step back.
Thank you.
George, please come forward.
Tell us about your werewolf
and how he fits into the world
of your already-established vampire.
The vampires had a mutation,
and through evolution, became werewolves.
And with these things,
he could slice them out
and then bite them.
And eat 'em up.
There's some really
elegant stuff happening.
The shape on the back is bat-like.
But what I like about this is the texture.
It does remind me of shark skin.
I think the palette is
rock-solid and sound.
I'm also a big fan of the coloring.
It's not black, but it's a mix of color
that gets this creature
quite dark on the back
without going straight to a black.
The wod efunct on the neck
was very, very cleverly done
and very effective and realistic.
Thank you.
The angle and length of
the finger extensions,
what a turnaround compared to last week,
your weakest point.
This week, it's a smashing success.
Thanks.
I think you did a really great job.
They definitely look like
they came from the same place.
They have similar coloring.
Your story is really cool.
So very nice job, George.
Thank you so much, Ve.
George, please step back.
Thank you, my friend.
Rashaad, you're up.
Tell us about the
backstory of your werewolf.
My werewolf just so happened to
get bit on a fire moon, a red moon,
so that gave him the ability
to conjure up fire element
to fight his vampire.
This is a great concept.
That is something very original.
I love the sculpt of the chest.
The fact that you extended it so long,
very much like a wolf.
I wish you carried on
the language of ornament
to the center of the chest,
because it looks like the
chest is a little plain,
almost like he's wearing a t-shirt.
But of a whole, it's a beautiful creature.
And I think it's a great, great concept.
Thank you.
We were really looking
for originality this week.
And this is certainly
an unorthodox approach,
which is a good thing.
The overall look is an issue for me.
This guy does not look like
he'd be able to hunt your vampire.
I'm still not really clear.
Are these supposed to be jewelry pieces,
these side bits up here?
Jewelry, not so much.
It's part of the animal.
- Like a scale, sort of?
- Yes.
Okay, now I got it.
I like him, 'cause you
gave it an underbite,
which gives it that whole animal quality.
The palette of this is really beautiful.
I also love the fact
that the ears are down,
giving him this very aggressive look.
Thank you.
Rashaad, please step back.
All right, guys, the judges have
heard what you have to say.
If you'd please head
back to the make up room
while they decide who
will move on to the finale.
All right, judges, well, we have a lot
to talk about tonight.
Why don't we start with Tyler?
He did an exceptional job of painting it,
right down to the sheen on the nose,
the black lip like a little dog.
He was the only true werewolf tonight,
the one that really felt like a werewolf
in the traditional kind of way.
That profile was beautiful.
He was capable of
presenting a clear ferocity.
But also, he was able to emote sympathy.
He managed to convey the world
of the previous design
but evolve the sculpture.
Here's the problem.
A huge part of this
challenge was that unique
weapon element... how do
they hunt the vampires?
Very lame approach to that,
the bone claw out of the wrist.
And looking at them together,
his vampire is still hurting him.
As a group, I'm still
not thrilled with them.
All right, judges, let's move on to Niko.
Overall, it's kind of a cool idea,
but he did such a poor job
of putting it in front of us.
He didn't refine the sculpt.
He didn't give it a good paint job.
You know what was a really
great prosthetic moment
were the corners of the mouth.
The fact that he got that to work,
open,  big, and not have it feel
completely detached
from the actor's mouth...
that was impressive.
That was... that was really very clever.
But why would he not give something
that he could cut that big tongue off with?
I thought that tongue
thing was a brave move.
But then your werewolf
ought to have something
to get rid of that baby.
Then suddenly, what we
didn't think was amazing
last week could have
come together this week.
All right, let's move on to George.
Boy, he came up with
an interesting approach.
Let's take the vampires and
have them turn into werewolves.
And it was very apparent that
that's exactly what happened.
When you put them side by side,
they're very similar
but completely different.
The precision around the lip and teeth area
was so well handled.
Because typically, that
gets bulky and thick,
but it was so thin.
He's showing off some expert-level skills.
Like, an area that's gonna be dark,
the dark isn't just black.
So it looked very natural.
On the down side, that great work
that appears in the back
disappeared on the chest.
All right, let's discuss  Rashaad's work.
If he could've made that gold organic
or have embraced the fact
that the gold was a metallic element,
it would've been a whole
different conversation.
But the fact that it was an
attempt to make it organic?
I loved his vampire.
But this really slips him
backwards, in my opinion.
He didn't concentrate on creating
proportion and strength,
and so it ends up looking
so measly compared to his vampire.
Okay, judges, have you made your decisions?
- I think so.
- Yeah.
- We have.
- Let's bring 'em back out.
All right, Glenn, who is
the winner of this challenge
and the first person to
make it to the finale?
The winner of tonight's challenge
and the first person moving
on to the finale is...
All right, Glenn, who is the winner
of this challenge and the first person
to make it to the finale?
The winner of tonight's challenge
and the first person moving
on to the finale is...
George.
You had a terrific concept, and it was,
overall, extremely well executed.
But most importantly,
your werewolf felt like
it came from the same
world as your vampire.
Thank you, guys. Thank you.
Oh, my God. I did it.
I won the werewolf challenge,
and it feels fantastic.
I feel really, really good.
George, congratulations.
You have made it to the finale.
Thank you.
Glenn, who is the next person
going on to the finale?
The next person that will be moving on
to the finale is...
Tyler.
Tyler, we thought that your sculpture,
paint job, and hair work
were all beautifully handled.
Huge rebound from you this week.
Yes! I'm in the finale! This is awesome.
This is a dream come true.
Family is gonna be so proud of me.
I am so happy.
Oh, my gosh.
Congratulations, Tyler.
You have also made it to the finale.
Thank you.
All right, we have one spot left
with two artists remaining.
After working so hard
and after all these weeks,
being in the finale would
mean everything to me.
Being right here, like, right at the door
of the finale, it would so
suck to go home right now.
Glenn, who gets the
last spot in our finale?
The last person that will be joining us
in the finale is...
Rashaad.
Wow.
Rashaad, you created
an interesting version of
the traditional wolf man,
but it was your vampire that
really put you over the top.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
I'm very proud.
I fought this whole
way, showing what I got.
And now I'm on my way to the finale.
I'm ready.
And I think I have a
good chance of winning.
Unfortunately, that means, Niko,
you will be leaving us tonight.
Niko, we really appreciate
your daring ideas,
and we do know what it was that
you were trying to do with this piece.
But it was really rough around the edges.
And it simply just wasn't enough
to secure you a spot in the finale.
Niko, I know it's tough.
But listen, I'm not too
concerned about your future.
You're a great, great conceptual artist.
You have fantastic ideas.
- You're in good shape.
- Thank you so much, guys.
It's been an honor just
to be with these people.
It has been awesome.
It's been awesome seeing your work, man.
Thank you.
Niko, I am so sorry, but
you have been eliminated.
It's been so great having you here with us
and seeing your work.
Please head back to the make up room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
- Bye, honey.
- Bye.
- Bye, take care, Niko.
- Thank you.
It's been a pleasure.
The three of you have done
incredibly well to get this far.
I will see you soon for your
last spotlight challenge.
Why don't you head home and get some rest?
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
Yes. Thank you, guys.
Good luck, guys.
- Good luck.
I'm bummed out that I
didn't get to the finale.
But this is not gonna stop me, you know.
Being here makes me
want to go further and further.
There is a lot I'm gonna take with me.
I got to learn new techniques, and I
actually have inventive and original ideas
that I thought I didn't have.
Getting this far has really pushed
my confidence and that feels awesome.
Synced and corrected by Mayastation
www.Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net