- That's extremely impressive.
- You did some weird stuff.
It's really rough.
Previously onFace Off...
The artists competed in
an extraterrestrial challenge.
Corinne's emaciated alien
- brought her the win...
- Thank you.
And Bethany was sent home.
Now 13 artists remain.
And tonight they explore
the world of fantasy.
I'm talking about dragons here.
We're so screwed.
No time, people.
But some will have
their hopes shattered.
- I always focus on one side.
- That's a big mistake.
It just cracks.
I'm having a breakdown.
It's killer.
You've got a lot of stuff
mixed up here.
- It was a really huge mistake.
- I'm getting crazy right now.
In the end, only one
will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan Professional
Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Face off!
Welcome toFace Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
You won.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Safe is good.
- Top is cool.
- Yeah.
And I don't want to be
on the bottom.
No, me neither. Me neither.
Being on the bottom
wasn't cool at all.
That didn't feel right.
I really hope
the next challenge
is gonna be an individual one,
so I can make my own decisions
and have more control
and do better.
I'm walking up the beach,
and I've never been to Malibu
in my life,
never seen the Pacific Ocean.
Look at the rocks.
So this is exciting for me.
There's seagulls.
There's waves crashing.
They're beautiful sights--
something you only see
in movies.
Look at that.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
Hey.
Welcome to Point Dume.
This breathtaking location
may look familiar
because it was used in Iron Man
as the backdrop for
Tony Stark's seaside mansion...
I knew it.
And the iconic final scene
inPlanet Of The Apes.
- Nice.
- Yeah.
This location could be
the perfect home
of the very thing that
you're gonna have to create.
Come on.
So this week
your spotlight challenge
is based
in the world of fantasy.
I'm talking about dragons here.
- Yeah!
- Whoo! Yes!
Yes.
My jaw just dropped.
I love dragons.
I've loved the fantasy
behind them, the stories.
We're all feeling--
"Aw, yes"--
amazed.
Now, Hollywood tends
to concentrate
on the fire-breathing dragons.
In movies and TV shows
such as Eragon, Beowulf,
Dragonslayer,
and Game Of Thrones.
But in the mythology
of some cultures,
dragons are capable
of breathing other things,
like ice, acid, even poison.
So, for your first individual
spotlight challenge...
Oh.
...you're gonna select one
of these shields
and create the dragon character
that inflicted the damage.
Fuck.
Dragons are so big.
It's essentially
flying sky elephants
that you have to create
in, like, 18 hours by yourself.
We're so screwed.
Now, your options are
"Frozen," "Charred,"
"Corroded," "Quilled,"
"Slimed," "Sandblasted,"
and "Tarred."
When I call your name,
please step up
and select a shield.
Daniel, you're first.
Ugh.
All right, guys,
go ahead and get started
on your designs.
When you're done,
head back to the lab,
and I will stop by later
with my dad
to see how you're doing.
Bye.
Good luck.
- Bye.
- Thanks.
I picked tarred
because I didn't want to go
with the classic
fire-breathing dragon.
I wanted something different.
I'm gonna try to cover as much
of the body as possible.
Build up a lot of armor pieces
along with some chains.
It's a lot of work
to do by myself.
But I'm ready to get
back on top.
I chose sandblasted.
I see all the seals
and the dolphins,
and I really like
doing aquatic creatures.
So I'm just gonna do
a sea-horse dragon.
I think the profile
will be really beautiful
with a big arch
in the back of the neck.
And then I'm gonna build
a bodysuit
that holds the arms in.
I definitely think
I can pull this off
if I really stay on track
and manage my time well.
I love dragons that have
that pointed-beak look
inspired by vultures and birds.
I'm definitely using the ice
or some elements as accessories,
bringing it out in the back
of the head,
having the ice even part
of its bone structure.
I've got kind of
a low-crawling,
doglike lizard
who vomits slime
to ward off enemies.
I'm thinking,
"Let's throw a couple
different eyes in there,
and let's hide the human eyes,
and let's give it
a big, weird mouth."
Like, a gross, pitbull-ish,
just slobbery monster.
I started sketching
different things
that I would like to do--
hands,
feet, backpieces, chest pieces,
even though I don't know
if I'm be able to make it all.
He's mostly
like a dragon slave.
_
Tar brings up
really strong imagery to me.
You know, I think stone.
I think desert.
So I'm feeling like doing maybe
a Middle Eastern-looking,
maybe even
Persian-looking dragon.
My concept is a female that
is banished from the castle.
She's waiting
for her husband dragon
to come back and meet again.
I'm really hoping
that a good-quality sculpt
will sell the dragon
more so than the slime.
Okay, everyone,
let's go back to the lab.
We get to the lab.
We only have five hours today.
I need to get the face
sculpted and molded
by the end of the day so
I can get it ready for foam.
My concept for my quill dragon
is that she's an archer.
So she uses her own quills
and feathers
to create her arrows.
My story is about a knight
who was messing around
with the wizard's wife,
and the wizard turned him
to a fire dragon.
It has to be
a strong, impactful image.
And I want to make him
cool and mean.
My dragon is
a treasure hoarder.
She's able to spit acid
to protect treasures.
When I think of acid
and corrosion,
I think of greens and purples--
my favorite colors.
So I'm thinking, "Okay,
this is an individual challenge.
And I've got to make sure
that I concentrate on the face
and the cowl."
Since it's about corrosion
and he spits acid
out of his face,
I have the bottom jaw eroded.
All the skin's gone.
I don't have time to make
a bodysuit or a tail or wings.
I've really got to put
some detail into this
and try to make it good.
I have a really clear idea
right off the get-go.
I want to break up
the human form
so it doesn't look just
like a guy in a dragon mask.
And I really want this dragon
to have huge, massive wings
to really sell the idea
of it being a dragon.
I'm not really thinking
about what I can and cannot do
by myself.
I'm just going
with my ideal dragon.
And then later on,
I'll have to be like,
"Ah, well, I can't really do
all of these things."
- It's not gonna work.
- It's not gonna work?
Not what I was thinking, nope.
I always focus on one side
when I'm trying
to figure shit out.
Yep.
That's a big mistake.
I made
the ultimate sculpture mistake
and only sculpted
one side of the face.
Now I have to match
the other side,
and I'm falling behind.
I still have to make the leg
and the headpiece.
You know, this is way
fucking harder than I thought.
All the other artists
are ahead of me,
and I'm starting
to get super nervous.
It just feels like the world
is crashing down on me.
I've just shitted myself over.
Coming up...
- It just cracks.
- It's not going to happen.
I'm tired. I'm stressed out.
I've had it for today.
- I'm going home.
- It's beautiful.
I don't know what it is
that you're trying to show me.
It's not your best work.
It's our first day of our
first individual challenge,
and I'm already falling behind.
- It's not gonna work.
- It's not gonna work?
- I sculpted one side.
- That's a big mistake.
There's not gonna be
enough time for me
to mold the face, so now
I have to mold it tomorrow.
Hey, guys.
- Here for a walk-through.
- How are you?
Hey.
- Hey, Tanner.
- Hello.
- Hi, Tanner. How are you?
- Hello, Mr. Westmore.
All right,
tell us about your dragon.
I got charred.
So I'm thinking the bottom jaw
is gonna be like charcoal.
- Across the lips?
- Yeah.
I think it'd be interesting
if-- would be to maybe
vacuform a chin piece
when they open their mouth.
It'll move the whole--
The whole thing will move
all at one time.
- That's a great idea.
- Okay?
So I chose frozen.
I thought that
a female ice dragon
would be really, really cool
and sexy.
I'm just wondering
if the human mouth
might make this dragon
too human.
Give it something
to make a little bit more
of a muzzle on it.
- Okay?
- Thank you so much.
The dragon is kind of like
a scavenger
of the frozen wasteland.
What color are you
planning on going with?
Definitely something
with blacks, blues,
and whites and grays.
- The thing is, don't over--
- Don't overdo it.
Don't overdo it.
So I don't ruin all the detail.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Yes.
Mr. Westmore always has
great things to say.
I always really try to take
his advice into consideration
all the time,
because at the end of the day,
he really knows
what he's talking about.
You're getting awfully thin
down in here.
This can be hard to apply.
You got all these edges
that have to go-- add more clay.
Otherwise, you're just gonna
have a problem
- on application day.
- Okay.
It's important
to teach your model
- how to walk.
- Do the hunch.
Not to walk in,
but to hunch over...
- Hunch over, yeah.
- And really take advantage
- of the space.
- That shape. Yeah.
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Good luck, Rashaad.
All right, everybody.
We're heading out,
- but good luck.
- Thank you!
- Bye-bye.
- Can't wait. Bye-bye.
Thank you.
I finish my skull.
I'm the first in the mold room,
and already I'm feeling good
because I have a leg up.
I have a chance to get
my facepiece out
and ready to go,
so I can have something
to go off of tomorrow.
Now we have one hour left.
Tyler is my buddy.
But we're competitors,
so I'm trying to keep up
with him.
By the end of the day,
he gets his mold done,
ready for foam.
I get my face molded,
but there's not enough time
to open it.
I'm gonna have to save it
for the morning.
Time, everyone.
So I'm really worried
about tomorrow
because I have to get
my mold cleaned,
mold up my cowl,
and on top of that,
I have to fabricate
an entire bodysuit.
No time, people!
No time!
It's day two
of the dragon challenge,
and we have 9 1/2 hours
in the lab today.
First thing that I'm gonna do
is finish sculpting the cowl.
I still need to mold the face,
mold the cowl,
sculpt the body piece,
mold the body piece.
I might be a little insane.
The cowl is done,
but I'm running around crazy
because I still have to sculpt
the face, hands, chest,
and get it all molded, cleaned,
and ready for foam latex.
I really want to show off
all the detail,
so I'm going to incorporate
scale texture.
I'm just trying to get it done
as quickly as possible.
I decided to fabricate
a muscle bodysuit.
You start by making a skin
for the actor,
and you block out where these
muscles are gonna go.
I also cut out
each individual scale
that's gonna go on the body.
Most people would sculpt.
But with fabrication,
you don't have to mold it,
you don't have to run it
in foam.
You just get it done
and paint it, and that's it.
After I get the face
ready and molded,
I focus on the legs.
I need to make
those insanely detailed
just like I did the face.
That's going to take me
a lot of time,
but I think it's gonna be
worth it.
I need to figure out
how I'm gonna put slime
all over this dragon.
And I decide on slime sacs.
So I start to make a bunch
of little round vacuforms
and start cramming them
into the cowl.
They give a nice, smooth,
and round shape.
I'm really happy
with this design.
So I get to the mold room,
and I'm about two hours behind
from my original schedule.
This is really not good.
The body sculpt
isn't even started.
I'm starting to sweat.
After I sculpt ten icicle pieces,
I vacuum four of them all in one shot.
it's quick,
and it's extremely lightweight.
I'm actually surprised
at what I got done on day one.
So I'm thinking
I can incorporate
another element,
which is wings.
I'm starting with big,
chunky pieces of foam,
armature wire, foam tubing
and bending it
to the shape that I want.
We got, like, 25 minutes.
We're getting
to the end of the day.
I get the top
of my big cowl mold open.
But then I can't get
the core out.
The mold is locked.
Graham, do you have a sec?
Everybody is just desperately
trying to help me
get this thing out,
because they all know
the consequences if I don't.
Finally, we pulled really hard,
and we open it.
- Fuck.
- We smashed the core.
Then we run over and spray it
out as quickly as possible.
- But nothing's coming out.
- It's not gonna happen, man.
_
There is clay stuck
in the top of the mold.
My fingers are cut.
I'm tired. I'm stressed out.
I'm hot.
I've had it for today.
But I know if I give up
right now, I'm going home.
It's the end of day two
of our dragon challenge,
and I'm having a breakdown.
I'm not gonna have enough time
to get my mold prepped
so it can bake overnight
in foam latex.
- Five minutes!
- Fuck.
You could do poly foam.
Poly foam doesn't work
very well.
It's hard to cut
and glue back together.
It's hard to seam it.
I just-- I don't have
a chest or anything.
I didn't get
that even started today.
Time's up!
That's it!
I'm freaking out right now.
I don't know how this
is all gonna be possible.
It'll be all right, Chloe.
It's application day.
We've got four hours in the lab
and one hour in last looks.
These are hot.
I think my pieces
look really good.
But there's a lot of things
that need to happen,
so I'm getting
a little worried.
The judges' critique
on the last challenge
was that I needed better paint.
So my primary goal is to get
the appliances
on as fast as possible
and then take the time to paint.
First thing I do is get
the bodysuit painted,
make sure it looks flawless.
I have to stay focused 'cause
I have a load of work to do.
It's time to run
the poly foam in my mold.
Thankfully, Niko comes over
to help me.
I have to wait
another 45 minutes
so the poly foam can cure.
The clock is ticking,
and I don't even know
if I have a piece yet.
- I'm Corinne. Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
We have to put
all your hair up.
Can you do me a favor, brother?
- Heat this up.
- Yep.
No time! No time!
After helping Chloe,
I go check my chest piece.
It just cracks.
What am I gonna do?
I don't have a chest piece.
I look at everyone else,
and they already
have pieces done.
I realize
I'm really, really behind.
Now I have to airbrush
the whole chest,
and that takes a lot of time.
The first thing
that I'm focusing on
is busting out those legs.
We're gonna do this.
Just don't rip it.
But I can't get the things
off the mannequin.
So I have to slice up the side
and take the legs off that way,
which creates this giant seam.
I have my model put it over
her legs,
and it's just not
even closing together.
Luckily, I had some
blender pieces made up,
so I have to safety-pin
the pieces together,
and this totally eats away
my time.
One of the colors
for the dragon
is intense red
coming through the cracks,
because it's a volcano
kind of fire dragon.
So I want it breathe through
the cracks of the skin.
So my first layer is red,
then I go with metallic black.
I think it's looking fantastic.
It needs a lot of work
on the paint job,
but overall, it looks how
I "visioned" it.
I need to get
this backpiece completed.
I still have to cut out
all of these different scales.
Dremel in texture,
glue them down, paint them.
I can't go small
when it comes to dragons.
I got to go big,
and that's a tall order
for one person to do.
Just hold this
on your face for me.
My cowl will not release
from the core,
so I have to cut it up
the seam.
It may be be too small.
Let me know.
So now I have a cowl
that's basically cut in half.
And it won't glue back together
because of the cell structure
of the poly foam.
The facepiece alone
looks absolutely ridiculous.
So I'm gonna paint the face
and the cowl
up to where the damage is,
and I'm gonna cover
the rest with the hood.
I'd rather go with something
that creates the shape
than just nothing at all.
I have an hour left,
and I need to start painting,
or I'm gonna not only have
a damaged piece,
but I'm gonna have
an unpainted piece.
I put a base coat
of dark black paint,
and then I go in
with some greens
and some golds
to highlight everything.
By going
with a dark tone first,
it gets in all the little nooks
and crannies of the scales,
and I'm able to dry-brush
a lighter color
to really pop out
all the detail.
I'm not rushing.
Everything's going as planned.
And I'm doing
really, really well with time.
I've got all
my prosthetics applied.
They look good.
Now all I got to do is cover
this giant dude in paint
and slime and sticks.
My slime is made from gelatin,
which can only be used
when it's been heated.
I start just slamming slime
left and right,
all over his slime sacs.
I'm sticking leaves.
I'm putting sticks.
It's looking really good.
I'm happy with how the slime
is coming out.
It's exactly what I want.
I'm running out of time.
I need to get her makeup on
and her based out
so that I can at least have
a good paint job.
We got six minutes.
That's time, everybody!
I'm super worried
about the hair.
The hair's a hot mess.
And there's not a single quill
on her face.
Absolutely nothing's
going right.
I only have one more hour left
to get everything done.
I'm fucking screwed.
Coming up...
That's the worst makeup
I've ever done in my life.
I might not put it up there.
I'm running out of time,
and that's scaring me.
I couldn't be more pleased
with this makeup.
My biggest problem is it's
rather ponderous viewing.
Head to toe, it's rough.
Left side.
Other--
It's last looks--
one hour
till we have to be done.
Head up a little bit.
Yeah, right there.
My heart's racing,
because if this thing
is as bad as I think it's gonna be,
I might just not put it up there at all.
I want to make sure I glue
on all my icicle pieces.
Ugh.
As soon as I get those on,
the whole makeup is complete.
I'm really worried
about this wardrobe.
I don't know what to do here.
It doesn't go
with my makeup at all.
But at this point, I just have
to go with it, you know.
Ten minutes, family,
ten minutes.
Stay closed.
I'm running out of time,
and that's scaring
the living shit out of me.
So I'm just shoving quills
wherever I can,
trying to finish
before time's called.
That's time!
That looks so good.
That's probably
the worst makeup
I've ever done in my life.
I can't believe
that I have to put this
in front of people
that I admire.
When I look at my makeup,
I'm heartbroken.
Welcome
to theFace Offreveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
First, let's say hello
to our talented judges--
Owner of Optic Nerve
Make-Up Effects Studio,
- Glenn Hetrick...
- Good evening.
Hi, Glenn.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist
- Ve Neill...
- Hi, guys.
- Hey, Ve.
- Hi, Ve.
Creature and concept designer,
Neville Page.
Hello, everyone.
- Hi, Neville.
This week, your first
individual spotlight challenge
was to choose a damaged shield
and create the dragon character
responsible for inflicting it.
Let's take a look
at your dragons.
Everything came together
perfectly.
I am just in awe
of what I accomplished
in three days.
I like the profile,
even though the paint job
still looks muddy.
I don't know if I feel happy
or satisfied or nervous or...
I'm getting crazy right now.
I think it's a really cool,
solid piece.
My vision came to life.
I'm happy with this makeup.
I'm a little bummed
that I went so heavy
with fabricating,
when that's not really
my strong suit.
This makeup is not exactly
what I was hoping it would be.
I'm liking his profile,
and I'm liking the fact
that he looks like a dragon.
So I'm just waiting to see
what the judges are gonna
think about this.
This guy's a tar dragon,
and he looks beautiful.
I think he definitely fits
the challenge.
She's got a beautiful
silhouette to her,
and she looks great.
I think
it really came together.
He looks so cool, just rad.
I'm super happy with him.
I really like it.
I mean, I like it a lot.
It looks really cool.
Overall, it just pops.
I really messed up.
I honestly cannot think
of a time
when I've seen a piece
this bad onstage.
I think her proportions
are totally off.
It's way too cartoony.
I'm not confident
with the overall paint.
This creature just sucks.
There's so much wrong with it.
There's nothing for me
to be truly proud of.
I'm really happy
with how it turned out.
I'm feeling really good.
I think it's the best
I've done so far.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look
at the dragons?
This is a cool
second chin here.
- I like that.
- Yeah, I didn't see that.
These are vacuformed--
Good idea.
On the face,
we have one solid color again.
I think there's far too much
activity sculpturally.
This is kind of confusing.
It's like armor sort of.
It feels more like a sea creature
than it does a dragon.
Yeah. Agreed.
Look at the detail
in this paint--
all the highlights and shadows
and modeling
in between the scales.
And there's a ton
of fabrication.
This kind of looks like
a Chinese dragon.
Yeah.
It's a beautiful,
original design--
Everything
that's happening here.
Really, really cool.
I'm just going to see
how far--
Could you hold this, please?
Glenn grabs for the hood,
and I know he's just gonna rip
that thing off.
Looks like there was
a problem or something,
But there's a lot of work.
I'm crushed.
I would rather
it not be out there.
I'm going home.
Who made your favorite
dragon character tonight?
Tell us on Twitter,
using #FaceOff.
Looks like there was
a problem or something.
- But there's a lot of work.
- Oh, yeah.
This doesn't look very good.
It's really hard for me
to watch this happen.
She's glued this thing on
so crookedly.
This goes that way,
and then that goes straight up.
All this detailing
and texture everywhere
is covered...
- And then--
- ...except nothing on the chin.
_
Thank you.
The judges have scored
your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Tyler...
George...
Tess...
Niko...
Rashaad...
Daniel...
You are the best
and worst this week.
The rest of you are safe.
You can head back
to the makeup room.
The judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
- George, please step up.
- Sure.
George, please explain
the concept
behind your dragon design.
He was a knight
in medieval times.
He fall in love
with the wizard's wife,
and the wizard got very mad
and throw him
to the pits of hell, basically.
It's so apparent
what you were trying to do,
and that's a huge compliment.
It's not that easy
to communicate
those types of ideas.
Particularly fond of the horn
placement and design.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
I love this dragon.
It really looks like it's made
out of some sort
of bronzed metal.
And you can just see fire
coming out of it.
I couldn't be more pleased
with this makeup.
Thank you so much.
As much as I really love this,
I also feel
that it's not terribly creative
in terms of inventing
something new,
but it's beautiful.
George, thank you very much.
Please step back.
Niko, you're next.
Please tell us what your
concept was behind your dragon.
He was a slave dragon.
He goes for revenge with
the people that attack him.
I feel that the sculpting
was very rough.
It's disproportionate.
It's kind of off in spots.
It's not your best work today.
I think in side view,
the quills work.
The paint on the face, though,
other than being mismatched
to the body,
it just feels like there's not
enough happening.
My biggest problem with this
is that
it's rather ponderous viewing.
My eye doesn't find
a place to go to.
I don't know what it is
that you're trying to show me.
Niko,
will you please step back?
Let's talk to Tess.
So tell us about the shield's
damage and your character.
I got "Quilled,"
and I wanted her
to be able to use
her feathers and her quills
to make her bow and arrows.
I like where you're going
with the idea of this,
but it's just rough.
Particularly around the mouth,
it just starts
to fall apart there.
A feathered serpent dragon
is a really cool idea.
But the feathers seem jammed in
underneath the appliance,
and that is a huge problem,
because that is the focus
of your design this week.
Yeah.
The headpiece went off
to the side.
It got a little crooked
in your application.
Also I think
you should have tried
to integrate her chin
into this makeup
a little bit more as well.
- I agree.
- Tess, please step back.
- Tyler, please step forward.
- Okay.
There she is.
Tell me how you integrated
the damage
on your shield
into this character.
The damage on the shield
is "Frozen."
And this dragon is
a vulture-like character
that wanders
the frozen wasteland.
It's killer.
It is super cool,
and that unifying concept
of vulture in your dragon--
it gives you motivation
for wardrobe,
wing shape, jaw shape.
Lots and lots
of wise decisions.
Thank you.
This is probably
the best set of wings
- we have ever had on the show.
- Yes!
It's just all part
of a creepy elegance.
- She looks amazing.
- Thank you very much.
What I want to compliment
you on the most
is just
some very intelligent choices.
Those half-vacform icicles
on the back of the head--
you accomplished a look,
and you allowed your actor
to still function.
Compliments to you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Tyler, please step back.
Daniel, please step up.
Tell us what your concept is
behind your dragon.
My damage was "Slimed."
And she is "outcasted" from
her legion of other dragons,
and she's living in a cave now,
hoping for the day
that she can get reconciled
with her husband.
It really is not
a pretty picture.
It's a very
uncomfortable-looking palate.
And that doesn't look
like scaling.
It looks like she's
got green chainmail on her.
It's very odd.
I think you got a lot of stuff
mixed up here this week.
The kimono is killing it.
You knew the palate,
but you didn't integrate it
in her design.
I think it was
a really huge mistake.
There's a conspicuous lack
of dragon elements--
horns, teeth, wings,
something that tells us dragon.
It's not here
this week, Daniel.
Daniel,
will you please step back?
Rashaad, please come forward.
So tell us
about your shield's damage
and what this character
is about.
The shield had tar on it.
So, when I thought of tar,
I thought thick, heavy, big,
and brutish.
It's mind-blowing.
How the hell
did you do this much
in the time that you had?
This looks
like it's a team effort,
and I can tell that you've got
a real great sense
of form language
in fabrication,
- which is impressive.
- Thank you.
Paint technique
is absolutely splendid.
Love everything
that you're doing.
Beautiful.
Can you turn him around
so we can see his wings?
The fact that you even
had time to build wings
and you continued that paint job
along the spine of the wings
is pretty great.
Very nicely done, Rashaad.
Thank you.
Rashaad, please step back.
- Awesome.
- Thank you.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
Could you please head back
to the makeup room
while they deliberate?
All right, judges, why
don't we talk about the looks
you liked the most this week?
Let's start with George's work.
It resembled a really amazing
Chinese dragon.
Yeah, the forms were
so well done.
Okay, let's move on to Tyler.
Taking a vulture
and the frozen idea
and then allowing
those two things to merge--
absolutely brilliant.
The teeth, the beak--
Tyler's got
some sculpting chops.
All right, judges,
let's move on to Rashaad.
What a massive amount of work,
featuring a massive amount
of detail.
It did not seem like a single
person pulled that off.
Okay, let's move on to
the looks you liked the least.
Why don't we start with Niko?
The sculpture was so fussy
and overly complicated.
The face was just one tone.
All right,
let's move on to Tess.
She put it on crooked
and had the dragon-like ears,
but she didn't finish
painting them.
She made some poor choices.
It does feel dragon-y to me,
but the paint kills it.
Let's move on to Daniel.
Why did he put that
Japanese kimono on her?
That doesn't bother me so much
as I can't find a dragon element
that's recognizable.
I have no idea how this fits
this week's challenge.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- Yeah.
- I believe so.
Let's bring them back out.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about the top looks.
George, your dragon was
powerful but graceful.
And it clearly communicated
your shield's damage.
Tyler...
the vulture concept
was a brilliant stroke,
and we felt that you also made
a ton of smart decisions.
Rashaad...
we were quite impressed
with the sculpture,
the paint, and the sheer volume
of work that you did.
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
Tonight's winner is...
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
Tonight's winner is...
Tyler.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
Head to toe,
we loved this character.
From concept to execution,
everything was spot-on.
Well done.
Thank you guys so much.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm just so happy and thankful
the judges saw my creativity
and what I think
a fantasy dragon looks like.
- Tyler, congratulations.
- Thank you.
You, Rashaad, George,
will you please head back
to the makeup room?
Unfortunately, that means
the rest of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Niko, the quill profile
was kind of cool,
but there were
significant issues
with the sculpture
and the application.
Tess, we really liked
a lot of your ideas.
However, your makeup
was quite rough
and generally incomplete.
Daniel, we understand the plan
that you had in mind,
but we were confused
by the choices that you made
with your sculpture
and your color.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Daniel.
You made
some perplexing decisions.
The challenge was to make
a dragon,
and we just didn't see that
in your character.
That means, Tess and Niko,
you are safe this week.
Please head back
to the makeup room.
Daniel, you got
a lot left in you,
and I'm hoping
that we get a chance
to see that down the road.
Thank you for the opportunity.
Daniel, I'm so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
It's been great having
you here with us.
Thank you.
Please head back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- Good luck, Daniel.
Thank you.
I am not gonna say
I'm not disappointed.
It's me, guys.
- Aw.
- What?
I'm really gladFace Off
gave me the opportunity
to show the world a little bit
of what I can do.
Oh, yeah!
It's been
an awesome experience.
Makeup is everything to me.
I love everything
about what it brings.
And I don't ever see myself
stopping.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net