- I am thoroughly impressed.
- Beautiful sculpting work.
Rock and roll, Hoochie Koo.
Previously onFace Off...
Daran's elegant rock goddess
brought him the win...
and Tess was sent home.
Now, 11 artists remain,
and tonight, their creations
will emerge from the shadows.
I'm scared.
That actually scared me.
For some, the challenge
will be too dark to handle.
The nose definitely
has to change.
It's little teddy bear,
little Whoville.
Well, that's not good.
I don't want a cute demon.
I fully locked it.
I don't have anything
but a face.
This is going to be
the end of me.
The most important part
of my makeup isn't there.
I dig it a lot.
It's creepy-licious.
I've never seen anything
like it before.
I'm really
kind of disappointed.
In the end, only one
will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Face off!
Welcome to Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Getting homesick can, like,
just wipe you out, man.
Got to remember
why we're here, though.
When I start feeling homesick
or I-I feel like I miss
my girlfriend or I miss my son,
I really have to sit down
and let myself know,
they're the reason
why I'm doing what I'm doing.
How do you feel about always
being the bridesmaid?
It's nice being a top look,
you know,
that the judges like
what I have.
But it plays in my head,
like, am I only good
for just top looks?
You know, am I good enough
for a win?
I've been top looks three times.
The judges know
what I'm capable of doing,
so I just need to keep
bringing it on.
- All right, guys.
- Let's go!
I don't know LA very well,
but we're somewhere downtown...
Whoa, that's cool.
...and there's
all these warehouses.
We're like, "Where the hell
are we going?"
And then, we get
to this doorway.
- Uh-oh.
- What the hell?
It's spooky in here.
We walk
into this big warehouse,
and it's super dark
and creepy...
- What the hell?
- I'm scared.
Except for McKenzie.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
I brought you here
to get you in the mood
for this week's
spotlight challenge.
In the world
of supernatural cinema...
Yes.
...films like Drag Me To Hell
and Paranormal Activity--
they get a lot of mileage
by teasing
but not fully revealing
the dark perpetrator.
I'd like to introduce you
to someone
who is an expert in this area.
He's produced films such as
Insidious, The Lords Of Salem,
and is the creator
of the blockbuster
Paranormal Activity franchise.
Nice.
Please welcome Oren Peli.
Oren has made the most
outrageously crazy,
creepy films.
So I'm really excited
at this point.
Thank you so much
for being here.
Oh, of course.
All right, now your films,
they're really scary.
What is your secret?
Well, I think a lot of it
has to do with building up
the audience's fear
and anticipation.
Sometimes the scariest thing
is not what you see
right in front of you,
but what's hidden
in the shadows.
Whoa.
All of a sudden, these lights
start to appear in the wall,
like, different shadows.
And we're like,
"Wait. What is this?"
That actually scared me.
Your spotlight challenge
is to select one
of these exaggerated silhouettes
and create the supernatural
entity that cast the shadow.
Whoa.
This is definitely
going to be intense.
I'm really excited
at this point.
Chloe, you're up first.
All right,
and I'm excited to say
that Oren will be joining us
onstage this week.
What are you going
to be looking for
in their final makeups?
Make sure
that it's a full head-to-toe
application and design.
The most important thing
is that it elicits
a natural reaction of fear.
All right, guys.
Get started on your designs.
When you're done,
I want you to head
back to the lab
and get to work.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
See you soon.
The silhouette is important
in every challenge,
but more than ever,
this one is where you
really have
to knock it out of the park.
Right now, I'm just sketching
kind of the outline
that I have in my shadow.
There are a lot of pieces
to this character
that have to be on there
to match the silhouette.
My concept is an angel of death
that's been sent from hell
to collect souls on Earth.
What scares me?
Cockroaches.
So I start designing a boogeyman
made out of bug parts.
The face is going to be, like,
a balding, old man.
But instead of having a mouth,
this creature has
all these little legs
with fingernails and teeth
that are used to just capture
and eat children.
Graham and I sat down together,
right beneath our shadow.
We get two people that choose
a shadow, so you're thinking,
"All right,
what's this person going to do?"
I am going to use the back
of this monster to my advantage
and have a huge mouth
come out of it,
which can suck up your soul.
I am terrified of bugs,
anything creepy and crawly.
This one reminds me of, like,
a scorpion.
I really want to focus
on the hump of the back.
It's going to be
these little egg sacs,
almost like it's the creature's
entities coming out
and coming to get you.
Ugh.
I'm really creeped out right
now, just thinking about it.
I really hate insects, so I'm
definitely going to play up
the insect part
of this character.
I'm going to be sculpting
really, really big
arm extensions
with these huge
praying mantis hands.
The shadow has
this huge horn sticking out,
right from the face,
so I really want to keep that
so that it looks
like the shadow.
Well, I chose this shadow here.
The first thing you notice are
these huge horns
coming out of the head.
So my concept is
a female seductive faun
that lives in this warehouse
and causes problems.
She likes to cause mischief.
I'm looking at the shadow,
and I'm thinking ancient demon.
I want his horns to be so big
that they grow through his body
and poke out the front.
The rest of him will be
very slender with spindly limbs.
I picked this one.
I'm doing a creature that was
a man who was deemed to hell.
Satan turned him
into this goat deity.
He goes around skinning people
and trying to wear their skin
to gain back his manhood.
He's going to be skeletal
with pieces of flesh
nailed on him.
And he's going to have giant,
oversized horns.
I'm excited.
All right, guys.
Let's head back to the lab.
Drop those pencils.
We have six hours
at the lab today.
Here we go, here we go.
No time.
- Let's go.
- We choose our models.
The first thing I need to do
is start the face.
In my silhouette, there's
a very pointed nose and chin.
My concept is a goblin
that creeps around at night
and attacks people.
How does this look?
That looks like a bull.
I chose the same shadow
as Chloe,
so I decided to make
this scary minotaur
that hunts the hunters
that attacks him.
_
I'm trying to make this head
a little bit bigger,
so I wanted to incorporate
fake eyes.
It's going to be a tricky one,
but I know I can pull it off.
- What are you doing there?
- I'm doing a demon.
Still a long ways to go.
I'm making this demon that rips
flesh out of her victims
and eats them alive.
I'm concentrating on the face
and the cowl and getting them
sculpted and molded
by the end of the day.
Hey, guys.
- We're here to check on you.
- How are you?
- Hi.
- Ready?
The character is going
through necrosis,
so his skin is very pale,
and it's got of lot
of that blood
where it's just pooled
and turned purple and blackish.
Mm-hmm.
I would paint him first
and then do
- the rest of your skin texture...
- Right.
...so you see depth
and translucency.
- Great.
- I had teeth here, right?
Should I put 'em
in the outside, or--
It's kind of tricky
to make it look like
- they haven't been glued on.
- Okay.
They could use their own teeth
but dirty them down.
Put a little food dye
in karo syrup and water.
Okay, cool.
So in the middle of the night,
this thing unleashes
these little creepy-crawlies
that come out of its back.
I would love to do little hints
of maybe yellow or white,
just to make it pop.
I'd go with a stencil,
as opposed to trying to go in
- and do things with a brush...
- Okay.
...which could get muddy
or really not read well.
This is awfully far apart
for your model to see.
Make sure you dig it out
underneath here
- when you're making your mold.
- Okay.
But they may have to do
a little bit of this...
- Right.
- ...to be able to see.
So that's the shadow
that I picked,
and this is my face sculpture.
You're gonna try to cover
the whole face with fur
or just come
around the edges with it?
Yeah, just kind of,
like, around here.
Mm-hmm. It's going to save you
time on painting.
This is actually still horn,
and then it'll go back
to the cowl, and then the horns
will come out at the front.
That's an interesting idea,
but I think the nose definitely
has to change a little bit,
because it's little teddy bear,
little Whoville.
It's reading
almost sweet or cute.
Well, that's not good.
I don't want a cute demon.
It needs a nose
that's meaner, stronger.
By adding more to the nose
and giving it a mouthful
- of piranha teeth or something--
- Right.
That's what you want
this character to do.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
All right, guys, we're heading out.
But it's looking really good.
- Good luck.
- Good luck, guys.
- Bye.
I'm sweating bullets
at this point
'cause time's just flying by.
I have to get these molded
and cleaned
before the day is out.
Resculpting the nose is going
to take a long time.
But if my creature's not even
scary, it could be my ass.
- Coming up...
- I'm in a sketchy place.
I fully locked it.
Shit.
I still have to mold the cowl,
and I don't know
if I'm going to finish this.
You've got some serious issues.
This is really
a beautiful piece.
It's day one
of our shadow challenge,
and given Mr. Westmore's advice,
I'm resculpting the nose,
making it larger
and not as tiny and cute.
It's really eating up
into my time,
but I think it's worth it,
because Oren Peli said
our creatures
need to be frightening.
Finally, my sculpture
is completed.
And I immediately start molding
faster than I've ever
molded before,
since I only have
one hour left.
- That's what you gotta do?
- Yeah.
You know, just everything.
Just everything in general.
Mold face, mold cowl,
sculpt chest, mold chest.
- Make arms.
- Make arms, make other arms.
Make some feet.
I'm not the fastest sculptor.
But when you're trying to force
bug legs into the jaw
and neck anatomy...
you need to take a lot of time.
That really has to be
done well,
in order for it to read
in the correct manner.
I hate cockroaches.
I hate them.
From the shadow,
you could only see
the four horns, the main horns.
But I want to make ten horns
because I want a great profile.
I decided to go with styrofoam.
It's easy to shape,
and it's lightweight,
so you don't have the actor
tipping over.
I'm feeling great.
I have more work to do,
but I'm in a great place.
You got 33 minutes.
At the end of the day,
I only have my face sculpted,
but the focal point of my makeup
is going to be
these big arm extensions
that look like
praying mantis arms.
I'm just starting
to sculpt them now.
Time's up, everybody!
- Let's go do some barbecuing.
- I've got a lot to do tomorrow,
and I'm just a nervous wreck.
Let's go.
It's day two
of our supernatural challenge.
Back to sculpting,
ladies and gentlemen.
We have 9 1/2 hours in the lab.
Already having my face
run in foam,
I have to finish my cowl,
do my rib piece,
and I have to finish
sculpting all 10 horns.
It's a lot of work
to do by myself...
This still has
to be shaved down.
...but I know
I'm going to get it done.
- Keeping the neck open, right?
- Yep.
Thanks.
All righty then.
Yep, that is awesome.
Let's mold you.
All I got to do is
finish a face, mold that,
make a vest, mold that,
make some extra arms,
open up the molds,
clean those out.
So you know, simple day.
I use a air hose to get
the plaster
into each nook and cranny,
because if it's not
molded right,
you won't see
all the work that you did
after sculpting something
so detailed.
I've got to make
a supernatural mouth
here on the back
of this carrier.
So I'm slapping on the wet clay
as fast as I can
and get the forms blocked out.
And it's kind of fishy-looking,
supernatural-looking.
Definitely not human-looking.
The horns are a very
integral part of my creature
because they set up
the whole silhouette.
And I need to make sure
that my design does
ultimately stay true
to the silhouette that I picked.
Yeah, that looks about right.
- Looks about right?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, cool.
I also need to get
this cowl sculpted.
It needs to have
enough bulk on it
that I can attach these horns
and they would stay on.
That's going to look so epic.
- What's your concept?
- It's a goblin.
While I'm sculpting the cowl,
I'm trying to make sure
that the ears are
really long and pointed.
As I finish the sculpt, I bring
it over to the light station
that's been set up,
so we can check
the silhouette
of our character.
I'm feeling pretty confident
because it's the exact shapes
I'm seeing in my silhouette.
I want to make an insect
that not only is scary,
but also creeps me out.
So the back has six inserts
where these egg sacs
are going to be.
I am vacuforming spheres,
and I plan to get scorpions
and incorporating them
into the egg sacs,
making them look
like they're embedded
inside them.
I need to finish the hands,
so I can vacuform them.
But I'm noticing that
they're a little bit too big.
- Cat?
- Yeah?
If I--
This I can vacuform.
You'd have to just
sculpt this separately.
Instead of fabricating
the hooves,
I just decided to sculpt them.
- This is a-done.
- It's looking good.
I have my face, chest, cowl,
and the two hands.
Molding time.
He's going to be making molds
the rest of the day.
Time is running out,
and I can't open my mold.
There is just
a lot wrong with it.
I'm in a sketchy place
right now.
I don't have anything
but a face at this point.
I'm questioning the fact
that I spent so much time
and effort making this cowl.
I'm really scared.
Shit.
I can't do this.
It's day two
of our supernatural challenge.
Time is running out.
I can't even open my mold.
I'm really scared, and I know
that the only way to save
my molding mistakes
is to walk away from it.
In this situation
we have to think quick,
so plan B is to take a wig
to create the skull shape
that I'm looking for
while using
premade ear appliances to get
the silhouette that I need.
I only have a face.
I have a face and a wig.
And I'm sure that's going
to get me in trouble.
As I'm going forward with
making this whole cup-horn idea,
there's a lot of fabricating,
and I'm already so invested
in this process
that I can't change it
at this point.
I'm really starting to worry
that since they're so huge,
there's really no way
for me to know
if it's going to work
until the very end.
And that could go really bad.
I'd glue both sides down.
You'd be a-okay.
- We'll see.
- We'll--
I want to create arm extensions
that look like scorpion claws
or even praying mantis hands.
so I take L200,
which is a type of foam
that can be
cut, manipulated, heated,
bent so that it can make
really quick, fabricated pieces.
So I use it to fabricate
the hands,
and I paint them
the best I can.
- Almost-- There we go.
- It's working.
I'm running out of time
at the end of the day.
I need to get this arm molded
so that tomorrow
I can run it in poly foam.
I still have to mold the cowl,
so I'm trying to go
as fast as I can,
but I don't know if I'm going
to be able to finish this.
How many minutes time?
3:18.
Oh, my God. I hope
this shit opens tomorrow.
So Niko and I are running
around the mold room
like crazy people, just trying
to get these molds done,
and Tyler runs in there
and really helps me out.
We got it, we got it,
we got it, we got this.
We get it done, but Niko
still has to finish his cowl.
Put some here, put some here.
Okay. Done?
Yes, yes.
- That's time, everybody.
- Look. We did it!
- Whoo!
- Nice, nice.
Thank you, thank you.
We finished it.
At the end of the day,
I feel pretty happy
that I have everything done.
I know I have a lot of work
to do tomorrow,
and I'm worried
that I can't make it all happen.
- Good luck, guys.
- Thank you, man.
Whoo!
It's application day,
and we've got
four hours in the lab,
one more hour at last looks,
and I believe that's enough time
to make this thing
good and creepy.
- Corinne.
- Megan, nice to meet you.
You're like a goddess of pain.
Oh, my God.
You're scary.
My strategy today is to start
the application immediately
because there are so many
elements to this character.
The dental appliance,
the face, the cowl,
everything laying
over top of each other.
There is no room
for error today.
Your character
is very mischievous.
Let me get around you.
Time is ticking down.
I've got to get the back piece
and the face piece on my model.
The back goes down perfect,
and I'm loving it.
Cool.
I open my mold,
and there's a huge seam.
It's going to take
a long time to fix.
My model has
no appliances on whatsoever,
and I just decide, look,
forget about these arms.
I need to worry
about just getting my model
applied and painted.
This is going to be
the end of me.
I finish applying the cowl
and face, and I realize
that his arms and his chest
are still just skin.
A little saran wrap to you.
So I start just gluing
this plastic wrap
all around my model to get
a sort of wrinkly texture.
- Pretty weird, huh?
- Yeah.
I've never done it before,
so I don't know
if it's going to work.
I look at him.
He's standing up.
And I'm like, "I'm doing, like,
a really big makeup."
This is, like, one of the
biggest pieces that I have done
and super, super fast,
so I'm really impressed
with myself.
I'm feeling
a little bit nervous
because everyone else
has much bigger creatures,
so I have to have
a great paint job,
in order to make this
a great makeup,
versus a simple makeup.
All right, everyone,
that's 15 minutes.
_
I know it's missing the arms,
which is a very important part
of the makeup.
At least everything's applied,
and he's got
his base coat of paint.
All right, everybody,
that's time!
I think I can pull the paint
together, but my model's
not going to match
the silhouette,
so I'm really worried.
The most important part
of my makeup isn't there.
Coming up...
These horns are
just too damn heavy.
Shit.
There's still
a lot of work needed
to pull my creature together.
It's not a good feeling.
I dig it a lot.
It's creepy-licious.
I'm at a loss of words
for this.
I didn't find it to be
particularly scary.
We have one of the shortest
hours in human history.
Turn around.
I just need to get
these huge horns to attach
that I don't know will work.
Will you hold this for me?
I need to add all of his
highlights and yellow accents.
There's still
a lot of work needed
to pull my creature together.
It's not a good feeling.
Hold still, buddy.
Hold still.
I'm trying to put the other
two side horns on that I made.
I sort of get one in.
I'm gluing the hell out of it.
Please stay still.
The horns are
just too damn heavy.
Shit.
It's just not working.
Damn it.
- 15 minutes left, everyone!
- Uh-oh.
All right, everyone.
That's time.
- Brushes down.
- Fuck!
I really screwed this one up.
Welcome
to theFace Offreveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
First, let's say hello
to our talented panel of judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Make-Up
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
Hi, everybody.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Creature and concept designer,
Neville Page.
- Hi, guys.
- Neville.
And please welcome back
writer, producer, and director,
Oren Peli.
Hi, guys.
Good to see you again.
Looking forward to seeing
your creations.
All right, guys, this week,
your spotlight challenge
was to select
an exaggerated silhouette
and create the supernatural
entity that cast the shadow.
Let's take a look
at your creations,
while the audience at home
tweets about their favorites
using #FaceOff.
I'm loving it.
It looks impressive
and-- and scary.
I love the fact the hair
is covering the face,
and the mouth
is coming out of the back.
It's very dark, and you don't
really know what it is.
I'm really excited.
This is a character
that I really love,
I had a lot of fun doing,
and he looks great.
I'm really worried.
He's probably the weakest makeup
this challenge.
I know I'm going to be
on bottom.
This guy looks really big
and really menacing.
I feel really proud of it.
She looks really creepy
and sneaky,
and I'm confident
with the paint job
and the success
of the actual makeup.
She's rocking it.
The shadow shape, the bug
quality to the whole character
is really coming through,
and I'm feeling pretty good.
I'm loving my horns.
I think they're scary.
I just hope Oren
and the rest of the judges do
because there are a lot
of other makeups
that are more intimidating
than mine.
This thing looks so creepy.
If I'm not at top looks, I'm
at least safe with this makeup,
because if I think
it's this badass,
then the judges at least
have to think it's cool.
This silhouette looks great.
It looks very similar
to what I was given,
but it also has a little bit
of my own flair
and style to it.
I know
I'm up the old proverbial creek
without a paddle
because all the imperfections
are staring me in the face.
I can't even look at it.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look
at our supernatural entities?
There's some really rad shapes
going on in the horns.
It's my favorite part
of this makeup.
It's really riffing off
of the shadow.
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
Looks a little bit
like a diseased homeless guy.
Please turn, so we can see
your back, please.
Oh, yeah.
What is that thing?
We have to ask.
I don't understand it.
- Can you open your mouth?
- Yeah, let's see it.
Oh, yeah.
There we go.
I like the overall design,
but it feels a little bit
- like a mask.
- It does.
I don't understand
the hard shapes.
Not very supernatural.
More like
an alien-insect type thing.
I'm worried. I see the judges
pointing out problems.
I know they're not happy
with it.
There's a good chance
that I could be sent home.
Who made your favorite
supernatural entity?
Tell us on Twitter,
using #FaceOff.
Turn your head sideways.
That's a cool silhouette.
That has nothing to do
with the silhouette in here.
I know I'm going to be
in the bottom.
I look at everybody else's,
and he's not
the strongest makeup.
Look at this brown iridescence
floating around in here.
It's really nice.
This guy looks
like he means business.
Like, if you see him
in a dark alley,
you're going to run
the other way.
Great.
Great paint job.
Very, very, very nice patterns.
Thanks.
I'm not sure what's going on,
- but it's cool.
- Yeah.
It's, like, half-human,
half-whatever.
This on purpose?
I think it ripped after he
put it on, so he colored it in.
I'm going to try playing
on the judges' mercy,
like, "Please, I'm--
I'm much better than this."
- It's not really scary.
- It's cute almost.
The judges have scored
your creations.
Let's find out
what they thought.
George,
Tyler,
Chloe,
Rashaad,
Matt...
Congratulations,
you are all safe.
You can head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you.
The rest of you
were the best and the worst.
The judges will now speak
with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Graham, please step up.
Graham, tell us how
you incorporated your shadow.
I tried to incorporate some
of the things that creep me out,
which are cockroaches, so I
threw in some creepy bug parts,
and this is what would really
end up scaring me now.
I love it.
I love the sculpture
of the face, particularly.
I dig it a lot.
It's creepy-licious.
Thank you.
You have a really great
transitional area
in the sternum.
It's done so well.
Thank you.
It definitely implies
something very off-putting,
so that's a gorgeous part
of this.
- Great work.
- Thank you.
Whatever this thing is,
I've never seen
anything like it before,
so it's very cool
and creepy and original design.
Thank you very much.
- Graham, please step back.
- Awesome.
- Good job, dude.
- Daran.
Tell us about your concept
and how you incorporated
your silhouette.
I saw the shadow as a demon.
I wanted to keep my focus
on the back
as a mouth for the hump.
And this mouth
will swallow your soul.
Turn your character around.
That does not look
like a mouth at all.
I'm at a loss of words
for this, Daran.
It doesn't even look like
you finished painting it.
I don't think
this is a great makeup.
Sorry to disappoint.
I think that you have achieved
kind of a classic vision
of horror, but I--
I think you just went
way too abstract.
It's just
not very supernatural.
Looks very human.
- Daran, you can head back.
- Thanks, buddy.
Let's talk to Niko.
So tell us how you interpreted
your cast shadow.
Once I saw the shadow,
I saw a bull
because of the horns
and hooves,
but I wanted to make it
more human.
That's when I went
with a minotaur.
- This is really a beautiful piece.
- Thank you.
You didn't use
the actor's eyes.
I think that this is
one of the more successful
- ways of doing it.
- Thank you.
This is probably
the scariest one of the bunch.
It matches the shadow
really well.
It's menacing.
It's scary.
- Very well done.
- Thank you.
Your work,
in terms of proportion,
is quite beautiful.
It's big enough to push
an already big model
into gigantic, but it's not
so big that it's clumsy.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
Niko, please step back.
Good job, baby.
Cat, please step forward.
Tell me about your concept.
How did you come up
with this particular design?
I hate bugs.
I think that's why I was drawn
to the silhouette.
It reminded me of a cross
between a beetle
and a praying mantis.
For me, it looks like
he's wearing a mask.
So I didn't find it to be
particularly scary
or-- or supernatural.
Mm-hmm.
I abhor the decision to have
this hard surface on his face,
and I don't see the silhouette.
I don't think
it's a very good makeup.
- I've seen you do better.
- I agree.
I think
one of the main failures for me
is your paint job
is a little weak.
It's odd to see yellow splotches
on the face.
Cat, you can step down.
Tanner, you're up.
Tanner, tell us
about your character.
I wanted a very old demon.
As deer grow older and older,
their horns get
larger and larger--
his horns getting so big that
nothing's going to stop them
from growing.
You've got some serious issues.
I-- Yeah.
I noticed
that there's a gaping aperture
next to what appears to be
some sort of vacuum tubing.
It was going to be
another set of horns,
but I was running
into a lot of weight problems.
Not good.
Tanner, can you tell us
what you used on his body?
It looks to me like
you wrapped him in cellophane
and hoped for the best.
Yeah, that didn't
really work too well.
- Wow, I'm disappointed.
- Yeah, I am too.
The other bigger problem is
that he's just really far
from being camera-ready.
- Absolutely.
- Tanner, you can head back.
Thanks, man.
Corinne, please step up.
Tell us the story
behind this character.
When I was looking
at the movements,
I decided that it was a goblin
that creeps
in the middle of the night
and does nasty things
while people are sleeping.
Nobody knows what hit them.
She is definitely
a creepy, little thing.
That is
a magnificent paint job.
Her arms are amazing.
Thanks.
I think that this is
a beautiful, subtle makeup.
This character feels plausible.
It's beautiful work.
Thank you.
Seems like you've nailed
supernatural entity to me.
Crawling around the corner of a
bedroom when a kid is sleeping,
it would be scary as hell.
Massive success on that level
of this challenge, for sure.
Thank you.
Corinne, please step back.
All right, guys, the judges have
heard what you have to say.
If you'd please
head back to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
All right, judges,
why don't we talk
about the looks you liked
the most this week?
Let's start with Graham.
I think he did a great job
at hitting the right notes
to tell the story
of a supernatural entity,
a shadow.
The chest was so cool.
That transition
from little finger things.
We've never seen anything
that looked like this before.
It's very cool and creepy.
All right,
let's move on to Niko.
That head was so
well-balanced, proportionally.
The sculpt of it was cool.
It was a riveting piece.
Out of all of them,
it's the one that evoked
the most genuine feeling
of fear.
Okay, let's move on to Corinne.
I thought this was
a really cool makeup.
I really enjoyed the paint job.
I especially liked
the treatment of the arms.
The particular challenge
aspect of trying to take
this shadow and create a makeup
of a creature
that could cast the shadow,
I think that she fulfilled that
the most accurately.
The quality,
the execution of it
- was really, really excellent.
- All right, judges.
Let's move on
to the bottom looks this week.
As you know,
you have the ability to give
special immunity this season.
- Yeah.
- Why don't we start with Daran?
For me, he did two things
that were a grave mistake.
The first one, an overly
simplistic idea from front view
and an overly complicated idea
from rear view.
Whatever was going on
in the back was just weird,
and I don't think
it worked on any level.
And the front looked human
with raggedy clothes.
He said that that back thing
was his focal point.
Well, if that's your focal
point, why isn't it finished?
All right,
let's move on to Cat.
The paint job,
I-I don't get it.
Looks like she just took
a brush,
and went bam, bam, bam,
and put polka dots on his face.
It looked like a guy
wearing an alien mask
- and not much else going on.
- She keeps saying it was a bug.
Doesn't look like a bug
to me at all.
Let's move on to Tanner.
This is one of the worst things
I've seen on this show.
Everything was falling off--
the chest piece,
one of the horns on the front.
The cellophane was unwrapping.
That was a bad choice.
He should've just
painted the skin.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
Yeah.
Okay, let's bring them
back out.
Glenn, tell us
about the top looks.
Graham, we really liked
your cockroach-inspired makeup,
and we love
that you gave us something
that we've never seen before.
Niko, you handled
the facial sculpture
of your character
extremely well,
and the character was
very well-proportioned.
Corinne, we love
that you presented us
with a beautiful,
believable makeup,
and your shadow inspiration
was very clear.
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of this challenge is--
- Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of this challenge is...
Niko.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Your character
was scary, imposing,
and it matched up
with its shadow.
- Great job.
- Thank you.
I'm really happy.
I'm super stoked.
It's-- it's--
This is why I came here.
- Niko, congratulations.
- Thank you.
You and Corinne and Graham can
head back to the makeup room.
Unfortunately, that means
the rest of you
are on the bottom this week.
One of you will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Daran, it was obvious that
you tried to do way too much.
The paint, in particular,
was very rudimentary.
Cat, your makeup did not feel
like a supernatural entity
to us,
and we did not see the
relationship with your shadow.
Tanner, there were
significant issues
with your overall character,
and it turned out
more cute than scary.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Tanner.
Unfortunately, everything you
tried this week didn't work out.
There were just too many
problems with this character.
That means, Daran and Cat,
you are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
I'm sorry, brother.
Tanner, you've exhibited
some amazing raw potential.
Combined
with your great attitude,
you'll go very far
in your career.
Thank you so much. It's been
an-- a wonderful experience.
Good luck, man.
Tanner, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
It's been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please
head back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- Bye. Thank you.
- Good luck, Tanner.
Bye, Tanner.
Good luck, hon.
I'm bummed.
I made errors.
That's the most
disappointing part.
I know
that I'm better than that.
Oh, dude.
It's been crazy.
I've never worked so hard
and so fast.
I'm going to take away
a lot of great experiences.
And I'm proud of the makeups
and the things
that I've accomplished here.
This experience has definitely
made me a better makeup artist,
so I'm going to keep going
buck wild with it.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net