You did it so damn good.
Well, that's impressive.
It's just gorgeous, guys.
Previously on Face Off...
Tyler's creepy cryptid
brought him
his second victory,
and Matt was sent home.
Now nine artists remain.
And tonight they're faced
with a magical challenge...
- Oh.
- No way.
...that will cause
one of them
- to disappear.
- Let's go.
That's gonna look like
a man wearing a mask.
At this point, I'm going home.
- It's actually starting to burn.
- Oh, really?
I may be screwed on this one.
You did one hell of a job.
Fucking gorgeous, man.
She looks like a refugee
from a craft store.
In the end, only one
will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a brand new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Face Off!
Welcome toFace Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Matt's gone.
There's another guy gone.
There's only three
of us left, though--
- only three girls.
- It's been what--
like, three challenges
since a girl went home?
- Four?
- Let's keep it that way.
I want there to be
a girl winner.
Girl power.
I think we've all done
some pretty cool stuff
and have good ideas
and are good at what we do.
So it's great to be here,
but I think at this point,
we're all competing
pretty hard.
- Yeah.
- I love them.
But I want to make it
to the end,
and I want to win.
Wouldn't it be cool
if all three of us
- made it to the finals?
- That'd be a first.
Let's make it happen.
Now, that's a castle.
We're in Hollywood.
We look up, and it's
the famous Magic Castle.
"Members and guests only."
Where everyone wants to visit,
but you can't get it in
'cause it's a club,
and you got to be a magician--
it's insane.
Hi, welcome to the world-famous
Hollywood Magic Castle.
This mysterious hostess
lady says to get in,
you have to say
the secret password.
Open sesame?
No way!
No!
There's so much cool stuff
all over the walls.
This is so cool.
And I'm just trying to take it all in.
This place is so cool.
We end up in front
of this stage,
and I have no idea
what's in store.
This is so cool.
Whoa.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Welcome to
the world-famous Magic Castle.
For over 50 years, this
members-only club has hosted
some of the most spectacular
magicians in the world.
And it continues to be
one of the most exclusive
hangouts in Hollywood.
Nice.
Now, throughout history,
magic was seen
as a source of great power
to be worshiped and feared.
Legends like Merlin
and Shakespeare's Prospero
perpetuated the idea
of an all-powerful wizard
who could cast spells
and control the Earth.
While all wizards are armed
with wit, wisdom, and wonder,
their abilities are lost
without one vital object...
their wand.
There's mechanical wands,
gold wands,
voodoo wands,
wands with ice on them.
There's so much to choose from.
Your spotlight challenge is
to choose one of these wands
and use it to inspire
an original wizard of your own.
- Nice.
- That's cool.
Already, my heart's going,
'cause I love Harry Potter,
Lord Of The Rings,
and I know
that I can win this thing.
Tyler, you're up first.
Pchew!
All right, guys,
I'm going to leave you here
to work on your designs.
When you're done, head back
to the lab and get to work.
Bye.
I picked this tribal wand,
so I definitely want
to incorporate the feathers.
I figure more
of a witch doctor,
shaman, have him wear
some furs maybe.
I got this wand 'cause
I love organic characters.
So I thought immediately
of doing a natural wizard.
And he's made up of tree bark,
pieces of wood.
And he's a protector
of the deep forest.
I went with this wand.
It looks really futuristic
and really sci-fi.
My concept is there's
this wizard
that wanted to have
an assistant,
so he created this robot.
But the robot kills the wizard
and takes the power of the wand.
So let's see
if I can make it work.
I got a super-cool wand,
kind of like,
a light saber kind of thing.
All the aspects of the wand
are gonna be integrated
into the cowl, the back, arms,
and a lot of cool
mechanical patterns all over.
He's gonna be
a very mean wizard.
I chose this wand
because I thought it was
the most beautiful one up there.
And it's very feminine.
So I want to do a woman wizard.
And she's becoming one
with the forest
and has all these vines,
plants,
and all these flowers
growing from her skin.
And I really want to have
this beautiful silhouette
of these leaves.
So I'm excited.
- Let's head back to the lab.
- Let's make some magic.
Today's the first day
of our wizard challenge.
And we get to choose our model
and start sculpting.
I'm not too much a fan
of magic and wizard.
And I have this idea
of, like, robot.
But how can I make robot
like a wizard?
Maybe instead of the muscle
and cables inside,
I can put the back of him
in front so it looks clear.
_
So I don't know if it's gonna
look good.
I just try to see
what I can do.
Let's go.
The wand itself has
this blue arc,
these twigs around it,
and barbed wire
tying it all together.
So I want to make my character
look like the wand,
all spiky and sharp.
So he has all these
little horns and things
pushing through his skin,
just like barbed wire.
I'm going more minimal
than I usually do,
and we'll see how that works.
I picked a wand
that has a chicken's foot
at the end of it
holding an eyeball.
And I'm gonna make this
a warlock
that has no sight of her own.
So she's gonna be using
this wand and this eyeball
to see everything.
And then I want to do
these really gnarly teeth
to give it a real scary look.
So I picked the crystal wand,
and I'm seeing
all this really
beautiful filigree
at the top of the wand,
and the crystal is
really predominant
so I decide to go
with the filigree
being a binding spell
that was cast
on this sorceress.
Man, I just signed myself up
for a whole shitload
of intricate detail.
Hey, guys.
Here for a walk-through.
- Hello.
- So he's merging with the wand.
The metal is actually
integrating into him.
Mm-hmm.
I would say make sure
you get all these things
deep enough to really see
all the detail
and all these gears
and everything.
- All right.
- Interesting.
Now, what drew you to this one?
The creepiness.
It has these sort
of voodoo-type skulls,
so I'm thinking he's sort of
been keeping himself alive
by collecting skulls.
I'm really needing to
incorporate the skull design.
So he's gonna be
sort of emaciated,
old man, voodoo lord.
I'm giving him these sort of,
like, tooth piercings.
I like that, yeah.
- This is a great idea.
- That's a great idea.
- I've never seen it.
- Thank you.
What made you choose this one?
I like the colors in it,
number one.
And I'm a real fan
of organic things.
I'm gonna do a witch face
with some really gnarly teeth
coming out.
And I'm gonna make
a second piece
and just put it over
the whole face.
Are you gonna age
as much of the skin
- as you can?
- Yes.
If you're gonna do that aging,
you need to do it quick--
little old age
on the throat too.
- Right.
- What made you pick this one?
Because it looks,
like, very futuristic,
and, like, I can work more
with a robot type.
- Mm-hmm.
- I sculpted this face piece.
Then, I want to sculpt
all the joints
on the robot on the inside.
And then I will put
the plastic on top of it.
This looks like
it could be Neanderthal
as opposed to more robotic.
Michael Westmore's opinion
means a lot to me.
And I'm already stressing out.
That's gonna look like
a man wearing a mask.
It's almost, like,
halfway the day.
And there's not enough time
to start all over again.
You're trying to get
a mechanical look on this too,
- aren't you?
- Yes.
It's gonna look like...
basically a human chest.
Maybe he's right.
Maybe it won't look good.
I don't know
what to do right now.
Coming up...
It looks like a mess.
I completely underestimated
how hard something like that is.
For the face,
it's not working out.
She just looks fantastic.
So much wrong about this.
This looks like
it could be Neanderthal.
It's day one
on our wizard challenge,
and Mr. Westmore
says that my shape looks
too round for being a robot.
Flatten out
some of your features.
By squaring these things off,
it would show off
your structure underneath.
Mr. Westmore tell me
some really good advice,
and hopefully
I can get everything done
by the end of the day.
This is a character
I always wanted to do--
something like a wizard
of the wood.
He's actually made up
of the forest and the trees.
Be careful, when you're
making your chest in here,
that it doesn't have
two human pecs.
It just brings the human
back out of it again.
I wanted to kind
of elongate the skull
to get more
of the Mayan type of a shape.
You've got it in your drawing,
but in here, literally,
start it back up here...
- Okay.
- ...so you have this
whole Indian type
of a look to it.
She's a pretty,
young sorceress,
but I wanted to make sure
she still looks different.
So I kind of built up her nose
with these fruits.
If you want to keep her
beautiful,
I wouldn't do that.
It makes it look like
there's been some trauma
that's going on.
All right, guys,
we're heading out.
It's looking good.
Good luck.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
I mean, I'm gonna paint them
to look like roots.
Mr. Westmore tells me
I should do less vines
around the nose area.
And it definitely makes me
nervous,
but I think
they're very important
to the character,
so I'm going to keep them.
I am zooming with my face,
and I think I actually
got it done in record time.
I get my mold done,
and I'm starting
to block out the chest,
the back, and getting
the bark placed,
ready to vacuum-form
first thing tomorrow morning.
My wand has all these wheels
that grind together.
So I want those lines
in the face,
and then I'll leave some kind
of human element to it,
so you can see
that it's a human,
that it's getting merged
into it.
What time is it?
1:19.
So I decide to make this face
and then put a vacuform
in top of it.
But the face is too bulky,
so it's not working out.
And then time's up.
All right, guys, it's time.
- Worse and worse every time.
- Really?
I don't like it.
I don't know what I'm doing.
I'm just getting
really frustrated.
_
I don't have a cowl.
I still have to work
on the chest.
And I have to figure out
this face.
So I'm getting
a little bit worried
because there's a lot to do.
It's day two
of our wizard challenge.
We have ten hours today.
I need to sculpt the chest,
but I still am having
a hard time
even falling in love
with this concept.
I'm hoping that I can pull
this off
because I just really need
something to get onstage.
I need to finish the cowl
and make sure to place
some feathers in
so I have a placement line
for where I want to put
the feathers
once I have the foam piece.
With such
a minimalistic makeup,
I'm really gonna have to have
a flawless execution.
Yesterday I ran my face
in foam latex,
so my plan is to
finish sculpting
the chest and the cowl
and also run a second face
to see if I can get
a better version
to apply tomorrow.
I like it.
- It's, like, badass-looking.
- Yeah.
The face mold comes out perfect
and cleans out immediately.
Good for me
and my molding abilities.
I move on to the chest,
and I'm trying to throw
a little bit of strangeness
into the design
because it needs to be
something
that hasn't been seen before.
So I want some cool
rib anatomy going on.
Suck in your stomach
as much as you can.
Oh, that's perfect.
I take a picture
of Niko's chest
and get a cool idea
off of that.
I want to sculpt the chest
to look as if his rib cage
is growing through his chest
and his skin is healing
around it.
I'm still feeling nervous
'cause I'm going more minimal
than I normally do.
I decide I need to give him
some height
without making a huge cowl
that's gonna really
weigh him down.
So I'm creating bark by
vacuum-forming shapes of clay
and then attaching it to him
as if it's almost
like a crown on his head.
Nice.
Those will be cheated down
'cause I put it way back.
And I can cock it
any which direction I want.
I am so inspired
by this challenge.
Oh, my God.
I am seeing my vision
come to life,
and I think people
are just like...
So I'm sculpting
the chest piece,
and I'm realizing that
this is taking way more time
than I really have.
The chest piece is
the same filigree patterning
as the neck,
tons of swirls upon lines
upon swirls
that all kind of flow
and connect together.
I feel like it looks
like a mess.
But I completely underestimated
how hard something like
that is.
There's so many fucking swirls.
I am running out of time.
I've already invested the past
two days into this piece.
But if I don't change
my design,
I'm gonna have big trouble.
It's day two
of our wizard challenge,
and the chest piece is taking
way more time
than I really have.
That's a lot of swirls.
The chest is really important,
because without it,
my makeup
isn't gonna make any sense.
There's so many fucking swirls.
Look, that's what it
calls for. Look at that.
Even though
I want to do smaller,
more intricate filigree,
I don't have that option.
I need to do it bigger so
that I have to do less of them.
I don't like it,
but I need to move on,
or I won't have a chest piece.
Okay, I incorporated
my little burgundy things
in my forehead piece.
As the day's going on,
I finished my sculpture
on my ornamental piece,
and I'm feeling extremely
excited about my wizard.
I've got my hands I've got
to knock out really quick.
So I'm doing hands, face,
and then a forehead piece.
Creepy hands done, sir.
Yesterday
I was having a problem
vacuforming the face.
My old concept wasn't working,
so I decided to go
for a new one.
So, instead of covering
the whole face with a vacuform,
I'm just gonna have his face
uncovered like a helmet.
So I'm feeling better,
and hopefully
I can get it all done.
It's cool.
I like the design.
It looks great.
So, after all my molds
are done,
I start fabricating
this huge flower
that's going to be growing
out of my wizard's back.
So I make a stencil out
of the vacuform with plastic.
And I take a heat gun,
and I start shaping it
to look like these huge petals.
Oh, nice.
I'm really excited about this.
Let's see what Tyler
is doing over here.
It looks pretty cool.
By the end of the day two,
I have the face
completely pre-painted.
The cowl is complete.
I'm starting to see
a wizard here.
And I'm like, "All right,
I just whipped this magic up
out of nowhere.
Here we go."
This is, like,
your dream challenge, huh?
Yeah.
That's time, guys.
Application day needs to come
because I'm ready to go here.
So it's application day.
We have four hours in the lab
and one hour in last looks.
Now I'm trimming
the flashing off
the chest and the back piece,
which had little rips here
and there.
But I'm gonna have moss
come out.
All right.
- Good to see you.
- George, bro.
This is gonna be you today.
- Ah, yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
First, I need to get
the cowl fitted.
Since I'm only doing
three prosthetics,
it could seem like
I'm going too simple,
so I really have to focus
on the details,
make sure that everything's
applied well
and fully painted.
I start applying the face,
and when it's almost
all glued down...
- It's actually starting to burn.
- Oh, really?
_
- Sorry.
- No, no, no. That's fine.
It starts to burn him.
He's allergic to Telesis.
Telesis is used to glue
the prosthetic to the model.
I start taking it off.
Okay, let's clean you up
so it doesn't burn you.
Thank goodness I made
an extra face.
- You made two?
- Yeah.
Just in case.
You never know.
I applied Pros-Aide
which is another type of glue.
It's perfect.
It works.
But now I'm way behind,
so I got to speed this up.
I start applying
the chest piece first.
And then I lay
the neck piece over that.
But now I'm starting to panic
because I still don't like it.
I got to pull
this thing together,
whether it's
with the beauty makeup
or a killer paint job.
But I don't even believe
in this piece.
And I don't know how the judges
are gonna believe in it either.
One of the extra things
I'd like to add
on to this character is
to take the hash marks
that are gored
into his chest and bring
that design out
all over the place.
I'm really excited about it,
and I can't wait to hear
what the judges think.
There, makeup done.
I start working
with my two arms.
I'm using L200
and different metal pieces.
So it look like he's getting
really infused with metal parts.
A lot of people are already
painting and airbrushing,
and I still have
to fabricate a lot.
And I just started painting.
I don't even know at this point
if I'm gonna have time
to do it all.
I'm extremely nervous
'cause I only have
an hour to paint.
And I have to get not only
a flawless paint job
between his skin, silicone,
and foam,
but I need a tribal paint
on top of that.
Because my wand has
a crystal ball
in the middle,
I'm incorporating globes
coming out of her chest.
After that, I start painting
like a madwoman.
I decide to paint her orange
to make her
less human-looking.
It's the same color scheme
as the actual petals,
so she looks
like she's part of the flower.
30 minutes, people.
Everything's glued down,
so now I have apply
these tube connectors
that are fusing into his skin,
then finish this paint job,
and put on the hands.
That's time, everybody.
Time's up, and I still have
to do so much.
I'm sweating bullets here.
I only have one hour
in last looks to finish this.
Whew.
I may be screwed on this one.
Coming up...
Everything I'm trying
to glue down
is not sticking.
I'm just getting
really frustrated.
This resonated through you.
- It's gorgeous.
- It's so well done.
I am really disappointed
in this makeup.
Hold on.
We get to last looks,
and I know I'm really gonna
have to scramble,
'cause I have to have
a great paint job
to make this
a great-looking wizard.
I know I have to finish
this paint.
I start going in
with highlights, shadows.
I have to blend the seams
around the chest and stomach.
And that's a lot of work
to do in an hour.
I'm starting
on the beauty makeup.
My hands are shaking because
of the stress and exhaustion
from trying to get this
makeup done.
30 minutes, guys.
I'm getting really frustrated.
Everything I'm trying
to glue down is not sticking.
I know it's not my best work.
At this point, I'm like,
"I'm going home."
I get the beard on.
It looks great.
And I'm adding
the moss everywhere.
There's so much involved
in the makeup,
but everything is coming
together.
Hey, everybody, that's time.
That's it.
Welcome to theFace Off
reveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
But first, let's say hello
to our talented judges--
owner of Optic Nerve
Make-Up Effects Studio,
- Glenn Hetrick...
- Good evening, guys.
- Good evening, Glenn.
- Hi, Glenn.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill...
- Hi, guys.
- Hey, Ve.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
- Hello.
- Hi, Neville.
So this week
your spotlight challenge
was to select a wand
and use it to inspire
an original wizard character
of your very own.
So let's take a look
at your magical creations
while the audience
at home tweets
about their favorites,
using #FaceOff.
My wizard turned out
exactly how I wanted it.
She's got vines
growing out of her.
She's got flowers
growing from her.
She looks like
she's one with nature.
I wish I would've done
something different
with the beauty makeup,
but it's out of my hands
at this point.
I think
he has the perfect look.
I like the silhouette,
and I'm really pleased
with how it turned out.
He looks like a freakin' tree.
He's standing there,
and I'm like,
"I did it.
This is great."
He looks cool.
I really like it a lot.
And I think I created
something unique here.
I'm very pleased with her.
She's looking very cool.
She goes well with the wand.
And I think
it's the complete package.
The first thing I see is
a seam on his chest piece.
I'm not happy,
and I know that the judges
are gonna notice it too.
This definitely looks like
I had imagined it
to look like, with some
of the voodoo elements.
So I love it.
I just don't feel good
about this.
It's one of the worst,
and I think I'm going home.
And I feel, like,
really frustrated.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look at our wizards?
I don't get it.
There's so many better ways
to approach this appliance.
Yeah, there's such
a lost opportunity.
And it's so orange.
Thank you.
It would've been nice
to have seen this detail
up here
on the forehead as well.
It just looks sloppy.
That's the problem.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
- I like the broken teeth.
- Yeah.
Using the war paint as a way
to hide these edges
is really smart.
Thank you.
Wow.
This guy's covered.
I love the unburnt transition
all the way to the charred
at the top.
This is so cool.
These ridges--
I don't understand them,
and I don't need to,
'cause it feels right.
Thanks.
I love the mask.
It feels so natural,
and it has
a feel of the forest.
Very cool.
These are particularly
rough edges all through here.
Can you turn to the side?
The seams are really bad.
Look at this.
Everything you don't want them
to notice, they notice.
For the first time,
I'm not feeling confident.
And from watching the judges,
I know I'm in trouble.
Who made your favorite
wand-wielding wizard tonight?
Tell us on Twitter,
using #FaceOff.
These are particularly
rough edges all through here.
Well, he did his best to use
the paint job
to cover them, though--
I'll tell you that much.
The judges go in
for a closer look,
and I have to hope that they
look at the overall design.
And I'm hoping
that'll be enough to save me.
What's he got going on here?
That's a fun treatment
I've never seen before.
- I love the teeth.
- I do.
I like all of this in here.
He has finger extensions,
though, too.
- Thank you.
- Very cool.
- It's a wreck.
- Yeah.
It doesn't have
the smoothness of metal.
- I can see streaks.
- Unbearable to look at.
Okay, the judges
have scored your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Rashaad...
Graham..
Daran...
Congratulations--
you are all safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you.
The rest of you
were the best and the worst.
The judges would now like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Corinne, please step forward.
Explain to me how your wand
influenced your concept
this week.
When I saw the wand,
it felt very tribal to me.
So I decided that
it was gonna be a dark shaman.
You did one hell of a job
executing the makeup.
You can do a minimal makeup
if you execute it
in a super-clean,
professional manner.
That's exactly
what you've done this week.
Thank you.
You have a stupendous paint job
all over his entire body.
Great coloring.
It looks like a mud treatment.
He looks fantastic.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
The paint job, the sculpt,
particularly the Peruvian skull
is really a very smart,
unique element--
- so well handled.
- Thank you.
Corinne, please step back.
Yeah, Corinne.
Chloe, you're up.
Tell us about your wand
and your character.
What I really liked
was the filigree
at the top of the wand,
which is all of this.
Overall, I don't mind
the whole concept.
I just think you went
a little heavy-handed.
It would've been nice,
instead of painting up here,
to have seen that
filigree carried around her face
so that it tied
the whole look together.
For me, really, the problem is
you bit off
a little bit more than time
would allow you to chew.
Trying to get all of that
filigree under that giant space
results in what is a meandering,
confused pattern.
Chloe, you can step back.
George, you're up.
Hey, buddy.
So tell us what it
was about your magic wand
- that inspired this.
- Okay.
I tried to integrate it
into my design,
like he's being possessed by it
and converted
into this metallic being.
There's so much about this
I really do like.
This showcases
sophisticated design,
form language, concept.
It is fucking gorgeous, man.
Thanks, man.
It really just is.
Thank you, brother.
Thank you.
It feels like this concept
just resonated through you
into every aspect
of what you designed.
- It's gorgeous.
- Thanks, man.
I especially love
your paint job.
The transition
from that metalized skin
onto that flesh tone
is so absolutely stunning.
Thank you.
Thanks a lot.
- George, thank you very much.
- Thanks, man.
- Thank you.
- Nice job, George.
Thank you.
Cat, please step up.
Cat, tell us about how your
wand worked into the concept.
Her name is Flora
Of The Forest,
and she protects the plant life,
and she heals people as well.
I'll tell you,
I absolutely love the wings.
Unfortunately, that is all
that I love about this makeup.
The style of the sculpture
detracts from the beauty
of the model
instead of augmenting it.
I am really disappointed
in this makeup.
She looks like a refugee
from a craft store.
The vine work on her face
feels more like a disease.
It's not working for me.
Cat, please step back.
Tyler, please step forward.
Tell us about the wand
that you got
and how it influenced
your makeup.
He is a wizard of the woods
and protects
the forest from fire.
I think you did a great job.
Everything blends together.
I mean,
it's all really well designed.
You clearly have spent time
in the woods,
looking and absorbing
what bark and branches do,
because it feels authentic.
- And that's hard to do quickly.
- Thank you.
It's tremendously successful.
The nose and chin are
very unorthodox,
and they really work.
Thank you very much.
Tyler, please step back.
Niko, please step forward.
Tell us about the magic wand
and how that inspired
your concept.
He has evil powers.
He controls
all metals and electronics.
And every time he use it,
he gets infused
with metal parts.
There's so much wrong
about this.
Be so careful about how far
you stretch your skill set
to the point where it snaps.
And I think for you,
it completely snapped.
When you're doing
hard surfaces,
you either need to make them
super, super smooth
so that when you paint them,
they actually look like metal,
or you have to apply
some sort of texture
that would be appropriate
for a metallic surface.
You have neither.
I think your problem
was your lack of knowledge
of the subject matter
that we were asking you to do.
I mean, yeah,
I have seen movies,
and I know,
but it's not, like, my type.
And I think that's
to your detriment this week,
and that's why this happened.
Niko, you can step back.
All right, guys,
the judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you would please head back
to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
All right, so, judges,
let's talk about the looks
you liked the most this week.
Why don't we start
with Corinne?
Simple, clean, so well done.
Yeah, very well executed,
great paint job,
- really clean application.
- It's killer--
perfectly asymmetrical,
very natural-looking.
All right,
let's move on to George.
I loved the way the flesh
tones came off of that metal.
And that beautiful paint job
that he did--
I mean, what a great choice
of colors.
There's one singular moment,
which is that fleshy bit
of skin.
That, as a makeup on its own--
so well handled.
The true magic
in George's work this week
is his ability to have conceived
and executed something
that brilliant
in the time that he had.
All right,
let's move on to Tyler.
I loved the transition
between the moss,
from the warmer wood up to
the deadening up by his head.
We all know what
a tree should look like,
but not everyone
can sculpt one.
That was impressive.
That was a lot of work.
All right, judges,
let's move on to the looks
we liked the least.
Let's start with Chloe.
She just bit off
more than she could chew.
That filigree
was the kiss of death.
She grabbed the wrong element
of the wand
to inspire her design.
It wasn't very cohesive.
It wasn't a really beautifully
blended makeup.
Let's move on to Cat.
I mean, it looks like
a bomb went off
at a craft store,
and that poor creature
got in the way.
All those hokey flowers
and painted bright orange.
It did feel like
she was being stifled
by the vines
instead of experiencing
- some sort of unity with them.
- Yeah.
Okay, let's move on to Niko.
What we saw was not good.
The paint job on Niko's
hard surfaces was awful.
It wasn't just the sculpture.
It was sloppily applied.
I could still see
brush streaks in it.
Okay, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- We have.
- Let's bring them back out.
So, Glenn, tell us
about the top looks.
Corinne, this was
a really beautiful makeup,
and we felt that it was
a perfect interpretation
of your wand.
George, you displayed
some spectacular
sculpting techniques
and meticulous paint job
which when combined, resulted
in a stunning wizard.
Tyler, you managed to create
a very graceful flow
from one part
of your character to another.
It resulted
in a very potent character.
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner of tonight's
challenge is...
All right, Glenn, who is
the winner of this challenge?
The winner of tonight's
challenge is...
George.
Thank you.
Oh, man, finally.
Your character transcends
the challenge,
and it had us in awe.
- Very, very fine work.
- Thank you, guys.
Finally, I got one.
I've always been
in top looks and never winning.
It was like, "Man, come on,
when is it gonna happen?"
- So I'm very grateful.
- George, congratulations.
You, Tyler, and Corinne
can head back
to the makeup room.
Unfortunately,
that means the rest of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Would you please step forward?
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Chloe, your struggle
to find inspiration
in your wand was quite evident
in your final makeup.
Cat, we had major issues
with your conceptual choices.
She looked more forced priestess
than she did wizard.
Niko, your metallic design
called
for sculptural perfection,
and clearly, you did not get
there this week.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Cat.
It was a very tough choice
for us tonight,
but we had a disconnect
with the arts-and-craft nature
of your character.
That means, Chloe and Niko,
you are safe this week
and can head
back to the makeup room.
Hey, Cat, we have no doubt
that you're gonna make
a fantastic makeup artist.
Focus on your designs
a little bit more.
Okay.
Cat, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
It's been great having you
here with us.
And if you would please
head back to the makeup room
- and pack up your kit.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Cat.
- Good luck, Cat.
I'm really sad to be leaving,
but I'm happy it's me
and not Niko.
It's Cat.
Aw.
It's okay.
Just kick ass.
There's a reason you're here.
- I love you.
- I want you to stay.
I want you to do really,
really well, okay?
I will.
This experience
has made me more excited
to get back out there
and keep doing what I love.
I'm just proud I made it
this far.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Cat just left.
We all feel sad and tired.
I just want to go home
and rest.
Hey, guys.
Oh, shit.
I really don't want to see
you right now.
You don't want to see me?
Why?
Here we go--
This is another challenge,
or there's gonna be
another person eliminated.
That's just too much for me
to handle today.
I do have something
really important to tell you.
Do you remember
in the beginning of the season
I said that it would be bold
and extreme
and full of surprises?
- Yeah.
- Uh-oh.
I'm taking you all to Japan.
- It's not a joke?
- It's not a joke.
- No, I'm serious.
- We're going to Japan?
What?
Are you kidding me?
Japan?
You guys better get some sleep
because it is a long flight
from here to Tokyo.
And we are leaving first thing
in the morning.
I will see you guys there.
Japan?
It's the other side
of the world.
It don't get any more bold
and extreme than that.
Now do you hate that I came in?
I'm sorry!
It's okay.
I still love you.
Konichiwa!
- Let's go!
- Hey, let's go to Japan.
Let's go!
www.tvsubtitles.net