- Whoa.
- Oh, boy.
The other contestants
are so strong.
This is it.
No more holdin' back.
I can give it a fight.
Bring the pain.
Welcome to theFace Off
season finale.
After a globe-spanning season
that was bolder
and more extreme
than ever before,
just three artists remain.
Tyler, the amount of reference
that is in your head,
that is something that other
people can't catch up with.
I really want to push
myself to freaking get that win.
Rashaad,
you are an amazing painter.
You've done some
beautiful work.
My dream is to make
monsters and creatures
for the rest of my life.
Winning Face Off will put me
that much closer to my dream.
George, your ability
to sculpt is fantastic.
I want to win it.
My newborn girl that's coming,
this is for her.
But their epic quest
for makeup immortality...
Frustrating.
...will push them
to the edge.
Oh, my God.
What the fuck?
That didn't dry at all.
I could just kiss
the grand prize good-bye.
I'm under pressure here.
I mean, it's tough.
Tyler, we can't mold this.
This is the finale,
and I feel like I'm blowing it.
And it all culminates in an
electrifying final performance.
Yeah!
In the end,
only one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Makeup to one
of their
85 international locations,
a brand-new 2014 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next
great name in movie magic?
Face Off!
Welcome toFace Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Being in the finale
means everything to me.
I'm very proud how I
fought tooth and nail
to get here, and now I'm ready.
I'm ready to show some
more of what I've got.
Rashaad!
- Daddy!
- Hi, baby.
On the computer
is my girlfriend and my son.
It's just a rush, you know,
just to hear their voice.
Aaron, you being good?
N--
My girlfriend,
she looks amazing.
You're staying focused, right?
- Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
- Good.
I can't wait to hold her again.
- Valeria!
- Baby!
My beautiful, lovely wife,
Valeria is right there.
Don't make me cry.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
I won't cry either.
Don't worry.
You don't know how much
you miss someone
until you're such a long time
apart from them.
I've been thinking
about you all the time.
Okay, now don't cry.
No crying.
Okay. No crying.
I'm part of the final three!
- Are you kidding me?
- Yeah!
- No.
- Oh, my God!
That's awesome!
It's a warm, welcoming feeling
to see my parents.
Everything is good.
Hurry up and win.
Yes.
Let me see your belly.
Wow!
Seeing them today is a boost
because it puts back
into the forefront why I'm here
and why I'm doing
what I'm doing.
Can I see the belly?
- Sure.
- Holy shit!
- Oh, my--
- Very low.
Baby is right there, man.
That belly is so cool.
I'm like,
"Baby, you hold there, okay?
Papa's coming soon."
This whole competition
has made me believe more
in myself and really push
the limits,
and I'm just very proud
to be your son, so--
Good answer.
My parents, no matter what,
are gonna be so proud of me.
All right.
Well, I'll see you guys soon.
- Okay.
- Okay. Love you.
All right.
Love you too.
- Mwah, mwah, mwah.
- Mwah.
I just can't wait to see
what this finale's gonna bring.
That was awesome.
That was great, dude,
like, made my day, man.
- Definitely did.
- Here we go.
Whoa.
What do we got?
Oh, my God.
We get to the lab
and there's, like,
stars and lasers,
and we're like, "Whoa."
I can't wait to see what
the challenge is gonna be about.
Congratulations
and welcome to the finale.
- Ohh.
- Thank you.
As promised, this has been
the season of extremes,
and this challenge
is no exception.
High-profile SyFy franchises
like Star Trek,
Babylon 5, and Defiance
have introduced audiences
to entirely new races
of aliens.
So with that in mind,
your final spotlight challenge
is to create
two rival alien races.
- Ohh!
- Oh, my God.
This is awesome.
I am getting so pumped right now
because I love space
and aliens,
but there's always that twist,
so I wonder what's comin'.
You'll each select one
of these constellations
to inspire your makeups.
We have Ursa Major,
The Great Bear,
Leo, The Lion,
Pegasus, The Winged-Horse,
and Cetus, The Whale.
Tyler, you're up first.
George.
And Rashaad.
All right, we have a lot of work
ahead of you
and there is a lot
at stake here.
So I brought some talented
artists to help you out.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Yes!
Awesome!
- Welcome back, guys.
- Thank you.
You will each get to choose two
of your former competitors
to join your team.
George, you get first pick.
I love you all, guys.
Corinne.
- Rashaad.
- Daran.
You got it, man.
- Tyler.
- Graham.
Yeah!
- Nico.
- What's goin' on?
Cat.
Chloe.
Okay, before you get started,
there is one thing
that I haven't told you yet.
Your final creations
must withstand
a mind-blowing dance
performance,
complete with a live audience
three days from now
at an underground nightclub
with a special guest artist,
who happens to be here today.
He has collaborated with
everyone from Adele to MIA.
Please welcome music producer,
DJ Extraordinary, Rusko.
- How are you?
- Awesome. Really cool.
- Hey, guys.
- I am super excited.
I love his music.
This is gonna be very amazing.
Thank you
so much for being here.
I can't tell you how excited
I am for this.
All right, now, Rusko
has one more piece
of information
about your challenge.
A huge part of my dance music
is an awesome laser light show,
so what I want you guys
to do is
incorporate lights into
your designs and your makeup.
Oh, boy.
This is gonna be a challenge.
On top of two aliens,
they have to be lit up.
- That's crazy.
- All right, guys.
Our friends at Kryolan
will be supplying you
with a revolutionary new product
called Aquacolor Plus.
Unlike other water-based paints,
these colors don't bleed
into one another.
- Oh, hey.
- That'll be nice.
All right, I'll be by later on
with my dad
to check in on your progress.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
We got six hours
to start getting together
a concept and start creating
our two rival alien races.
Okay. Constellation.
Here we go.
Let's see the description.
What would be two opposing,
like, aquatic creatures?
I got the Cetus constellation,
which is also known as
The Whale.
It's all aquatic,
so I'm thinking for the female,
she's gonna have
a jellyfish feel to her,
and then for him
he's gonna be more crustaceous,
which will give him
a more powerful look.
Nico, you get this flower goin'
for the chest of the girl.
Okay.
These two races of aliens,
we have a gentle race
and the aggressive race.
Leo represents the lion,
and my concept is the battle
between brightness and darkness.
They're evil.
I want to do that--
the spike dread things
with the lights.
The female is more elegant,
and the male alien
is gonna be a dark character,
very demonic looking.
- You want to do...
- The lioness.
Like, lion noses
on each of 'em essentially?
Not lion noses.
Kind of like an--
Okay, maybe an alien version
of that.
Yeah, I got a really
good team here.
I mean, I have Graham
who can mold to perfection,
and Chloe is excellent
at beauty makeup.
They're both very,
very strong artists.
One of the things
that stands out for me
about Ursa Major is that it's
one of the brightest
infrared galaxies.
I want our female alien
to have bioluminescence,
so the male hunts
the females to kill them
and take their light and use it
so that they can actually see.
They're gonna have
different color schemes
because I really want these alien rivals
to have a night and day feel to them.
Rounded over
or pointed kind of?
You can round it.
- Okay.
- Nice.
So, Daran is working on
these silicone pieces
that are gonna go
on our female character.
Cat breaks off to work on
the female face,
and I do the male face.
You know,
I want to sculpt the faces.
It's the first thing
the judges are gonna see.
Corinne is working on
the female cowl.
Something more flowy
to the back.
Okay.
And Nico is gonna block out
the female chest,
which is gonna be like
a sea flower of light
that's gonna glow
out of silicone,
so it looks like the power
of the red star
of the constellation
is emanating
from her from within.
Nice, Nicolai.
Hey, guys.
Here for walkthrough.
- Hey!
- Hey.
Let's see what you have.
The female is gonna
be the gentle race
and the male race
is going to be evil,
so we're really thinking
he would have
these really cool dreads
that have
the lights coming down.
These are what is interesting
because this can be
an alien-type of a mane.
Is there anything else
you're putting in here
that speaks of lion?
Even on a nose to give a little
of the feline look to it.
So, kind of maybe bulk out
a little bit of the tops?
I would maybe get a little bit
of a muzzle into it.
Okay.
We got Cetus constellation.
- The Whale.
- Yeah, The Whale.
It has that aquatic quality
to it, so--
Is she supposed to be pretty?
Uh--
If you want to definitely know
it's a female,
be able to see her human lips
as opposed to covering them up
and, you know, makin' it
fish-like
or something like that.
Something to think about.
Beautiful.
I want to make the female
more light heavy,
keeping her very smooth,
everything round,
and then with the male
it's gonna be pointed
and everything jagged,
almost skeletal.
Now, remember though,
in your paint jobs,
that this has to show
from 10, 20 feet away,
'cause you've done
a lot of detail,
and I'd hate to see you
lose it.
You don't want to lose that.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
All right, everybody.
We're heading out.
Can't wait to see your finale.
Good luck to everybody.
There's a lot of creativity
goin' on.
Keep it goin'.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
Bye!
Tyler,
we can't mold these faces.
I'm in the middle of sculpting,
and I'm running out of time
at this point.
This whole competition,
I've always got my face piece
ready to go for foam
on the first day,
but not this challenge.
Yeah, we're gonna have
to figure out the light strips.
Yeah, that's, like,
the least of my worries though.
I have to worry about
the performance, the lights,
and two
completely different faces.
I am scared and nervous as hell
because this is the finale,
and I feel like I'm blowing it.
Coming up...
That didn't dry at all.
I could just kiss
the grand prize good-bye.
Oh, my God.
What the fuck?
We got a gigantic rip.
The winner of Face Off is--
- We're gonna have to figure
out the light strips.
Yeah, that's, like,
the least of my worries though.
It's day one
of our rival alien challenge,
and I just feel so behind.
I'm realizing that I'm not gonna
have anything molded
by the end of the day.
We still have
a lot of work to do.
It's driving me crazy,
but this is the finale.
This is not the time to rush
'cause the details count.
Concentrate on
getting 'em perfect.
That's time, guys.
By the end of the day,
we've got our faces detailed.
They just need some last minute
touch-up work.
I know tomorrow's gonna be busy,
but I'm here to win Face Off
and that's what I'm gonna do.
Let's do this, guys.
It's day two
of the rival alien challenge,
and I've got a lot to do.
The main goal is to finish
everything for the female alien
and tomorrow get everything done
with the male.
You could do some kind of
a patterny type thing
that goes down the center.
Exactly.
So we have somewhere to pop...
- The little bulbs.
- Silicon, yeah.
And we got to put lights
everywhere in the makeups
and probably battery packs
and all kinds of cables,
and it's gonna make things
a little bit more complex.
First thing I do is
jump into Corinne's cowl
and start detailing it.
After I get that,
I jump into Nico's chest
and start the
finishing touches.
All set?
I'm taking
Mr. Westmore's advice,
and I'm gonna incorporate
the lion aspect
of the constellation
into my sculpture,
and Chloe is focusing
on the female cowl
while Graham
is molding the first face.
It's like this assembly line
kind of thing,
and it's really great to know
that I don't have to worry
about molding because Graham
is the mold master.
Seeing 'em next
to each other looks so cool.
I start working on the faces
while cat is blocking out
the cowl,
and Daran's sculpting the
chest plate for the female.
I want to get both of the faces
run in foam latex
by the end of the day.
They're looking good.
We want to incorporate
some vacuform sections
into our different sculpts,
because I want to give
the illusion of layers.
That's pretty good.
The sculpt that Chloe's
working on,
we cut a section from the back
of the head to give the sense
that this thing
has a functioning brain.
The male chest will have
this illuminated
vacuform plate,
which is gonna hold the lights,
and then a ribcage go over it
so when the layers are lit up,
the effect in the chest
will be intensified.
I'm afraid.
She's already got that goin' on.
- Oh, that shape?
- Yeah.
Even though both of my aliens
come from
the constellation Ursa Major,
I really want these two
to be different
because they have to be rivals.
A female has a raised point
in the back of her head,
but I don't want to do that
with the male's cowl,
so I hack off a big section
of it
and go a different direction.
You can make it like
a hard crab shell cap.
You know, like the bottom
of a turtle?
- Yeah, there you go.
- I get what you're sayin'.
38 minutes.
All right, guys!
It's time!
- All right.
-  Excelente.
By the end of day two,
we got most of our molds done
for the female.
We can't run 'em in foam yet
because we're running some
of these parts in silicone
to make that
bioluminescence quality
to them.
We got a lot to do yet.
The pressure is on.
It wears on you, you know?
It really gets into your head.
- See what we got.
- Yeah!
It's day three of our
rival alien challenge,
and we have 9 1/2 hours
in the lab.
What do you think?
That looks lovely.
Oh, fuck.
The female alien face ripped
right here.
This is not good.
It's the last day to sculpt,
and we still have to finish
everything for the male,
so there's no time
to try to patch this thing.
I got to run it again.
All right.
Let's get goin'.
It's just roughed out,
you know?
That looks awesome.
Chloe and I are touching up
all the final details
in all the sculpts
and Graham is getting
everything molded today.
This is the last challenge,
and everything's startin'
to come together,
and I have a shot.
I want to win this thing.
- We got 2:20 on the clock.
- All right.
Cat's molding the cowl
and she's being very detailed
in the way she does it because
it's one of our key pieces.
This thing
has a difficult wall.
I'm a little worried
because this thing has to cure
before we can even pop it
and get it run in foam.
All right.
After I finish the cowl
I move on
to the male chest piece
and back piece,
which are very important because
they have lighting emanating
from the chest, both of them.
That's what connects them
from the same planet.
I'm sculpting them as fast
as I can, but I'm on the clock.
I'm under pressure here.
I mean, it's tough.
_
We don't want to rush
the mold drying process,
but it's gettin' down to,
like, the last ten minutes.
Let's do it, son.
We let it sit
as long as possible.
Now we've got to try
and open this thing,
and get it out in foam.
Oh, my God.
Look.
What the fuck?
_
Our mold didn't set.
This is definitely not
a good position to be in.
I have no idea what to do.
This key piece
I need for the big finale makeup
might not be there.
What are we doin'?
I could just kiss
the grand prize good-bye.
Where we at?
It's day three of our
rival alien challenge,
and we're running out of time.
Oh, my God.
Look.
_
This is not a good thing.
You don't want to open
a wet mold
because then you ruin
your detail layer,
and that's the most important
layer of the molding process.
- All right.
- I say we leave it alone.
- Sweet.
- And just let it sit?
Yeah, 'cause if in the morning
it's dry,
then at least we can polyfoam.
_
That's time, guys!
All right.
Frustrating.
I really want this cowl
to be foam latex
rather than running
it in polyfoam,
especially with a dance.
Once polyfoam dries,
it doesn't allow
the same flexibility.
All we can do is keep
our fingers crossed
and just hope for the best.
- Wardrobe?
- Yup.
All right.
Polyfoam, polyfoam.
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab,
one hour at last looks.
Either it works or it don't.
Our biggest concern of all
of this is having the cowl.
- We got one beautiful side.
- Yes, sir.
And one horrendous side.
We had our fingers crossed
it would be perfect,
and it's not.
This alien got burned.
That sets us apart.
Now I have to clean it out,
get it prepped for polyfoam,
and it'll be ready to go.
Get to work.
Oh, my God.
What the fuck?
Holy shit.
That one is bad.
We got a gigantic rip on
the face of the male character.
It's like, "Oh, my God.
Another rip."
Yeah, we'll have to,
like, glue it.
This is not good.
I just Crazy Glue it
and then cover patch it.
I do want to take my time
to make it beautiful.
I mean, it's the finale.
While I'm patching it up,
Corinne is cutting out
the silicone pieces
and glue them down.
Nico's gonna work on the props.
We're trying to go
as fast as we can.
- Hello.
- Christian.
Christian, how are you?
I'm Tyler.
Nice to meet you.
Our models arrive
and Chloe and I
start applying everything.
Wow, that already looks
really cool.
Without them even painted
they look amazing.
I'm just so excited.
Yeah, that's gonna be cool.
It starts with here.
Oh, I see beauty.
We start opening the mold,
and it takes us a while,
but we get it out.
She's beat up
but she's useable.
We'll have to make it a scar,
make it a burn
from battle damage,
but we got our cowl.
It's all damage.
Life gives you lemons,
you make lemonade.
Yeah, boy!
Every edge is smooth, Nico?
Most of it.
Patching the face took me
a little while,
and it threw me
a little bit behind.
Just seam this
so it looks pristine.
Now we got to hurry up
and finish applying everything,
but I'm running out of time.
Oh, boy.
I start prepainting everything
and it looks so cool.
Chloe's startin' on
the base coat
and him in the red, it's like,
"Wow, there's such a crazy
contrast."
These things are really
gonna hold up
and really look well on stage.
No, Rashaad.
That's too slow.
Do it.
We still got to glue lights in.
We're just rushing to get
everything applied and painted.
We're really under the gun here,
and I don't want
to do everything in last looks.
Let's do it.
That's ten minutes, everyone!
All right, everyone!
That's time!
Brushes down.
Time is up
and we got everything applied,
but we don't have no paint
on it yet.
My God, we got so much to do.
It's like, "Oh, my God."
Nerve-racking.
All this is very stressful.
- All right!
- For the last time.
Yeah.
All right, everybody.
Feel privileged.
Greg's on the other side
doin' makeup.
Going into last looks,
not only do we get to work
on our characters
but the backup dancers are also
in the room with us,
and who's in charge of that?
Greg Cannom.
This guy's resume
goes way back.
I mean, from Dracula
to Mrs. Doubtfire.
I mean, whoa.
_
There's so much to do
in an hour.
We have to finish painting.
I have to make sure the side
of my female's face
looks like a burn,
make sure that our LED lights
are working
and a million other details,
but I'm not worried because
I have a great team
and we're gonna get it done.
I'm not happy
with the paint job.
I think it's too muddy.
I'm also concerned about
my aliens lookin' too similar,
but I'm running out of time,
so I just want to get it done.
I'm using Kryolan's
Aquacolor Plus.
It doesn't bleed
into other colors.
It's so cool,
and everything's going smoothly.
Chloe's doing gorgeous
beauty makeup
on the female's eyes to really
make her pearl essence pop.
We got 15 minutes left, guys.
15 minutes!
I think we should turn on
the lights
'cause we don't want
to forget that.
Get it goin', guy.
Get it goin'.
Want to punch it up
or turn it down?
All right, guys!
That's it! It's time!
I have two complete characters,
and I think they look amazing.
Everybody's work is great,
so you'd never know,
but I'm thinkin' maybe
I got a shot.
Coming up...
Welcome to
the Face Off season finale.
This over here
looks like damage.
This is it.
This is everything
I've worked for.
All right, Glenn.
Who is the winner of Face Off?
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome
McKenzie Westmore.
Welcome to
theFace Offseason finale.
Tonight, our artist's creations
will be taking part in
an incredible dance performance
featuring one
of the world's top DJs, Rusko.
For their final
spotlight challenge,
I asked each
of our finalists to create
two rival alien races
inspired by a constellation,
and because our theme tonight
is all about light,
they were also required
to incorporate
lighted elements
into their designs.
With that,
I'd like to introduce you
to our incredibly talented
and accomplished judges.
First, we have owner of
Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio,
Glenn Hetrick.
Three time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
Creature and concept designer,
Neville Page.
All right, it's time to see
our finalists'
phenomenal creations.
Our first pair of makeups
is from Tyler,
and they were inspired
by the constellation Leo.
Let's take a look.
Let's go Tyler.
I'm not nervous.
This is like a celebration.
I am so proud of myself
and my team.
I believe these
are the coolest characters
I've done in this competition.
I'm feelin' pretty good
because we pulled something
together that most people would
have thought impossible.
Everybody was worried about us,
but they look amazing.
I'm proud of my team.
I'm proud
of what we accomplished.
I'm loving the way they look.
Okay, guys.
We are just getting started.
Now it's time to put
these aliens to the test.
Performing his hit Lift Me Up,
give it up for
internationally acclaimed
music producer and DJ, Rusko.
♪ 'cause everybody needs love ♪
♪ they never seem
to get enough ♪
♪ to show you
what it's made of ♪
♪ just need you to lift me up ♪
♪ 'cause everybody
needs love, needs love ♪
♪ needs love, needs love,
needs love ♪
♪ 'cause everybody
needs love, needs love ♪
♪ needs love, needs love,
♪ needs love, needs love ♪
♪ 'cause everybody
needs love, needs love ♪
♪ needs love, needs love,
needs love ♪
♪ Needs love, needs love,
needs love, needs love ♪
♪ 'cause everybody
♪ needs love, needs love ♪
♪ needs love, needs love,
needs love ♪
♪ 'cause everybody
needs love, needs love ♪
♪ needs love, needs love,
needs love ♪
♪ needs love, needs love ♪
♪ 'cause everybody
needs love, needs love ♪
♪ needs love, needs love,
♪ needs love, needs love ♪
Oh, my God!
Give it up one more time
for Rusko!
Give it up for the dancers.
Hello?
All right, guys.
Thank you so much
for being with us tonight.
Now it is time for our judges
to take a closer look
at the makeups
and deliberate in private.
Thank you for joining us.
Such a complicated sculpt.
What's interesting
is his lighting
is extraordinarily subtle.
Can you turn around
for us, please?
He's got the lights in here
as well.
That's a lot to integrate.
It feels very crustacean.
It makes sense.
This is really different.
I like it.
Odd decision
when you have the chance
to create two separate things,
to make them so similar.
You know what?
I think the thing that makes 'em
similar is the paint job.
Wow!
This over here
looks like damage.
I'm ready to pass out
because this is everything
that I've worked for.
There's a lot of
emergency repair happening here.
That side of the face
came out bad,
and I know that the judges
are gonna notice it too.
Who made your favorite
alien rivals?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
This over here
looks like damage.
I know that that side
of the face came out bad,
but I want them to notice
that there's
a complete character.
I love how this flows
into this stuff
so that we can see
the light through.
It's very celestial feeling.
Thank you.
That is so beautiful.
Can you turn to the side?
I do love the colors.
Love the palette.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
That's gorgeous.
Thanks.
Bare your teeth
as much as you--
- Oh, that's wild.
- Yeah, it is.
I dig that,
and now open
with it real wide like that.
Yeah.
That's super cool.
- Amazing teeth.
- Yeah.
Wow!
Beautiful paint job.
- Wow!
- Look at that.
- That's beautiful.
- That's a chest.
I've never seen
anything like that.
That form on the chest?
- That is gorgeous.
- Gorgeous.
Thank you.
All right, judges.
How did they do tonight?
I was thoroughly impressed.
Everyone did
a massive amount of work
and all of it is so detailed.
I couldn't have asked for more.
Thank you.
All right,
the judges would like to speak
with each of you to learn more
about your work.
Tyler, you're up first.
Tyler,
tell us about your aliens
and how your constellation
inspired your work.
My constellation was Leo.
My female alien represents
peace and elegance
and their essence
is their bright light,
and my rival
wants nothing but darkness.
There are some
incredibly well done things
on these makeups, Tyler.
Thank you.
I do like
the multitudinous layering
of the plates
on your male character.
It feels
like functional organic armor.
Good.
I think you've done
two really beautiful,
cohesive makeups.
I especially like your female.
I love those subtle colors,
the blues and the lavenders.
Your male has some really
interesting things going on.
Can you turn him around for us?
I just love the transition
into the paler colors
so that you can really see
that skeletal treatment.
Very well done.
Thank you very much.
Really great stuff.
On your female,
that plainer nose
and havin' the nostrils
on the side
was a really nice way
of treating it,
and as for your guy,
I love the depth
you've achieved in his chest.
It looks like this guy
is hollow.
- Yeah.
- Congratulations.
Thank you very much, guys.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Rashaad, you're next.
Rashaad, tell us about
your rival aliens
and how your constellation
inspired your creations.
Well, the constellation
that I got was Ursa Major.
She's a hunter on her planet,
but his race
has no problem hunting them
because they shine so much,
so they're easy to find
and they kill them
and take their light.
I got to tell you,
I think you did
an excellent job.
I really love the coloration
on your male.
It's so striking.
I noticed that your female
has what appears
to be some sort of a burn
on the side of her head.
Very much a happy accident
with the molding process.
Since they're supposed
to be fighting,
we thought a scar
would be great on her face.
I think it was very successful
because that's exactly
what it does look like.
Really cool characters, honey.
Thank you.
The palette is beautiful,
and the two of them
have a great contrast
in warm and cool.
The bioluminescent
sternocleidomastoid feature
is so beautiful.
When she came out
and the lights were out,
it was one of the most powerful
uses of light on a character.
It's a gorgeous sculpt.
That's what we're lookin' for.
Great stuff.
Thank you.
Your female character
is so celestial.
My first impression was,
"How could they possibly
have worked the lighting out that well?"
It looks like you'd had weeks to think
about just the lighting.
With your male character,
I could see
all of the inspirational notes
that you're taking from nature
to create rival alien species.
I couldn't be more pleased
with the beautiful work
that everyone did on your team.
Thank you.
George, you're next.
Tell us about your alien rivals
and the constellation
inspiration.
I choose the constellation
of Cetus.
The red emanating
from each of their chests
is the last source of power
that arise from the red star,
the dying star.
It's some
of the most gorgeous work
that I've seen you do
in particular.
Thanks.
The male character,
his head and his shoulders,
it's a gorgeous bit
of sculptural work right there.
Congratulations
to you and the team.
- Yeah.
- Did some beautiful work there.
It's some of the finest
sculptural work that we've seen.
The male character
is awe-inspiring.
That combination of forms
is something I've never seen,
and I'm particularly fond
of your female in profile.
However, in terms of the color,
I understand that
you were trying to unify
your characters,
but at the same time,
them being rivals
is wholly absent
in a visual manner.
You did a really remarkable
job of creating
two really beautiful characters,
and the sculpting
is really good.
Well done, George.
Thank you so much, Ve.
All right, guys.
The judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you'd please head backstage
while they decide
who will become
this season's champion.
Thank you.
All right, judges, let's talk
about our finalists tonight.
Let's start with Tyler.
I did love the female.
Really beautiful paint job.
Those subtle, beautiful,
luminescent quality
that he put on it
with that pale lavender.
Not so much the red guy.
It had, like,
a weird sea anemone nose on it.
But the skeletal forms
that he's chosen to do,
they were handled so well
around the eyes
and in the detail that makes it
a good-looking piece.
He did a really great
treatment of that chest.
It really did look like there
was almost nothing behind there.
He has been such
a strong competitor all season.
His dragon
was incredibly strong.
He pulled off
incredible rendition
of the mouth belly gag.
Tyler is visionary.
He's got such cool designs,
and he has the skills
to execute them.
All right,
let's move on to Rashaad.
He had the constellation
Ursa Major.
Well,
I loved the color choices,
especially on that
aqua and purpley-blue guy,
and the female
had the strongest light element.
Wow!
It was stunning.
The sculpting work that he did
on his male character
was just gorgeous.
The precision and the craft
within it was incredible.
Looking at how successful
the integration
of the light is on the female,
he couldn't have done that
any better.
And as the season
has progressed,
he has just gotten better
and better and better.
Out of 14 challenges,
he was only on the bottom once.
I mean, that's pretty amazing.
I mean, he was either on the top
or safe every other time.
All right,
let's finish up with George.
He had the constellation cetus.
That sculpt was so good
on the male.
He's such a strong designer,
such a strong sculptor,
and I love the female head.
I love the female head
in profile.
I definitely love it
from the back.
What did you think
about the lighting?
It was obvious that
that brown paint had obscured
the light source unfortunately.
It didn't so much on the female
because she had that big crest
going on.
One thing that George
has shown consistently
throughout the entire season
is his sculpting prowess.
He knows form in ways
that I don't think
most makeup artists do.
That's a pretty amazing gift
to have.
All right, judges,
have you made your decision?
- Yes, we have.
- Yup.
All right,
let's bring 'em back out.
Okay, one of you is about to be
crowned the winner of Face Off.
Glenn, tell us about
tonight's makeups.
Tyler, your characters
were incredibly successful
in embracing
the lighted elements,
and we particularly loved
the beautiful iridescent
paint job of your female alien.
Rashaad, we thought you had
some really exciting
conceptual ideas,
and the lighting design
on your female alien
made her feel almost angelic.
George, using a dying star
as the source of power
in the crux of your character's
relationship was very clever,
and the sculpting
on your male's head
is some of the best
we've ever seen.
All right, Glenn,
who is the winner ofFace Off?
The winner of Face Off is--
- All right, Glenn,
who is the winner of Face Off?
The winner ofFace Offis...
Rashaad.
Congratulations!
This is gonna change my life.
In the beginning
I was always questioning,
"Do I have what it takes?
Am I good enough for this?"
I guess I am.
Here are the keys...
- Awesome.
- ...to your new car.
Rashaad freakin' deserved it,
man.
- He's such an amazing artist.
- Take a breath.
- Ohh.
- Are you all right?
- Oh, yeah.
- Brother.
I got to be in the finale
with two amazing guys,
and I got to showcase
all my work
in front of millions of people.
How cool is that?
I don't feel like a loser.
I was in the finale
for crying out loud.
That's a winner in its own.
I've learned to push myself,
take advice,
and just branch from there.
WinningFace Off changes a life.
I was working 24/7
wanting to do more for my family.
Not to mention my dream
of coming out here
and starting a studio
and being a makeup artist.
I feel like this is a dream,
and one day
I'm just gonna wake up,
and it's not gonna be here,
but, it's happened.
It's really happened.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net