- Previously on
"AllStars... "
It's time for the returning
queens to get their revenge.
The top two returning queens
will lip sync
for the power
to give one of
the bottom queens the chop
and get the right to return
to the competition.
- We're in the company of
some amazing queens tonight.
- Where?
(all laugh)
- The rosebuds
were in full bloom.
- The assholes were out,
literally.
(all laugh)
- Roxxxy Andrews.
- I thought your entrance
was strong,
and then it was like someone
took the needle off the record.
- With the--with the--
with the glory hole, right?
- Phi Phi O'Hara.
- You had some
funny jokes in there,
but for me, it turned into,
like, a scene study.
- Hmm, okay.
- Tatianna,
you're a winner, baby.
And Alyssa Edwards,
you are also a winner.
- Yeah!
- We're gonna do it.
- Alyssa, which queen have you
chosen to get the chop?
- Tonight, I chose
Phi Phi O'Hara to go home.
- Tatianna.
- Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Phi Phi O'Hara,
sashay away.
- Congratulations,
we made it out!
- We're here, girl.
Not one, but two of us now
are officially back
in the competition.
Phi Phi went home.
It was a unanimous vote.
- "I wanted to avoid hugs
because of tears."
- Huh.
I was taken back
a little bit.
- That's okay. Bye.
- Do I believe Phi Phi's
explanation
for not hugging Alyssa?
No.
- I was just freaking out
that both of them were going
to be going home tonight.
Obviously, I'm very excited
that Roxxxy's still here,
but it sucks
to see Phi Phi leave.
But if she had to go
in order for my girl to stay,
I'm happy with that.
- Six again.
- I know.
What the fuck?
We go from a top five
to a top six.
That kind of sucks.
- At this point
in the competition,
stakes are so high and
everybody's on their A game.
We all want to win.
I can't wait to see
how this turns out.
- The winner of "RuPaul's
Drag Race AllStars"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
a coveted spot in
the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize
of $100,000.
With extra special guest judge,
Graham Norton.
-  "RuPaul's Drag Race"
May the best woman
Best woman win
- I don't jump guns.
I am the boom-boom gun.
- Here, let me
put this gig back up.
- New morning
in the workroom,
and one bitch down,
two bitches back.
I just want everyone to go home
so I can win already.
- Are you refreshed?
- I was concise, I was
consistent, I was confused.
- Mm-hmm.
- About all this conflomba.
(all laugh)
- We going down to the worm
with the bottle, girl.
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Hello!
- Hi.
- Ladies, I want to share
with you
the secret to my success.
All the big business deals
are made on the golf course.
- Oh!
- So I've invited
designer Andrew Christian
and these sexy beasts
to help us play
a few rounds of...
butt-butt golf.
(all laugh)
Ladies, take a moment
to get into a quick golf drag
and meet us
on the back nine.
Go!
- Where's my plaid at, girl?
- Choices.
- Oh, I feel so hot.
- All right, ladies,
it's tee time.
Why, look,
it's Dinah Shore weekend
at "RuPaul's Drag Race."
First, you swing your thing
to hit the ball through
the legs of these manimals.
And the AllStar
that can sink the ball
into the big pink hole
in the fastest time wins.
First up, Roxxxy Andrews.
Go! Keep your eye
on the ball
and not
their Andrew Christians.
- These balls are so saggy.
- You should be used to it,
girl.
- You're gonna have to
back up into that, girl.
- Ooh.
- Oh!
- All these hot mens can't
disturb me today, honey.
I need to get the ball
in the hole.
- Oh, yeah.
A hole-in-one hour.
Detox.
- Uh-oh. Oh.
- She's doing
the side maneuver.
Her technique
is very unusual.
- Move.
- Oh!
(all laugh)
- Okay, Detox, time is up.
I'm afraid we're gonna have
to pull the butt-butt plug
on this one.
(all laugh)
Tatianna,
look at the thrust.
Now, that
is how you play this game.
- Oh, wow!
- Hole-in-one.
- That's a hole-in-one.
- She's getting
the swing of it.
- Yes.
Alyssa Edwards.
- I'm taking my time.
I'm getting good technique.
- Girl! (laughs)
I think Alyssa
know what she doing.
She may not have
the fastest time,
but she's clearly winning
this game.
Katya. It's tense
on the green right now.
She's between a rock
and a hard place.
A really hard place.
- Oh!
(cheering)
- Yes!
Alaska.
Oh, yeah.
Wow, she is aggressive
in her approach.
Looks like she's going
for the full--yes!
Yeah, get it in there, girl.
She's in
the home stretch now.
All right!
- (growls)
- All right, ladies.
The winner is...
- Alaska.
- Yay!
- You've won
a $2,000 prize package
from Klein, Epstein
& Parker.
Suits made to measure, like
the suits I'm always wearing.
- Wow.
- And we're posting more
butt-butt golf video
at LogoTV.com.
Ladies, now that you've
played with the big boys,
it's time to show me
that you mean business.
For this week's
maxi challenge,
you need to create
merchandise
worthy of your unique
AllStar brand,
and then shoot a commercial
that really sells the goods.
And the top two
will get their merch
produced and sold at
the next RuPaul's Drag Con.
(applause)
- Think "Shark Tank,"
but fishier.
#RuPaulsFishTank.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
- Bye.
- Coming up...
- My product is going to be
the Roxxxy Andrews wig glue.
- Why does that glue
make it special?
- It's called Katya's
Crisis Control.
- The only crisis here
is the product.
(RuPaul laughs)
- For today's
maxi challenge,
we have to create
self-branded merchandise
and then shoot a commercial
to sell it.
- I want to make, like,
a trash-talking receptacle.
Anytime you, like,
throw trash away,
it, like, yells at you
and reams you.
- (laughs)
- What you doing, girl?
- I'm marketing executive
opulence fashion tape.
- Oh, that's fabulous.
What do you think
I got going on over here?
- It looks like you've got
Alyssa's go-go juice.
- (laughs)
- Is that what it is?
- It's a shot of G3,
the go-go-go.
- Ooh.
- When people think
of Alyssa Edwards,
they think of high energy.
It don't have to be
a Tuesday or a Saturday.
Full speed, full throttle,
full out.
- I mean,
I guess I'll try it.
My name is Alyssa Edwards,
and this is the true secret!
It's substantial shenanigans
and buffoonery and goonery.
A score!
- (laughs)
- Hey, ladies.
We've got company.
Say hello to Marcus Lemonis
from CNBC's "The Profit."
- Hello, ladies.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Hey, Roxxxy,
meet Marcus Lemonis.
- How are you? Marcus.
very nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- On this challenge,
where you are going
to market your product,
this is the man
you need to run it by
to figure out
if it's gonna work or not.
- So what's your product?
- My product is going to be
the Roxxxy Andrews wig glue.
- Why did you choose glue?
- I'm always known
for my hair flips.
- See, now, Marcus,
we wear lace-front wigs
where you have to glue
the side down.
- What would be different
from that glue
or any other glue
I could buy?
Why does that glue
make it special?
- I'm gonna have
to think about that.
- (laughs)
- You have to convince
everybody.
That glue is going to be
packaged differently,
and there's going to be
instructions connected to it.
- You've got a DVD
that's included,
and I'm going to show you
exactly how much
you can flip your hair
without it going anywhere.
- This is what
you're selling.
Your expertise, your knowledge
and the glue is just a bonus.
- Okay.
- Oh, my goodness.
You just got
a million dollar lesson.
- Yes, girl.
- I cannot wait to see
your presentation.
See you in a minute, Roxxxy.
- Thank you so much, guys.
- All right.
Hey, Katya.
- Hello, mother.
- We are excited to hear
what your product is.
- So it's called
Katya's Crisis Control,
and it's a refreshing
body mist,
and it also packs
the right amount of thorazine
to protect from anxiety,
fear, hallucinations or ghosts.
- So you're selling...
- I'm selling a feeling,
a sensation of, like, um...
- You know that's the first way
to kill a brand
is to sell something
that doesn't have value.
So I think you have a little bit
of branding identity crisis.
- Okay. Well, that's
very on-brand for me.
- I think, right now, the only
crisis here is the product.
I want to have something that
somebody actually wants to buy.
Just lose the bottle
and the whole idea.
Start over.
- Okay.
- I'm sorry.
- Thanks, Katya.
- Thank you.
Whoo!
(all laugh)
- Hey, Tatianna.
- Hey.
- What's the product?
- It's a tea set,
perfect for talking shit
or "spill tea," as we like
to say it in the biz.
- So you've got
this tea set.
How's the commercial
going to unfold?
- It's going to be
very much just me walking,
saying, hey, you like
talking shit?
You can now spill the tea
with me, Tati.
And then they'll be
cutaways of me,
like did you hear
what she did?
- I see.
- Girl.
- You basically hooked me in
by asking me if I wanted
to talk crap about somebody.
If anybody says they don't,
they're lying.
The commercial was maybe the
best presentation I've heard.
- Wow.
- Well, blam.
- Well, get back to work.
Can't wait to see it.
- Will do.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
- See you. Okay.
- All right, ladies,
gather round.
Now, in a few moments,
you'll shoot your commercials
with Michelle Visage
and Carson Kressley.
So good luck
and don't fuck it up.
- Thank you.
- Oh, my God,
what are you gonna do?
'Cause I just--I heard
that they were saying,
like, nope, start over.
- Yeah, I don't have time
to start over
and I like my idea,
so I'm just gonna do it.
- Katya's walkthrough
didn't really go that well,
and when somebody kind of shoots
the shit your entire idea,
that's a little
nerve-wracking.
- I'm not gonna panic
because I don't do that anymore.
It's gonna be okay.
- Coming up...
- Want to wake up
and just be cute?
- If you're selling an energy
drink, you gotta be energetic.
- Okay.
- And I might even show you some
of the best wig reveal secrets.
- (laughs)
(RuPaul laughs)
- Hi, Katya.
- So for today's
maxi challenge,
we have to pitch a product
that reflects our brand.
- You've got props,
you've got pit crew,
and you've got furniture
courtesy of our friends
at Riverworks.
- Is there a pig?
Oh, there's a turkey.
That's even better.
- (laughs)
- I'm gonna hold the turkey.
I'm in a kitchen.
- You look confused.
So you're in the kitchen.
- I'm in the kitchen.
- Okay.
And you're gonna be
standing there.
- Standing here
in the kitchen.
- What's your lines?
- Um, these days, being
a woman is really hard.
Keep going?
- Is there more?
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
That's the whole commercial.
- So Detox,
ready to try it?
- Mm-hmm.
I'm nervous going into
shooting my commercial
because I focused
a lot of my attention
on making my little
trash can come to life,
so I'm kind of winging
everything as I go.
- And action.
- (laughs) Sorry.
Detox's trash-talking
trash receptacle
has many catch phrases.
I've had it.
Officially.
This tastes like shit.
- This tastes like shit
is a catch phrase?
- It's gonna be new ones.
- (laughs)
- Oh. Smart.
- Alaska
Thunderfun Fashion Tape.
Anus-thing is possible.
(both laugh)
- Great.
- Great. Next?
How many more do you have,
Alaska?
- Um, there's 14.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
- You might want
to prioritize.
- Okay.
- I can't wait to see how
this feature film turns out.
Thank you, James Cameron.
Alyssa. And action.
- Why wake up
and just be cute
when you can spring up
and be drop dead gorgeous?
- What you just did wasn't
really full of energy.
- No.
- Okay.
- If you're selling an energy
drink, you got to be energetic.
- Okay.
- Oh, yes. Ooh, ooh.
Oh, the phone's ringing,
the phone's ringing.
Oh, someone's calling.
To the camera,
to the camera.
- Pick up your step.
Yeah, yes.
And kick and layout.
Yes! Whoo! Whoo!
- Come on, Debbie Allen.
- Right?
- (laughs)
All right, here we go.
And action.
- I'm going to show you
all of my wig tricks,
and I might even show you some
of the best wig reveal secrets.
- Cut.
Um, your wig line
is really back right now.
Oh--yeah, there you, girl.
- Schnappy.
- Action.
- Mmm...
- No?
- No.
You're selling
this wig reveal.
- This is the money shot.
- Of the whole video.
- And it's not working.
It's got to work.
Ms. Tatianna.
And action.
- She says her face
is on billboards,
but I hear it's actually
on wanted signs. (laughs)
- Cut. Yeah, Tatianna, you
should probably be bitchier
to stay with the character.
- Done and done.
- Action.
- She says her face
is on billboards,
but I hear it's actually
on wanted signs.
(laughs) Stupid bitch.
(both laugh)
- Brava.
- Is that everything
you wanted?
- I think so, yeah.
- All right.
- Okay, great job.
- Thank you.
- No, thank you.
- Another day.
- Doll, boo!
- The rooster
has done cockadoodle-doo,
woke us wide awake, 'cause
today's category is...
pants on the runway,
darlings.
Pants on the runway, pants on
the runway, pants on the runway!
Pants-- (all laugh)
I can't wait
to see how this turns out.
- Hmm.
- Detox, you have a really
specific, like, brand,
which I think is, like,
really important,
especially with, like,
a challenge like this.
- Yeah, completely.
You know, I let myself down
being here the first time around
just 'cause
of everything going on,
and I feel so much more
in tune to who I am.
It's been such a needed thing
for me to be here.
And you as well,
getting in tune
with who Alaska is.
I've been so proud of you.
- Being here
is, like, so important
and there's nowhere else
that I would be
rather than, like,
right here in this room.
- Right here, right now.
That's exactly
how I feel.
- Now doing this.
My biggest weakness Season 5
was my mind was scattered
all over the place.
Now I'm working really hard
on having a laser,
precise focus.
- You've, like, topped yourself,
like, times 10.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
- This will be
the most Relaskatox moment
they'll ever have
on this season,
and I love it 'cause it's
a beautiful, like, genuine--
- Oh, my girl.
- Relaskatox
is not in effect.
I know it may
come across that way.
We definitely love
and support each other,
but we're not here
to be a clique.
- I just got my foundation
all over you.
- So the thing I like about you
is that you are very quiet,
but you're also
really out there.
- I'm really, really selective
about who I spend my time with.
People who can call you
when you shit
if you're, like,
getting grand
or you're starting
to feel yourself,
I just get really fearful
of letting the quality
of my shit deteriorate.
And those, like,
right or die friends
are really good at holding
you accountable to that.
- I don't see how you could
deteriorate any further.
- I was gonna say it, bitch.
- (laughs)
- Sounds like
a drunk seagull.
- (laughs)
Oh, my God, you got--
you gutted, rotted,
paint-scraping fucking
IRS-cheating, Gila monster.
- (all laugh)
(RuPaul laughs)
-  Cover girl, put the bass
in your walk
Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk
Head to toe,
let your whole body talk
Cover girl
(applause)
- Welcome to the main stage of
"RuPaul's Drag Race AllStars."
A lady who's always up
in my business, Michelle Visage.
- Darling, I own 51%
of this company.
- Oh, really?
(all laugh)
Style superstar Carson Kressley,
you buying what I'm selling?
- If I can put it
on layaway.
- The new star of "Kinky Boots"
on Broadway,
the incredible Todrick Hall.
- Hello, Ru. You better
put some lace in that walk.
- And the one and only
Graham Norton.
- Beyond excited
to be here, Ru.
I just hope some of your
fabulousness is catching.
- Darling, there's
an ointment for that.
(all laugh)
This week,
we challenged our queens
to create and pitch
their own AllStar merch.
And tonight on the runway,
the category is pants.
Pants, I said.
(all laugh)
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
Up first, Roxxxy Andrews.
- That is Wigstock.
- Oh, she's putting the ho
back in Navaho.
- This outfit represents me
and my brand
because it's always
going to be glamorous
and you can see every piece
of my bootylicious self.
- Now, that's what I call
a power bell-bottom.
(all laugh)
Katya.
The Russians are
taking over the runway.
- I'm giving you 1980s
lesbian literary agent,
disinterested, pissed-off
Ellen Barkin fantasy.
Comrade Katya.
- To androgyny and beyond.
- Alyssa Edwards.
- She's showing
a lot of beaver.
- I'm giving you all
a rich white woman.
"Dynasty," "Dallas,"
Joan Collins, rich.
My hair is so coiffed,
I don't care if my fur's fake.
- All that tail.
Detox.
- I always wanted to know
what happened to Raggedy Ann.
- My runway look
is inspired
by a vintage
Terry Leclair look.
But it's very, like,
futuristic cruise-wear.
- Now, this is how
they wear capris in Capri.
- I think
it's a clam digger.
- What the fuck
did you call me?
Alaska.
The other Miss Ross, Betsy.
- Yeah.
(all laugh)
- I feel like
a real American she-ro.
These pants are very bizarre
and I guess
that's very much my brand.
- You know, I love the fringe
benefits of a government job.
- That's her lunatic fringe.
- (laughs)
Tatianna.
- Ooh, all T-Boz, all shade.
(laughs)
- I'm choosing to work it out
to my T-Boz impersonation.
So I break out the slide and
the "Waterfalls" choreography.
You know, I'm always known
as, like, the pretty,
but I can do
other things, too.
- She ain't too proud
to drag.
- Uh-uh.
- Now, don't go chasing
waterfalls.
Coming up...
- You never want
to be forgetful.
- It's just so ugly.
It's a really piss-poor
prototype.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Welcome, ladies.
Let's take a look
at your commercials.
First up,
Foxy Roxxxy Andrews.
- Oh.
I'm Roxxxy Andrews,
and I'm here
to give you what
you've all been waiting for.
The Roxxxy Andrews Wig Tricks
Instructional DVD.
You ever
been making whoopie
and all of a sudden
you lose your wig?
Or performing at the club
and you show the audience
how much hair you really have?
Baby, this wig
ain't going nowhere.
I'll even show you some of
my best wig reveal secrets.
- Yes.
- If you order now,
I'm going to throw in
Roxxxy Andrews'
super tacky Wig Glue.
Now, go out there
and get your life, honey.
(applause)
- Here's the thing
with the video.
Even though the sight gag was
there with losing the hair,
it's almost like
when you see it once
and it's really funny,
then next time,
it's like, oh, okay.
That made it
a little bit forgetful,
and you never
want to be forgetful.
- You wore that kind of,
sort of beige nude under it.
It was a bit sort of
granny on her honeymoon.
But it just looked like
it needed a good boil wash.
- Okay.
- But I love this bell-bottom
look that you have going on.
I think it really accents
your womanly shape.
- All right.
Thanks, Roxxxy.
- Thank you.
- Up next, Comrade Katya.
- (Russian accent)
Riddled with anxiety?
Crippled under the burden
of existential pain?
(groans)
Hello, my name
is Katya Zimuchkiva.
You know, these days,
being a woman is tough.
When I'm not struggling
with my weight
or worried about wrinkles,
I am bombarded
by a cacophony
of demonic voices
in my head telling me...
(deep voice)
you're not good enough.
That's why I created
Crisis Control,
a moisturizing body spray
that provides relief,
while heavy doses of thorazine
shield the psyche from pain.
So go ahead,
control yourself.
(laughter and applause)
- That is ge-nee-us.
Your commercial
is brilliant,
just very, very funny
the whole way through.
- You were really working
within your whorehouse--
I mean, wheelhouse.
- (laughs)
- Let's talk about
this runway look.
You looked gorgeous.
You really, like, were modeling
the shit out of it.
- The outfit is so wrong,
it's right.
- Everything you did,
your commercial,
your product and your look
are on brand.
- Thank you.
- Up next, Alyssa Edwards.
- My fellow Americans.
Now, I know you've all
been dying to know my secret
and I'm here to share with you
the latest energy enhancer, DDG,
Drop Dead Gorgeous,
that puts the go in go-go.
So if you're looking
to refuel your life
and get a nice good kick
and a boost,
why wake up and just be cute
when you can spring up
and be Drop Dead Gorgeous?
Not only am I a consumer,
I'm also the president.
(laughter and applause)
- So let's talk about
your runway look.
I love it. I think you look
like Cruella DeVille
decided to go
all the way black.
And once you go black...
- You never go back.
- The commercial.
Why were you in front
of the White House?
- For my season, I tried
to develop a perfume.
- Oh, I know. I've seen.
- Okay.
The Americans
have been asking me
for the last three years,
what is really your secret?
So I was doing
a press conference.
- I thought
it was all about
you being the president
of the company.
- Yeah, that, too.
(all laugh)
Fortunately, everyone was
laughing when it was airing,
so you got the job done.
- I love the energy drink.
I think it will sell.
I think you should've called it
Tongue Pop, though.
- Okay.
- Give me some of that
Tongue Pop, baby.
- Okay.
- I'm a marketing genius.
I marketed subversive drag
to 100 million motherfuckers
in the world.
I'm a marketing motherfucking
genius over here.
Up next, Detox.
- Oh, hey, there,
it's me, Detox,
everyone's favorite
trash-talking transvestite,
here with Detox's
Talking Trash trash receptacle.
Hi, Detox.
Oh.
Detox's Trash Talking
trash receptacle
has many catch phrases,
such as...
And new takes on
your old favorites like...
Detox's Trash Talking
trash receptacle
is made of 100% plastic.
More plastic than me!
Only 35.99,
batteries not included.
- Oh, my God.
- This look, I think
it's really gorgeous.
It's sort of fresh.
It's continental.
It's a real kind of head turner
on the catwalk.
- I thoroughly enjoyed
the commercial.
A trashy trash can
is very much you.
- One of the things
that bothered me
is that you were moving
your hand there.
Then it became like
a ventriloquist type of moment,
where it wasn't
supposed to be.
- It's just so ugly.
I know
it's just a prototype,
but it's a really
piss-poor prototype.
- He didn't mean it.
- I did.
(all laugh)
- All right.
Thank you, Detox.
- Thank you.
- Up next, Alaska.
- Hi-ee.
In a world of oppression,
I speak my mind.
(deep voice) Anus.
That's why I use Alaska
Thunderfun Fashion Tape.
What makes this product
different, you might ask?
That's a stupid question.
It makes you beautiful.
Ooh, tighter.
It makes you fashionable.
And it costs
lots of lots of money.
(whispering) I'm so rich.
Available
in three unique shades...
Alaska Thunderfun
Fashion Tape.
Anus-thing is possible.
(laughter and applause)
- I had high hopes
for your commercial,
and you really
didn't disappoint.
It was properly funny,
really kind of captured
that sort of pretentious
1990s perfume ad,
like an old legal tease.
It was very, very good.
- You had so much
to get through,
but you were able
to change on time.
- You, like, Spielberged
the shit out of it.
- You know,
it's what I love to do.
It's, like, my passion
and it's my calling.
- The runway look,
from the neck down,
you're going to some
fabulous Studio 54 disco,
but your hair
is going bowling.
- Up next, Tatianna.
- Do you like gossip?
Do you spreading rumors?
Do you like
just talking shit?
If so, then you're in luck.
Hi, I'm Tatianna,
here with Spill the Tea
with Tati,
a designer tea set
designed by yours truly.
It's perfect for any wear.
Wearing chartreuse
doesn't work for everybody.
(laughs) Choices.
She literally shit herself
down the stairs.
Cleanup on aisle feces.
Am I right?
My teacups work
for all kinds of beverages,
like coffee, cocoa or sake.
You also receive
my handy travel tea tote,
perfect for when
you're on the go.
She's a fucking cunt.
So make sure that you spill
the tea with me, Tati.
Thank you.
(laughter and applause)
- On the runway, you came out
and we were gagging.
I mean, it's really good.
- Thank you.
- Would you please,
just for my own satisfaction,
do that dance
that T-Boz does?
Ooh, love it.
- Yeah, yes.
- TLC tip.
- Moving on
to the commercial.
Even though you were being
really
see you next Tuesday-ish--
- Choices.
- We still liked you.
You're really,
really charming.
What you didn't do
is really feature the product.
That was a miss for me.
- I saw
what you were going for,
but I felt like maybe you
didn't get all the way there.
- Gotcha.
- Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
I've made
some business decisions.
Alaska, Katya,
con-drag-ulations.
You are the two top AllStars
of the week.
You've each won a custom wig
wardrobe from Weaven Steven.
- Oh!
- Plus, a limited edition
of your AllStar merch
will be available at
the upcoming RuPaul's Drag Con.
- Yes.
(applause)
- Alyssa Edwards, Detox,
you are safe.
That means Roxxxy Andrews
and Tatianna,
you're the bottom two.
Alaska, Katya, each of you
needs to decide
which of the bottom two
you'll eliminate
if you win the lip sync.
So while you queens
deliberate in the workroom,
the judges and I
will be skeet shooting.
- I don't know
what that means.
- You may leave the stage.
Coming up...
- Who the fuck
do I send home tonight?
Roxxxy's been in the bottom
however many times,
but Tatianna hasn't
been here the whole time.
(RuPaul laughs)
- (sighs)
This is bizarre,
because it is the same
exact top and bottom two
from the Snatch Game
episode.
- We're lip synching yet again
against one another.
- And we're in the bottom.
- With those two
in the bottom.
- Oh, my God. I didn't
even think about that.
- It's dj vu
all over again.
Let's hope
that this doesn't go
the way that it did
the first time around.
- I'd like to talk one on one
with you guys if you want to.
- Sure.
- I'll be over there.
- Fuel.
- Actually, Detox,
can we talk,
like, over there?
- Sure.
- Who the fuck
do I send home tonight?
- I don't want to see
my sister go home,
but out of who's left, she's
been in the bottom the most.
- Roxxxy's been in the bottom
however many times,
but Tatianna hasn't been here
the whole time.
- She's missed two challenges
until her return.
- I need to hear these hos.
- So before we start,
I just want to give you
a couple of moments
to give me some compliments
about my outfit.
- Uh, living.
- (laughs)
- Living out loud.
- I'm so glad you did that
on the runway.
- Thank you.
- How are you feeling?
- I know that maybe
I tripped on this challenge,
but the next one
I'm going to fucking pick
that shit up and keep going.
I definitely think that
I was brought back for a reason.
I've been given
a second chance,
and I want
to fucking be here.
I really think that my
performance speaks for itself.
Roxxxy's commercial was not
as entertaining as mine,
and my runway look
was better.
- How are you feeling,
honey?
- You know what, I'm so thankful
to still be here.
At the end of the day,
I don't feel like
I got the harshest critiques
like usually.
And I don't know
if this is my time,
but God does, so we'll see
what he decides for me.
And regardless of what happens,
I am so proud of you.
- Thank you.
Thanks for letting me
borrow this top.
- You're welcome.
I've fallen in the bottom
so much,
my drive is a little lacking
right now.
But I feel like my commercial
was better than Tatianna's,
so if we're sticking true
to our plan, I should be fine.
- How are you feeling?
- I felt like
I had a great commercial,
but what I've been giving
has landed me in the bottom,
so I don't know
what else I can do, you know?
If you decide me, no T.
If you decide to keep me,
no T.
It's up to you.
I don't care either way.
I've been in the bottom
four times.
- If you're not trying
to express
how much
you want to stay here,
that must mean that you're
kind of ready to hit it.
And to that, I say hit it.
- All right, well...
- I love you. Mmm.
- Love you, too.
- Based on my last experience,
Alaska didn't send Roxxxy home,
and that's an alliance
that's very evident now.
- Girl.
- Although, I'm not going out
without a fight at all.
Today was possibly
a missed opportunity,
but this isn't deterring me
from, like,
wanting to fucking kick ass
in this fucking competition.
I clawed my way
back in here.
Like, that's a huge
fucking deal.
So, yeah, I'm not ready to go
by any means.
I will never say, oh,
what happens happens. No.
To you, I say keep a bitch.
- Pull!
(rooster crows)
Ooh, I got it!
(laughter and applause)
All right, all right.
Silence.
Bring back my girls.
- After talking with Tatianna
and Roxxxy in the workroom,
I kind of go with my gut
with this decision,
and I feel
pretty comfortable.
- I still have no idea
whose lipstick
I'm going to choose.
If I send Tatianna home,
then people will say
that I'm favoring Roxxxy
because she's my friend.
If I send Roxxxy home,
then I'll look like
kind of a bitch
because she lent me
this shirt that I'm wearing.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Welcome back, ladies.
Two top AllStars
stand before me.
Ladies, this is your chance
to impress me,
win $10,000,
and earn the power
to give one of
the bottom queens the chop.
The time has come
to lip sync
(echoing) for your legacy.
- Katya's really amazing
at lip syncing.
I beat her once before,
but who knows what's
gonna happen this time?
- Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
(music plays)
-  Can't stay at home,
can't stay at school
Old folks say,
you poor little fool
Down the street,
I'm the girl next door
I'm the fox
you've been waiting for
Hello, Daddy,
hello, Mom
I'm your
ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-cherry bomb
Stone age love
and strange sounds, too
Come on, baby,
let me get into you
Bad nights
causing teenage blues
Get down now 'cause
you've got nothing to lose
Hello, Daddy,
hello, Mom
I'm your
ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-cherry bomb
Hey, street boy,
want some style?
Have you, grab you
till you're sore
Hello, Daddy,
hello, Mom
I'm your
ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-cherry bomb
Hello, world,
I'm your wild girl
I'm your
ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-cherry bomb
Cherry bomb
(laughter and applause)
- Ladies,
I've made my decision.
Alaska,
you are a winner, baby.
- Thank you.
(applause)
- Con-drag-ulations.
You've earned a cash tip
of $10,000.
- Second time losing
the lip sync to Alaska.
Ugh. It sucks.
- Katya, you are safe.
- Thank you.
- You may join
the other girls.
Will the bottom two
please step forward?
Alaska, with great power
comes great responsibility.
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
- One of these queens,
week after week,
has brought a level
of prestige and beauty
and excellence
to this runway
and to the art form
of drag.
And one of these queens
is the person
who lent me this very shirt
that I'm wearing tonight.
So based on that,
I've chosen...
Tatianna.
Tatianna, I think
you're stunning.
- Thanks.
- As it is written,
so it shall be done.
Tatianna,
you are an AllStar.
Now sashay away.
- Thank you.
(all laugh)
(laughter and applause)
- Even though
I didn't get to feature
everything that I wanted to,
I think I showed a lot
while I was here.
I got to introduce myself
to people who didn't know
who Tatianna was,
and I got to impress
the people
who have been my supporters
from the jump.
And that,
I'm very proud of.
Thank you.
- My fierce five,
con-drag-ulations.
You're one step closer to
the Drag Race Hall of Fame.
Now, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen
up in here?
- Amen!
- All right.
Now, let the music play.
-  Throw you hands up
Time to get down
Time to get down,
down, down, down, down
Throw your hands up