- Previously
on "AllStars..."
It's time for Snatch Game.
(cheering)
- Why don't you come on up
and fuck me in the ass
sometime?
- Oh.
- They remove
their testicles.
- (laughs)
- Brrr.
- Is that a wig
on your head?
- If you're not
wearing wigs,
then you're not doing drag.
- Let's hear you sing
to them.
(no sound)
Oh.
Alaska,
you're a winner, baby.
(applause)
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
- The queen
that I have chosen...
is Tatianna.
- Tatianna, sashay away.
- (sighs)
- Tatianna's been eliminated
and it's sad,
because she's a fierce,
fierce, fierce queen.
Oh, ho-ho-ho-ho-ho.
- Thank you.
- I think Tatianna's amazing,
and I'm really glad
that she's sort of being
reintroduced to the world.
- And I think that the fear
that she had
about not getting the chance
to do that is unfounded.
- Can I ask you what was
the determining factor for you?
- Sure.
Roxxxy and Tatianna
both floundered
in the Snatch Game,
but Tatianna did not bring it
on the runway
in the way that Roxxxy did.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, girl.
I'm proud of Alaska for going
off of the judges' critique,
and I'm even more proud
that she kept her word.
- Tatianna is an AllStar.
- Some of us agreed it should
be based on judges' critiques
who we send home, and if you're
the weakest link that week,
then, sorry, but that's
just what we agreed on,
and I think that's fair.
Katya, can we ask who
you were gonna send home?
- Oh, yeah. Um...
I chose Tatianna as well
for the same reason
that Alaska just said.
Roxxxy slayed the runway.
- Slayed.
- I feel like
in this instance,
it was a lot easier
to be objective about it.
- Yeah.
- I know you wanted
to get critiqued.
- I feel like I finally
really stepped outside of my box
as far as the aesthetics go.
So I'm safe for
the second week in a row.
I felt like my Snatch Game
was really, really strong,
and I'm giving
glamour toad realness.
What the hell else
do I have to do
to get a little recognition
in this gin joint?
- Girl, we are
really sitting here.
One, two, three, four,
five, six--eight.
- There's seven.
- Seven.
- One, two, three...
- You can't count.
- Four, five, six--
top seven.
- You were looking
at yourself in the mirror,
so you counted
yourself twice.
(all laugh)
- Lookit! She's still
looking in the mirror.
- She's just talking to herself
in the fucking mirror.
- Ah-ha!
- On that note...
- Good day, good night,
you shady lady!
(all laugh)
- I love Alyssa,
but someone needs
to take her go-go juice away
'cause she's a little...
- But you look so right!
- Alyssa, take my hair off!
(laughs)
- I wish you would snatch
my wig, girl.
I wish you would!
Come on! Come on!
Come on, bitch!
- Oh, my Jesus.
Just nonstop.
I mean, at this point,
it's just background noise.
I gotta focus on me.
I can't listen to this.
(all laugh)
She is funny sometimes.
Sometimes.
- Come get me up, baby.
- The winner of "RuPaul's
Drag Race AllStars"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia
Beverly Hills cosmetics,
a coveted spot in
the Drag Race Hall of Fame
and a cash prize
of $100,000
with extra special
guest judge Jeremy Scott.
- ¶ RuPaul's Drag Race ¶
- ¶ May the best woman ¶
- ¶ Best woman win ¶
- So it's a new day
in the workroom.
I hate those new day
in the workroom bites.
I have? Okay.
It's a new day
in the workroom,
and I'm feeling very good
and sexy
and really grateful
to be here.
(laughs)
What kind of
vindictive machinations
do you think
they've concocted?
- I hope Todrick makes a video
and we're all in it.
- That would be so rad.
- Did he lend you
this jacket?
- Log off, B. Log.
- Don't log off.
Delete the account.
(all laugh)
- You're so stupid.
Girl, you looked over
at Detox yesterday
and said, you're a beast.
Beast!
- Beast!
- You're like
the Gila monster, though.
- You're a Gila monster.
- If you are that grotted,
you could be a monster,
a Gila monster or a beast.
- Beast!
(all laugh)
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Hi!
- Ladies, for this week's
maxi challenge,
you'll be performing
a lip sync extravaganza
that salutes the baddest
bitches in herstory.
#HerstoryOfTheWorld.
- (snaps fingers)
- Alaska, you'll play
the original
naughty girl Eve.
- Sss...
- Phi Phi O'Hara, you'll play
the face, face, face
that launched 1,000 ships,
Helen of Troy.
- Oh.
- Ginger Minj, you'll play
Russian ruler supreme
Catherine the Great.
Detox, you'll play
the queen of cakes.
You know, cakes,
Marie Antoinette.
Alyssa Edwards, you'll play
gun-slinging superstar
Annie Oakley.
Roxxxy Andrews, you'll play
Argentina's former
first lady Eva Peron.
And Katya, you'll play
the people's princess,
Diana, Princess of Wales.
Now, ladies, you'll be
performing together,
but you need to do whatever
it takes to steal the show.
Later today,
you'll be meeting
with choreographers Ant and Ash
from the Squared Division.
- Nice.
(applause)
- And you know
they work with
pop goddesses Britney,
Taylor Swift, Kylie Minogue.
So don't fuck it up.
(laughs)
(applause)
- Oh, is that--that's
the Helen of Troy outfit?
- It is.
- (gasps)
It is so cool.
Can I try it on?
- Yeah.
(crunch)
- Um, okay.
You need to calm down.
I thought
that you had resolved
all this anger
from your season.
This is so cool.
This is so pretty.
- Thank you.
- Thank God you're talented
at something.
- My dress is so shitty
compared to everybody else's.
- I think this is the most
iconic Diana, though.
- Yeah. It's just
a little wrinkly.
During my season,
we had a similar challenge,
and I bombed it so hard,
it landed me in the bottom.
Damn, girl.
- It's long.
- It's really long.
We could literally perform
the number on your train.
- What I've come to realize
is that I have to cut off
the fucking train.
And now it's just
a simple wedding dress,
but there's just absolutely
no way I can perform with it on,
even though it is
my dead grandmother's dress.
It's actually my friend's
dead grandma's dress.
Rest in peace, grandma.
Oh, my God.
- Girl, I need to--I need to--
I need to--I need to--
I need to get up in this
Annie Oakley get-up gig.
On season 5, I hated playing
anything other than Alyssa.
But I want to prove to Ru
that I'm more
than just some pageant queen
that can kick and twirl.
I can be a character.
- What are you doing
with your hair?
- I think I like her.
- Oh.
- Girl, you better believe
I'm gonna do my best
to steal the show.
That's the name
of this game.
- Alyssa's like fuckin
batshit fuckin funny, crazy,
but I don't think she knows
how to really channel that
into, like, the acting
or, like, the comedy.
She's definitely a star.
She's feeling it. Like,
she thinks she's sickening.
- Girl, please.
- Alyssa's too concerned
about how many GIFs
she can get made after this,
and, you know, what T-shirt
she's gonna sell next.
- Coming up...
- I'm Annie Oakley
and this is my band.
- Okay.
This can be
obviously really funny.
It kind of looks like
you're taking a shit.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Welcome.
- Our maxi challenge
this week
is a bad girl
lip sync extravaganza.
Now it's time to hit
that main stage
and start rehearsing our
choreography with Ash and Ant.
- Hi, I'm Ashley.
- Hey, I'm Anthony.
- And together, we're
the Squared Division.
It's wonderful
to meet you all.
- Oh, my gosh, I'm
fan-girling a little bit.
Two choreographers
that I respect so much.
They're beyond creative.
- Catherine the Great.
So Ginger, are you a dancer?
- Nope.
- No.
- I'm a Tony Danza.
- (laughs)
- So you've got
a lot to deal with
'cause you're gonna use
a horse prop.
You'll use it like a cane.
- I'm a little resentful
at Ginger
because she gets the part
not only that's Russian,
but also fucks a horse.
(horse neighs)
- My dress is huge.
It's got a cape with
a little bit of a train.
- Gosh, you've got a lot
to contend with, don't you?
- I do.
- Okay, so from after this,
you'll bring it
behind your head and...
- Okay. Oh! Sorry.
This is going very well.
Well, I'm a little
freaked out.
Not only is dancing
not my strong suit,
as anybody who watched
Season 7 will attest to,
I also have this giant
Catherine the Great costume.
¶ Every Tom, Dick or Igor
and even Mr. Ed ¶
- It's just timing.
And your dress
is not gonna help.
- Coming into "AllStars"
with a group of gals
who are so larger than life
and so amazing at what they do,
it's a little intimidating.
But I can't let that
get to me.
I've got to get
right back in there.
¶ All of Russia
is my shtomping ground ¶
- Yes, exactly.
Gorgeous.
- I may be 5'2,
but I'm gonna stand above
all these other motherfuckers.
Ha!
- That's better.
We're moving on.
- Stay and stay and then you
guys can just take a rest.
- Okay.
- I like Phi Phi a lot,
but I think Phi Phi had
certain notions in her head
when she walked into
this competition
about what she needed to do
to redeem her reputation
from her season,
what she needed to do
to last a while,
and all of those things
don't necessarily mesh well
with one another.
So sometimes it feels like
she goes out of her way
to ruffle somebody's feathers
or to plant a seed
of self doubt.
It's weird.
- All right.
Annie.
So we shoot.
(imitates gunshots)
I'm Annie Oakley,
and this is my band.
- During rehearsal,
I'm ready to work.
Bitch is clocked in.
Bang, bang, bang, bang.
You stumble.
And your gun shoots--
shoots all the girls down.
Exactly.
- Bang, bang.
- Yeah, bang.
Ha! The steps are there.
You need to now
work on the balance
between it looking hot
and proper,
'cause you're a dancer,
but then characterizing that
at the same time.
- Okay.
- (off-mike) And that's decent.
Walk into, um...
(continues off-mike,
indistinct)
- All right,
let's move on.
Marie Antoinette.
Detox, you're gonna
give it, like, almost like
a chasse, pas de bourree,
and then soutenu.
- What the fuck?
- Chasse, pas de bourree,
soutenu.
It's step, cut, cut, cut,
phoom, phoom.
It has to be like a little,
um, a little waltz.
Let me see that again.
- And be funnier.
- All right. Ooh.
- It kind of looks like
you're taking a shit.
- Yeah.
- This can be obviously
really funny,
and I don't think
it's quite that funny yet.
It's missing something.
- Right now, I'm just trying
to focus on this little bit,
so I'm, like, in here.
- Okay.
- I'm not believing it.
- It could be so funny,
and I'm not getting that.
- A lot of work to do.
- This is the baddest bitches
in herstory, honey.
- I'm sitting next
to the baddest bitch
in RuPaul's Drag Race herstory
right here, if you ask me.
You were like, this bitch
is annoying me,
so I'm going to fuckin
talk about her.
- I have no apologies.
I wasn't going to be
something I wasn't.
Alyssa, you know this.
Like, that drag
just was not something
I grew up with in Texas.
It was all about how many
pageant titles you had.
So when I see someone
like Sharon
and I saw that
she was winning everything
and I saw her as,
like, a threat
and I think that's where
a lot of the anger came from.
It didn't help me
afterwards.
- What happened afterwards?
- I think that people
couldn't look past.
I watch reality TV and I don't
like people on there, too,
but I would never go
and, like, threaten them
or want to throw acid
in their face.
- People threaten
to throw acid on your face?
- Yeah.
Actually, in L.A.
You know who really
hated me during my season?
Detox.
- Really?
- Did you?
- I was evil to her because
there was this fucking cunt
who was evil and rotten
to everybody
and, of course, I wanted
to protect my sister.
That's my family,
you know what I mean?
So, like, every week, I would,
like, attack three people.
You blocked me
for a while, too.
Here in California, we
all look after each other,
and so when somebody
is coming for our girls,
we are in full attack mode.
- Did that ever hurt
your feelings, though?
- I literally had
one breakdown moment,
and I remember
crying in the car.
- Aw.
- After season 4,
there was a slight period
of time I almost quit drag.
It was just
too much to handle.
I just didn't feel safe
going anywhere.
People really take it seriously
and they wanted to hurt me.
So they just were, like, maybe
it's best you don't show up.
- That is insane.
- That is awful.
- Obviously, time has passed,
we're friends.
But I do feel bad.
I feel guilty
and a little responsible
for making her afraid
of West Hollywood.
- I just hope
that there's a movement
toward people being
a little less awful
and hateful on social media.
Treating people that way
is, like, so unacceptable.
- No, totally.
- I think that people are people
and we do the best we can.
And if you're attacking
someone online
who you think is a monster,
then maybe you're a monster
inside.
Be nice.
Fuck's sake,
it's just drag.
- Coming up...
- ¶ Herstory, yes ¶
(RuPaul laughs)
- ¶ Covergirl, put the bass
in your walk ¶
(echoing)
¶ Walk ¶
¶ Covergirl, put the bass
in your walk ¶
¶ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ¶
¶ Covergirl ¶
- Whoo-whoo.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul's
Drag Race AllStars."
The baddest girl I know,
Michelle Visage.
- And when I'm bad,
I'm better.
- (laughs) Style superstar
Carson Kressley,
are you ready
for a herstory lesson?
- Oh, yes.
Teach me a lesson, mama.
- The incredible
Todrick Hall.
It's your first lip sync
extravaganza.
- And after tonight,
I will no longer be a virgin.
- Oh, dear.
And the people's designer,
Jeremy Scott.
So glad you're here.
Love the shirt.
- My mother and father
designed it for me.
(all laugh)
- This week,
we challenged our queens
to celebrate the baddest
bitches in herstory,
and then on the runway,
category is The Future of Drag.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
- Hey, it's me, God.
Good girls may go to heaven,
but bad girls rule the world.
Who's the baddest bitch
in herstory?
Well, who am I to judge?
- ¶ In the beginning,
there were one, two, three ¶
¶ Adam and me
and my best friend Steve ¶
¶ They started making out
in front of me ¶
¶ That's when I told them that
they had to leave, get out ¶
¶ But they took
all the food from me ¶
¶ Except the apple
on the tree ¶
¶ It was forbidden ¶
¶ God, are you kidding? ¶
¶ Then the snake
told me to bake ¶
¶ An apple pie
and not a cake ¶
¶ So I did it ¶
¶ I went and bit it ¶
¶ And then everything
went to shit ¶
¶ and I realized
I was naked ¶
What?
That's right.
- ¶ The most beautiful face
in the world ¶
¶ That launched
1,000 ships ¶
¶ She mesmerized us
with her smile ¶
¶ But, oy,
when she opens her lips ¶
(heavy metal music)
¶ Troy, Troy,
I'm Helen of Troy ¶
¶ Troy, I'm Helen of Troy ¶
¶ I'm Helen of Troy ¶
¶ Yeah, I'm Helen of Troy ¶
¶ Troy, I'm Helen of Troy ¶
¶ I'm Helen of Troy ¶
(hoofbeats)
- ¶ I had a great many lovers
that I took to bed ¶
¶ Every Tom, Dick and Igor
and even Mr. Ed ¶
¶ There's more of me to love
with these few extra pounds ¶
¶ Everybody knows
I like to horse around ¶
- (whinny)
- ¶ Horse around ¶
¶ Giddyap and get down ¶
¶ I said, giddyap ¶
¶ Horse around ¶
¶ Come and take a ride
on my merry-go-round ¶
¶ Horse around ¶
(neighs)
¶ Get down, get down,
get down, get down ¶
¶ Horse around ¶
¶ All of Russia
is my shtomping ground ¶
("Call to Post" plays)
I got a nice big carrot.
Dah!
- If you are looking
to start a revolution,
I created
a social media solution.
Put on your opulent jewels,
air and dress,
and say it
in 140 characters or less
¶ Let them eat cake ¶
¶ Let them eat cake,
cake, cake, cake, cake ¶
¶ Let them eat ca-a-a-ke ¶
¶ Let them eat
ca-uh-uh-ke ¶
ca-hoo-ha-hoo-- ¶
(inhales)
¶ Ca-a-ake ¶
¶ Let them eat cake ¶
(gunshots)
- I'm Annie Oakley,
and this is my band.
The Sharpshooters.
Five, six!
(gunshots)
¶ Been on my own
since I was young ¶
¶ Came out my mama
with a gun ¶
¶ A better shot
than anyone ¶
No one can beat me.
¶ But there's a story
y'all don't know ¶
¶ My draw was fast
and his was slow ¶
¶ It really was
his time to go ¶
Ha-ha!
¶ So I went bang, bang ¶
(gunshots)
¶ Bang, bang ¶
¶ These double barrels
pumped him full of lead ¶
(gunshots)
¶ I went bang, bang ¶
¶ Bang, bang ¶
(gunshots)
¶ He's six feet under
lying in my bed ¶
(gunshots)
Well, I guess I'm done.
Yippy-yi-ki-gay.
- ¶ I'm Eva Peron, so honey,
don't you cry for me ¶
¶ I'm an actress, not a diva
and the first lady ¶
¶ I give the people hope
for a better mañana ¶
¶ I was Evita, after all ¶
¶ I played it better
than Madonna ¶
¶ I did it for the rights,
I did it for the kids ¶
¶ I did it
for the sick and poor ¶
¶ I did it for the fame,
I did it for the money ¶
¶ I did it
'cause I wanted more ¶
¶ I gave the people joy,
I gave the people life ¶
¶ I gave the people drama ¶
¶ And I did it,
oh, yes, I did it ¶
¶ Better than Madonna ¶
- I'm Princess Di,
I'm very shy ¶
¶ And the world
fell in love with my eyes ¶
¶ To everyone,
I was his wife ¶
¶ And we lived out
a fairytale life ¶
¶ And then,
shit hit the fan ¶
¶ I got divorced from my man ¶
¶ They made me
give up my crown ¶
¶ But they can't keep
a girl down ¶
Be careful what you wish for
'cause this English rose
has thorns.
- ¶ They say
it's a man's world we miss ¶
¶ So, girl, we've been
breaking the rules ¶
- ¶ And it started with me ¶
- ¶ We're the baddest bitches
in herstory ¶
Yes!
(cheers and applause)
- Coming up...
- You're a star.
- It left us gagging.
- Listen, everybody
was so fantastic,
but decisions must be made.
(RuPaul laughs)
- ¶ Drag queen ¶
¶ Sexy, sexy drag queen ¶
- Serving the future
of drag, Alaska.
In the future, if you're not
wearing three-foot nails,
you're not doing drag.
- Aah!
I'm serving alien
princess ele-gwanza.
- The higher the hair,
the closer to Uranus.
- Yes.
- Aah!
- Phi Phi O'Hara.
- C3P-ho.
- This outfit really embodies
everything that Phi Phi is now.
Like, she's a cosplay queen.
She's not trying to be
this pageant queen anymore.
- Set phasers to stunning.
Ginger Minj,
voulez-vous coucher.
- In my delicate
little mind,
the way I picture
the future of drag
is that whole retro Brady Bunch
space age kind of design.
- In the future, we'll all
have hair like Chaka Khan.
- Yes, we will.
Detox.
Oh, oh, oh, okay.
Oh, my God!
- Aah!
- I'm practically naked
walking down the runway,
and I look like a sexy,
silver fembot fuck toy.
- She's serving
the fifth element,
the sixth element,
and magnesium.
- (laughs)
- Alyssa Edwards.
- She's horny, baby.
- Girl, I got
my beaded wig on, girl.
I got the horns.
I got the moon boots.
I am giving y'all
everything.
- Oh, I just noticed
the boots.
- Yeah.
(all laugh)
- Now, is that a fascinator
on her head
or a doggy bag?
- Ha-ha!
- Roxxxy Andrews.
- Ugh!
- She just fixed herself.
- (laughs)
- I feel like a warrior
in my outfit.
It's Wonder Woman/goddess
of planet Roxxxy.
- Space age face
with an Oakland booty.
(all laugh)
Katya. Whoo.
- I'm pretty sure this is my
Aunt Harriet at a Bat mitzvah.
- I'm giving you
intergalactic mom.
The piece de resistance of
this outfit is the giant hair.
It's kind of like a doughnut
on acid.
It is the most glamorous I've
ever looked in my entire life.
- Live long and prostitute.
(all laugh)
Welcome, ladies.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
First up, Alaska.
- Aah!
- Huh.
(all laugh)
- Your Eve
was truly enjoyable.
You started off the show,
so you needed to nail that
and you did.
- Tonight,
the future of drag.
Yes, it's great,
it's fun, it's Alaska.
But Alaska is an alien
and comes from
the planet Glamtron.
I was expecting you to go
completely all the way.
- Up next, Phi Phi O'Hara.
- As far as
scene-stealing went,
to me, you did fade in
the background a little bit,
but I will say
tonight on the runway,
this is really,
really fantastic work.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, the laser gun
is amazing,
and you didn't give us
just silver,
which I'm seeing a lot of.
- I am so proud of you,
as far as evolution goes,
from where you were in your
season to where you are now.
- Yay.
- Up next, Ginger Minj.
- You should have
a one-woman show on Broadway.
You're a star.
- But there were some moments
where I was like,
oh, look, she's still in,
and then some moments
she kind of faded
into the background.
- This look is not
one of my favorites.
There's a whole lot
of everything going on.
Like, I need Ritalin
to look at you right now.
- Yeah. It's just
a little bit wah-wah.
- Well, these light up,
all these things light up.
- Why aren't they?
- They are lit up.
I just didn't realize
you couldn't see them.
- Oh, right.
- I actually quite liked it
'cause don't take this
in the wrong way,
I felt like you were channeling
Miss Piggy, "Pigs in Space."
- (laughs)
- Up next, Detox.
- I loved Ne-Antoinette.
She could've been
a whole collection.
And, of course, your iconic
jaw movement was at play there.
- And then
you came out tonight.
What you did and the way
you executed it,
it left us gagging.
- Thank you very much.
(sniffles)
- Don't cry, Detox.
You'll rust.
(all laugh)
Up next, the always understated
Alyssa Edwards.
- Annie got her gun and she
murdered the competition.
I could not
take my eyes off you.
- Yeah, and the challenge was,
you know, stealing the scene.
You stole the show.
- Thank you.
- But I have no idea
what is going on tonight.
We are part Cleopatra,
part Saturday night takeaway.
- I will just
come out of the closet here
and say that this is fashion
and I love it.
- It's just epic and only you
could pull this off.
- Thank you very much.
- Up next, Roxxxy Andrews.
- Don't cry for me,
Roxxxy Andrews.
Your Evita was spot on.
- But tonight on the runway,
I do think this is plain
compared to everybody else.
- Maybe this isn't
my favorite of the looks,
but it's very
Queen of the Night,
Whitney Houston kind of,
um...
- Buy "The Bodyguard"
soundtrack, track 9.
(all laugh)
- Up next, Katya.
- I love that you took
Princess Leia's bun
and blew it up and made
one giant hairdo out of it.
- Right, but I'm not just crazy
about the outfit.
I think it's a little too
covered up.
And your Princess Diana,
the overall performance was
a little monotone for me.
- It felt almost
a bit solemn.
- But I felt that out of all
the lip syncs, you were spot on.
- But I wish the sleeves
were obnoxiously poofed
like the gown was.
I wish you had
a 5,000 foot train.
Also, the hair was more
like Ellen DeGeneres
than it was Princess Di
for me.
- It needed to be more of that
feathered back iconic look
so we're not figuring it out
from the lyrics.
- Now, in Katya's defense,
Princess Diana
is really the only figure
that we remember
what she looked like.
The other characters
were open to interpretation.
Listen, everybody
was so fantastic,
so we have to pick at
some of the smaller things
because ain't much
to criticize here.
But decisions must be made.
So based on
the judges' critiques,
I declare that Detox
and Alyssa Edwards,
you are the top two AllStars
of the week.
- Congratulations.
(applause)
- You've each won
a three-night getaway
to Palm Springs, California,
from
VacationPalmSprings.com.
Con-drag-ulations.
- Thank you.
- When I call your name,
please step forward.
Ginger Minj.
Katya.
You are the bottom two
of the week.
- Oh, good Lord.
Being in the bottom two
is bad enough.
against my best friend is worse.
I don't like how this
is going to end either way.
- That means Detox
and Alyssa,
each of you needs to decide
which of the bottom two
you will eliminate
if you win the lip sync.
- (sighs)
- So while you queens
deliberate in the workroom,
the judges and I will be
giving each other mani-pedis.
You may leave the stage.
Coming up...
- Do you think
that the girls in the top
are going to stick
to our idea
of what did the judges
have to say
and that's who
we're going to choose?
- I'm iffy of one of them.
- Who?
(RuPaul laughs)
- (sighs)
I feel like
this is going to be
a really difficult
deliberation.
All of the critiques
were really, like,
equal across the board.
I mean, Katya's critiques were
slightly worse the Ginger's,
but, still, it's very close.
- Congratulations still go out
to everyone, honestly,
because, girl, we killed.
- What a fucking show.
- Right?
- Did they really rate
anybody's performance?
- Uh, yeah, they said mine
was, like, solemn.
- Katya, come here.
I wanted to call you out
over here
'cause I just kind of saw that
you're going through something.
Are you okay?
- Um, on my season,
I was just like crippled
with, you know, with fear.
And then, this time,
coming here,
I feel like
an enormous change.
I actually feel like a star.
I'm not nervous.
- Right.
- But if you don't your A-plus,
plus, plus, plus game, poof.
- I wasn't expecting them
to read so much into, like,
the whole costuming
and outfits and everything.
- All the things they said
of course made perfect sense,
and I'm just like, fuck.
- I honestly was not expecting
this, so it feels weird.
- There is definitely a grim
undertone to our conversation,
so I would not be surprised
if she chose me to go home.
And I really want to stay.
- It's so hard because
that's my best friend.
- I know, but I feel like
if we continue to stay true
to how we've been wanting to,
I think it's Katya.
- Katya
had the most critiques.
- Oh, God.
- Katya, come on.
My mind is racing.
It's very easy for us to take
one critique and run with it.
But there's so many factors
to take into consideration,
so I'm conflicted.
Do you feel if
I were to win the lip sync
that I should save you?
- I can't make that decision
for you.
- In my opinion, I think
there's so much more to you
than just one challenge
or maybe one runway look
that didn't work.
But do you think
falling short tonight
should remove you
from this competition?
- Um...
- Katya's defeated
and you have to be confident.
That's
the disheartened part.
But I see the emotion
in her eyes.
She wants to be here.
- So do you think
that the girls in the top
are going to stick
to our idea
of what did the judges
have to say
and that's who
we're going to choose?
- I'm iffy of one of them.
- Who? Which one?
- I'll say it out loud.
I mean, no, no--
- No, I know we're both
thinking the same person.
- Because she's been vocal
about it.
Like, it's not a secret.
Alyssa.
- Yeah, Alyssa.
- The one that I feel
would play it the way that
we said we would is Detox.
- Yeah.
- If I were to win this
lip sync tonight, why you?
- Well, on the personal side,
that's my best friend.
- Mm-hmm.
- I don't want to be responsible
for her going home.
But if we're going to judge
by the criteria
that we had all talked about,
she got critiqued
on performance and on runway.
I only got critiqued
on runway.
I also want to say that
no matter which way it falls,
I'll be all right with it.
But I wish it was lip sync
for your life,
because, baby, I've got
this fire in me right now.
- That's what I wanted
to hear, bitch.
- Alyssa looks in my eyes
and says, that's
what I wanted to see.
The fire and the passion.
And from the moment Katya
got called into the bottom two,
she resigned herself to the fact
that she's going home.
She's not
putting forth a fight.
- Do you know what?
I think Ginger Minj
has a lot more fight
to be in the competition,
but Katya was just
in the top last week.
She just won
the Snatch Game.
And in the end, they both
have pros and cons.
Oh, this is a tough decision
to make.
- So I'm gonna tell you
what I said.
- Okay.
- Number one,
you're my best friend.
- Mm-hmm.
- But if you asked me my opinion
on what we all agreed on--
- Yeah, yeah.
I got the lowest points
tonight.
I can't really delude myself in
the face of objective criteria.
- Well, if this had worked
in my favor with the lighting,
it'd be a different story,
but...
- No, it's still ugly.
(all laugh)
- All right.
(blowing)
Silence.
Bring back my girls.
(blowing)
- Although
it's a difficult feeling,
it's not a difficult
decision to make.
I feel confident
in my choice,
and I'm gonna stick
by that decision.
It's just a shitty decision
to have to make.
- It's like
a never-ending walk
because there's no win
in this situation.
I'm gonna follow my heart
on this one.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Welcome back, ladies.
Two top AllStars
stand before me.
Ladies, this is your chance
to impress me,
win $10,000,
and earn the power
to give one of
the bottom queens the chop.
The time has come
for you to lip sync
(echoing) for your legacy.
- I'm very confident that I can
win the lip sync against Alyssa
because I look amazing.
I didn't have to change
to put on a fuckin show.
- I am looking RuPaul
dead in the eyes.
I'm in it to win it.
- Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
(music plays)
¶ I feel the night explode ¶
¶ When we're together ¶
¶ Emotion overload ¶
¶ In the heat of pleasure ¶
¶ Take me, I'm yours,
into your arms ¶
¶ Never let me go ¶
¶ Tonight
I really need to know ¶
¶ Tell it to my heart ¶
¶ I can feel my body rock ¶
¶ Every time
you call my name ¶
¶ The passion's
so complete ¶
¶ It's never ending ¶
¶ As long as I receive ¶
¶ The message
you're sending ¶
¶ Love, love on the run ¶
¶ Breaking us down ¶
¶ No, I can't let you go ¶
¶ Tell it to my heart ¶
¶ Tell me I'm the only one ¶
¶ Is this really love
or just a game? ¶
¶ Tell it to my heart ¶
¶ I can feel my body rock ¶
¶ Every time
you call my name ¶
- (laughs)
- Word!
- Ladies, I have made
my decision.
Alyssa Edwards,
you're a winner, baby.
You've earned a cash tip
of $10,000.
- Whoo-hoo-hoo.
Oh, my gosh.
You did it.
Girl, you're leaving
your legacy.
Thank you very much.
- Detox, you're safe.
- Thank you.
Congratulations, girl.
- Will the bottom two
please step forward.
- Alyssa Edwards,
with great power
comes great responsibility.
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
- I often tell my students
that winning isn't everything,
but wanting to is.
I chose the queen to stay
based on when I looked
into her eyes,
the conviction that I felt.
Sometimes
being in the bottom
could just be
a one-night kind of gig.
So the queen
that I'm sending home...
That's Ginger.
- As it is written,
so it shall be done.
Ginger Minj,
you are an AllStar.
Now, sashay away.
- I truly respect you
from the bottom of my heart.
(applause)
- They got me, gal.
(laughs)
(all laugh)
- Katya, I love you.
You have a lot more to show.
- I'm not surprised
that Alyssa sent me home.
From day one, she's been gunning
to get rid of the competition,
and I feel like
I was competition for her.
She and I do
kind of the same thing.
But I have no hard feelings
towards her.
It's a gift that--
(alarm)
- Ooh, girl.
- What the hell?
- RuPaul:
Ginger, not to worry.
All is not lost.
You still have a chance
to return
for your revenge.
- What?
- (laughs)
Revenge?
I'm ready to knock Alyssa
out of this competition now.
Let's do it.