- Previously
on "AllStars..."
- Whoo, girl.
All is not lost.
- No way.
- You still have a chance
to return.
- Wait, does this mean
I get to come back?
- For your revenge.
- What?
- Alyssa Edwards,
sashay away.
- I am sick
of hearing them say,
you can wear shit
on stage,
but it's okay
'cause you're Alyssa.
It was sloppy.
To me,
she was more concerned
about throwing you two under
the bus during deliberations.
- Oh, my God!
- Trust the Duchess.
It ain't over
just yet, baby.
- Oh, my God!
- Bitch!
- What's going on here?
- Do you remember when you were
in high school on the phone
and you were like, girl,
I can't stand her,
she is so fake.
And then
your friend was like,
well, Melissa, what
do you think about that?
And they were on three-way.
Phi Phi's crack was
that three-way phone call
in high school cracked.
(laughs)
- (cheering)
- Oh, no, no, no!
- Come on.
(cheering)
- Oh, the two-in-one look.
- What's up, hookers?
- Oh!
- Come on, Minj.
- Aw!
- Whoo!
- Oh!
- I'm back, back, back,
back, back again.
- Oh, my God.
- So Phi Phi was just running
off at the mouth about Alyssa,
and then all of a sudden,
there's Alyssa
staring dead in her eyes,
and it's like...
- Before we go on, Phi Phi
obviously has a lot to say.
- I mean, if you want to act
all foolish
in front of the cameras,
we could,
but you said yourself
it's not personal, it's drag.
These are my opinions.
- So why couldn't you
say that to me, though?
- I didn't need to.
I was sitting there--
- You're that girl.
I knew you were.
- You know what?
You're looking foolish
by sitting there
and acting like a child.
- So you know what?
- So you can do that
and that'll be cute. I'm done.
- Let me just respond
to this real quick.
I ain't never been nobody
to not be 100 to the face.
I didn't throw you or you
under the bus.
Did I say everything I said
to you to y'all?
Did I not over there?
- You did, you did.
- Thank you.
- All right. You can play
the victim, go ahead.
- Being the victim
of what, girl?
I just sat right there and heard
everything you had to say,
and you didn't say
none of that to me.
I was just in the room
with you.
We grown folk, but okay.
- I think it's funny
that you do want to come in
and play the victim,
because you had no problem
sending me home
last week, girl.
- Oh, I'm nobody's victim.
I had no problem
sending you home.
I gave a reasoning
why I did, too.
- But I felt like your reasoning
was bullshit.
- I say consistency.
It was not personal.
- I didn't say
it was personal.
- That was
a really tough night,
because I was expecting
to go home.
- Yeah, well, and I wouldn't
have let you go home.
- What?
- I feel like
you deserved to stay.
- Last week, the bottom two
were Ginger and Katya.
So are you
basically saying
you wanted me to choose
Katya to go home,
and then you would
nominate yourself
to go home instead of her?
I smell a stunt.
Ginger, she just came off
of winning.
If it was a strategic way,
I probably
would've sent her home.
- Okay.
- I just think my issue
has been standing there
hearing that I throw
people under the bus.
That's not me.
That's not my gig.
Never has been.
Never will be.
- I said I felt.
Now, if you want
to sit there and talk shit
about how I'm feeling, then that
just speaks on your character.
I said I felt, coming
from sitting there--
- Relax, Phi Phi, relax.
Take a deep breath, sweetie.
- Don't try to play
the victim, boo.
Alyssa's trying to play
this little victim card
in front of everybody,
and I'm not buying that.
Girl, you threw people
under the bus.
You're just upset
that I called it out
and you had to hear
that I called it out.
- Everything I heard
and knew about her,
I'm glad she validated it.
- You can say
whatever you want,
but you know what,
I played fair.
I played who I thought Ru
was gonna go home,
so do not get mad
because I said
that I was gonna play it
that way.
You choose to do what you want
with someone else's words
and let them affect you,
and that's exactly
what she's doing right now.
You can't get upset
because you were eliminated
and someone had their opinions
on why you should be gone.
- Miss Phi Phi
is getting defensive.
Here's my thing.
I don't mind
all the theatrics,
but if you gonna be loud
and rowdy-rowdy
and think you're
a bawdy-bawdy bitch,
stand up and be one.
But, girl,
don't be weak sauce.
- It's about to get
real interesting.
- The winner of "RuPaul's
Drag Race AllStars"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
a coveted spot in
the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize
of $100,000.
-  Drag Race,
may the best woman
Best woman win
- Back to the back, back,
back, back, back, back, back.
I'm here!
- Welcome back.
- Well, hello to you!
- So we were the top five,
and now we are
the top nine again.
We don't know
how this is gonna go down.
I don't know
what's going on.
I'm just here to look
pretty, that's it.
- Hello, hello, hello.
Oh, my God.
Welcome back, strangers.
- Hey.
- It's time
for the returning queens
to get their revenge,
and I can't wait to see
who gets the last laugh.
- Oh, God.
- Because for this week's
AllStar maxi challenge,
you'll be doing
a stand-up comedy show,
and you'll be doing it...
in pairs.
- Oh, ho, ho, ho.
- The top two
returning queens
will lip sync for $10,000
and the power to give
one of the bottom queens
the chop.
But most importantly,
get the right to return
to the competition.
#RevengeOfTheQueens
- I'm good with this.
I'm good.
- And one other
small little detail.
Tomorrow,
you'll be performing
in front of a live audience
packed with
Drag Race Aluminati.
- Oh, ho!
- You know,
the queens you beat out
to make it here
on "AllStars."
- Oh, God.
If we don't get pelted
with rotten vegetables,
they're just gonna be
sitting there stone-faced
with their eyes crossed,
giving us the middle finger.
- Now, the returning queens
get to pick
their comedy partner
from those
still in the competition,
starting with
the last queen eliminated.
Alyssa Edwards.
- I need a redo,
so I pick Alaska.
- Ooh.
- Girl, I choose Alaska
because I have something to
prove to her as a partner.
I'm gonna make it count.
- Ginger Minj.
- I'm gonna pick my BFF,
Katya.
- Oh, thank God.
(laughs)
- Tatianna.
- I think I'm gonna go
with Detox.
I picked Detox
to be my partner
because she's funny,
she's dirty,
and she's not Phi Phi
or Roxxxy.
Choices.
- And Coco Montrese,
who do you choose?
- I'm gonna go with Phi Phi.
- Phi Phi.
Roxxxy Andrews,
since no one picked you,
you'll be working solo
as the emcee of the show.
And if you win,
you will have the power
to chop a bottom queen
and decide which one
of the eliminated queens
gets to return.
- What shit!
- Can we start over?
(laughs)
- Gentlemen,
start your engines
and may
the best AllStar win.
- So we know
what my character is.
I'm Ru's cousin
from the projects.
- I think I'm just gonna do
my ghetto chola.
- Okay, that'll work.
- I'm not good at writing
standup comedy.
But I was thinking, like, maybe
we could pick apart our flaws.
- I'm fine with that.
- And we can talk about
how I'm no longer orange.
- Girl, and I went
from orange to fudge.
- You went from orange
to fudge.
(laughs)
- And they think
you have many faces,
that type of thing.
- I'm gonna be honest
with you.
I think it's only one person
in this room
that feels that way
about me.
and I think
that's bullshit.
Like this beef with Alyssa.
I didn't come here for that.
I mean, I've worked so hard
with how to control things,
and I almost let someone bring
me back to that unhappy place.
- Yeah, but this the thing.
Focus on you, 'cause mama
got to go to work.
I really don't want
to get into this conflict
between Alyssa and Phi Phi
'cause I'm trying
to get back in the game.
Oh, these girls.
Oh.
- Coming up...
- I'm so glad that I got
to you in time, though.
- Girl, in time for what?
- Oh.
Mama, did you forget?
I have the audition today.
- Time out.
You got to make it funny.
- Bea and I met
at our friend Patty's
Pooches with Prolapse
garden party.
(bleep) were out.
(RuPaul laughs)
- So Ru tells us in our
maxi challenge this week,
the girl that has been
eliminated who wins
is going to be sending home
somebody who's already here.
So it's their turn
to get their Ru-venge.
- So the last time
we were paired together,
you ended up being in
the bottom and going home.
- You got me.
- I don't know
who sent you home.
Whoever did, I will never
forgive them.
- No, girl.
Even though Alaska chose me
to leave the competition...
- Alyssa Edwards.
- I still have so much
mad respect for her,
and I feel like the respect
is mutual between us.
- Okay, I think we need
to play to your strengths.
- Yes.
- Your strengths
are off-the-cuff buffoonery,
responsive, like you're--
- (laughs)
- Yes, exactly.
- Let's do it.
- For this challenge,
I really want Alyssa
to have the freedom
to go off on Alyssa
Edwardian tangents,
'cause that's when
she's really funny
and that's when
she succeeds.
- You make an outline,
I can go with it on the fly.
Now, I'm gonna have
my cleft notes.
- Cliff's notes.
Like the person's name
is Cliff.
- Cliff's?
Who told you that?
- I read them.
They're books.
- Yes, exactly.
- (laughs)
- Hi.
- How are you feeling?
- Hosting is what I do
and I can do my best...
- Right.
- On my own.
I don't want
what happened last week,
as far as the teams,
you know,
somebody outshining me.
And I would really love
to win this
just to prove it to myself.
- Yeah.
- Winning at being pretty
in challenge, I get it.
That's what I do.
Being funny
and showing that I've grown
would mean even more to me.
- You know how to
fuckin do this shit.
- Oh, girl.
- Katya and Ginger Minj.
- Hi.
- Don't walk that fast.
I have asthma.
- So today, we have a coaching
session with Ross Matthews
and special guest Chelsea
Peretti, who is hilarious.
I love her.
- (Russian accent)
Good evening, everybody.
My name is Ekatarina
Petrovisamochkiva.
I flew here all the way
from Russia,
and, boy, are my arms
covered in track marks.
- (laughs)
- And I flew here
in first class,
because unlike some,
I actually made it
to the top three of season 7.
- All right, stop.
What is the idea?
- So it's like
we're friends,
but I'm like the Russian hooker
and she's the--
- Southern country belle.
We kind of based it
on the fact that
a lot of fans
were saying to her,
"Why are you friends
with Ginger"
She's a bitch."
- You should explain that.
- Yeah, like people think
we wouldn't be friends
'cause I'm a this
and I'm a that.
So that'll really set
the stage of who you are.
- As different
as those two things can be.
- As different as
those things can be--
- No, no,
I'm just saying like...
(all laugh)
- I am so grateful
to be going into
this challenge with Katya.
This is just the pairing
that I need
for a successful week
for me.
- My name
is Lydia Ladybits.
- And I'm Beatrice Backdoor.
- Bea and I met
at our friend Patty's
Pooches with Prolapse
garden party last year.
- Everyone was wearing
pink socks.
- Mm-hmm, yes.
The assholes were out.
(laughs) I took
the whole family to Key West.
- Isn't that
the gayest place on Earth?
- I got to learn a lot
about the Key West culture.
- Like what?
- They love AIDS.
- Wha--wha--what?
- Lemonades, limeades,
orangeades.
- Hearing aids?
- Of course.
- Oh, okay.
- Maybe.
- It's a risk.
- It is.
There was a lot of crassness
going on here.
- Yeah, I think
you should lean into
the socialite thing
a little bit more.
- Because if it's
the same note over and over
of how can I
gross you out...
- Okay. Choices.
I've got a lot
on the line here.
I don't want my failure
on Snatch Game
to be my defining moment
in this competition.
So we really have
to work this one out.
- Girl, it's nothin' on,
goin' on out here, honey.
- I'm so glad that I got
to you in time, though.
- Girl, in time for what?
- Oh, mama, did you forget?
I have the audition today.
I'm planning on leaving
this life behind me.
- You should let me do
your makeup.
- You'd do that for me?
- Time out.
So that's great.
- Okay.
- But you gotta make it funny.
- Let's just go with it.
- I can't go with it
if I don't know where I'm going.
Um, okay.
- Let's go with the original.
- Whatever you say.
- Okay.
How's that singing career
going?
- (off-key) Mi, mi.
Jumping from car to car
- Whoa, whoa.
I think I got something.
- Oh, what's this?
- It's a key since
you can't seem to find one.
- Oh.
- All right.
That's good.
That's a joke.
Oh, my God,
you need jokes.
- I'm not Bianca del Rio,
you know.
This stuff just doesn't
come out of my mouth.
Somebody's gonna be leaving
and somebody's
gonna be returning.
There's a lot
of pressure now.
Okay.
- I could tell Phi Phi
ain't all there right now.
And I think that fight
with Alyssa
is still on Phi Phi's mind.
Let it go.
- Can we talk?
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, what I said
last week,
it was just how I was
feeling in that moment.
- The only thing
that bothered me is, like,
I've never been one to like
throw people under the bus.
When, in fact,
people in your season,
that's exactly what they said
you did the whole season.
- No, actually, if you ask
everybody and they admit it,
even Alaska, that Sharon
threw me under the bus.
I didn't throw anybody
under the bus.
- Here's my thing.
If someone's gonna own up
to being the bitch role,
just be unapologetic.
- But that's not what
my intentions were.
- But you were
the name-caller.
You called me a victim.
- Okay.
Well, from my side,
that's what it looked like.
And you know what, the costume
thing, let's be real.
Have they not said
already before,
like, it's okay
'cause it's you.
You can fart on stage and
they're just gonna be like,
oh, it's okay, it's you.
- But let's be real.
We all got different drags.
Alaska's drag
wouldn't look good on me.
- I'm not saying that,
but--
- Your drag
wouldn't look good on me.
- I feel like my words
are getting twisted.
- No, I didn't--
- That's not what I mean.
- I think Phi Phi
is so talented,
but she is spending
so much time
second-guessing
everything she does.
Is it gonna be liked?
Is the fans gonna receive it?
Is she getting
a redemption story?
Girl, breathe and let it go,
because all that matters
is you just being you
and showing your creativity.
Look,
we can squash it, girl.
I love what you do,
so I'm like,
I don't want to sit there
and fight with you.
- Done.
Now give me a hug.
This is stupid
and I'm glad it's squashed
and I'm glad
that we were able to find,
like, this happy medium.
Like, we can agree
to disagree.
Now get away
from my station.
(laughs)
- That was just like Obama
hugging Donald Trump.
Uh-uh. I ain't buying it.
- Coming up...
- This one right here
has more fish
than an all-you-can-eat
seafood buffet.
- I'm sure you know
all about the buffet,
you know,
because you're fat.
(RuPaul laughs)
-  Cover girl, put the bass
in your walk
Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk
Head to toe,
let your whole body talk
Cover girl
- Whoo!
(applause)
- Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul's
Drag Race AllStars."
And tonight, the whole family
is back together.
This week,
we challenged our AllStars
to perform standup comedy
in front of an audience
overflowing
with Drag Race royalty.
And, tonight,
the returning queens
have a chance to earn their way
back into the competition.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
(cheers and applause)
- Hi, everybody!
Well, I'm gonna be
your hostess and emcee.
I'm just gonna start off
with saying I'm sorry.
So how many of y'all
saw season 5?
Season 5
"RuPaul's Drag Race?"
(cheer and applause)
You saw the roast?
Yeah, I sucked.
I sucked more than Michelle
Visage at a truck stop
with a roll--with a--
with a glory hole, right?
So listen, I'm here to,
you know, just struggling.
Another thing I struggle with
is my weight.
Anybody struggle
with weight?
- Whoo!
- Yeah, girl, I mean,
I just don't know
how to get rid
of those extra pounds.
And these damn airports.
You know, the bags
can only be 50 pounds,
and it costs a lot of money
to looks this cheap, you know.
But I'm so excited.
Are y'all ready
for some real comedy?
- Yeah!
(cheers and applause)
- 'Cause I'm dying up here,
ladies and gentlemen.
Now, I'm not the funniest.
(all laugh)
- You killed that one, sis.
- First up out of the gate,
besides myself,
is these two girls.
One thing that they do love
is the color orange.
Coco Montrese
and Phi Phi O'Hara!
(cheers and applause)
- Whoo. Hey, daddy.
- Oh, my God, coquita!
There you are!
How's everything out here
on the strip tonight?
- Oh, girl, it ain't goin'
too good, honey.
The last John I sat on,
whoo, I had Mexican food.
It wasn't that good.
- Oh, man,
I'm so sorry to hear that.
But I have a little favor
to ask of you.
- What you want, girl?
- Think you could do
my makeup?
- Sit down.
I got my good stuff.
- Oh, my God,
I'm so excited.
You know, every time I'm on like
your social medias and stuff...
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm always looking
at your pictures
and I'm like, oh, my God,
no filters.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay, well, first tell me,
what is the first step
in this, you know,
coquita makeup tutorial?
- First, you gotta take that bag
of cheesy chips, girl.
- Okay, okay.
- Crush it up real good.
- Then you gotta--you--you gotta
just take it and beat that face.
I mean, girl,
you got to beat it.
Beat it
like you stole something.
Girl, what's this audition
for anyway?
- Oh, well, I'm gonna be
an actress.
- Girl, I hope it's not
a musical.
You know, any instrument
you play, you gotta blow.
- Oh, that's not true, mama.
I've been writing
a lot of stuff.
(off-key)
Jump in a car
And jump out
The cops will come and put
their hands on the hood
- Oh, oh, oh, girl,
hold on, hold on.
Hold on, girl.
I got something for you.
- What's this?
- I got you a key.
- A key?
- 'Cause you can't seem
to find one, girl.
- Coco and Phi Phi are not
so much doing a comedy routine,
but a live-action
off, off, off, off Broadway
theater production
of Hookers at the Point.
- Coming up...
- Alyssa, describe
Michelle Visage in one word.
Go.
- Beast!
(silence)
(RuPaul laughs)
- Hey there.
What seems to be going on?
- (laughs)
- So Roxxxy
was bombing up here,
so yeah, she asked me
to come
and finish the show for her.
You don't want to see
any more of her, right?
My name is Tosha Salad.
I was on Season 5
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
Do you remember?
I am so excited to be here.
I just got off
the best Italian vacation.
I was over in the beautiful
Thousand Island
on a beautiful ranch.
And let me tell you,
I flew in just to try
and save her ass.
Are you ready
for some more comedy?
Are you ready? Are you ready?
Are you ready?
Ladies and gentleman,
she is the blue cheese
to the other one's crumbles.
Make some noise.
This is Alyssa Edwards
and Alaska!
(cheers and applause)
- My name is Alaska,
just like the state.
- My name is Alyssa Edwards,
and this definitely
ain't nobody's secret
that this gigarama
is completely full
of buffoonery, wiggery
and straight-up tomfoolery.
(laughter)
- Totally.
Alyssa, we're in the company
of some amazing queens tonight.
- Where?
(laughter)
- Ouch.
Detox and Tatianna are here.
- The Hills Have Eyes,
part 2, the remix.
- Bam.
Alyssa, describe Michelle Visage
in one word. Go.
- Beast.
(laughter)
- Burn.
Alyssa, I want to thank you
so much
for being
my partner tonight.
Don't worry.
If drag doesn't work out,
you'll always have
something to fall back on.
Your back rolls.
(cheers and applause)
- These next two girls, let me
tell you, they are so nutty.
Besides Wal-marts--
walnuts and almonds,
these are my favorite nuts,
ladies and gentlemen.
Make some noise. This is
Ginger Minj and Katya.
(cheers and applause )
- Hello.
It's not the first time
she's gotten clap
from a room full of people.
Well, hey, y'all,
how are you?
You know, I'm so excited
to be here tonight
sharing this stage
with my BFF Katya.
(cheers and applause )
Now, I know most of you
might be sitting out there
asking yourself, self--
that's what you say.
You say, self, now how does
a delicate, petite,
little cross-dresser
for Christ
become best friends
with a disease-riddled,
low-rent Russian whore?
- You see, I spend most
of my time on my back,
while she tries to find
someone to shave hers.
- It's funny
'cause it's true.
Seriously,
this one right here
has more fish than an
all-you-can-eat seafood buffet.
- That's funny, Ginger.
I'm sure you know all about
the buffet, you know,
because you're fat.
- Shut up!
I will turn you into
immigration, Balki, all right?
- But through it all,
we have plunged head first
into the most beautiful
friendship,
and we have never
looked back.
Mostly because
she doesn't have a neck
and she can't really
turn her head.
Thank you all so much.
Good night.
- No, bitch, get back here.
I got asthma,
but I will catch you!
- Ladies and gentlemen, do I
look a little slimmer to you,
like I lost some weight?
Do you want to know
my secret?
I started using
light dressing.
Get it?
- We got it, girl.
We got it.
- Okay. Next up, well,
one of these girls,
she is so fishy, she is
the sardines in Caesar dressing.
The other girl prefers
uncut carrots in her salad.
Make some noise.
This is Detox and Tatianna!
(cheers and applause)
- Well, hey, hey.
- Hello, hello.
My name is Lady Ladybits.
- And I'm Beatrice Backdoor.
Thank y'all so much for coming
to tonight's event.
It's a benefit for babies
battling bulimia.
- And I already see
there's a bevy
of beautiful bitter bitches
already here
hitting the buffet.
Bea and I met last year
at Patty's Pooches
with Prolapse Garden Party.
We did.
- The rosebuds
were in full bloom.
- We were out, literally.
Especially this one's date.
- Date? I came alone.
- You came with
Carlos the gardener.
- When?
- Well, what?
You were blowing
saliva water balloons.
I know you guys are here
giving your time
and your money
to this lovely benefit for
teeny tiny, teeny tiny tots.
But I just want to know
when you're gonna have
some teeny, tiny tots
of your own there, Bea.
- I've always wanted some.
My doctor keeps telling me
that my testi--
that my ovaries
are just getting in the way.
You know, I've always wanted
to tell you something.
There's a secret behind the
woman that you see here today.
- Oh, no, is there really?
- Oh, this is hard for me.
- It's okay, dear,
spit it out.
No matter what
you're about to tell me,
you will always be in my eyes
by best girlfriend.
- You see... (lower voice)
I used to have braces.
- Oh! Bea!
You are incorrigible, Bea.
We'll see you next year.
Oh, ho, no!
That Sally Field, that cunt
lied to me about the Boniva.
- Come on, Boniva.
(cheers and applause)
- Ladies and gentleman,
did you all enjoy the show?
Say yeah.
- Yeah!
- We want to thank you guys
for coming out tonight.
And if you can't laugh
at yourself,
how in the hell are you
gonna laugh at somebody else?
Can I get an amen?
- Amen!
- Thank you. Good night.
- Coming up...
- Your punchlines were there
and you delivered them.
- I didn't want it to end.
- It was work.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Welcome, AllStars.
It's time for
the judges' critiques
starting with
Roxxxy Andrews.
- During the show, I thought
your entrance was strong
and then it was like someone
took the needle off the record.
- With a roll--with a--
with a glory hole, right?
- And some of the jokes
just didn't land.
- Then you enlisted the help
of Tosha Salad,
which you get kudos for,
but you were the only one
who was solo.
You really could've stolen
the show from everybody.
- Up next, Coco Montrese
and Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Coco, I think your makeup
looks fantastic.
- And Phi Phi, I'd turn up for
anybody with a Shanaynay nail.
(all laugh)
- I will say you had
some funny jokes in there,
but for me, it turned into,
like, a scene study
instead of
a comedy routine.
- Yeah, we wanted to go
a different route,
like that "SNL" skit type of
thing instead of just standup.
- I get it,
but it turned into
more of like
an Afterschool Special.
- Hmm, okay.
- Up next, Alyssa Edwards
and Alaska.
- I thought the two of you
probably worked together
the best as a team.
Alyssa, you are comedy gold.
All you have to do is go...
and purse your lips
and I'm entertained.
- And Alaska, smartly,
I think you didn't let
Alyssa steal the show.
You know, you had me trained
to look back to you
for that zinger.
I mean, this is a show
I would've paid to see.
- Up next, Ginger Minj
and Katya.
- I liked your relationship
as partners.
You had some good zingers.
- But I think
you were so focused
on the competition
part of it,
I wish I would've seen
a little more joy.
Just...it was work.
- Katya, this jacket
is giving me everything
that I could possibly need
from 1983.
- It's giving me shingles.
(all laugh)
- But there's no relationship
between the two of you.
Even if there would've been
one piece of teal on Katya
or one piece of black
on Ginger,
something to sort of say,
like, hey, we're a team.
- Up next,
Tatianna and Detox.
- I would like to start
by saying
you made my face hurt
from laughing and smiling,
and that is a feat
because I haven't felt
anything on my face in years.
Tatianna, you gave us that ditzy
Stepford Wife fundraiser,
which I loved.
- And De, the character
of Lydia is so funny
and you had so many jokes,
but you almost
couldn't hear them
because of the accent
you were putting on.
- But your punchlines
were there.
You believed them
and you delivered them.
- The material,
the delivery, the wardrobe,
I didn't want it to end.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
Based on the judges critiques,
I've made some decisions.
Alyssa Edwards and Alaska,
Tatianna and Detox,
you are the top AllStars
of the week.
(applause)
You've each won a couture gown
from S&L Designs,
designed by Sasha Lauren
valued at $2,000.
Katya, you are safe.
That means Roxxxy Andrews
and Phi Phi O'Hara,
you are the bottom two
of the week.
Ginger Minj, Coco Montrese,
I'm afraid we must
say goodbye once again.
- When it hits me
that I do not get to come back
to the competition, it hurts.
It's not an easy pill
to swallow
to be told thanks,
you did a great job.
Now go home again.
- Alyssa and Tatianna,
as the returning queens,
you'll lip sync for $10,000,
the power to eliminate
one of the bottom queens,
and the right to return
to the competition.
So while you queens
deliberate in the workroom,
the judges and I
will do some scrapbooking.
Thank you, ladies.
You may leave the stage.
- So, girl, why don't you
go ahead and sell yourself.
- I don't want
to sell myself.
I really respect
the both of you,
and if you win the lip sync,
choose how you feel fit.
And if you win the lip sync,
- Yeah. You'd rather have
your work speak for you.
- I respect that.
I'm just saying, I'm gonna beg.
I am not too proud to beg
for $100,000.
I'm not that girl.
- Okay.
Well, you know what?
The girl that I am
is not gonna beg somebody.
- I don't really get
why explaining to someone
why you should stay
in this competition
would be considered begging.
You gotta let a bitch
know why you should stay.
That's completely ego
talking.
- Everybody knows,
obviously,
I'll say whatever the fuck
I want to say.
- You do, yeah.
- And my real feelings
is I don't--
I don't feel I need to beg.
- I'm gonna be honest
with you.
To me, if I was a fan,
you know what I would say?
Is she fuckin
in it to win it?
- If that's what
you're questioning, bitch,
I want to be here.
I don't feel I need
to kiss anybody's butt
to stay here because
if you look me in the eyes,
you would see that I have
fire and passion
for this competition.
- I want to tell you,
though,
I know last week we were
heated with each other.
- Yeah.
- I celebrate what you do.
- Thank you.
- And I wish you luck, girl.
May the best woman win.
- True.
- Like Ru said, you know, no T.
- Okay.
- I'm not holding a grudge
against Phi Phi
when I'm deliberating.
I'm definitely gonna take
into consideration
the consistency level,
the critiques,
and how well
they sell theirself to me.
Girl, I'm gonna keep it real
with you.
Last night, when I walked from
that door to get that trophy,
I didn't come here
for that trophy.
You didn't either.
Roxxxy, girl,
you can set over there
and own that to this group.
Just let's all stand up
and fight for it
and say, I want to be here.
- I do.
- Do you want to be here,
Roxxxy, in the top three?
- More than anything I can ever
explain to you right now.
- Then I'm gonna
keep it real with you.
You had the hardest job.
You didn't even have
a second opinion
to ask is this a good act.
Here's the thing.
They've both
been in the bottom.
They've both won.
Roxxxy's also won
one of the lip syncs.
It's hard making
this deliberation.
I have a connection
with both these two gals,
and we've shared
this experience.
We've traveled together,
we've performed together.
But I understand
the responsibility
of this competition.
- So how's it going?
How are you feeling?
- You know what?
Alyssa and I had a talk,
and she was like,
do you want to be here?
And I was like, yes,
of course.
Obviously I fuckin
want to be here.
At the same time, like,
I don't want to beg.
I was only in the bottom once,
and every week,
I've been getting better
and better and better
and I won last week.
I think, honestly,
I fuckin killed it tonight.
So I was like, all right,
we did it.
- Yeah.
- Well, I'm glad
you're in the top again.
You guys
were funny up there.
I was worried about
the Detox thing.
I'm gonna be honest
with you.
It was really hard to hear
what Detox was saying
with the accent.
- Well, what are you
trying to do there, girl?
It was really good,
but, like, you couldn't hear
anything that Detox was saying.
But she told Detox
you were funny,
but Tatianna
wasn't very funny.
Ooh, bitch.
Phi Phi is playing
a little motherfucking game.
- You better be changing.
- Oh, I will.
- Yeah.
- Trust and believe.
- Do it.
- Hey, I totally enjoy
Phi Phi.
She's become
a really good friend.
But if you're gonna play a game,
girl, play it right.
- These pinking shears
are amazing.
- Oh, my God,
that's gorgeous.
- Does anybody have
another furry ball?
- Not one that I can detach.
- Eew.
- Silence!
Bring back my girls.
- I'm real close
to just pulling
an eeny, meeny, miney, moe,
to be honest with you.
It really ended up being
a neck and neck decision for me.
- I done weighed it all out
and I know the decision
I'm gonna make
and I'm gonna say bye.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Welcome back, ladies.
Two top AllStars
stand before me.
Ladies, this is your chance
to impress me, win $10,000,
and the power to give one of
the bottom queens the chop.
But most importantly,
the winner will earn the right
to return
to the competition.
The time has come
for you to not only
lip sync for your legacy,
but to lip sync for your
(echoing) life.
God, I love saying that.
Good luck
and don't fuck it up.
-  I've been looking for
a driver who's qualified
So if you think
that you're the one
Step into my ride
I'm a fine-tuned
supersonic speed machine
With a sunroof top
and a gangster lean
My engine's ready
to explode, explode, explode
So start me up
and watch me go, go, go, go
Get you where
you wanna go
If you know what I mean
Got a ride that's smoother
than a limousine
Can you handle
the curves?
Can you run
all the lights?
If you can, baby boy,
then we can go all night
'Cause I'm zero to 60
in 3.5
Baby, you got the keys
Now shut up and drive,
drive, drive, drive
'Cause
you play that game
Got what I got
Baby, don't stop,
it's a sure shot
So step inside
and ride, ride, ride, ride
Ride, ride, ride, ride
Ride, ride, ride, ride,
ride, ride
So start me up
and watch me go, go, go, go
Get you where
you wanna go
If you know what I mean
Got a ride that's smoother
than a limousine
'Cause I'm zero to 60
in 3.5
Baby, you got the keys
Now shut up and drive,
drive, drive, drive
Shut up and drive,
(applause)
- Ladies,
I've made my decision.
Tatianna...
you're a winner, baby.
- All those good feelings.
I'm feeling all of those.
- And Alyssa Edwards,
you are also a winner, baby.
- What?
- Con-drag-ulations.
You are both back
in the competition.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
- Yes.
- I'm giving you each
a tip of $5,000.
- Thank you.
- And you both
earned the power
to eliminate
one of the bottom two.
- So you mean to tell me
if one of them's
got my lipstick
and one of them's
got Phi Phi's,
we're both going home?
Ooh.
- With great power
comes great responsibility.
Alyssa, which queen have
you chosen to get the chop?
- I think you're both great
entertainers and competitors.
However, tonight...
I chose
Phi Phi O'Hara to go home.
- Tatianna.
- This was a really difficult
decision to make,
but with that said,
I went with...
Phi Phi O'Hara.
- As it is written,
so it shall be done.
Phi Phi O'Hara,
you are an AllStar.
Now...sashay away.
- I love you.
- Fuck them bitches up.
(laughs)
Thank you.
- That's okay. No.
Bye. Love you.
Mwah, mwah.
Mwah.
Yes. Yeah, of course, yeah.
- Phi Phi,
I tried to hug you, though.
- You know what, it's
always okay to make mistakes,
and just know that you
can always grow from them.
It's never the end.
You can always start over.
Love you all.
Phi Phi O'Hara,
jump in a car
(all laugh)
Honestly, I don't feel
I deserve to be eliminated.
Tatianna's decision, eh.
She hasn't been here, so it
doesn't really surprise me.
But, Alyssa, yeah.
I mean,
it's kind of hypocritical.
She always tells people
it's about consistency,
and then you're
gonna get rid of me
when I've only been
in the bottom once,
Roxxxy, three times.
But you know what,
let's be real.
I fucking killed it.
Do I get this?
Like, could I
at least sell this thing
for, like, $10,000?
(scoffs)
- Con-drag-ulations,
AllStars.
Now, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen in here?
- Amen!
- Now let the music play.
-  Throw your hands up
Time to get down
Down, down, down, down
Throw your hands up