- Previously
on "AllStars..."
Transform your loved one
into a member
of your royal drag family.
(all laugh)
Katya.
- You're giving us something
like they would wear in
Real Housewives of Minsk.
- Detox.
- The strongest
family resemblance.
I mean, it's unbelievable.
- Alaska.
- I think this
was a bit lazy tonight.
I expect more.
- I fucked up this week, man.
I fucked up.
It fucking really
fucking sucks a lot.
- Detox,
you're a winner, baby.
(applause)
- Yay.
- Which queen have you
chosen to get the chop?
- I chose Alyssa.
I'm sorry.
I can't send him home.
- Alyssa Edwards,
sashay away.
- (sighs)
- Girl.
"I love you all
always and forever."
- I can't believe Alyssa
went home.
- She to me is the most
memorable creature
to ever walk through
that door.
- It was
a very tough decision,
because I was like
how my supposed to say goodbye
to one of my best friends?
And it would be like
I'm the one
who sends
my best friend home.
- Ru was legitimately gagged
when you sent Alyssa home.
- I chose Alyssa.
I'm sorry.
I can't send him home.
- It's a controversial
decision.
Based on the overall
performance,
Alyssa should have advanced
to the final four, not Roxxxy.
- So, Katya, I know
that we both had
a difficult decision
to make.
- Yes, we did.
Roxxxy, I chose you.
And I'm going to look you
in the eye and say this
so you know that I mean it.
I do not have a personal
vendetta against you.
Here's the thing.
I can't send you home.
You've been slaying
the competition.
Roxxxy's been in the bottom
so many times.
I'm going by who I think
is the strongest for the finals,
and that to me is Alyssa.
- I'm still here
to prove myself.
Thank you, Detox.
Like I'm going to fight
to the bitter end.
- And you, crazy,
your little temper tantrum,
I was so surprised.
- Season 5, I was never
in the bottom two,
so I was never standing there
having my heart race like that.
It was really scary seeing
almost this whole thing
be taken away
in one instant.
I really wanted and needed
to be in this final four.
I need it!
- Somebody who's going
to win this competition
is somebody
who can handle themselves
and still be able
to go out there
and do their fucking job.
And right now,
you're crumbling.
Obviously I want my sisters
to do really well,
but obviously I want
to do better than them.
I'm here for the kill.
- The winner of "RuPaul's
Drag Race AllStars"
receives a one year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
a coveted spot
in the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize
of $100,000.
-  RuPaul's Drag Race
-  May the best woman
Best woman win
-  Everyone
can be someone
- (sighs)
All: Go outside and hook.
- I'm in the motherfucking
top four.
H-E-A-R, bitches.
I am here!
- Hello, hello, helleer.
(cheering)
- Come on, shoe.
Final four.
Con-drag-ualtions.
This is it.
- Thank you.
- For your grand finale
challenge,
you'll be forming
and AllStar supergroup.
- Ooh.
- Seduction.
- God, no.
First, each of you
needs to write
your own rap lyrics
for RuPaul's new bitch track
"Read U, Wrote U."
- Ooh.
- Then you'll head over
to the studio
to lay down your vocals
with AB Soto.
You'll each make an extra
special guest appearance
on RuPaul's podcast
"What's the Tee?"
(cheers and applause)
After that, you'll work
with choreographer Travis Wall
to come up with a showstopping
production number.
And tomorrow
on the main stage
your supergroup
will make its world debut.
#DragRaceFinale
Gentlemen...
All: Start your engines,
and may the best woman win!
- I'm working on
my award winning rap track.
- I love to rap.
I feel like Lil' Kim.
- It's really important to do
well in this final challenge.
I need to show the judges
that I can pick myself up
after defeat.
- All right, guys.
I'm gonna go record.
I am so excited
to record my rap,
and I'm excited
to show the judges
why I am still here, honey.
Yeah!
- Good luck.
- Slay them hos.
- Hi.
- Hi, Roxxxy.
I'm AB.
For this challenge,
I'm looking for
lots of personality.
I want the queens to show me
their own unique
individual style. Here we go.
-  I'm Roxxxy Andrews,
and I'm here to make it clear
I know you love me, baby,
that's why you brought me here
I'm really feeling
this flow right now, girl.
You can't tell me
I'm not Nicki Minaj.
You're going crazy
And seeing two
- And stop the track.
Your energy's a little low.
A little more energy
and a little more sexiness.
- Oh, my goodness,
look who's here,
our first guest,
Alaska, the 49th state.
- I'm excited
to do this podcast
with RuPaul and Michelle.
- So what are your wishes
for your career and life
post "AllStars?"
- To create a space
where the rules aren't
so rigid about gender.
And if we can laugh
about it a little more,
the world will be better
and we can get
to a "Star Trek" future.
- Hmm, that sounds delicious.
- Yeah.
- I want to talk about
how you were in the bottom
the last challenge,
and I seemed to detect
a little bit of a tantrum.
- I'm sorry if I was a brat.
- Now, it looks like
Rolaskatox
is back together again.
- Well, we're not actively
practicing Rolaskatox-ism.
It's very unnerving
to hear RuPaul
saying the dreaded word
Rolaskatox.
- We're going to take our
selfieonastick.com selfie.
There you go.
- It's upsetting.
-  You a basic asshole,
and it's your time to go
So, bitch,
let me show you the door
Lenin in the streets,
Dostoyevsky in the streets
Oh, fuck I fucked up
that part.
I'm like the sugar free
French Vanilla Ice of drag.
This is gonna sound great.
Rapping's hard.
- It is hard. Yeah.
- AB's giving me
really good feedback.
He's like
blinking his eyes a lot.
Lenin in the streets,
Dostoyevsky in the sheets
Which I think in Dominican
means, good job.
- Whoops.
Okay, here we are.
The finale.
- Can you believe it?
- I pinch myself
every fucking day.
- And when you pinch yourself,
can you feel it?
(all laugh)
You know, it's funny.
Here we are
at this point
in the competition,
and here's Rolaskatox
back together again.
- Ish. Ish.
I love them.
I mean, there are certain times
when I'm like, oh, okay.
I don't want to hang out
with you for too long.
- Now, you've always had your
own look, your own aesthetic,
but this season
it is so refined.
Where'd you get
your sense of style?
- Growing up loving
Teri McGlone
and like
the Vogue Fashion Awards.
I just always loved fashion.
- Yeah, I can tell.
- I don't like
to toot my own horn,
but easily I have killed
everyone in this competition
when it comes to the runway.
I pissed
all over that thing.
- Ready?
Look. My tits look huge.
- Stunning.
(humming)
It was really fun.
- My podcast was consumed
by Rolaskatox
and my brattish behavior
last week.
- We're at the end.
LIke the finishing line
is right ahead of us,
and here we are again.
- And it's the same people.
- Yeah.
- I'm so glad Katya's
here with us, too.
- She's such a weirdo
and I love it.
- Um...
It hits me all at once,
this is Rolaskatox
and one other person.
This is not good.
It just all is seeming very,
very oddly, strangely familiar.
The last time
it was the three of us
and a lovable weirdo.
We all saw how
that fucking worked out.
So I don't want us to get
fucking all comfortable
because I'm really like
trying to stay fucking focused
so I can win
this fucking thing.
- I think you're coming way out
of left field for this, though,
because I don't feel
like anything's similar
to our last time
being in this position.
- It really means a lot
and I want to win
because I did the best.
- I feel the same way.
I'm definitely vying
for my spot on the top
because I feel like
I really deserve it, too.
And I've worked my ass off
and I want to fucking win
just as much as you do,
so...
Alaska is acting ridiculous.
- I'm lost.
- It's very self-centered.
I'm not gonna win because
I'm hanging out with you guys.
Well, fuck you.
I'm trying to win.
We're all trying to win.
You know what I mean?
- Yes, I know what you mean.
- It's not just about you,
girl. Sorry.
- Coming up...
The winner of "RuPaul's
Drag Race AllStars..."
Is...
(RuPaul laughs)
- Alaska is flipping out
right now.
I need her to just let this
little shit go, girl.
You need to fight
to the end.
I don't want the bullshit
with the Rolaskatox thing
to deter you from what you've
been doing in this competition.
- I know.
- Stick to what you're doing.
That's stress
you don't need.
- I know. It's just...
I know.
(sobs)
You guys are my friends,
and I love you so much.
And I don't want to feel
like that
is a disadvantage
to us winning.
- Everything
is so different this time.
- So just worry about you
getting to the finish line.
We love you.
- And I really am glad
you're here.
Rolaskatox creates
a reaction in me
because
it was a stupid thing.
I can't live in regret.
In life, really
the only thing you can do
is take experiences
that are embarrassing
and turn them into the things
that make you stronger.
Trash into treasure, girl.
- Oh, my goodness.
Look who just walked in.
- Hi.
- Hi, Katya.
- So now
your mother was here.
I thought
she was just a dream.
- Isn't she amazing?
- She really is.
Thank God dad's a sociopath,
so there's balance.
- Well, there's balance.
And you know, that's the secret
of life is having a balance.
- Absolutely.
And you know what?
This season, it started out
so much better.
But still, there was
a little bit of like--
- The voices?
- One thing that I've been
coaching myself with
is like I sort of
name that voice.
I call her Brenda.
- Uh-huh.
- And I just say,
you know what, Brenda?
Shut the fuck up.
- I love that.
- Yeah, so...
- I've found
that what you do is
you develop another voice that
sort of counteracts that voice.
- Yeah, Carl.
- Wait a minute.
It's not Hot Carl, is it?
(all laugh)
- Being excited
to talk with Ru
is new sensation for me.
Our rapport is fantastic.
So this is the moment
that I know how far I've come
in the competition.
- Gorgeous.
- Yay.
- Hi-ee.
- Hey, Alaska.
Are you ready?
- I'm so ready.
I'm excited.
- Yes.
All right, from the top.
-  Hey, girls,
my name's Alaska
I got a tiny little
question to ask ya
Who's that bitch
that's on the top?
Oh, wait, that's me,
hey, porkchop
- And cut. I love
your signature Alaska sound,
but make it a little bit
more animated.
- Today's been really
emotional for me,
but I have to get back
in the game.
I need to come in
absolutely nothing held back.
- Cue music.
-  Legacy,
remember my name
'Cause you're gonna see me
hanging in the hall of fame
- So good.
I love that.
- Hi, Roxxxy.
- So now,
how are you different
than you were whenever
you were here before?
I have no idea
how long ago that was
because I have
no concept of time.
- I realized that you have
to live with your mistakes
and you have to grow
from them.
- I know that you didn't like
how you came off in that season
'cause all these bitches
want to say,
oh, I was edited
unfavorably.
It's like, no, bitch,
you said it, you did it,
that's how it was.
- I own up to everything
I said on the show.
I couldn't believe
how messy I got.
So coming onto "AllStars,"
it was like the--
oh, my God,
I got a second chance.
- When you have your eye
on the prize,
you do whatever it takes
to win.
And sometimes, it's not
the nicest move, but you do it.
- What's funny
about this whole interview
is you've said nothing about
seeing my makeup this close.
- It's hard to look at you,
you're so beautiful, stunning.
- Why, thank you. Jeez,
it's like pulling teeth
to get a compliment
out of these girls.
Ooh, child.
- This is my crowning look.
- (laughs)
- What are you thinking about?
- What if
Roxxxy Andrews wins?
- Um, I would be confused.
- If she wins, it's gonna be
a fucking uproar.
- If we're racking up points,
then no, she's not going to win.
- Mm-hmm.
- I won three.
I was in the bottom
two times.
- I was in the bottom
one time.
I've won three challenges.
And your track record has
been bottom once, won four.
- Yeah.
- But it's not going to be
a math equation.
I mean, or maybe it is,
I don't know.
- I won the most, but winning
doesn't make you likeable.
And I've been very focused
and I've been very driven,
but those aren't
likeable qualities.
Having passion and having drive
is a double-edged sword.
It's easy to look cutthroat
and ambitious,
but on the other hand, it's
the biggest strength I have.
- If you didn't win,
would you be devastated?
- Well, I mean,
I've been there before.
But I want to win.
How about you?
- I want to win.
- Me, too.
- From the top.
Detox coming at you
with a slow verse
Imma speed it up,
I had to shut it down first
I feel really confident
about this rap challenge.
And the only thing that's
holding me back would be myself,
and I don't plan
on holding myself back.
D to the E to the T to
the O to the--hold it--
X
- Detox is definitely the
strongest queen I've seen today.
Oh, my God, so good.
- I feel so gangsta,
you guys.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
(both laugh)
- Hi-ee.
- Yeah.
- It's time for us
to learn our choreography
for our stage performance
with choreographer
to the stars Travis Wall.
- Obviously, there's so much
riding on this performance,
so what I'd like to do now
is work with you individually
on your solo parts.
Today, we are doing
lots of choreography.
There's a couple props
involved.
We're pulling out
all the stops,
and this has to be
a showstopping performance.
Pick her up
and get her legs in the air.
- (laughs)
I love Alaska, but we all know
she can't dance for shit.
- We just look like
a chicken a little bit.
Are you flexible?
- A little.
- Maybe.
- What do you want me to do?
- I want you to see
if you can get into
a middle split
on top of him again.
- Okay.
That's ambitious.
- Flick, flick,
and then split.
(all laugh)
One, three, five, seven,
one--
- Oh, I'm so sorry.
As excited as I am to do
this whole chair routine,
the minute I'm up on the chairs,
I start freaking out.
Oh, God.
- I want you to fall
backwards this way.
- Okay. So just trust
these motherfuckers.
- Yes.
- Okay.
It looks easy,
but it's really not.
- Shenae over to him.
Shenae. Wrong foot.
Left leg. Your left leg.
What would you do to him
to get your attention?
- A lot of things.
(all laugh)
- Why don't you
get behind him.
- It's my favorite place.
- Maybe push him down.
- Down into this?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Choreography is hard.
I need some duct tape.
- I've never worked
with you, Katya.
- Yep. I'm not
an actual dancer,
but I am extremely flexible.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
- The idea is you're going
to slide into your right split
and then bring you up.
You want to try that?
- Yeah.
- Slide and up. Nice.
- We can even go lower
than that, you guys.
- There you go.
Slide and up.
Amazing. Love that.
- Shit, oh, my God.
- Five, six, seven,
plie shoon.
- Oh, that feels
fucking sexy.
(all laugh)
- Oh, my God.
Katya is like
a fucking rubber band.
It's very intimidating
because it's something
that's going to be
very memorable to the judges.
- Handstand.
Put your legs together.
There you go.
Now open and go down.
- Oh, that's fun.
Let's do it again.
- Great job.
Yeah, so good.
- Shit, fuck
mother fuck shit.
- Coming up...
- What was
your favorite moment?
- When you were in
the bottom two, Roxxxy.
- Oh!
- Fuck!
(RuPaul laugh)
(RuPaul laughs)
- Yeah.
(speaking French)
- This is our final day.
At this point
of the competition,
there's no holding back.
I don't know
who I gotta move,
but I'm going full force
to that win.
How do you feel, Katya?
- Um, I feel good.
I think one of the things that
I'm most proud of myself for
is making it this far
with you guys
because I haven't had
as much experience
as a professional
post Drag Race girl.
Do you know what I mean?
- Mm-hmm.
- I feel like in the short time
since my season,
I've already grown so much.
And I want to win
"AllStars,"
and objective, scientific
research has shown
that it is totally possible
for me to do that.
What about you, Alaska?
What are you feeling?
- I feel good about how I've
performed in the competition.
I've had moments of going
a little fucking crazy,
and I apologize
to all of you
if that fucked up
the energy of the room
and of this experience.
I was trying to stay
so focused,
and I didn't want to show
any signs of weakness.
One of the things
that I wish
I would've done differently
is I wish I wouldn't
have been quite so serious.
I'm absurd and I'm obsessed,
but I think I'm the best
RuPaul's Drag Race queen ever.
So I want to win.
It's my destiny.
- How do you feel, D?
- I feel really good.
Like, I feel very confident in
everything that I've done here.
I feel like myself,
which is the first time
I've felt like truly me
in a long time.
I would love to say
that if I did not win,
that it would be fine.
But to get this far and to be
so proud of what I've done
and then to still
just miss the mark
would be devastating.
It's been an amazing experience,
and now I just feel bad
that I'm going to have
to crush you guys' dreams.
(all laugh)
- What was
your favorite moment?
- My favorite moment
was when you were in
the bottom two, Roxxxy.
(all laugh)
- Oh!
Which time?
- Damn!
- Oh, my God.
- Fuck.
-  Covergirl,
put the bass in your walk
Covergirl,
Head to toe,
let your whole body talk
Covergirl
(applause)
- Welcome
to the grand finale
of "RuPaul's
Drag Race AllStars."
Tonight, it's just family.
Michelle,
can you handle this?
- Of courrr.
- Carson,
can you handle this?
- I think I can.
- Todrick,
can you handle this?
- Well...
- And Ross Matthews.
- Ru, I don't think
I can handle this. Whoo!
(all laugh)
- This week, we challenged
our final four
to write and record lyrics
to my new bitch track,
"Read U, Wrote U."
And now they're ready
to dance their padded asses off.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
(music plays)
-  Lookie here
Listen up
I'm the one
(echoing) Ow!
-  Hey, girls,
my name's Alaska
I got a tiny
little question to ask ya
Who's that bitch
that's on the top?
Oh, wait, that's me,
hey, porkchop
You're butt-naked,
the rest is drag
But your face
just needs a paper bag
Give me a challenge
and I'll impress you all
Changing the game
like my name's RuPaul
Line them up
front to back
I'm sending bitches home
like a heart attack
Mess with me and you'll
wind up in a casket
I'm Dorothy, you're Toto,
get in the basket
I'll read you
down beneath the ground
Could you hold my purse
while I snatch the ground?
Legacy, remember my name
'Cause you're gonna see me
hanging in the hall of fame
-  Got to read it
-  I'm the one, one, one
I'm the one, o-one, one
I'm--I'm the one
-  Detox coming at you
with a slow verse
Imma speed it up,
I had to shut it down first
Killin' bitches so hard,
need a pink hearse
I ain't saying I'm the best,
but I ain't the worst
You see me shining
I'm trying to take this
primetime
I see you whining and crying,
take that to Lifetime
So epic that it's poetic,
I spin it all the time
Oh, baby, you look pathetic
with that nursery rhyme
You can't stand me?
I don't blame you
If Ru is number one,
I'm number two
You disagree,
well, that's on you
Eyes on the chalkboard,
I'll spell it out for you
D to E to the T to the O
to the--hold it--
X
Naomi Campbell-ing
these hoes to the ground
Next!
Now I'm, now I'm
with you, with you
Told you, told you
Now I'm, now I'm
with you, with you
Told you, told you
Now I'm with you
- You been read.
-  I'm the one, one, one
Ow!
I'm the one, o-o-one
-  Katarina Petrona
Zamalawchickova
But your dad
just calls me Katya
Katya with
the long blonde hair
Always keep them
coming back for more
You a basic ass ho
and it's your time to go
So bitch,
let me show you the door
'Cause it's me
who's getting laid
And I'm always
getting paid
The only high class
Russian whore
I'm a scorching hot mess
in a skintight dress
That's a rash,
not a herpes sore
Lenin in the streets,
Dostoyevsky in the sheets
Baby, are you ready
for this Cold War?
Katya Zamalawchickova
-  Wrote you, told you,
now I--now I read you
Wrote you, told you,
- You been read.
-  I'm Roxxxy Andrews
and I'm here to make it clear
I know you love me, baby
That's why
you brought me here
Was a bitch on Season 5
I'm gonna make it right
Give me
a sewing challenge
And I'll give you
what you like
I'm full of tricks, baby,
just like on Halloween
A room full of monsters
and it makes me want to scream
I have to get this right
so you don't waste your time
Not like my comedy,
I'm killing on this rhyme
I'm gonna show you
what I can do
You're going crazy
and seeing, too
It's not fault,
you can't blame my game
All these other hos,
but they're all the same
-  Wrote you, told you,
now I--now I read you
Wrote you, told you,
- You been read.
I'm the one, one, one
-  Wrote you, wrote you,
told you, now I--
told you, now I read you
Read you, read you
- Oh, my God.
- Whoa!
- Wow.
- Coming up...
I feel proud
to pass my legacy on
to the four of you
standing here right now.
But it's time
for your final critiques.
(RuPaul laughs)
- The category
is AllStar Glam-o-rama.
First up, Alaska.
- It's Glamorgan Fairchild.
- Yeah.
- I want to show the judges
that I can do more
than just convey humor,
camp in my runway looks.
I'm wearing a gold dress,
and gold is like trophies.
- So what's
her Glitter handle?
- (laughs)
Detox. So glamorous.
- It's Kylie Man-ogue.
- Usually Detox
is very severe up in here,
but this is a softer side
of Detox,
the softer side of Sears.
This is the best
I've ever felt here.
- This is a slam dunk
for me.
Nothing but netting.
- Yes.
- Katya.
- Wow.
- Ooh.
- Do the bustle.
(all laugh)
- I am the confident,
complex regal matriarch
of a Russian mafia family
enjoying
her last days on earth
before she is set ablaze
by jealous relatives.
- I know where I'm hiding
if there's an earthquake.
- Yeah.
(all laugh)
- Roxxxy Andrews.
- Victor Victorious.
- I'm giving them the full
thick and juicy fantasy.
Showing off
the Andrews goods.
I am getting
my complete entire life.
- That's not
a sequins dress.
That is
a crystal extravaganza.
- These have always
brought her luck.
- Welcome, AllStars.
It's time
for your final critiques.
First up, Alaska.
- Let's start
with this look tonight.
The hair, the makeup,
flawless.
- Thank you.
- You know I'm a big fan of rap
and hippity hop music.
Your lyrics
were my favorite.
They were so funny
and thought out.
I remember in Snatch Game
and I thought to myself,
everyone else in this
competition better watch out.
And you've kept
that level up for so long.
And I think you had a moment
when it all caught up
with you a little bit,
and that's rough.
But way to come back
tonight.
- Thank you.
- I think you've done
a pretty amazing job
this journey.
You've come a long way since
auditioning for Season 1.
- Up next, Detox.
- You are the rapper
of the group here,
and I think your delivery
was outstanding.
- How about
the chair-ography?
It was really good.
- You looked like you were
just living your life.
- And then it culminated
with this look tonight.
So beautiful.
- You're living my ballerina
fantasy right now.
One of us had to.
(all laugh)
- Up next, Katya.
- Your performance tonight
was genius.
- I love when you do like
the athleticism stuff.
I'm like
so unfamiliar with it.
(all laugh)
- I love that you did
like a Russian rap.
- It's a rash?
What did you say in your rap?
- It's a rash,
not a herpes sore.
- Oh, if I had a dollar...
- Right?
(all laugh)
- I think
your sense of humor
has been spectacular
the whole season.
And it's always
a little bit off.
- And insanity
is part of why we love Katya,
but it doesn't justify
this skirt.
Um, so...
- You're nuts. Listen, yes,
it's not exactly the way
we've seen it done before,
but neither are you, honey,
and that's why we like you.
- Thank you.
- Up next, Roxxxy Andrews.
- This look is everything.
It's like J-Lo and Liberace
had a baby, okay?
- Okay.
- Rapping
is not Roxxxy's forte,
but I thought
you had fun with it
and it looked like
you had a--
- So much.
- Yeah.
- When that fan came on,
I was sold.
- I'm such a sucker for
a this way and a that way
and just--I'm so jealous.
Someone clip an extension on me
stat so I can try it.
- Ladies, I am overcome
with emotion right now
looking at the four of you.
And I couldn't be more proud
to know that you
are part my legacy,
seeing each of you
so beautiful.
And I'm telling you
right now,
I feel so confident to pass
my torch on to the four of you.
No matter what happens
on this stage tonight,
you are a star forever.
Coming up...
One final question.
Why should you
and not your fellow AllStars
be inducted into
the Drag Race Hall of Fame?
(RuPaul laughs)
- Ladies,
one final question.
Why should you
and not your fellow AllStars
be inducted into
the Drag Race Hall of Fame?
Alaska.
- Yes, I've thrown fits.
I've thrown tantrums.
Perhaps I'm just a RuPaul's
Drag Race obsessed super fan.
Was I obsessed when Chanel
was Miss Absolute Mandarin?
(slurps)
Yes, God.
Was I obsessed when India,
Farrah and Phoenix
walked into the workroom in the
same wig and the same outfit?
In the words of Gia Gunn,
absolutely.
For it is
my fanatical devotion
and my undying love
and respect
for the world that RuPaul
has created here
that puts me wig, head and
shoulders above any competitor.
- Oh, my God.
- Look into your hearts
where you will find
that the only inductee
into the RuPaul's Drag Race
Hall of Fame
is I, Alaska.
Hallelujah!
Yes, God! Oh, brrr!
(laughter and applause)
- All right.
Detox, same question.
- All I can say is how
magical of an experience
this has been to me.
It's been full of joy and tears
and perseverance.
And I don't want to throw
these girls under the bus,
but...
I will say that I feel like
I have shown
such an amount of growth
and maturity and humility
that I want to just
travel around the world
and share that with everyone
and say that
it will get better.
No matter how crazy or weird
you may be,
that I could be some kind
of beacon of hope
for all those weirdoes
out there.
And thank you.
(all laugh)
- Katya.
- (Russian accent)
Charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, talent.
What do these qualities
have in common?
I don't know.
I'm not a scientist.
(all laugh)
I stand here
a charismatic woman
of grace and dignity
with a unique sense of humor
and point of view.
(no accent) In Season 7,
you let me show the world
that I'm good enough,
and here...
you let me
believe it myself,
and I can't thank you enough
for that.
Like they say in Russia...
(speaking Russian)
- What does that mean?
- I have
a carburetor outside
that I just have to do
some work on.
(all laugh)
- Thank you, Katya.
- Thank you.
- All right, Roxxxy,
same question.
- I came onto "AllStars"
to prove to America and myself
that I can compete
and do it the right way.
And if you decide
to crown me,
I just want you to know
that I will never give up.
I'll always keep fighting
and, you know,
I can stand here
so proud of myself.
I won
when I walked in the door,
and every week after that,
I was winning.
(sobs)
I can't tell you not to crown
one of these three girls
because
they're so phenomenal.
But I want you to crown me.
(all laugh)
- Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
While you untuck
in the workroom,
for the first time
this season,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
Just between us girlfriends,
let's just break
the shit down, okay?
Alaska.
- Every single week,
she's come
and she has slayed
the competition.
- She understands
how Snatch Game works.
Either you know it
or you don't.
- Yep.
- And she got it.
- She's so prepared,
so smart.
Her Bette Davis
was off the chart.
- What I didn't expect
from Alaska
was when she fell that she would
be so bitter or childlike.
- Yes, she had a bad week
when her mom was here,
but if you go
by the numbers,
she would probably still
get a 98 out of 100.
- She is a package.
She is ready for it.
- Let's talk about Detox.
- From a fashion
sensibility point,
she blew everybody
out of the water.
Every look, week after week,
told a story and told it well.
- I could see Detox
being the creative director
of a fashion house
because she's got
that kind of an eye.
- I like to watch somebody
who makes me feel something.
- She shows her heart
and her ass.
- Yes, she does.
- Yes.
- All right.
Let's talk about Katya.
I mean, what a difference
from Season 7 to "AllStars."
- I love how zany she is.
I love that she takes risks.
- It's funny
and it's quirky,
but it's a very smart
sense of humor.
- And she does it
in a fun, fresh way
that invites everyone
to the party.
- And the potential
is endless, really.
- Endless.
Roxxxy Andrews.
- I think she's kinder, softer,
sweeter and more polished.
And she was even
really polished in Season 5.
- She was.
- Yeah.
Not the greatest actress,
but I could look at her
all day long.
- She's been
in the bottom five times,
but she's one of those girls
that have such stage presence,
even if she's sucking,
you can't take your eyes
off of her.
- All right. Silence!
I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Welcome back, ladies.
The winner of "AllStars"
will be inducted
into the Drag Race
Hall of Fame,
receive a crown and scepter
designed by Fierce Drag Jewels,
and win a grand prize
of $100,000.
Ladies, each week
I've named the top two AllStars,
but after
this final deliberation,
three of you
have earned the right
to lip sync for your legacy.
Alaska.
Detox.
Katya.
You are the top three
AllStars of the season.
Roxxxy, my dear,
this is not your time,
but you are and will
always be an AllStar.
Now sashay away.
- I'm a little disappointed,
but I'm walking away so proud.
I got to show
who I truly was.
I will forever be thick
and juicy.
Bye-bye.
(laughter and applause)
- Ladies, this is your
last chance to impress me
and prove to the world
that you belong in
the Drag Race Hall of Fame.
The time has come
for you to lip sync
(echoing) for your legacy.
Good luck
and don't fuck it up.
-  If I were your woman
And you were my man
You'd have
no other woman
You'd be weak as a lamb
If you had the strength
To walk out that door
My love
would overrule my sense
And I'd call you back
for more
If I were your woman
And you were my man
Mm, baby
-  Girl
- I should be America's
next drag superstar
because I'm the complex
female character.
I have the passion
do to something different
and disturbing
and challenging.
-  When she lets you fall
- I want to win "AllStars"
because I'm obsessed
with "RuPaul's Drag Race."
I can't think of anyone
who could possibly
have their picture
on that hall of fame
besides me.
-  You're a part of me
- I should be America's
next drag superstar
because I want to be
the queen of the weirdoes.
I know I joke about it
all the time
where I say
the crown is mine,
but I really feel
like it's fucking mine.
And I deserve it.
I want it so bad.
-  If I were your woman
If you were my woman
-  Here's what I'd do
Never, never, never
stop loving you
- Wow.
(applause)
- Ladies, the time has come
to crown our queen.
The winner of "RuPaul's
Drag Race AllStars,"
the next queen
to be inducted
into the Drag Race
Hall of Fame is...
Alaska.
-  You're a champion,
greatest of them all
You're a champion,
never gonna fall
- (gasping)
- Con-drag-ulations.
You're a winner, baby.
- (sobbing)
- Here you are, darling.
On behalf of your millions
of fans around the world,
my queen, I bow to thee.
Now, is there anything
you'd like to say?
- Anus-thing is possible.
- Now, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen
up in here?
- Amen!
- All right.
Now, prance, my queen.
- Okay.
- Prance!
-  You're a champion,
greatest of them all
- I'm feeling so proud
and so honored
and so grateful.
I couldn't be more happy.
-  You're a champion
and you'll always be a hero