- Previously
on "AllStars..."
You'll be performing
a lip sync extravaganza.
Herstory
- Do you think that
the girls in the top
are going to stick
to our idea of
what do the judges
have to say
and that's who
we're going to choose?
- I'm iffy of one of them.
- Who?
- Alyssa.
- Alyssa Edwards,
you're a winner, baby.
Which queen
have you chosen
to get the chop?
- Sometimes
being in the bottom
could just be
a one night kind of gig.
So the queen
that I'm sending home,
that's Ginger.
- Ginger Minj, sashay away.
- Whoo, shit.
- Oh...
- Good old Minj Ging.
- What we said
we were gonna do
was eliminate the girl
who got the harshest critiques.
I just feel that Katya got
harsher critiques than Ginger,
so the vibe
in the room right now
is kind of like
what just happened?
- I wanna say that
both of you guys
got feedback that was
kind of on the lower end,
but when
I really talked to you guys
after looking at last week
and the week before
and taking all that
into consideration,
I think you're consistent
and I think you have
so much more to give.
I think
you just fell short today.
I think what Ginger does
is fabulous,
but I didn't feel like it
was fair send to Katya home
'cause I was going
based off consistency.
Katya, I know
you looked at me
and you were
a little surprised,
but you should never
be surprised.
I think
you deserve to be here,
and that's just me
following my heart
and keeping it real
with you guys.
I think Ru would have
taken into consideration
what she just did the week
before in the Snatch Game.
She hit a homerun,
so tough decision to make.
I stand by my decision 100%.
Detox, how did you feel?
I mean...
- I based my decision
off of the critiques.
- Okay.
- And my decision was you.
And you know how much
I fuckin live for you.
- Of course.
- And this is a fuckin
tough decision to make.
- I hope that that you see
that just consistency for me--
- No, and I do.
- Me personally,
I would still go with you
only because
I said from day one
I was going
to play it that way.
Alyssa switched it up.
It's pretty obvious.
Katya, should have
gone home tonight.
I feel that
if Ru was up there judging,
she would have
actually sent you home.
- I'm struggling
with the thought
that maybe the other girls
don't think this was
a fair elimination.
- Katya, you're here.
Let it all go.
I'm very confident
with my decision.
We can all agree
to disagree.
Alyssa keeps bringing up
consistency, consistency,
and I don't know
which way she's gonna go.
So if she wins again,
who's going home?
- The winner of "RuPaul's
Drag Race AllStars"
receives a one year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
a coveted spot
in the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize
of $100,000.
With extra special guest judge
Nicole Scherzinger.
-  "RuPaul's Drag Race"
-  May the best woman
-  Best woman win
- New week, new me.
- Yeah, baby!
- Yep.
- We're walking
into the workroom,
and I notice that
there's a little letter
written by old Ging Minj.
- "PLay a fair game
and be proud of your choices,"
- So is she implying that
the game hasn't been fair?
- You know why?
I think because--
Look, let's be honest.
We all said
that we were gonna pick
who Ru said was,
you know, the weakest link,
and Alyssa switched it up.
- No, I didn't switch
nothing up, baby.
- No, I'm saying--
Will you let me finish?
- No, but let's choose
our words wisely.
- I am.
You didn't let me finish.
What I'm saying
is you switched it up,
which you did,
and in all honesty,
they critiqued you
on your--
Hold on, baby.
Let me finish.
They critiqued you on your
runway and your performance.
- Phi Phi is a little
hung up on the decision
because I think in her head,
she probably could be thinking,
okay, well,
this could affect me.
I was in the bottom
the first time.
There was a lot of factors
taken into consideration,
but I do think I was fair
in my opinion.
I think, you know,
it's hard.
It's very hard,
but I stand by it.
- Katya, how do you feel?
- I mean, you know,
she made the decision.
She feels proud of it.
I'm happy to be here.
End of story. Boom.
- Ha! Take that, everyone.
You're back.
- I am ready to shrug off
the guilt and shame and doubt
like a lice-ridden coat.
- It's going to be interesting
to see what happens
down to the nitty gritty
how fair the game
continues to be played.
- If y'all send me home,
it was rigged.
Riga-morris, girl.
It was riga-morris, girl.
- Who's Morris?
Rigormortis.
- Is it rigormortis?
(all laugh)
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Oh!
(applause)
- You look gorg.
- Ladies, for this week's
maxi challenge,
you'll be starring
in drag shequels.
Parodies inspired by
some of my favorite movies.
#DragShequels.
- Oh.
- All right.
- You'll be working
in pairs,
so first, I want you
to pick your acting partner.
Go.
- All right.
- I look and see Roxxxy,
I look and see Phi Phi,
and I'm thinking,
where the fuck is Detox?
- Well?
- Detox.
So I grab her because
I am not gonna be stuck
with a weak performer
for this challenge.
- All right.
- Now, I've green-lit
the following films.
First up, "Showsquirrels,"
starring Phi Phi O'Hara
and Roxxxy Andrews.
- Yes!
- Next, "Velma and Weezy,"
starring Katya and Detox.
- Yes.
- Last but not least,
"Wha' Ha' Happened
To Baby JJ?"
starring Alaska
and Alyssa Edwards.
To create your characters,
you can use wigs
provided by Weaven Steven.
And if the script
calls for it, the pit crew,
in or out of their
Andrew Christian underwear.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may
the best woman win.
(applause)
- The parody shequel.
Katya and I are assigned
the "Velma and Weezy" script,
which is a shequel
to another
very famous movie
with similar
character names.
Are we doing accents?
- I think so.
- We have to. Yeah.
If you can't eat your friends,
who can you eat?
- (laughs)
- "Showsquirrels."
Mama Versayce, a middle-aged
former showgirl.
- Accurate.
- We chose to make me
Mama Versayce
and Phi Phi's gonna be
Lil' Versayce.
- No, you were just
a tired-ass showgirl.
- You were just
Now go back to obscurity
where you belong.
- Oh, my God.
I've heard that somewhere.
- I feel like
I'm typecasted.
- Okay, let's get
these costumes together.
- No pressure,
but like I'm the only one
left of the girls that
has not been in the top yet.
What if we switched it
and like you were
the big pageant girl?
It's all about taking chances
and doing something.
Switching the roles
is a brilliant idea.
I'm telling you, I just think
that would be so much funnier.
And then you--
- You're scaring me.
I just get scared
of those things,
but I know that you're good
at what you do.
- I really think we should.
- Okay.
- I know it's a risk,
but I'm gonna take it.
And Roxxxy has no choice
but to follow.
- Coming up...
- We take the crown.
We wear the shaw.
- Cut.
Um, what's a shaw?
- Huh?
(RuPaul laughs)
- I was never a whore.
I was a dancer!
- You were suh--
[stammers]
- That's not the line.
- For this week's
maxi challenge,
Alyssa and I are assigned
"Wha' Ha' Happened
To Baby JJ?"
(evil laugh)
For me,
there's no question.
I have to play Baby JJ.
She's old and crazy
and evil.
Where do you think you're going,
you miserable bitch?
- No!
- There's really no choice.
Sorry, Alyssa.
I work alone.
- I hope we win.
I'd like to be
at the top two once.
Thank you.
- How does that
make you feel?
- I'm a little intimidated,
to be honest.
Since Alyssa changed it up,
which--even though she
wants to pretend she didn't.
- You feel like
she flipped the script.
- I don't feel.
She did flip the script.
I'm not saying I don't want you
here, but you know what I mean?
- No, no, no, no, no.
I completely get it.
- Like, is that gonna be,
like, oh, well,
Phi Phi's never been in the top,
so let's get rid of her.
So I don't know.
We'll see what happens.
I'm a little frustrated.
I don't want
to leave the competition
until I've had a chance
to make the world
fall in love with Phi Phi.
And I need a win now
to prove that I need to be here.
- Howdy.
- Hi, Katya and Detox.
- Hi, y'all.
- So pretty.
- So it's time
for Detox and I
to perform in our shequel,
"Velma and Weezy."
And I have never felt more sexy
in my entire life.
- Your parody shequel.
And action!
- We don't need money,
Velma.
We're zombies.
- We need the cash
to get drunk.
Fuck. Buy booze.
- Yeah, we need the cash
to buy booze.
- Um, start over, okay.
- Bitch,
this is the shequel!
- Uh!
Fuck. I forgot.
- Cut.
Get those lines down
so the back and forth
can be more organic.
- Have fun with this.
One of the first rules of acting
is reacting to the other people.
- I'm not totally
in the moment.
I just think, what the hell
would Amy Sedaris do?
- And action!
(knock on door)
- You order room service?
- No.
- Oh, motherfucker.
- (laughs)
- 'Cause suddenly
I'm very hungry.
- Whoo-hoo!
- Weezy, you zombie skank,
you motherfuckin--
I just fuck you.
If I wasn't dead already,
I'd--
- And cut.
Best one yet.
- Great.
- Fantastic.
Hello, Alaska and Alyssa.
- Hi.
- "Wha' Ha' Happened
To Baby JJ?"
Action!
- Guess who's in a wheelchair
now, Bland?
- You know
I haven't been able
to use my legs
since the accident.
- And cut.
Alyssa, you're scared
of your sister,
but you still have a voice,
so you don't--
Every (mumbles)
Let us hear
what you're saying.
- Okay.
- Action!
-  Camptown ladies,
sing this song
-  Doo-wah, doo-wah
- Cut!
- It's doo-dah.
Doo-dah
-  Doo-dah
- Correct.
You just have to say...
- [both] Doo-dah, doo-dah.
Here we go.
-  Camptown ladies
sing this song
-  Doo-wah, doo-wah
-  Camptown racetrack
five miles long
- Cut.
Doo-dah.
- Doo-dah.
- Oh, to do--
oh, da doo-dah
- Welcome,
Phi Phi and Roxxxy.
- Hi!
- "Showsquirrels."
All right. Here we go.
- Action!
- I used to love
eating dog chow.
- Ugh. So you're telling me
that not only be conce--line.
- I thought being conceived
in a swimming pool.
- So you're telling me
being conceived in a swim--
- No. Ugh.
I thought being conce--
- Oh. Ugh.
I thought being conceived
in a swimming pool was gross.
(gags)
- Cut.
- I just want you
to give me more character.
I feel like I'm seeing
a lot of Roxxxy in there.
I think that
you could do something
to push it to another level.
- Okay.
- And action!
- We take the crown.
We wear the shaw.
- Cut.
Um, what's a shaw?
Roxxxy?
- Huh?
- We take the crown.
We wear the shaw.
We wear the shaw, the...
- Sash.
- How you spell it?
- Sash?
- S-A-S-H?
- Yeah.
- Sha...sha...
- Sash.
Oh, God. This isn't another
sequins moment, is it?
- I'm afraid so, honey.
- That is a wrap
on "Showsquirrels."
- See you on the runway.
- In the end, I want to say
that we
might not be the best,
but Team Phoxxxy did A-OK.
- Coming up...
- You're gorgina.
- You did a great job.
- Little things in this
situation have to matter.
(RuPaul laughs)
-  Covergirl,
put the bass in your walk
Covergirl, put the bass
in your walk
Head to toe,
let your whole body talk
Covergirl
- Wow.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Welcome to the main stage of
"RuPaul's Drag Race AllStars."
Star of the classic film,
"Boobarella," Michelle Visage.
- And the TV show,
"Leave It To Cleavage."
- (laughs)
Style superstar,
Carson Kressley.
I love what you're wearing.
- Thank you.
(misprounouncing) It's Versayce.
- (laughs) The incredible
Todrick Hall.
Now, how'd it go
with my girls yesterday?
- Ru, I'm gonna have to give
your girls two thumbs up.
- Try three.
They'll enjoy it much more.
(all laugh)
And the devastatingly gorgeous
and talented Nicole Scherzinger.
You finally made it.
- Yes, my love.
You're giving me
fierce tiger fish
with that dress right now.
- Thank you.
So glad you're here.
Now, this week,
we challenged our queens
to star in movie shequels.
And tonight, it's double trouble
on the runway
because the category
is two looks in one,
inspired by Violet Chachki.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
-  Gotta go now
-  Sexy, sexy
- Up first, Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Ooh, she's crowning.
- She is.
- That's a nice ascot.
- Ah, yes.
- Beautiful.
- I'm super proud
of this look.
I came up with
the design myself,
and I feel gorgeous.
- If it's yellow,
let it mellow.
(all laugh)
- Roxxxy Andrews.
- Flamenco.
- Sombrero.
- Yes.
- Oh!
- Yes, please.
Selena in the house.
- Hello.
- If anybody knows anything
about a reveal,
she, me, her, she does.
I'm serving Latina diva
on this runway.
- Bitty, bitty, bum-bum.
- That's a Spanish fly girl.
Katya.
Ooh, Barbara Eden.
- I dream of weenie.
- Oh, there she goes.
- Oh!
- Oh, thank you.
- (laughs)
- I'm giving you full health
by a Sharon Tate fantasy.
It's Rosemary's babushka,
and I feel (deep voice) amazing.
- Not tonight, Satan.
Not tonight.
Detox.
- Dark lady.
- Sexy.
- Oh.
- Oh, yes.
Oh, and there's more.
- Every time
I step on the runway,
I want it to be
something different.
I want to blow them away.
- Oh!
- And that's the fun
of drag to me.
- Kung-pow.
- Ancient Chinese secret,
huh?
- (giggles)
- Here she comes,
Alyssa Edwards.
Ooh, the Le Croix poof.
- Yes.
- What?
- I'm ready for my closeup.
- Ah.
- Oh, I love it.
- Girl, please. I'm taking
selfie to a whole 'nother level.
Paparazzi who?
Oh, I see why you love me,
darling.
- That is amazing.
- Kodak mammaries.
Up next, Alaska.
What?
It's like a Fellini film.
(gasps)
- What the--
- Oh.
(all laugh)
- It's Little Poundcake!
- Little Poundcake
is the insane pageant girl.
She's stunning,
and I'm really excited
to get to bring her to life.
- I think she needs
some go-go juice.
-  Sexy, sexy drag queen
- Welcome, ladies.
It's time for the world premiere
of your movie parodies.
First, Phi Phi O'Hara
and Roxxxy Andrews
starring in "Showsquirrels."
When last we saw
our troubled showgirl,
she was hitchhiking
to Hollywood
after crashing and burning
in Sin City.
Now, years later,
her own daughter
is a junior pageant queen
bitten by the showbiz bug.
- All right. Five minutes
till the talent competition.
- You heard him.
Only five,
fa-five, five, five minutes.
- Thanks, darling.
- Hey, little Versayce.
I just know you're gonna win
the Wee Little
Miss Pacoima Goddess Supreme.
- That wouldn't suck.
- Now, remember,
Little Versayce,
when you get
in front of them judges,
do some of them dance moves
your mama taught you in Vegas.
- I'm a little too young
for that whorish look.
- Ooh!
But you are a whore, mommy.
- Versayce, how dare you?
I was a dancer. Huh.
- I don't know what the hell
you did in Vegas,
but it sure wasn't dancing.
- I was the biggest star
on the strip.
They could've gotten
LaToya Jackson, Paula Abdul,
but The Stardust
went with me,
and, frankly,
I still got it.
- You are just
a tired-ass showgirl!
Go back to obscurity
where you belong!
- Obscurity?
(laughs)
Now, go on, show them what
you got, Little Versayce.
- Don't worry about me,
mommy.
I will.
- Aah!
(all laugh)
Mommy, how could you?
- I guess you don't...
know me.
- Oh!
(all laugh)
- Up next, Katya and Detox
starring in
"Velma and Weezy."
When last we saw
Velma and Weezy,
they were taking a short cut
to the bottom
of the Grand Canyon.
They may be dead,
but they're still best friends.
- Where is she?
Velma,
what took you so long?
I think I'm having
a nervous breakdown.
- The Quicki-mart
didn't sell brains,
so I ate the clerk's brains
instead.
- Ah.
- Oh, and I robbed the store.
- We don't need money,
Velma.
We're zombies.
Hold on.
I got a great idea.
- Oh.
- Whew.
Selfie!
- Whoo-hoo-ee!
(knock on door)
- You order room service?
- No.
- Motherfucker!
'Cause suddenly
I'm very hungry.
- Whoo-hoo!
If it isn't that handsome
Brad Pitt lookalike
that stole all our money.
What are you doing here, BJ?
- You come back to give us that
money you stole from us, baby?
With interest?
- Maybe he's just here
to see what it's like
to get some head
from the walking dead.
- Bitch, he's mine!
- Oh!
Bitch, this is a shequel!
- Weezy, you zombie skank!
You motherfuckin--
(both shouting)
Aah!
Look what you did!
- Look what you did!
- Thanks, ladies.
- That sexy son of a bitch
took our money again.
- No matter what happens,
I'm glad I got to be
a zombie with you.
- I've never felt more...
dead?
Hey, Velma, do you mind
if I partake
in your little arm here?
- If you can't eat your friends,
who can you eat?
(all laugh)
- Yes.
- Oh, my God.
- That's so cute.
- All right. Up next,
Alyssa Edwards and Alaska
in "Wha' Ha' Happened
to Baby JJ?"
When last we saw Baby JJ,
she nearly killed her sister
Bland on the beach.
But she survived.
Now, 50 years later,
they're still trapped together
at the senior home.
(door creaks)
(beeping)
- Guess who's in
a wheelchair now, Bland?
Just kidding.
You are!
- Baby JJ?
You know I haven't been able to
use my legs since the accident.
I'd escape from you
if I wasn't 109 years old.
- But you are, Bland.
You are!
Look over here.
It's your din-din.
- Oh, no.
- I made your favorite.
Pork chops!
- Aah!
- (evil laugh)
Come on.
We gotta rehearse
for the talent show.
- Oh, my God.
- My music's over there.
- (grunts)
Never mind.
I'm gonna do this one
Acapulco.
(off-key)  Camptown ladies
sing this song
-  Doo-dah, doo-dah
- Hey!
- Ow!
- Sorry, sis, I work alone.
- Somebody help me!
She's emotionally disturbed!
- Where do you think you're
going, you miserable bitch?
- No! No!
- Oh, girl down.
- My sister Bland fell.
Can you help her?
- Of course.
Come on, Bland.
- Oh!
See? Even the nurse
likes you better.
-  Camptown ladies
sing this song
-  Doo-dah, doo-dah
-  You already know
- I work solo.
- Okay.
-  Camptown races
all night long
(applause)
- Now, it's time
for the judges' reviews.
- Coming up...
- You were like
the Dustin Hoffman
of, like, queens for acting.
- You needed a lot of work.
We shouldn't give you passes
because we've all been guilty
of going, that don't--
she's so funny,
that don't even matter.
No, but it does.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Ladies, now it's time
for the judges' reviews.
First up, Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Let's talk about
your runway look.
Each of the looks
individually, hmm, okay.
What I think you executed
so well
was how it converted.
- Mm-hmm.
- That took
a lot of ingenuity.
If this doesn't work out,
you could work at NASA.
- As far as the performance,
you know it's my all-time
favorite movie.
- Yeah.
- And I was literally
so proud of you.
- Oh, thank you.
- Not only did you look
just like Mama Versayce,
but you embodied
the character.
- You did a great job.
- Yes.
I've been trying so hard
throughout this
entire competition. Ah!
And you guys like it,
I don't know what to say.
- All right.
Thank you very much.
Up next, Roxxxy Andrews.
- You're gorgina.
- You are.
Like, I don't even want
to look at you you're so pretty.
- Ah! The outfit.
I want to borrow that.
It's so creative,
so beautiful.
- The bad part for you
was Phi Phi was so strong
that it was hard to keep up.
With you, I think
you had to work harder
and it was
a bit more forced.
- Phi Phi was just
stealing the scenes,
whereas your character
should've been the character
that stole the scene.
And unfortunately, it kind of
got lost a little bit.
- Up next, Katya.
- Let's talk
about the runway.
I didn't think the two looks
were wildly different,
but I liked the humor
behind it.
- Thank you.
- Your conversion told a story,
and I liked that.
- In your movie, I think
that you were in your head
a little bit
in the beginning.
- But as soon as Michelle and I
talked to you, you delivered.
The scene with you and Detox
is my favorite of the three.
- Up next, Detox.
- As far as your scene goes,
you were 100% in
from the beginning.
- And it was really
collaborative.
You worked well
off of each other.
Let's talk about
your Ms. Peking Tuck look.
When I see, like,
a two-for-one look,
I want to see it, like,
you know,
turn from, like, a toaster
into, like, a Nissan Sentra.
So not the most
amazing transition,
but I loved the end result.
- All right,
Alyssa Edwards.
- You needed a lot of work.
I think
the biggest problem for me
was your enunciation,
because nobody understood
that you were saying "nurse".
- Nurse!
- All we heard was Na-a-ah.
- I don't care
about your diction.
All you have to do is, like,
make weird, big googly eyes
and do funny things
with your mouth
and that mumble, aah, aah.
I think your fans
got their money's worth.
I think it was okay.
- As far as the runway look,
I don't feel like
it was a great reveal,
but it didn't even matter.
The cameras everywhere
was just so wacky.
- Can I add
something to that?
Little things in this
situation have to matter.
- I don't care.
I love this look.
It's funny and it's smart
and I like to see stuff
like that come down the runway.
- But we shouldn't
give you passes,
because we've all been guilty
of going, that don't--
she's so funny,
that don't even matter.
No, but it does.
- Thank you, Alyssa.
All right, let's move
on down to Alaska,
tonight on the runway
as Little Poundcake.
Now, Little Poundcake was your
concoction on your season.
- Lineysha Sparx and I made her
for a mini challenge.
- Coming out as Little Poundcake
tonight was brilliant.
You picked the right time
to do it.
You looked fantastic,
and it's so fun.
- The acting was so good.
You were like the Dustin Hoffman
of, like, queens for acting.
- You were born
to play Bette Davis.
All the nuances,
the insanity,
it was just
so, so brilliant.
- Thank you.
- Anything you want to say?
- You're not my real mom
and you never will be.
(all laugh)
- Well, thank you, ladies.
Based on your performances
and your
two-in-one runway looks,
I've made some decisions.
Phi Phi O'Hara, Alaska,
con-drag-ulations.
You are the top two AllStars
of the week.
(applause)
You've each won $1,000
shopping spree at Fabric Planet.
- Oh, fuck.
I'm finally in the top two?
My heart's ready to, like,
jump out of my chest
because I'm so happy
right now.
- Detox, you are safe.
That means Roxxxy Andrews,
Katya, Alyssa Edwards...
You are in the bottom three.
- I'm a little upset
because I don't feel like
I should be in the bottom
this week.
But here I am.
- Phi Phi and Alaska,
each of you needs to decide
which of the bottom three
you'll eliminate
if you win the lip sync.
So while you queens
deliberate in the workroom,
the judges and I will make
prank phone calls.
(ring)
You may leave the stage.
Coming up...
- This is Alyssa's first time
being in the bottom,
but I do believe
that you got the harshest
critiques out of the group.
- We've only had
four challenges.
You've been in the bottom
twice.
- Katya and I both have
been in the bottom twice.
(RuPaul laughs)
- I feel like I should be safe
based off my performance,
but I don't know if the other
girls agree with me or not.
- We have this really
difficult decision
that we're going to have
to be making.
- Do you guys know how
you're going to do it?
- I said from the get-go
I was going to do
what I felt the judges
said was the weakest.
But it really is close.
- I mean, does anyone
who's in the bottom
think that
it wasn't that close?
- This is Alyssa's first time
being in the bottom,
but I do believe
that you got the harshest
critiques out of the group.
- They did like my runway,
and they liked a lot of things
about what
I was doing in it.
We've only had
four challenges.
You've been in the bottom
twice.
- Katya and I have both
been in the bottom twice.
- So that's why I don't feel
that I should go home
because of one challenge.
- Ooh.
- That's how I feel.
- I know that normally
we do one-on-ones.
In my case, I don't know
if I really need to do that.
- I want to do one-on-ones
with the three girls
who are in the bottom.
Thank you
for coming to my office.
- Do you want me to plead
my case really quick?
- Yes, I do.
- All right.
So I stumbled a little bit
getting warmed up
in the challenge,
but then nailed it.
On the runway,
I agree the transformation
wasn't as dramatic
as it could've been,
but I think the overall look
was different and good and fun.
Okay. Thanks, mom.
- Thank you, honey.
Can you send in
the next model, please?
Hi, honey.
- (sighs)
As my partner,
I don't want you to feel
like I let you down.
I really did try.
I took their notes
and I was full-out every time.
Just, I fell short.
- If not you, then who?
- I definitely think
it's one of them two.
They've been in the bottom.
But I don't want
to pick one of them.
I just want
to talk about me.
I was great
in the talent show.
I came prepared
for the Snatch Game.
Got showed up in, you know,
the dance challenge,
and I just fell short today.
That's like if you were
in the bottom tomorrow.
And your development,
I couldn't judge you like that.
So I hope that, Alaska,
you take into consideration
all of the accounts.
- I will, and I have
a lot to think about.
- I understand.
Thank you.
- Oh.
- It's a conflicting moment,
so can you plead your case?
- Yes. I know I wasn't as well
as Phi Phi in my challenge.
Acting's not my thing,
but I feel like I did well
in this challenge.
And I've been in the bottom
twice and so has Katya.
I don't feel like
this is a challenge
I should go home for.
- It's going to be
a really difficult decision.
- I just want you to know that
send me home or not, I love you.
I feel like I should
still stay here
because I wasn't the worst,
so why send me home now?
- I have a question.
Do you have
that little pink thing
that you wore in the video?
- Yeah.
- 'Cause I want to wear that
on top instead of, like...
- Oh, my God, yeah.
Let me
safety pin it on you.
- I have a question,
though for Phifs.
I feel like
when Phi Phi says
that she doesn't need to do
one-on-ones,
it's kind of
a little bitchy, honestly.
It's like
she couldn't be bothered
with having to know
what their opinions were.
Usually we all
take everyone aside
and, like, have our little
pow-wows and one-on-ones.
What made you
come up with the decision
to not do that
with these girls tonight?
- I just don't want people
talking in my ear
and trying to beg me
to stay.
I want to just listen to Ru
and go through my head
and think.
- All of a sudden, like,
this kind of snarky, bitchy
monster is coming out.
It's definitely interesting,
especially for her saying
she wants to avoid that
appearance this time around.
But it looks like
she's just coming back
to how she was portrayed
on season 4.
(telephone rings)
- (old woman) Hello?
- I'm looking for Mike,
last name Hunt.
Has anyone seen Mike Hunt?
(all laugh)
This never gets old.
- Never, never.
- Silence!
Bring back my girls.
- I feel great
about my decision.
I'm constantly
just going in my head,
what did the judges say,
what did the judges say?
I'm sure
the queen that I chose
is not going to take this
very well,
but it's part of the game.
- It's really hard
to contemplate
the idea
of sending a friend home.
I've made up my mind,
but I hope
it's the right decision.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Welcome back, ladies.
Two top AllStars
stand before me.
Ladies, this is your chance
to impress me, win $10,000,
and earn the power
to give one of
the bottom queens the chop.
The time has come
for you to lip sync
(echoing) for your legacy.
- I really want to show Ru
that Phi Phi's a force
to be reckoned with.
- Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
(music plays)
-  What you think, ah
I think I love you, baby
What you feel now
I feel I need you, baby
What you know, ah
To be real
Ooh, your love's
for real now
You know that your love
is my love
My love is your love
Our love is here to stay,
ay, ay, ay, oh
What you think, ah
I think I love you, yeah
What you feel now
I feel I need you
to be real
Got to be real
To be real
Real, real, real
- Yeah!
(cheers and applause)
- Ladies, I have made
my decision.
Alaska, con-drag-ulations.
You're a winner, baby.
You've earned a cash tip
of $10,000.
- Thank you.
- Phi Phi O'Hara,
you are safe.
- Thank you.
- Will the bottom three
please step forward?
Alaska, with great power
comes great responsibility.
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
- As it gets
fewer and fewer,
it gets
more and more difficult.
And so
I hope that this queen,
who I consider
to be my sister,
will understand the decision
that I've made tonight.
So the queen
I've selected...
is Alyssa Edwards.
(sobs)
I'm so sorry.
- Alyssa Edwards,
as it is written,
so it shall be done.
You are an AllStar
always and forever.
- Thank you.
- Now, sashay away.
- I'm so sorry.
I love you so much.
- Don't be sorry, girl.
Well, I was a lovely
fifth alternate.
(all laugh)
Always and forever,
Alyssa Edwards.
I'm going to take
my own advice.
Winning isn't everything,
but wanting to is.
There are so many people that
want to be in this competition,
and I'm
one of the lucky ones.
A true champion
isn't the one
that necessarily
leaves with a trophy.
(alarm)
- Alyssa, it ain't over.
Con-drag-ulations, AllStars.
Now, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
(muffled) how the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
- "It's not personell,
it's drag.
P.S. log off."
Aw.
- Alyssa
was just eliminated,
and it feels like a giant chunk
of the Drag Race tapestry
was just burned out.
- I feel like I sent
my really good Judy
away from here,
and I feel like shit
about that.
- So who did you choose?
- I also agreed.
It was Alyssa.
And can I be
completely honest?
I am sick of hearing them say
you can wear shit on stage,
but it's okay
'cause you're Alyssa.
It really bothered me
and I just kind of felt like
it's not fair that the judges
just let her slide.
If that was me,
I'd get my ass served to me.
It was sloppy.
I think that concept
was cool, but it was sloppy.
And if any of us did that,
we would get read for filth.
It was like she kept saying,
like, you shouldn't send me home
because I've only been
in the bottom once.
And she was too concerned
about saying this is your
second time in the bottom,
you should go home.
What even, like, made that
decision even easier for me
is it seemed to me
she was more concerned
about throwing you two under
the bus during deliberation.
- What? Oh, my God!
- Oh, fuck! My God.
- What is going on here?
- Boom!
- Face crack
of the millennium.
All of the eliminated girls
are standing behind the mirror.
They look mad.
They look really mad.
- What the fuck?
- Oh, shit.
There's Alyssa Edwards.
I'm surprised the bitch
hasn't dove through
the fuckin mirror yet.
- Trust the duchess
when she says this.
Y'all thought you all
had packed me?
It ain't over
just yet, baby.