- Ladies and gentlemen,
for your consideration,
the best of the best,
my legendary children.
Category is "All-stars."
(speaking foreign language)
- My name is Yekaterina
Petrovna Zamolodchikova,
but you can call me Katya.
(snorts)
You may remember me
as the lovable Russian
hooker from Season 7
with the crippling
anxiety problem.
But I'm back with a refillable
prescription for Xanax.
- Yowza, Babe-raham Lincoln.
Pass me the fucking
baby oil, bitch.
- You did
a beautiful obscenity.
- When do I get
to blow them?
I can't say that?
(speaking foreign language)
(laughs and snorts)
During my season,
I feel like
I held back out of fear.
Whenever
anything went wrong,
I wanted to jump off
the hotel balcony.
But this time around, I want to
just spread my legs even wider.
(speaking foreign language)
- Well, this is
hauntingly familiar.
Here we go again.
Rehab is back in session.
My name is Detox
and I am from Season 5,
where I came in fourth.
- Oh, gorgeous.
- Gorgeous.
- Caw caw!
- She is a hot mess.
- Whoa!
- Oh!
- I didn't get my fucking
tag lunch,
and I want it, goddamn it.
- Hey, bitch. Hi.
- I'm really excited
to get to know Katya
because I think
she's bat fucking crazy.
My ass looks good.
- Your ass
always looks good.
- Did you get more
pumped into it?
- No, I've just gotten fat.
(laughs)
I'm here to put my face
in that hall of fame.
Give me the fucking crown.
(laughs)
- All right.
- Oh, my God.
- My name is Alyssa Edwards
and I need, I need,
I need, I need,
I need to get up
in this all-star gig.
Baby, I'm Alyssa Edwards
representing Season 5,
and I was a lovely
fifth alternate.
Thank the lords above.
I'm back, back, back,
back, back again.
(clicks tongue)
Alyssa Edwards, real miss.
'Cause I'm what?
Sick bitch.
(clicks tongue)
- Back rolls?
- Ooh, she has got
my Russia get-up on.
- I love that you're
wearing a cape again.
- You know, I didn't know
if I wanted to be Goldilocks
or Little Red--
- Red Riding Ho.
Alyssa Edwards,
she looks like just she did
when she walked
in Season 5,
just with a little better hair
and slightly less rolls.
(laughs)
- Girl, look at us.
- Get up in the mirror,
girl.
- This is a really good
picture. Okay, okay.
- You cannot have
a conversation with Alyssa
if you're in proximity
to a mirror.
And even if, like, Ed McMahon
had risen from the dead,
presenting her with
a $300,000 check,
she'd be...
(slurping)
One second, one second.
- It's nice to see that
they regrouted the brick.
And, no, I was not talking
about you that time.
- Oh, she already started,
girl.
The shade is knee deep
already, girl, day one.
- (laughs)
- Ooh.
- Riddle me this,
riddle me that,
watch out, girls,
this bitch is back.
I'm Phi Phi O'Hara
and I'm playing a villain.
Get it?
I mean, I'll start
where I left off.
- You look good.
- Thank you, I showered.
- Bitch.
- Hey.
Last time, I had
a lot of built up anger
and stuff in me and I didn't
know how handle situations.
Tired ass show girl.
- At least I am a showgirl,
bitch.
Go back to Party City
where you belong.
- After my season,
a lot of people
had this perception of me,
so it was hard
to get bookings.
People genuinely thought
I would come
and, like,
blow their club up.
So it took a lot of work
to show people
that I'm professional.
I'm just really worried about
kicking your ass off the show.
(all laugh)
No, no,
I've changed my ways.
No sabotaging this time.
My drag has changed.
My makeup has changed.
I stopped tanning.
I want the world to see
that I have changed.
(clears throat)
- Whoo!
- Come on, all-stars,
let's get...this over with.
(all laugh)
Ribbit, ribbit, the glamour
toad is in the building.
- Where in England
are you from, Adele?
- My house.
I flood my basement, bitch.
Aah!
Ginger Minj is back
with a vengeance, baby.
It's a whole new me.
- Aah!
- You better pose,
bathing suit competition.
- Oh, my God, it's good
to see you, diarrhea.
Season 7
got a lot of hate
for being a lackluster
bunch of girls,
so I am here to say,
now, Miss Thang,
we are just as talented
and worthy
as the rest of these girls.
You look so much better with
half of your face covered.
Oh, wait, I'm supposed
to be nice this time.
Everyone looks so beautiful.
I'm wearing a corset,
though.
Apparently, all it takes to win
is a corset, so I bought one.
- Oh.
- Ooh, ooh, ooh.
- We'll edit that out.
- Ooh.
- Will they, though?
Will they?
- No, they will not.
- Thick and juicy's back,
bitches.
- Oh!
- My name is Roxxxy Andrews,
and I still rep
for the girls
who are thick and juicy
'cause even though
I lost weight,
I'm always thick and juicy.
I don't care if I'm 300 pounds
or 200 pounds,
thick and juicy
is Roxxxy Andrews.
I'm so excited
to be here today.
- All that ass. Bam!
- So what has been
your favorite moment
throughout this competition?
- Seeing you
in the bottom two.
On Season 5,
I let the competition
get the best of me,
and I was playing messy.
So I have a lot to prove.
I can compete and win
because I deserve it
and not because
I'm knocking people out
by playing mind games.
- Oh, yes, bitch!
- Oh, my God,
my baby Roxxxy's here.
- Not the Rotox.
- When I saw Detox,
I was like, bitch,
we get to do this again.
That's my girl.
- There's a lot of you
Season 5s here.
- That's funny, because
I think 4 put it on the map.
- Oh. (laughs)
- Okay.
(all laugh)
- Oh, no, ma'am.
- Orange you girls
happy to see me?
- The face crack
of the century.
- Bitch, that was so
three years ago.
- Yeah!
(all laugh)
- Girl, we had
buried the hatch.
We put it in the ground
12 feet under.
She ain't coming back out,
okay?
- Come on, Season 5.
- Yes!
- I am Coco Montrese.
I was the lip-synch diva
of Season 5.
- Girl, you look like
the black PeeWee Herman.
(laughter)
- Girl, look how orange
you fucking look.
- I'm not joking, bitch.
(all laugh)
- Girl, you got
some Dorito fantasy?
- Yes, girl.
- Let me see.
- Look how orange I look.
- I'm not joking, bitch.
- Girl, you're covering
your face in that hat.
Show them that pretty skin.
It ain't that orange.
- Girl, that's
custom couture made.
- In a garage.
- Some girls
don't change their makeup.
It's the same black eye shadow
and the same lipstick.
I am not gonna say no names,
Roxxxy Andrews.
- Greetings.
My message for the human race
is really quite simple.
Hi-ee. Hi-ee.
- Whoo!
- Hi.
- I think I was chosen
as an all-star
because nobody can do
Alaska except Alaska.
But I encourage you to try.
It's fun.
- Aah!
- I just wrote anus.
Little poundcake enjoys
being a straight up
mother-fucking pig.
(all laugh)
I will stand out from
the rest of these queens
because I am more "all"
and I'm more "star" like.
Star-ish. Star-esque.
- Mwah, mwah.
- I just came
from Party City.
I'm the groupon girl.
- Don't we look pretty?
- Yeah.
- Five from 5.
- Oh, girl.
- Yeah, five from 5.
- Season 5 all over.
Last time I was here,
I was concerned
about my relationship
and how people
were perceiving me.
And now, it's just me,
and I'm focused
and galvanized
and ready to take the crown.
- Aah!
- Thank you.
- Morgan McMichaels
walks into the--
Wait, that's not Morgan?
- My name's Tatianna.
I placed fourth on Season 2
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
The suspense
is boring me to pieces.
Tyra is a complete bitch.
What's up, hookers?
- Hey, bitch.
- Kylie Jenner.
- She is beat.
- I think the other queens
are thinking,
all this is really right.
- Girl, how excited are you
to be back up in this gig?
- I'm so ready.
- You're the only 2 here.
Tatianna might be
the weakest link
only because she's kind of
like the old school.
She's from the old batch of,
you know, "Drag Race"
and "Drag" has changed
so much since her season.
- Come on, Season 2.
Let's get sexy!
- Come on through, Season 2.
(all laugh)
- If they'd watched Season 2,
they should know
not to underestimate me,
'cause it doesn't really
work out in the end.
Thank you.
- Meow.
- Yay!
- Oh shit!
- My name is Adore Delano,
and I'm a messy slut.
(laughs)
I'm known
for being really messy.
- Give me one that Logo
will actually sign off on.
- Oh, okay. Because
big dicks are French?
(laughs)
It was very subtle.
I'm a fuckin Libra.
(speaking foreign language)
- Are you cinched?
- Um, I have a hog body
right now.
(rapping)
I'm fucking hood.
I'm from Azusa.
I'll stab a bitch.
(laughs)
- All right.
- Bitch, hi!
- Adore Delano giving you
smell my punani
poetic justice realness.
- Adore Cilantro.
- Mwah, mwah, gals.
Yeah.
I want to look like
a Monster High doll.
My drag sell today
is a bit controversial.
I'm inspired by
the grunge movement,
the riot girl movement
of the nineties,
but a lot of people
don't get that.
They'd like to say that
I'm lazy about my drag,
but I love being
a nonconformist.
I mean, I can't crowd surf
in a corset.
- Who's ready to make teams?
- No.
- Please, no teams.
I fuck belong by myself.
(all laugh)
(alarm)
- Oh!
- Ooh, girl.
- She's already
done had hers.
- I've heard that shit
in my dreams.
- My queens,
the best of the best.
Welcome to "All Stars."
At this point
in the competition,
I have to ask the question.
Who deserves to go home
tonight and why?
What, too soon?
(laughs)
- Oh, my fucking God.
- Bye.
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Shit?
(cheers and applause)
- Crazy. My darlings.
I can't believe
you're back.
No, really,
I can't believe you're back.
I thought the restraining order
was still in effect.
Hey, famous thang.
You know, there are
so many fierce queens
I could have invited back.
But you 10 were chosen
because I believe
that each of you
still has something
to prove to me,
to your fans, and most
importantly to yourself.
So from this moment on,
everything you do is about
building your legacy.
- Okay.
- Yeah!
- But wait.
There's more.
Because you are all-stars,
I will not be eliminating
any queens this season.
- What?
- Bitch, what?
- What's happening?
We're all freaking out.
- What was the question?
- The winner of "RuPaul's
Drag Race All Stars"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
a coveted spot in the
"Drag Race" hall of fame,
and a cash prize
of $100,000,
with extra special
guest judge Raven-Symone.
-  RuPaul's drag race
-  May the best woman,
best woman win
(RuPaul laughs)
- I will not be eliminating
any queens this season.
- What?
- Because you are all-stars,
I will only be rewarding
success.
Each week,
instead of the bottom two
lip-synching
for their lives,
the top two will lip synch
for their legacy,
and the winner
will receive...
$10,000.
- Ooh!
- Holy shit!
- Bitch!
- Shut up!
- Bitch better have
my money.
- This totally changes
everything.
Nobody's gonna go home
the whole season,
and we get $10,000
in addition to
the grand prize of $100,000.
Oh, fuck.
I could walk away
from this competition
with at least $350,000.
I didn't go to fucking
school for math.
- Now let's take a moment
to get reacquainted
"Drag Race" style.
Oh, pit crew.
- Ooh.
- Darlings,
in the great tradition
of "Paris Is Burning,"
reading is what?
- Fundamental.
- Exactly.
- Day one of "All Stars,"
read the hell out of each other.
Get up out of here.
- Phi Phi O'Hara,
you're up, darling.
- This is so hard
when they're your friends,
which is why
this should be easy.
(all laugh)
You know what Adore and the
value menu have in common?
They're both cheap
and full of fat.
(all laugh)
Adore, I'm sorry.
Can you move out the way?
Sweetie, if you don't have
a wristband,
you can't be in here
for the meet and greet.
(all laugh)
- Alyssa, you are like
the Abby Lee Miller of drag.
Except when Abby Lee Miller
dresses her body,
she can cover
her back rolls.
(all laugh)
- Hold my clutch, bitch,
and let me take this cape off.
- And Venus Delight.
- Bye. See you.
Goodbye.
- Janet Hagson.
Oh, I'm sorry, Coco Montrese.
How exciting for you that
Janet has a new album out.
You can both
come out of retirement.
- Oh!
- What?
- Tatianna, thank you
for letting the PAs know
who to pack up first.
- Coco Montrese,
I always wanted to know
what the female gremlin
would look like in 25 years.
(all laugh)
- Fuck!
- That was a good one,
bitch.
- Ginger Minj, in my eyes,
the true winner
of Season 7 of TLC's
"I Didn't Know I Was Pregnant."
(all laugh)
Roxxxy Andrews, I think
about you all the time,
especially in the morning
at the bus stop.
- Ooh!
- Oh!
- Too soon? Too soon?
- Alyssa Edwards,
my darling dear,
I can't stand it
when you're near.
Come on, Mother Goose.
- Alaska, I'm sure Katya
can see you from her backyard.
- Coco, thank you
for proving in Season 5
that orange
is the new black.
(all laugh)
Adore Delano, do you know
what makes you
the number one fan favorite
of all time?
- No.
- Neither do I.
- Allow me to introduce to you,
"Monsters, Inc."
(all laugh)
- Alaska gutted.
Roxxxy Andrews, rotted.
Phi Phi O'Hara,
gila monster.
And that brings us
to Coco Montrese, bitch!
(all laugh)
- Alaska, I finally
got to listen to "Anus,"
and I get it
'cause it sounds like
what my anus does
after eating Mexican.
Mmm, choices.
(all laugh)
Alyssa Edwards,
you are so talented,
and you haven't let it go
to your head.
Nothing's changed you
or your overbite.
(all laugh)
- Coco Montrese,
doesn't it suck
that it took you longer
than my existence
to figure out
what shade of makeup to use?
- Peg Bundy
ate Kelly and Bud.
(all laugh)
Party! Roxxxy Andrews,
it's good to see
a filler bitch this season,
and I'm not talking
about that ass.
- Alaska,
like her outfit, trash.
(all laugh)
Coco, way too old.
And Adore Delano,
um, really?
(all laugh)
- Y'all bitches are hateful.
- Detox. No, really,
I mean that.
This is actually
your intervention.
You should really stop this.
Adore Delano,
these other girls
are gonna say you have
terrible makeup skills,
you have no fashion sense,
and you're dumb as a rock.
But they're wrong.
You don't have
terrible makeup skills.
(all laugh)
Roxxxy Andrews,
obviously a diet
consisting of nothing
but hatred for Jinkx Monsoon
does a body good.
(all laugh)
Come on, All Stars,
let's get all started.
Oh, brrrrrr. Chh!
(all laugh)
- All right, ladies.
The library
is closed officially.
The winner is...
Alaska.
You've won a $2,000
shopping spree
for glamorous glasses
at the legendary house
of LA Eyeworks.
- All right.
- I won
the reading challenge.
I'm not trying to win
Miss Congeniality.
I'm trying to win
"All Stars."
- And I'll be posting more
of your reads at LogoTV.com.
- Yes.
- Now, ever since
you sashayed away,
I've had my eye
on each and every one
of your astonishing careers.
You've all come
a long way, baby.
And to prove it,
for your first maxi challenge,
I'm throwing an "All Star"
talent show extravaganza.
Tomorrow, in front
of a live audience,
you'll each get a chance
to show us
how your charisma, uniqueness,
nerve and talent has grown.
#dragracetalentshow.
(clicks tongue)
(applause)
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may
the best All Star win.
- It's like I never left.
- Oh, home sweet home.
- Roxxxy, don't unpack.
It's a talent show, okay?
- Whoo.
- (laughs)
- Our first challenge
is a talent show.
This is showing Ru
who is an all-star,
so you've got to make
a statement
coming right out the shoot.
- Twinning. Twinning!
- Oh! (laughs)
- Oh, girl, they left you out.
- I don't do that no more.
- I would've bought three,
but, you know,
Rolaskatox didn't work
for us last time.
Rolaskatox is Roxxxy,
Alaska and Detox.
Rolaskatox.
She's moved on from us.
The Rotox show.
- The original parts
of Rolaskatox are here,
however, that does not mean
the band
is getting back together.
- What are you doing
for your talent show?
Are you dancing?
- I'm gonna do, like,
a little gymnastics routine.
- Work!
- What are you doing?
- I'm a singer/songwriter,
so I'm gonna sing a song
that I wrote.
- What song are you singing?
- Well, I'm actually singing
a cappella.
- A cappella.
Girl, I've been singing
my whole life,
and I don't sing a cappella.
If you go off your tempo,
your timing, your anything,
you are fuck.
- I know it's pretty ballsy,
but, like, I hope
that it shows
that I'm a real singer
tomorrow without any music.
- You do what you do
and your fucking
tells us if you work hard.
- Nothing like a sensible
tank top with rhinestones.
Very subtle, you know.
- I brought fan underwear.
- Fan underwear?
Like, underwear
a fan gave you?
- Yeah, on the stage.
- People give you
their underwear on stage?
- Yes.
- Those have always
brought me luck.
- You're like Tom Jones,
basically.
- I'm like David Cassidy.
Look.
- (laughs)
- America's sweetheart.
My biggest competition
in this talent show
I think
is going to be Adore.
She's got a great voice.
-  When you love me
- This is something that
she's gonna do very, very well,
and it scares me a little bit
because right now,
you want to be on that top.
You want that $10,000
and you want to show the judges
that you're an all-star.
You deserve to win this.
So let's get this done.
- [Voiceover]
Coming up...
- RuPaul's not eliminating
anyone this season.
Do you feel like people
are going home?
What's coming?
I'm scared.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Hey, hey, hey.
- We are here.
H-E-R-E, here.
- Time to get ready for the "All
Star" talent show extravaganza.
I haven't done a talent show
since, like, third grade.
I sang Selena.
(laughs)
- I'm just really nervous.
I feel like
it's too good to be true,
and I feel like
people are going home.
RuPaul said that he's not
eliminating anyone this season,
but I think we're all just sort
of feeling an impending doom.
What's the twist?
What's coming?
I'm scared.
So why did you two decide to
come back for "All Stars?"
- I feel like I want to show
everyone where I'm at now.
- It's been a while.
- It's been a minute.
I have figured
a lot of things out.
- Like what?
- Like to not shop
at Wet Seal
when you're gonna come
to "RuPaul's Drag Race."
- (laughs)
But it was different.
Like, it was sort of
more like ready-to-wear
and over time,
the show has evolved.
- Yeah.
- You know.
- I came back
'cause I think--
I mean, I have
a whole lot to prove.
I have
a whole public audience
that thinks
I'm a certain way,
and I don't want them
to think I'm that way.
- Oh, you mean everyone
thinking you're a bitch?
- Oh, ooh.
- I do have a bitchy side
and that's an honest side.
I just want them to know
there's more to me
than just some angry
little orange monster.
- Ha!
- I was super embarrassed
about how I was behaving
and acting on Season 4.
I do have a lot to prove,
especially to the audience.
And at the same time, my drag
style has completely changed.
Now I do a lot of cosplay,
and it's really cool and fun.
I'm not just
this tired ass showgirl.
There is a star in Phi Phi,
and she's ready to shine.
This is like
a family reunion to me.
This is fun. Like, how are we
gonna fight and stuff?
- I'm sure
you'll find a way.
- (laughs)
- You know,
Roxxxy's over there.
(all laugh)
- Don't be shady.
Be a lady.
- I was a bitch on Season 5.
This isn't a joke to me.
- I don't think it's--
- This competition
is extremely serious.
You're Jinkx Monsoon
playing a character.
A lot of girls
want to blame editing,
and I'm not that girl.
I said the things I did.
I played those mind games.
Anything on this TV show
that is said, you said it.
I let the competition
get to me.
I was playing dirty
and at the time,
Jinkx,
I'm so close to the crown
that how
am I gonna get her?
I'm obviously
not as funny as she is.
not as smart as she is
and I have to do something.
And my stupid self said...
I've learned from my mistakes
and I changed my attitude
and there's no way that
that can happen again.
I don't want to be
that girl.
I mean, I won't be.
I refuse.
This is our second chance.
Redemption, honey.
-  Can I get an amen?
- Some of the girls
might be more focused
on rehabilitating
their reputation
rather than just
winning the competition.
But I'm here
to show the world
that I've turned into
a total fucking monster.
(laughs)
(RuPaul laughs)
-  Cover girls, put the bass
in your walk
Cover girls,
put the bass in your walk
Head to toe,
let your whole body talk
Cover Girl
(applause)
- Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul's Drag Race
All Stars."
Michelle Visage,
what's a nice girl like you
doing in a place like this?
- Well, in the words
of a famous older woman,
we are all stars.
- (laughs) And style
superstar Carson Kressley,
are you ready to be gagged?
- I don't gag easily,
but yes.
- (laughs)
The newest addition
to our "Drag Race" family,
the incredible Todrick Hall.
- Thank you so much
for having me, Ru.
You look amazing.
- And the super talented,
Ms. Raven-Symone.
No, Symone is how you say
her name, okay?
Yes, hello.
- It's true. It's Symone.
- I'm so happy you're here.
- I'm so happy I'm here.
I missed your face.
- Thank you.
- (chuckles)
- This week,
I challenged my girls
to showcase their charisma,
uniqueness, nerve and talent
in an "All Star"
extravaganza.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
Coming up, Roxxxy Andrews,
Detox, Katya,
and Alyssa Edwards.
- We are one step closer
to finding Alyssa's secret.
- (inhales)
(RuPaul laughs)
- Welcome to the "All Star"
talent show extravaganza.
First up, Adore.
Talent, singing.
(cheers and applause)
-  Baby,
you're a work of art
A shooting star
Lighting up the darkness
So lucky
that we found this, yeah
You know you've got me
losing sleep
I can't believe
the beauty of this moment
It's all
I've ever wanted
But I can't love you
I can't love you today
I can't love you
tomorrow
I can't love you anyway
I can't love you anyhow
I can't love you,
love you
How are you guys feeling
tonight, cool?
(cheers and applause)
I can't love you today
I can't love you
tomorrow
I can't love you anyway
I can't love you,
love you
Thank you.
(cheers and applause)
- Party!
- Up next, Alyssa Edwards.
Talent, variety.
- Alyssa Edwards,
welcome back.
- That's right, Mama Ru,
I'm back,
just minus the back rolls.
- Now, I have a feeling
that we are one step closer
to finding Alyssa's secret.
Let the music play.
- [Voiceover]
Long, long ago,
there was a little gay boy
from Texas.
- Mesquite, Texas, darling.
Baby, hand me that script
and let me tell the real story.
I packed a bag,
hopped on a plane
and moved all the way here.
Alyssa Edwards,
a star is born.
- [Voiceover]
Girls and boys,
live tonight,
our kind of gal,
Alyssa Edwards.
- Alyssa's performance
is quintessential Alyssa.
She has a puppet of RuPaul.
She has a tear-away.
It's everything.
-  Oh, she's
our kind of girl
- That's me.
All right.
-  I'm back, back,
back, back, back again
Giving you a dose
of what's happening
All these crowns
I'm snatching them
Got more discards
than the Vatican
My name's Ms. Edwards,
I'm a champion
- Coco Montrese.
Talent, dancing.
- I decided
to step out of my box
just to show
a different side of myself.
I hope it pays off for me
this time.
- We all make choices,
but that was a choice.
(applause)
- Detox. Talent is singing.
-  Supersonic,
it's supersonic
We're on it,
yeah, don't you want it?
- Detox is spraying
glow paint everywhere.
Girl, don't get it
on the dress.
(cheers and applause)
-  Majestic,
the future is electric
Erratic,
accelerate the static
Supersonic,
it's supersonic
We're on it,
yeah, don't you want it?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
- Ginger Minj.
Talent, singing.
-  When I was a child
I asked the starry sky
What will I be?
A butterfly,
a better me?
'Cause it's hard to be
a different kind of boy
Making lots of noise
inside a crazy world
When you take
all those feelings inside
And you want
to run and hide
So fly,
wings lit by a flame
Don't worry how high
Dream your own way
(cheers and applause)
- Coming up...
Yesterday, I promised
I wouldn't be eliminating
any of you
because this season...
(RuPaul laughs)
- Welcome back to the "All Star"
talent show extravaganza.
Up next, Katya.
Talent, gymnastics.
- This bitch is over here
on her hands pussy-popping.
All right, Ms. Katya,
you get the gold from me.
- Phi Phi O'Hara.
Talent, a cappella.
-  I'm going out tonight
I'm gonna lose my mind
(cheers and applause)
Shall we speed it up
a little bit?
- Yeah!
-  I'm going out tonight
I'm gonna go
lose my mind
Oh, DJ, can you find
just another beat
To give me life
- (inhales)
-  With the melody of music
Moving through
our veins, ah
We're gonna make love
to the clap tonight
- Girl, find the note.
Find the note.
-  Tonight we're gonna
lose control
Tonight we're gonna
lose control, ah
(cheers and applause)
- Roxxxy Andrews.
Talent is burlesque.
(all laugh)
- Okay, bitch.
I'm buying it.
- Yes! Yes!
(cheers and applause)
- Yes!
- Alaska. Talent, singing.
- There are times
when it seems
that the world doesn't
appreciate me being me.
I haven't always
been pretty.
I haven't always been nice.
But I've always been...
(cheers and applause)
Gay
I'm pretty and witty
and dapper and clean
I'm campy and classy
and cunty and mean
I'm the queeny-est queen
of the queeny-est queens
I'm as girly
as a girl can be
Whoo
(cheers and applause)
- Tatianna.
Talent is spoken word.
- This piece is entitled
"The Same Parts."
- This piece.
(laughs)
- People at the party,
and I'm wanting to dance.
Other ugly-ass bitches
ain't standing no chance.
Dudes looking at me like
they want to get in my pants.
Come on, bitch,
see me with the pants.
See me with the pants.
His back on the wall.
My ass on his hump!
Grinding for a second.
His stuff's getting thick.
- (gasps) Ooh, girl.
- He doesn't know it,
but I'm getting firm, too.
His boys really need to know
before calling me boo.
Because what you see
isn't always the truth.
Say it with me.
What you see
isn't always the truth.
Thank you.
Because, baby boy,
I've got all the same parts
that you do.
The same parts.
(lower voice)
(laughter)
(whispering)
The same parts.
(cheers and applause)
Thank you.
- The nineties beatnik
doing a spoken word piece
about her genitals.
Tatianna's number
is my absolute favorite.
(cheers and applause)
- Welcome, ladies.
Now, week after week,
season after season,
I've had the thankless task
of sending home some of my most
beautiful and talented girls.
Now, for "All Stars,"
I've decided
to turn over a new leaf.
Yesterday, I promised
I wouldn't be eliminating
any of you,
and that's true.
Because this season,
you'll be eliminating...
Each other.
- Okay.
Welcome to "All Stars."
(RuPaul laughs)
- This season,
you'll be eliminating...
Each other.
That's right.
In addition
to receiving $10,000,
the winner of the lip synch
will be given the power
to eliminate
one of the bottom queens.
Now who's your sister
in drag?
- Now it's up to us to vote
each other off the island?
Bitch, what show
did I sign up for?
- I'm in a complete state
of shock.
I forgot
what I was gonna say.
- Now, based on
your performance
in the talent extravaganza,
I've made some decisions.
Alyssa Edwards,
Detox,
Katya,
you are all safe.
- (exhales)
- Please step
to the back of the stage.
The rest of you represent
the tops and bottoms
of the week.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
First up, Adore.
- First and foremost,
this is "All Stars 2."
This is the best
of the best.
I mean, we are looking at
such a powerhouse of talent.
I'm going to break down
all the T.
If you get hurt, get over it
and up your game.
Moving on.
I will say,
on a positive note,
I didn't hate your hair.
- Oh, thanks.
- Which, when you came out,
I thought
I was gonna hate it.
It didn't suck.
- It's human.
- It really doesn't matter
whether it's human or not.
- I did it myself.
- That shows you've done
something.
- Oh.
- Because the outfit, girl.
- Okay.
- This is
a 14th Street dress,
like, that doesn't fit you.
I don't care if you're gonna
give me your hog body line
or whatever it is.
- Oh, my God.
- It's just,
I expected more for you.
We see your stuff out there.
You're doing your thing.
You've got your album.
- Mm-hmm.
- You're rocking the world.
- Why the gloves?
- I thought it looked cool
to just kind of, like,
have the focus point
be on the legs.
I thought
it was pretty neat.
- I think
your rock star-ness
needs to be more leather.
- I've got a lot of it,
girl.
- I know, and it needed
to happen, 'cause it didn't.
- Yeah, but, I mean--
yeah.
- But do you care?
'Cause, like,
everything's like blas.
- Girl, I completely care.
I mean, I've expected, like,
you to kind of go ham,
but you went ham,
so I mean,
that's a human reaction
to kind of feel shit.
- But when I think of you,
I don't think of somebody
who's gonna
come out wearing
some type of glamorous
crazy cinched outfit,
and I think
that's part of your brand,
and I thought
you sounded amazing.
- Thank you so much.
- All right. Let's move on down
to Coco Montrese.
- I thought
it was a very brave move
to do something
very old Hollywood,
but I lost your choreography
with the dress.
And once it got
30 seconds into the number,
it was just
kind of predictable.
- I was waiting
for something to happen,
but the train
didn't leave the station.
- Here's my main thing
tonight.
In your season,
you were orange.
Tonight, you went
from Doritos to soot.
- I thought maybe
you were trying to give us
that kind of silver screen,
old Hollywood look,
but then I thought, wait,
the face and the hands
aren't matching.
- Yeah, I ran out of time
and didn't do my--
- Didn't get to the hands.
- Yeah.
- I wish your hands
would've matched.
Then maybe
you could've sold it to us.
- Okay.
- Up next, Ginger Minj.
- Regarding your voice,
I thought your pitch
was perfect.
- But I felt like this
was a song you would sing
after already performing
for 30 minutes.
This is "All Stars."
I was expecting more.
- You look beautiful
tonight,
but one thing you have to keep
in mind being a plus-sized girl,
when you wear a Palazzo jumpsuit
in that kind of stretchy jersey,
when you walk, it creeps
and it gives you a Va-gegy.
Literally, I couldn't take
my eyes off of your vagina.
- Thank you.
(all laugh)
- Up next, Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Your Balma dress.
You're tiny, Phiph.
It totally encompasses
your teeny little body
and you just
look like a box.
- I think the dress
is spectacular. Sorry.
- When you started to sing,
those first couple of bars of
that a cappella was so powerful.
- But then I couldn't
even focus on your voice
because it was going
in and out of the key
and the audience was clapping
completely different rhythm.
- Right. I would've loved
for there to be
some support for your voice,
because it did get
a little wonky.
- Up next, Roxxxy Andrews.
- I'm grateful to see
that even though through
your weight loss and fitness,
you're still thick
and juicy.
- This ass and these legs
ain't going nowhere.
- Thank you, Dr. Zizmore.
(all laugh)
- I haven't been turned on
by a man like that
in a very long time.
- Maybe you don't sing,
maybe you don't tap dance,
but what you do have
is major charisma.
You're such a superstar.
- And I loved the reveals.
It was like
a Russian nesting doll.
There was wig under a wig.
Your performance
was an event.
- I happen to have on
an extra wig
underneath this one.
(all laugh)
Thank you very much, Roxxxy.
- Thank you.
- Up next, Tatianna.
See me with them hands,
bitch.
- See me with them hands.
- Look at that body.
Are you cinched?
- A little.
- I'm gonna fucking
key your car.
- I was the most skeptical
about your performance
because it was so long since
the time you were on here.
But you were so fresh
and so current,
and I think that you're
a force to be reckoned with
in this competition.
- You let your smarts
do the talking,
and I thought
that was really clever.
There was double entendre.
- You had me at piece.
- (laughs)
- That was so amazing,
so good.
- And congratulations on your
face, because you're gorgeous.
- Okay?
Face is beat, bitch.
The face is beat.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Up next,
last but not least, Alaska.
- Your song is genius.
I felt like I took mushrooms
and was watching
"Pick of Destiny,"
and then you flew in
on Valcore and--
(all laugh)
- And I love that
you out-gayed even me.
(all laugh)
I mean, that was fantastic.
My only negative, I would've
like a different nail.
- Yeah. They just drew so much
attention away from the dress.
- I love the nails,
you guys,
'cause they're so wrong
and so right.
- Thank you, ladies.
I think I've heard enough.
Based on
the judges' critiques,
I've made some decisions.
Roxxxy Andrews, Tatianna,
you are the top two "All Stars"
of the week.
(applause)
Con-drag-ulations.
You've each won
a custom jewel collection
from Fierce Drag Jewels.
- I am in the top two.
I cannot believe it.
I'm ready to lip synch,
child.
What's my song?
- I am so happy.
- Alaska, Ginger,
you are safe.
That means Adore, Coco
and Phi Phi,
you are in the bottom three.
- I'm crushed.
I'm baffled.
I just feel like
I'm gonna vomit.
Like, I watch competitions
and I'm like, how do people
get to that point?
And it's not a good feeling
at all.
Uh, no, it's...uh-uh.
- Tatianna and Roxxxy,
each of you needs to decide
which of the bottom queens
you'll eliminate
if you win the lip synch.
And I'll remind you that
the winner of the lip synch
will win $10,000 cash.
So while you ladies
deliberate in the work room,
the judges and I will enjoy
a fruity cocktail.
- (slurps)
- You may leave the stage.
Coming up...
- I'm gonna lose a friend.
- She's gonna probably
send me home next week.
I'm gonna send her home now.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Girl.
- As we walk into the room,
you could hear a pin drop.
It's silent.
We're all nervous
because we don't know
how this deliberation
is going to work.
You don't really know.
- I do not envy you guys
at all.
I would not want to be
in your fuckin shoes.
- We're eliminating
our sisters.
- Exactly. That's the thing.
- And, you know,
what do you do?
Eliminate competition
or do you eliminate somebody
because you think
they were weak?
- Do you eliminate
who you think did the weakest
or do you eliminate the
strongest to-- (clicks tongue)
- And if you squeak by
just because of a friendship,
don't you think, like,
the backlash from that
is going to be worse?
It needs to be fair.
- This sucks, but
a decision has to be made.
My perspective
is you have to base it
off of the challenge itself.
That seems like the only way
we can find some fairness
out of this entire crazy thing
that Ru has thrown at us.
- Yes.
- If there's a week where you
feel like I was like booger,
send me home.
- Yeah.
- Exactly.
- But a lot of what they said
negative, I didn't agree with.
And if I'm going to have to be
the judge at the end of the day,
like, I'm going off
of what I'm thinking
and not necessarily
what the judges are saying.
- But, you know, that's why
they're the professionals.
- Well, it's funny, because
I said, you know what?
I don't need to be paid.
I will pay you.
- Oh!
- Yes!
- I like that.
- It's the truth, though.
- (laughs)
- This is delicious.
- Mmm.
- Let's say a few weeks
down the line,
there's someone that you know
could totally kick you off.
Things can change.
Like, we could totally
be like, nope,
she's gonna probably
send me home next week.
I'm gonna send her home now.
- That's what would suck.
Bitch,
I could've sent you home,
and now you just want to send me
home because you're spiteful?
Okay, well--
- Well, it's not even
necessarily spiteful,
more so
than being strategic.
- I don't think that the
decision to send someone home
will always be based on the
challenge or the critiques.
I think later on, people
will choose friendships.
I think alliances will
definitely start to factor in
and girls will start
kicking off other girls
who they feel are a threat.
Anything could happen
in this situation.
- This is the thing.
If we stick to critiques
and everybody say that
that's what we're going to do,
then you know already
who's going home.
- Do you know
who you're sending home?
- No. I want to have
the conversation
with all three girls,
just for a quick second.
You want to come first?
- I'm terrified.
All I'm thinking right now
is, like, you just got here
and then you get put
in the bottom
on something
that you love doing.
And you haven't even
shown the world
this Phi Phi that you've
worked so hard to build up.
And I don't feel from
from the judges critiques
I was in the bottom.
I honestly don't.
I think they were
way harder on Coco,
and I think they were
extremely hard on Adore.
- I'm going off of
who I thought was the weakest,
and that's what
I'm making my decision.
- No, totally, no, and I get it,
but it's scary.
I worked too hard
to be here.
- Phi Phi is upset,
and I don't blame her.
I feel for her and I think
I'd feel the same way.
But at the same time,
I know for myself,
I came to play a fair game,
and I'm going to choose
the girl that I feel
was the girl that RuPaul
would send home.
- I'm not pulling anyone over
to talk to them in private
because based on
the performances,
I have a pretty good idea
of who I will eliminate
if I have to.
- What's the D, bitch?
- Girl, it's a struggle.
- I'm feeling
a bit embarrassed.
You know,
working on my confidence
and just growing so much,
I didn't think that
a lot of these feelings
would be coming back.
And it's not a feeling
that, like,
I'm completely obsessed
with right now.
My thing is,
I came into here
with a different idea
of what it was going to be.
I literally work at, like,
punk rock venues
for a living with a band.
Like, I wear T-shirts
and, like--I'm like--
I'm like a drag musician,
so to be told that, like,
I have to be put back into
a bubble of cinching my waist,
it's just not the G
for me.
I, like, wrote this song,
and this shit
is personal to me.
Like, music is, like,
my fuckin gateway, man.
So it's hard.
- I get it, girl.
You belong here.
I think that
it was just a hard day.
I feel like Adore
came back on here,
but she didn't think over
the part
about going back on that runway
and exposing yourself
and putting yourself up there
to be critiqued.
And I don't think
she was ready for that.
- Cocs, she wants to talk.
- My heart's in my stomach
right now.
I'm praying
that Roxxxy wins.
We're from the same season.
We're closer sisters.
- What's the T, girl?
- I stepped out
of what I normally do.
I do it seven nights a week.
And then, it's like,
yeah, we get it,
but you needed to be
a little bit more.
I'm like, I...
- Now, if you were in this
position, what do you do?
If I sent Adore home,
we just met.
She's gonna be like,
oh, well, she's still a bitch.
If I sent you home,
you're my lifelong friend.
We go back before
all this bullshit.
I'm gonna lose a friend.
- No.
- You tell me
if I send Phi Phi home,
is she not gonna
stop talking to me?
- I feel like Roxxxy's
leaning
a little bit more
towards Phi Phi.
I'm hoping that's the case.
- You know what?
This is a fuckin
hard decision.
Is this money
really going to be worth
me losing
these girls' friendships?
There's too much at stake.
- I know this was your whole
hang-up coming into it
was them coming
for your aesthetic.
- Completely.
- Adore's very opinionated
about her look,
and I knew particularly Michelle
was gonna go in on it
because she and Michelle
had this dynamic on tour
where she would go every day
that we would do a show,
she would go, Michelle,
what do you think about this?
And Michelle
would just go, ugh.
- But when it comes
to aesthetic,
I've taken all of their
fuckin amazing knowledge,
shit that Michelle and I
argue with on the road,
I've taken--
- Constantly.
And I've taken.
- And I've taken
and I've used it.
And I brought all this T
to come here
and fit the challenges
in my own definition.
- And get where
they're coming from.
They're feeling 'cause
you're in "All Stars,"
they want you to step it up.
But it's like, this, to me,
for you, is stepping it up.
- If they're ruining this,
what Bianca Del Rio
picked out for me,
girl, like, good luck.
Uh...
(sniffles)
I've worked a lot
on my confidence,
and I feel like
the critiques
were picking at the confidence
that I built up.
And at this point,
it's bringing me back
to baby Adore days
of being defeated,
and I can't relive that.
- You're all wrong,
because it's pork chop.
- Oh!
(all laugh)
- Wait, wait, wait.
Silence, silence!
Bring back my...
(inhales deeply)
Girls.
- This is it.
We have to pick out a lipstick
of who we think should go home.
- (sighs) It's definitely
a heavy feeling.
These are girls
that we're friends
and we work together
out in the real world.
And you know that you have
the power to dash their dreams.
- I think I know
who I'm sending home.
And if I win this lip sync,
I don't feel like she's
going to talk to me again.
But I just--I can't--
I can't eliminate somebody
that I feel
should still be here.
I just can't do it.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Welcome back, ladies.
Two top "All Stars"
stand before me.
Ladies, this is your chance
to impress me,
win $10,000,
and earn the power
to give one of the bottom queens
the chop.
The time has come
to lip sync...
(echoing)
for your legacy.
- I'm making sure
that I am going to
work it the fuck out.
I've got my eye
on the prize.
I want this first win,
and I really want
that $10,000.
- I haven't seen Tatianna
perform since Season 2.
Does she kick?
Does she split?
Does she buck?
I don't know,
but I got a whole lot
of shake it,
shake it,
shake, shake, shake it off.
- Good luck,
and don't fuck up.
-  I stay up too late
Got nothing in my brain
That's what people say,
mm-hmm
But I keep cruising
Can't stop,
won't stop moving
It's like I got this music
in my body
Saying it's gonna be
all right
'Cause the players gonna play,
play, play, play, play
And the haters gonna hate,
hate, hate, hate, hate
Baby, I'm just gonna shake,
shake, shake, shake, shake
Shake it off,
I shake it off
My ex-man brought
his new girlfriend.
She's like, oh, my God,
but I'm just gonna shake.
And to the fella over there
with the hella good hair,
won't you come on over, baby,
we can shake, shake, shake.
- (laughs)
-  Yeah, oh
'Cause the players gonna play,
play, play, play, play
And the haters gonna hate,
hate, hate, hate, hate
Baby, I'm just gonna shake,
shake, shake, shake, shake
Shake it off,
I shake it off
You've got to shake it off,
( cheers and applause)
- Yeah, shakers.
- Ladies,
I've made my decision.
Roxxxy Andrews...
you're a winner, baby.
(applause)
- Thank you so much.
Who do you think won
the lip sync?
I did.
Oh, my God, I'm so excited.
I came on this show
to prove something,
and I'm already
starting it off good, girl.
- You've earned a cash tip
of $10,000.
- My biggest tip yet.
- Tatianna, you are safe.
- Thank you.
- Will the bottom three
please step forward?
Roxxxy, with great power
comes great responsibility.
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
- When I was making
my decision,
I put myself in your shoes.
Listening to your critiques, and
we got to watch the talent show,
my decision was based off of
who I agreed with you all
was the bottom.
So I won money
and I might lose a friend,
but the girl that I chose...
Was Coco.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, honey.
I'm sorry.
- As it is written,
so it shall be done.
Coco Montrese,
you are an "All Star."
Now sashay away.
(applause)
- Wow. I'm the first
to be sent away
by a friend and not Ru.
It's very disappointing,
but "All Stars"
don't give up.
- Well, con-drag-ulations,
"All Stars."
You survived
to live another day.
Now, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell are you
gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen
up in here?
- (all) Amen.
- All right.
Now let the music play.
-  Throw your hands up
Time to get down
Time to get down,
down, down, down, down
- I don't know what's next,
but it's not the end of me.
So it's not the last
you've seen--
(alarm)
- Whoo, girl.
Coco, girl, all is not lost.
So stay thirsty, girl,
'cause it ain't over.
- Oh.
- You still have a chance
to return for your revenge.
(evil laugh)
- No way.
I got a lot to give,
and trust me, I'm not
holding shit back.
Oh, at all.