- Previously
on "AllStars..."
You need to create
merchandise
worthy of your unique
AllStar brand.
Alaska.
- Anus-thing is possible.
- You really
sort of captured
that sort of pretentious
1990s perfume ad.
- Katya.
- Your commercial,
your product, and your look
are on brand.
- Thank you.
- Tatianna.
- What you didn't do
is really feature
the product.
- Choices.
- Roxxxy Andrews.
- Losing the hair, it's almost
like when you see it once
and it's really funny,
the next time it's like,
oh, okay,
and made it
a little bit forgetful.
- Alaska.
You are a winner, baby.
- Thank you.
(applause)
- Which queen
have you chosen
to get the chop?
- One of these queens
week after week
has brought
a level of prestige
and beauty and excellence
to this runway.
One of these queens
is the very person
who leant me this very shirt
that I'm wearing tonight.
So based on that,
I've chosen...
Tatianna.
- Tatianna, sashay away.
- Thank you.
- (sighs)
(exhales)
"Had a blast.
Love you all.
Thanks, Tati."
We love you, Tatianna.
(applause)
- Thank you
for saving me again.
- I love your pussy, girl.
I know that it appears
that there's some sort of
Rolaskatox blood oath pact.
It's really not that.
I mean, is it fair
to let someone advance
who hasn't been here
the whole time?
Tatianna
went away for two weeks,
and Roxxxy lent me
the shirt that I'm wearing.
How could I send her home?
So Adorde--
I mean Katya--
- Oh, my God, bye.
- Do you have a lipstick
in your titty or something?
- I chose Roxxxy.
Here's the thing.
When I was talking
to Tatianna,
like, she--
there was like a fire.
I was, like, I want
to see more of that.
I know you know
it's nothing personal.
- Not at all.
But I do want you to know
that I have drive,
I do care,
I want to be here.
So I want you all
to know that.
I can't blame her.
I've been in the bottom
four times.
But all I can do is prove
why the girls have kept me here
and try to pull off a win.
- So two wins.
- Two-two.
- How many for you, D?
- Two.
I have been
grandslamming everything,
and killing every runway
runway that I step on,
And to continue to be just safe
is kind of irritating.
It's like you think of fucking
store bought roll-up tape
is more genius
than a talking trash can
or a spray bottle
that has nothing in it?
You know what I mean?
It's frustrating to me.
Four, though. I mean...
- Girl, yes.
I'll be honest.
I feel good about my position
in the competition.
- Two for me, and Roxxxy?
- One.
I wish I won
that lipsync, though.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sure
that there's some hos
who would love
to get me out of the way.
I feel like
Jessica Rabbit. Uh!
I would want
to get me out of the way
if I was up against me.
Luckily I am me.
Sorry about that.
- The winner of "RuPaul's
Drag Race AllStars"
receives a one year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
a coveted spot
in the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize
of $100,000.
With extra special
guest judge Aubrey Plaza.
-  RuPaul's Drag Race
May the best woman
Best woman win
- Top five.
- Oh.
- We made it.
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Hi.
- Ladies.
Now, queens, as gay people,
we get to choose
our families.
Because sometimes
the families we grew up with
don't understand us.
So when I recently
reached out
with an invitation
to your moms and sisters,
I'm sorry to say
that not one of them
accepted my invitation.
They all did.
- Aah! (laughs)
- So let's give a big
"Drag Race" family welcome
to Alyssa's sister Tabatha.
- Oh, my God! Yeah!
- (laughs)
- Alaska's mom Pam.
(laughter and applause)
- Oh, my God!
- How are you?
There's RuPaul.
- Detox's sister Heather.
- Yes!
- Seeing my sister
walk into the workroom
is stirring up
all these emotions
because just last week
it was the anniversary
of my father's passing.
So that's been on my mind
a lot lately,
and to have my heart
and my soul, my best friend,
it's like a godsend.
My heart is like fucking
beating out of my chest.
- And we have
Katya's mother Pat.
- (laughs)
My mom!
I hate that fucking cunt.
No. Just kidding.
- And Roxxxy's grandmother
Sonia.
- Oh!
- Roxxxy!
(laughter and applause)
- Welcome, you beautiful,
beautiful women.
You guys are the reason
we are here,
and I thank
each and every one of you.
Thank you.
Now, queens.
You need to transform
your loved one
into a member
of your royal drag family.
(all laugh)
All while using Anastasia
of Beverly Hills cosmetics.
- Ooh.
#DragFamilyValues
(all laugh)
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
(applause)
- Oh, we got shoes
and fabric.
- How does it feel
to be in Hollywood?
- Oh, my God,
I feel like a star.
- This is it.
This is it.
It's so different this time
like from Season 7 though,
because it's like
a lot more joyful
and less riddled
with anxiety,
which is a new thing.
- That's awesome.
- Yeah.
It's so cool to have
my mom in the room now
when I'm not
a nervous wreck.
What I'm thinking
is sexy Russian trophy bride
with her peasant mom.
- And who am I?
(both laugh)
- This is definitely
going to be a transformation.
I don't think my mother
has ever worn heels in her life.
She's used to spending
under $10
for a blouse at Savers.
I probably
shouldn't say that.
Oh, my God.
It fits you
like a fucking glove.
That's incredible.
- I'm very close
to my sister Tabi.
I'm so happy
to see her here.
When's the last time
we've seen each other?
Oh, mom's funeral.
- Yeah, a year ago.
You know, tomorrow
makes a year.
Yeah. But at the same time,
there are
so many mixed emotions.
Mom would have loved
to do this.
She would have.
- Yeah.
- (cries)
- I'm glad we're together,
'cause it's a sensitive time
for us.
- (sobbing)
Thank you for coming.
The day that they closed
my mother's casket,
I just shut down.
I just threw myself
in my work.
I felt that
if I didn't see my family
or I shut them out,
I didn't have to face
the passing of my mother.
So now seeing Tabatha,
Oh, I'm facing it.
- It's just a piece of me
will never be...
I'll never be complete.
- I felt like
there was so much on me.
That's why
I just said I have to...
I have to focus on work,
keep myself moving.
- Keep yourself busy.
- That's why I've been
traveling so much.
- Yeah.
- I needed time.
It was too much for me.
It was too much.
I'm feeling guilty because
I just don't think that
I've been a good big brother
because I should have been there
more for my family.
It's just kind of something
that I'm holding heavy
on my heart.
As much as I want to be
in this challenge to win,
it's just hard
to get my head in the game.
It's like I'm at capacity.
- Coming up...
You're the only queen left
who is not from Season 5.
- I noticed that.
If I end up in the bottom,
it could be
"RuPaul's Best Friend Race,"
which means I go home.
(laughs)
(RuPaul laughs)
- I'm going to wear that?
- No. No, no, no, no, me.
For this week's challenge,
we are going to be making over
our loved ones,
getting them in full drag.
- Hi. I'm Katya.
Nice to meet you.
So how come
you call her mom?
- She's legally
my grandmother,
but she's taken care of me
since I was three years old.
- No way.
- She's the only mom
I've ever known.
So that's my mommy.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Raised him.
He turned out
to be wonderful.
He finished high school.
(all laugh)
- High expectations.
Having my mom here
is just beyond words.
She made her own T-shirt
for the occasion.
Like it's good times.
So I'll make us
matching outfits.
I'm gonna make
some quick dresses.
Good thing I'm good at it.
- I know.
- This challenge couldn't
have come at a better time.
I won the makeover challenge
Season 5,
so this is something
I'm very strong at.
I think this is gonna
pull me off a win.
- This is amazing
that you're here.
- Hell or high water,
I was gonna be here.
- When I first
started doing drag,
my mom was afraid
that I was like
a cross-dressing prostitute
doing drugs
and getting into trouble.
Which I was, but...
(laughs)
- You're probably a lot more
clearheaded this time
than you were on Season 5.
Now that you're clean,
you're probably clearheaded.
- I am. I really am.
- And doing so well.
That makes me happy
more than anything.
It really does.
- Right after Season 5,
it was really easy
to say yes
when I was offered,
you know,
all the things
you get offered
when you're being treated
like a rock star on the road.
I've won
four challenges, mom.
- (gasps) Oh, Justin.
Oh, my God, that's so great.
I'm so happy for you.
Not that that matters.
(both laugh)
- I'm glad that
I was able to stop
and reassess in time.
Now I focus on the work
rather than the after party.
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Hi.
- Hey, Katya. Hi, Pat.
- That lace front looks like
it's coming out of your head.
- (laughs) It isn't?
(all laugh)
- Now, did you watch
your child on "Drag Race?"
- Yes, I did.
- What was the most shocking
thing you learned?
- When he got
really personal
about his struggle
with anxiety,
hearing that heartache,
I mean, I knew it,
but to see it so raw
that was shocking my heart.
And thank you
for counseling him.
You did wonderful.
- Oh, that's very kind.
Thank you.
Now, Katya,
you're the only queen left
who is not from Season 5.
- I noticed that. Yeah.
- Do you think that
the Rolaskatox girls
are, you know--
- Conspiring against me?
Picking off the other seasons
one by one?
I'm the only one in the group
who's not from Season 5,
which means that they all have
stronger bonds with each other
than they do with me,
especially Rolaskatox.
So if I end up
in the bottom,
it could be
"RuPaul's Best Friend Race,"
which means I go home.
(laughs)
- Hi, Heather.
- Hi, Ru.
- Hi, Detox.
- You're a lawyer.
- I am.
- Are you the reason Detox
is out of prison today?
- I can't take credit for that,
but I'm the reason
that if you steal his name
and likeness, you'll get sued.
(all laugh)
- Now, Detox, you lived
with Heather at one point.
- Mm-hmm. I was in a bad place
when I was a kid.
I was misunderstood,
and she kind of encouraged me
to come out and live my life
as who I am,
help me blossom
as a young artist
and a freak and a weirdo.
- Were you just
a naturally nurturing person,
or did you just see
my kid brother
is in a lot of trouble.
I've got to step up?
- Basically.
- (laughs)
- Now, is there going to be
a strong family resemblance?
- People tell us all the time
we have the same nose.
Obviously, sadly.
(all laugh)
- It's a gorgeous nose.
- I love our nose,
especially now.
But before, we were like,
we gotta get
brother/sister nose jobs.
- Yeah. I'm still
not opposed to that.
(all laugh)
- The key
to winning this challenge
is by creating
a family resemblance,
and it's like we're
the same fucking person.
She's just got
a real vagina.
But I need to focus
because I haven't had
a win in a while.
And even though
I've been on the top,
I want to win.
- Hey, Roxxxy.
- Hi, Ru.
- Hi, Sonia.
- I can't believe
I'm meeting the woman
who singlehandedly
raised this gorgeous child.
- Can you believe that?
- It's just amazing.
Did you watch your child
on "Drag Race?"
- Oh, yeah.
- Because the world
got to hear
this incredible story
of how you really came
to this kid's rescue.
- My mother left my sister
and myself at a bus stop
when I was three,
and I remember it
like it was yesterday.
And like I come off
as this strong character,
I try to stay so strong,
but I'm so weak
at the same time. (cries)
- We were all heartbroken...
- I know, I know.
- When we heard the story.
- Maybe he needed
to do that.
Sometimes you need to...
- You have to get it out
of your system, you know.
- Mm-hmm.
- And we took that story
and we put it in our hearts.
And now
you're on "Drag Race."
- This is unbelievable.
- Are you planning
to just tear it up?
- Whoa, am I.
(both laugh)
- Roxxxy needs to win
this challenge.
- Whatever it takes.
Oh, yeah.
Stand up on my head.
- Oh, my God.
- All right,
see you in a minute.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- Alyssa Edwards,
you've brought Tabatha here.
- I have.
This is my baby sister.
- Now, you don't
seem like someone
who's that flashy.
- Right.
- Where do you think
this one has gotten
the Alyssa flair?
- Our mom.
That's where it came from.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- She had a personality
that was just--
it lit up a room.
- Yeah, energetic.
- My mom danced.
I got that from her.
She felt like everything
I touched was gold.
- She was always
encouraging me.
- I had one person
that believed in me.
She protected me
from the cruelty of the world.
- You are what you are
because of her.
- Yeah. (sniffles)
- What was your mom's name?
- Sherryanne.
- What does it say here?
- "Love never dies,
but someday we all will."
Tomorrow's
the one year anniversary
of our mom's passing.
- So is this
a dedication to her?
- Yes.
- And have you processed
all of this yet?
- I feel like I haven't--
- No.
- Today was taking the time
to sit down and like
face it a little.
And it was the right time.
- (sighs)
- I'm glad you guys
get to be together,
because I think
this needed to happen.
This is for Sherryanne.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- The world gets to see her
fabulousness through you.
She's with us.
- She is, definitely.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- Gather round, family.
Now, as an extra
little treat,
in a moment,
you and your loved ones
will get a brow tutorial
from Anastasia
of Beverly Hills.
- Ooh.
- Yes.
- Oh, one more thing.
Tomorrow, in addition
to your drag transformations,
each family unit needs
to vogue the house down
in a special performance
on the main stage.
So good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, pardon my French.
(all laugh)
Okay.
- Bye.
- Coming up...
- Girl, you are beating
the hell out of me.
- I still cry
when I don't get my way.
- I feel like Katya.
I laughed in the mirror
and I went, oh.
(all laugh)
(RuPaul laughs)
- It's so nice having real women
in the workroom.
- This week's maxi challenge is
the family affair drag makeover.
We're all happy to have a family
member here in the workroom,
but it's still a competition
and it's the best of the best,
so any little mistake
could put you in the bottom.
- I don't want you to just
be cute, girl, drop dead--
- Drop dead gorgeous.
- Ah, you remember that,
girl?
- Hello, everybody.
I'm Anastasia Soare
and I am here
to fix your eyebrows.
- Nice.
- Oh, I love Ms. Anastasia.
Mama is done.
- I would love to invite you
on my chair.
So I will do freehand
Pat's eyebrows.
Obviously,
she tweezed so much
her eyebrow for long time.
- Way to go, mom.
- I know.
But she's beautiful
and just learning
how to fill in
her eyebrows.
It's gonna add
so much beauty.
I am going to use
the pomade.
It dries,
and it doesn't move.
This highlighter
define the eyebrows
and highlights
the brow bone.
I mean, look at that.
- Lovely.
- Huh?
(applause)
- That's nice.
- You're a brow genius.
- Thank you, ladies,
so much,
and keep your eyes gorgeous.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Bye.
- We're here.
- That's my mama.
Now it's time to get
our loved ones dragged up.
It's really exciting.
My mom's really pretty,
so this will be fun.
- I'm putting you
in full drag today.
- I can't wait
to see us side by side.
- I think
when I get in drag,
I see--in me,
I see so much of you guys.
- Yeah,
and we all have mom's eyes.
- Yeah, the big eyes.
- Yeah, beautiful.
- Today's the day.
It's the one-year anniversary
of our mom's passing.
What do you think?
And I'm like, okay, just be
strong, be strong, be strong.
Tabi,
we're going to do this.
I don't want
to be so sad today.
- No. We need to be happy
and show out for her.
- Yeah, we're gonna
show out for her.
I didn't come here to half step
and be nobody's runner-up.
- Please prepare yourself.
You're going to get really
stunning really fast.
- Alaska, what were you like
as a kid?
- He was a really good kid,
as a baby even.
Hardly ever cried.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
You made up for it later on.
(laughs)
- I was a fuckin monster.
I still cry
when I don't get my way.
- Last week, on the anniversary
of dad's passing, I was here.
- I was thinking
about you a lot,
wondering
how it was going and...
- It's been tough.
Not everyone knows this,
but my head wasn't really
in the game Season 5
because before I came
into the competition,
my father got really sick,
and at the time, we didn't
have the best relationship.
I had a tough time with dad
being accepting.
So right before he passed...
- I think he accepted you
before that.
I mean, he was not very easy
to share his feelings.
- Watching me on the show
and him being so close to death,
it opened the door
for a lot of conversations
that we never really had,
and I'll be forever grateful
for that.
Well, I mean, I could tell,
like he was like making
amends before he left.
I was in Orlando working
at Pulse and he showed up.
And I remember,
like, bawling
'cause my fucking daddy
was at my drag show.
You were there.
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, at least he'll see that
we're together and having fun.
I think
that's all that matters.
The fact that I can
share this with my sister
and feel him here today
is like--
it's like come full circle.
It feels right to me.
- Girl, you are beating
the hell out of me.
- This is a beat.
- We're all showgirls
tonight.
- Oh.
- I feel like Katya.
I laughed in the mirror,
and I went, oh.
(all laugh)
- Oh, those glasses,
mom goes.
- Mom, you are good.
That was so good.
- Coming up...
- Really, one of the highlights
of the evening.
- I was like, yes.
- I felt like
it was like a weird,
like, birds of death
nightmare.
(RuPaul laughs)
-  Covergirl, put the bass
in your walk
Covergirl,
put the bass in your walk
Head to toe,
let your whole body talk
Covergirl
(applause)
- Welcome to the main stage of
"RuPaul's Drag Race AllStars."
It's my soul sister
Michelle Visage.
- Power to our people,
darling.
- Style superstar
Carson Kressley. Yo, bro.
- 'Sup, bro?
- And my play cousin,
the incredible Todrick Hall.
- But let it be known
I was always the favorite.
- That's true.
And the shilarious
Aubrey Plaza,
welcome
to our twisted family.
- Thanks. This is
the best day of my life.
I'm killing myself tomorrow.
(all laugh)
- This week, we challenged
our Allstars
to do drag family makeovers.
And to kick things off, they're
ready to vogue the house down.
Gentlemen,
start your engines.
And may the best woman win.
(music plays)
-  Let's do it
- Yes, yeah.
- Oh!
Oh! Aah!
(laughs)
-  Let's do it
- Whoo!
- I like it.
- Serving glamour
family style,
Alyssa and Ava Edwards.
Oh, my goodness.
- They're all out of Aquanet
at the store.
- Oh, baby.
So much hair on the runway.
Ms. Tabatha, AKA Ava Edwards
is all up in the gig.
- Ooh, honey,
don't mess with Texas.
Up next, Alaska and Hawaii.
- The pussy doesn't fall far
from the tree.
- No, ma'am.
- It sure don't.
- We're sister spies
who've just robbed a bank,
but then we went out
shopping.
- Oh!
- Hi-ee.
- Does anyone
still wear a hat?
- Up next, Detox and D-Rama.
- Ooh.
- The sisters are doing it
for who?
- Themselves.
- We are superhero,
badass, glamizon bitches
serving major
bada-yada-yada-yadi-yadi.
- Detox and her
technicolor dream girl.
Up next,
Katya and Svetlana Borisivna.
Ah.
- Yodi-lay-hee-ho.
- Emphasis on the ho.
- Mama!
(all laugh)
I'm giving seventies
Soviet Anna Karenina
and she's giving fused,
bumbling babushka.
- What they're wearing, would
you call that Russian dressing?
- I think that was it, yeah.
- Up next, Roxxxy
and Raquel Andrews.
- Wow.
Cougars doing leopard.
- Uh-oh!
- What a cheetah.
- My mom and I,
we look sexy as can be.
We look like
the house of Andrews,
and we are getting
our complete lags, honey.
- Panthers on the runway.
Give 'em hell, Raquel.
- Coming up...
- This is "Allstars."
I think this was
a big lazy tonight,
and I expect more.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Welcome, ladies.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
First up,
Alyssa and Ava Edwards.
- I loved the vogue so much.
I felt like
it was like a weird,
like, birds of death
nightmare
that I never wanted to end.
- I did think you had too much
going on in that ensemble,
Alyssa, even for you.
But this runway tonight
is everything that I love
about Alyssa Edwards.
- I have to agree,
and you look so fantastic.
- Thank you.
- I think you nailed
the challenge perfectly
because
you look like sisters.
- Thank you so much.
- Up next,
Alaska and Hawaii.
Aloha.
- Aloha.
- I thought that the performance
was really fun.
- But what's having
a disconnect for me, Alaska,
was that you let your mom
come out on the main stage
in flip flops,
and you're done in a gown.
And mom has a piece
of sheer sequined fabric
wrapped around
what looks to be a corset.
Because this is "Allstars,"
I think this was a bit lazy
tonight, and I expect more.
- It could be because
you've been doing so well,
expectation is so high.
But this is the top five,
so this wouldn't be the week
to not go 100% full out.
- Up next, Detox and D-rama.
- I thought that you two
had the most cohesive
performance of the night.
If this was a lip sync,
I'm not quite sure which one
of you would be winning.
You were that good.
- I loved all of this.
I loved
the origami fascinators.
It's like Donatella Versace
for the Hunger Games.
- And the strongest family
resemblance.
I mean, it's unbelievable.
I'm just super proud
of the thought and the work
you put in tonight.
- Up next, Katya
and Svetlana Borisvitna.
How'd I do with the name?
- Terribly.
- Yeah.
Say it for me.
- Borisivna.
- And this is Svetlana
Borisvis--ahh.
(all laugh)
- I think
the vogue-ing thing
was not high up on the scale
of things I love to do
in life for Katya.
- Yeah.
- But then you came out here
with this storyline,
and I was like, yes.
- It just completely
flipped the switch for me.
It felt so Katya.
- You're giving us this, like,
vintage Misoni kind of look.
It's something
that they would wear
in Real Housewives of Minsk.
- Yes, it's--
- Really one of the highlights
of the evening.
- I will say, sidebar,
your mother
completely stole the show.
- Yes!
- Your acting,
I mean, you deserve
a Tony Award for that.
- Thank you.
- Up next is Roxxxy
and Raquel Andrews.
- You don't have to show
a lot of skin to be sexy,
and those suits were so hot.
- But I might've liked
some crazy accessory
or something else to just
make this look more drag runway.
- But you look sexy.
I hope you don't mind
me saying that.
- No. Oh, no, go ahead.
(all laugh)
- Calm down, mom.
- Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
Based on the judges' critiques,
I've made some decisions.
Detox,
Katya,
con-drag-ulations. You are the
two top Allstars of the week.
You and your loved ones
have each won a $2,000 gift
certificate from Marc Jacobs.
- Wow.
- (laughs)
- That means this week,
if you're not in the top...
You are up for elimination.
- Fuck.
- You may leave the stage.
- This feels like
the most difficult decision
thus far in the competition
because we are determining
who gets to go into the final
and who has to go home.
Okay, so I'm detecting
a very solemn tone.
- It is super solemn.
Everyone did so fucking great
and then to put us in, like--
- I didn't do great
this challenge.
I got really
terrible critiques
and I fucked up
and I feel terrible about it.
And I'm sorry that I won so much
because it fucking sucks.
- You're beating yourself up.
- Yeah, you need
to just stop it.
Just chill out.
- No, I'm uncomfortable.
Drag fuckin hurts.
I've tried to stay really
focused and really strong
and not show any signs
of weakness,
and now
I'm not able to hide it.
I'm just feeling it
all crashing down around me.
- I want to talk to people.
- Sure.
- I don't know
if you need to or not.
So if you would like
to join me.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Let's do
a little one-on-one.
Alaska, you're up.
- Okay.
- I don't want
to see anybody go.
Everyone did a great job,
minus Alaska,
but she's been killing
the competition.
And I've known Roxxxy
for 13 years.
She's one of
my best friends.
How am I going to send
my best friend home?
What am I gonna
fucking do?
- You can come over here,
Roxxxy.
Come over here.
- Get over here.
- We're sisters, all of us.
- Right.
- You know that.
I personally feel like
it would be you,
but you've been in the bottom
five out of seven challenges.
Consistency.
- Right.
- It's Alaska's first time
in the bottom, my second time.
Going into the final four,
me and Alaska should be safe
just based off statistics.
Do you think that's fair,
though?
- On the last couple weeks,
I got my critiques
to be in the bottom.
I don't get today.
- But he didn't save nobody.
He said if you're not in
the top, you're in the bottom.
- I guess.
- I think Roxxxy
is feeling nervous.
She's been saved the last
three times consecutively.
But I think Roxxxy
has the upper hand on me
because she is
her good Judy.
- So what happened this week?
- I don't know.
I guess all I can say is
I really want to stay
and I think
I deserve to stay.
- Alaska doesn't know me
very well,
and, you know,
if I win the lip sync,
I don't know that she's
100% sure I won't send her home
because she's
my biggest competition.
- I need to go to the end
of this competition.
I need to.
- Party.
- Okay.
My heart is sinking.
I think my spleen
is going to explode.
Queens in the past
have completely disregarded
someone's past performance
and sent people home
because of a terrible critique
on the runway.
Even I, in the past.
So it's terrifying.
I fucked up this week, man.
I fucked up,
and it really sucks.
It fucking really
fucking sucks a lot.
And I need to be
in the final four,
and now I--now I'm
potentially looking at--
I'm not going--
I'm not going to be,
and it really fucking sucks.
- I'm shocked
with Alaska's behavior.
She's really acting
like a brat,
and it's not...
it's not attractive.
It might throw my thinking
process off of the elimination.
If you're going to act like
a brat, like, right now,
how are you going to act
the rest of this time here?
- Well, I'll give you $10,000
if you let me stay.
Before taxes.
I'll transfer it to you
via PayPal,
because I need to stay
in this competition.
I need to be
in the final four.
Acting this way
only exacerbates the problem.
I know that.
I'm an adult.
But it's like
the end of the road
is flashing before my eyes.
It's really hard to take.
- This is such an
incredibly difficult decision
because on the one hand, Alaska
absolutely performed the worst.
But then Roxxxy's
been in the bottom
consistently throughout
the competition
and Alyssa is somewhere
in the middle.
So I could make the case
for anyone to go home.
- I feel nauseous,
and, you know, I just feel like
a dick no matter what happens.
I'm just going with
what my heart is telling me.
That's what I gotta do.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Welcome back, ladies.
Two top Allstars
stand before me.
Ladies, this is your chance
to impress me,
win $10,000
and earn the power
to give one of the bottom queens
the chop.
The time has come
to lip sync
(echoing) for your legacy.
Good luck
and don't fuck it up.
-  Step to the beat,
to the beat
Go freaky
Boom-shang-a-lang,
work that thang
All right now!
All you biological females
who used to have
the upper hand,
it ain't like that
no more, honey.
It's a-got real tough
up in here.
You got your trisexual.
You got your bisexual.
You got your inner sexual.
You gonna have
to step your pussy up.
Handy.
- Yeah!
- (laughs)
Whoo!
-  If you're trying
to be somebody
Girl, you better
step it up
If you're trying
to be somebody
Girl, you better step it up
and step it up
(all laugh)
If you ain't gonna
step inside this
Then you better
drop a sign then
- Girl, you have
to step your pussy up
- Oh!
(all laugh)
You better drop a sign
then
If you're trying
to be somebody
Girl,
you better step it up
If you're trying
to be somebody
Girl,
you better step it up
Better step it up
Girl, you have to
step your pussy up
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
(applause)
- Yes.
Ladies,
I've made my decision.
Detox,
you're a winner, baby.
(applause)
- Yay.
- You've won a cash tip
of $10,000.
- Thank you very much.
- Katya, you're safe.
- Thank you.
- Will the bottom three
please step forward?
Detox, with great power
comes great responsibility.
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
- On one hand,
you have Alaska,
who has been slaying it
this entire competition.
And then you have Alyssa,
who has also been slaying.
And then you have
my best friend,
who I feel like
there have been several times
where she didn't necessarily
deserve to be in the bottom,
and tonight, especially,
was one of them.
And unfortunately,
I do have to make a decision.
I chose Alyssa.
I'm sorry.
I can't send her home.
- It's okay.
- I'm so sorry,
but I just couldn't
send Roxxxy home tonight
because she's been so amazing,
and I just couldn't do it.
I'm so sorry.
- Don't be sorry.
- (sobs)
I love you so much,
and I just hate this.
- As it is written,
so it shall be done.
Alyssa Edwards,
you are an Allstar.
(clucks tongue)
(all laugh)
Now sashay away.
- Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
Good luck, you all.
Well, now I was a lovely...
fourth runner-up.
(all laugh)
I'm not angry.
I'm not upset.
Today was so magical.
I had the opportunity
to work with my sister,
and I did everything
that I wanted to do.
I can't leave
this competition
with nothing other than
a sense of joy.
So I'm very proud.
Aw...
Don't cry.
Why are you upset?
- Because you're always
a winner to me.
- That's all that matters.
- And they did what
anybody else would've done.
They eliminated
their biggest competition.
- Oh, was I the biggest one?
- Yes, yes.
- (laughs) That's my sister
right there!
I'm leaving this
a better Alyssa than I came in.
That's the win.
I am Alyssa Edwards
always and forever.
(clucks tongue)
- The final four,
con-drag-ulations.
You've survived the chop,
but do you have what it takes
to make it to the top?
And I want to hear from you,
the fans.
Which queen do you think
deserves to enter
the Drag Race Hall of Fame?
Are you #TeamAlaska,
#TeamDetox,
#TeamKatya
or #TeamRoxxxy?
Let your voice be heard.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen
up in here?
- Amen!
- All right.
Now let the music play.
-  Throw your hands up
Time to get down
Time to get down,
down, down, down, down
Throw your hands up