- Previously
on "All Stars,"
I will not be eliminating
any queens this season.
- What?
- This season,
you'll be eliminating
each other.
The winner of the lip sync
will eliminate
one of the bottom queens.
- That was a choice.
-  We're gonna make love
to the clap tonight
- Girl, find the note.
- I didn't hate your hair.
- I did it myself.
- That shows
you've done something.
I don't care if you're gonna
give me your hog body line
or whatever it is.
- Oh, my God.
- It's just--
I expected more for you.
- Roxxxy Andrews.
You're a winner, baby.
(applause)
You've earned a cash tip
of $10,000.
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
- I won money
and I might lose a friend,
but the girl
that I chose...
Is Coco.
- Coco Montrese,
sashay away.
- Bitch.
- Coco.
- Oh...
- I'm very torn about
winning these lip syncs.
Having to pick these girls
week by week
is going to be so hard,
but I also came here
to play the game, so...
- Bye, Coquita.
- Well, this is definitely
"All Stars."
Tatianna,
who was your choice?
- It was, um,
it was Coco also.
I didn't think
she represented herself
to the best
of her abilities.
Giving the winner
of the lip sync
the power to send one
of the bottom people home
changes
the whole competition.
I feel like now I have to
not only impress Ru,
but also impress
my competitors.
It's not fun.
- This is a fucking doozy
and it's just starting.
- Just starting.
- When she said safe,
I was like, okay, bitch.
So then they gave her
her critiques.
I said, well, damn.
- Yeah.
- I'm glad I got my one-way
ticket to the back room.
- Exactly.
- Like, we were back there,
like, Jesus, they're
going the fuck in.
- And they were poking,
bitch,
just like every little
wrong thing,
they got everybody for.
- It's become immediately
very clear,
this is "All Stars."
This is gonna be hard.
There's so much talent
in this one room,
this is gonna be
something to see.
- Every time.
- Whoo-whee!
- You know, coming
in this competition,
you think you can prepare.
It's like everything
you thought you knew
flies out the window
while you're
going 90 on the highway.
- We're still here and we get
to send people home next week.
- Who would you
have sent home?
- I thought
I would've chosen Phi Phi.
- I don't know, man.
- I don't, either.
I don't know
if I could do it.
- Ru gave us
a responsibility.
As the competition
progresses,
it's going to get
more difficult.
And could it be
one of those situations
where you scratch my back,
I'll scratch yours?
It's going to be interesting
to see how this turns out.
Baby, this is "All Stars."
Game on.
- The winner of "RuPaul's
Drag Race All Stars"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
a coveted spot in the
"Drag Race" hall of fame,
and a cash prize
of $100,000.
-  Drag race,
May the best woman
Best woman win
- The category is
Bundt cake.
(all laugh)
- It's a new day
and I've been able
to kind of sleep
on everything.
This new power that we're
given, it changes everything.
It's like fucking drag
survivor, so nobody's safe.
No one.
- Tatianna said like this.
Tatianna,
here's Tatianna.
- And choices. Choices.
- I'm still feeling a bit burned
from the judges' feedback.
I'm feeling sideswiped
and I'm not liking
how I'm feeling.
(alarm)
- Ooh!
- She's already
done had hers.
- Hey, queens.
- Hey.
- Now, I brought you here
because you are all stars.
But now,
I want all new stars.
Don't worry,
it's not personal.
It's drag.
So who else you got, huh?
Hello, hello, hello.
- Hi.
- I'm giving you all
Mini Mouse.
- Ladies, here in Hollywood,
all the biggest celebs
know that the key to
longevity is reinvention.
So for this week's
maxi challenge,
you get to reinvent
yourselves all over again
because it's time
for an "All Star" edition
of Snatch Game.
#SnatchGameAllStars.
- Oh, my God.
Snatch Game already.
- It's like Christmas
came early.
Oh, God,
I can't even say it.
I'm not even gonna say that.
I was gonna make
a joke about--
- Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
(all laugh)
Come on, okay.
- This is the snatchety snatch
snatch, snatch, snatch, snatch.
- Who are you doing?
- Teresa Caputo.
- I was also
going to do Teresa--
I'm going to do, um...
- She's like...
- I'm doing Teresa Caputo.
- All right,
battle of the Teresas.
- And you?
- Mae West.
Who are you doing?
- I'm going to do Bjork.
- Oh, right.
- "All Star" Snatch Game
gives the chance
for those who bombed in their
season to really stand out.
So Alyssa, Detox and Phi Phi
have a lot of work to do.
- Girl, the last minute
Snatch Game fucking sucked.
In Season 4, I sucked
on the Snatch Game.
Work it, girl
Give a twirl, give a twirl,
give a twirl
So this challenge
is important.
- I think I'm gonna do
Nancy Grace.
I think that'll be fun.
It'll be something
different for me.
It's super important
for me to do very well
because I shit on myself,
pretty much,
the last time around.
- You're at the Snatch Game,
honey.
- What's that?
- So the pressure
is very high.
- You're doing
Joan Crawford.
- Yeah.
- Joan Crawfish.
- Ms. Mommy Dearest.
- Yes, God.
- Now, can talk like Joan
without your accent?
- I think you should leave
the accent.
- I've fought worst monsters
for years in Hollywood.
(all laugh)
- Alyssa's got to redeem herself
from the Katy Perry.
- Have you ever
kissed a girl?
- Oh! Rue, never.
- But, uh, yeah.
- 'Cause it's either
going to be a train wreck
or it's gonna be a fun,
hilarious train.
It's gonna be a train wreck
regardless.
- Who did you--oh, you won
the Snatch Game in your season.
- I won the first ever
Snatch Game.
- Oh, so you think
you're somebody.
- A little bit.
A little bit.
My Britney Spears
got me far.
- Britney,
Dumb Dee Dee's so dumb,
last night she got arrested
for driving without a...
- A baby in her lap.
- (laughs)
- Do you feel like
you have more pressure now
that you already won?
- Um, a little bit,
but I'm trying not to even
get in that mindset.
- Yeah.
- Should have let her know,
bitch,
that was unintentional,
darling.
The one joke she had
was an--Adore, are you okay?
- Uh-huh.
Even though I'm trying to put on
a smiley face for the day,
everything's
just processing.
And at this point, I'm just
trying to figure shit out.
(sniffles)
- Hello, hello, hello,
kitty girls.
- Hi.
- Adore Delano.
- Hi, Ru.
- Now, last time, your
Anna Nicole Smith was on point.
It was iconic, actually.
- Thank you.
- Who are you doing?
- Um, Jan Crouch.
- I live for her.
- Yeah.
- Why are your eyes all red?
- Um...
I didn't expect--
I just didn't expect it
to be like this, I think.
I'm thinking of going home.
- Of tapping out?
- I think so.
(RuPaul laughs)
- I'm thinking
of going home.
- Of tapping out?
- I think so.
- Why?
- I think that, like,
the critiques last night
and just, like, the vibes.
- You felt
they were extra harsh?
- Yeah, I did.
The Adore thing
is the flannel
and the fucking Riot girl
and grunge-inspired nineties
movement kind of thing,
and it's such
a sensitive subject for me
to work with hundreds of queens
that don't get it.
And then to come back here,
and I feel like Michelle
does not take me seriously.
I believe in beauty
in a denim jacket and barefoot.
- I love all forms of drag.
- Of course.
- But if you're saying
that because of the critiques
on the main stage
are the reason
you're tapping out,
is that enough
to tap out for?
I feel like
you are being sabotaged
by your inner saboteur.
- I look really dramatic
right now,
but it means a lot to me
to just stick to my guns.
I know how hard it took
for me to gain
that confidence
and own my stardom
like you taught me how to.
- What you're doing sounds like
the opposite of confidence.
Confidence means you'll weather
the storm no matter what.
I just know that
you're stronger than this,
and I feel that you're making
this decision based on fear.
The idea of tapping out
and not sticking it through,
what do you think that says
to your young fans?
- I've taken what
you've given me
and I've built a career
off of my aesthetic,
and that speaks to them all.
On social media, there
was some critiques made
about my drag aesthetic,
and I tried to kind of like,
you know, zhuz it up.
At the meet and greet,
one of the fans came up to me
and she was upset.
She was just, like,
you look so uncomfortable
and I know you did this
because of this.
And just know
that what you do,
this is why we dress up
like you.
And there's no one
like you right now.
And to hear them say
how much it means,
that's all
running through my head.
- You know,
you are loved here,
and I want you to stay.
I feel that you will live
to regret this,
and that's
your prerogative.
- I am so forever grateful,
and I love you like
a fucking family member.
You've changed my world.
I have to go.
- Is there anything
I could say to you
that would make you
change your mind?
Is there anything
in the world?
Because I'll say it.
- I feel really confused.
- I'd like for you
to talk to Michelle,
because I know what she said
on the main stage
is a big part of this.
I respect
whatever decision you make.
- I'm so sorry.
- Well, let me give you
some love.
I want you to go
and talk to Michelle
so you can resolve that,
okay?
All right.
I love you, kiddo.
- Thank you very much.
- All right.
- I cannot believe Adore
is actually
seriously considering
leaving the competition
voluntarily.
I'm hoping that Michelle
can say something to Adore
that will make her stay.
- Hello, Alaska.
- Hi-ee.
- Things are just changing
around here by the second.
- I'm so disappointed
in what is happening with Adore,
and I can't even believe
that it's even happening.
This is a huge opportunity,
so it's really upsetting,
and I hope
she changes her mind.
- Yeah. I hope
But, you know,
when you're up against
that kind of energy
that's in your head,
it's hard to overcome it.
All right, well,
let's talk Snatch Game.
You did Lady Bunny last time,
and you did it very well.
You were very funny.
- Thank you.
- And this time
I see a big hat.
Is that Mae West?
- Oh, yes-uh.
- (laughs) Have you ever
done Mae West before?
- No.
- You know, a lot of her catch
phrases--she had a ton of them.
- Mm, yeah, a hard man
is good to find, mm, mm.
- (laughs)
Mae West is a funny character,
but the thing is,
there are a lot of
fierce bitches here.
Don't underestimate
what they can do.
- Absolutely.
- Well, I cannot wait to
see you in the Snatch Game.
Make me laugh.
Bye-ee.
- Bye-ee.
- Hi.
As I see Michelle outside,
a bunch of emotions
are coming.
I'm upset, I'm confused.
- Honey, what's going on?
- I'm leaving.
- Tell me why.
- I just didn't feel like
this is for me.
- Because?
- You're a bit harsh, bro.
- Listen.
- But it didn't seem
constructive.
It felt like let's kind of--
- Like take her down
a notch?
- Yeah.
- If you thought it was
personal, absolutely not.
- I thought it was personal.
It sounded personal.
- No. Absolutely not.
- I wanted to throw out
my soul.
- What did you think you were
going to come into?
You know that everything I say
is not for me to be a bitch.
It's for me to push you
and push you and push you.
I want to see you,
in 20 years like RuPaul.
I want to see that.
We've talked about
your drag aesthetic.
We've had many arguments
about it.
I'm pushing you to do something,
yeah, okay, off-brand maybe
or something
you wouldn't do normally.
- Outside
of this competition,
Michelle and I have worked
a lot together.
She definitely tries to do
the mother hen thing
with my aesthetic.
- While we are here to celebrate
all that makes you different,
it's still a competition.
- I also don't want you
to think
that I am being a brat
or unappreciative.
The reason why
I get so emotional
is because
I do care about you.
And going back
to getting judged by you,
the dynamic
is completely different.
- It is!
- And it's fucking with me!
- Again, I can only
apologize
if it came out harsher
than it was intended.
I'm apologizing to you
in front of fucking cameras.
I don't even apologize
to my children.
That makes me sad.
- I know.
It makes me sad.
I'm not even, like, myself.
I'm not Eeyore.
Like, I'm sick of it.
Like, I'm, like, walking around
with puffy-ass fucking eyes.
I'm trying to smile
and shit
looking like
a fuckin swollen baby.
- Tomorrow's--
You're so stupid.
Tomorrow is another day.
I don't want you to wake up
tomorrow morning
and go, what did I do?
And that's a possibility.
- I don't want to put Michelle
or myself in a position
to where either one of us
have to compromise.
This is her job.
She's a judge.
I'd be damned
if I go down that runway
and her look at me
and be like, fuck,
I got to take easy
because she's the chiona.
There's a part of me
that's saying, like,
can I stick it out?
- Coming up...
- Can I be honest?
I think your Joan Crawford
is more like...
It's too you.
- I'm definitely noticing,
working with Phi Phi,
she's very strategic.
- I'm just saying,
you sounded like Alyssa.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Hi, Tatianna.
- Hello, Ru.
- The last time
you played Snatch Game,
your Britney was exquisite.
You won the challenge.
How are you gonna repeat
your success?
- I'm doing Ariana Grande.
- Oh, my God,
of course you are.
- Yeah.
- What are her
catch phrases?
- She doesn't have
too many catch phrases,
but she's given
a lot of funny moments.
- I have a feeling that for
the decades since you were on,
that you have been waiting
for this moment
to see all these bitches
with your hands.
Am I right?
- Yeah,
to a certain extent.
I realized never try to win over
the naysayers and the haters.
Put all of your energy
into impressing the people
who were supporters of you
from the beginning.
- That is very wise,
because you know what?
I ain't got time
for the people who hate me.
I'm too busy loving
the people who love me.
- Exactly.
- Are we gonna see you with
them hands on the Snatch Game?
- Oh, yes.
- Make it funny.
- Definitely.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- (laughs)
Hey, Roxxxy.
- Hola, mi amor.
Como estas?
- You won $10,000 last week.
- Oh, my God.
- You had to also
eliminate a queen.
- A girl that I've known
since I started drag.
- Wow.
- And I might not have that
friendship because of it.
- But, honestly,
she's a seasoned queen.
She knows
how this competition works.
Do you really think that
she will hold it against you?
- I know if she
was thinking like me,
I would think
that's my girl, Roxxxy.
Since she won,
maybe she'll keep me.
Like, you know,
she's on my side.
- Now, last time you played
Snatch Game, you did very well.
- Boom! Yes!
- Yes, you did
Tamara Braxton.
- Tamara Braxton, yes.
- I have no idea.
- A Latina.
I love Ellen.
- I don't know.
- Sofia Vergara.
- Of course.
- Oh, my God.
- I cannot wait to see you
out there in the Snatch Game.
Just make me laugh.
- I will.
- All right.
- I promise.
- Thanks, Roxxxy.
- Thank you.
- All right,
listen up, ladies.
In a few moments,
I'll meet you
on the set of Snatch Game,
where we will be joined
by two legendary queens.
"Drag Race All Stars"
Raven and Juju
will be your celebrities.
- Oh, my God.
- Juju and Raven
are going to be here?
Fuck.
It's gonna be
a son of a bitch.
- So good luck
and don't fuck it up.
- Whoo.
- Adore finally comes back
into the work room.
She looks like she had just
been crying or something.
- Um, I just don't feel
like I'm in it.
It was something different than
I thought it was going to be.
I think I need to go.
I'm leaving "RuPaul's
Drag Race All Stars 2."
I feel like shit.
- I love you,
but I don't want you
to give in to giving up.
- I just don't think
that this is for me.
It's so hard to say goodbye
to everybody.
Good luck.
- Oh.
- I know that not everybody is
going to agree with me, but...
- It's disappointing.
This is a huge opportunity
that we've been given,
and so many people wish
they could've been here.
It does suck because,
you know,
he's a good friend of mine.
But at the same time,
just one bitch down
who also was
a strong competitor.
So I'm just that
much closer to the crown.
- How do you feel?
Can I be honest with you?
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm just gonna be honest.
I think your Joan Crawford
is more like...
It's too you.
- (scoffs)
- I don't want you, like,
offended by what I said.
- Oh, I'm not offended.
- Okay.
I'm just saying, like,
you sounded like a Alyssa.
- So...
- I'm definitely noticing,
working with Phi Phi,
she's very strategic
in this competition.
She's dropping
little comments,
I think in an effort to
make us a little insecure.
- Are you sure?
I'm second guessing
this accent.
I am totally getting
in my head about it.
I'm thinking I am going
to change my character
completely.
- Coming up...
- You know,
I'm black by injection.
(all laugh)
- (laughs)
- Where's the body?
- Barbara, please.
- (laughs)
(RuPaul laughs)
- Welcome to the "All Star"
edition of Snatch Game.
Let's meet our contestants.
A stay-at-home mom
from Riverside,
California, Raven.
And a flight attendant
who likes long walks
on the beach,
big dicks
and fried chicken, Jujubee.
- Hi.
- Ladies, are you ready
to meet our stars?
- Yes!
- Praise the Lord,
it's Tammy Faye Baker.
- Forget it.
- Are you wearing makeup?
- Just a little Chapstick.
- My goodness,
you are one of my favorites.
- I know. (sobs)
- Moving on, the original
blonde bombshell,
Mae West is here.
- Well, howdy-doo, Ru?
- How's my little chickadee?
- When I'm good, I'm good,
but when I'm bad, I get
a serious venereal disease.
- (laughs)
Next, the totally whacky
and original Bjork is here.
- I love your suit.
- Thank you.
- It reminds me of the lining
of my small intestine.
- (laughs)
Next, the Long Island
medium, Teresa Caputo.
- Ru, does December 25th
mean anything to you?
- Yes, actually it does.
- Did you receive a gift
on that day?
- I absolutely received
a gift on that day.
- I got a gift.
- Wow.
- Don't mess up my hair,
please.
- Sorry.
- Now, ladies and gentleman,
the legendary Joan Crawford.
How are the kids, Joan?
- Deliberately
trying to embarrass me
in front of these reporters.
- Oh-ho-ho!
- I fought worst monsters
for years in Hollywood.
- Yes, I know.
- Barbara, please.
- (laughs)
- Don't fuck with me,
fellas.
- (laughs)
All right, now TV's
toughest legal eagle,
Nancy Grace is here,
ladies and gentlemen.
- Breaking news, we need
to get down to the basics
of the alleged child abuse.
- Joan Crawford?
- Where's the body?
- Christina,
bring me the ax.
No!
- Moving on down,
Ariana Grande is here.
- Hi, Ru.
- Are you ready
to break free?
- Yeah.
- Next, the one and only
Alaska 5000.
- Hi-ee.
- Roxxxy Andrews total
last minute decision
to switch to Alaska.
- I just have to ask,
is that a wig on your head?
- Uh, if you're not
wearing wigs,
then you're not doing drag.
- Girl, even I know
that Alaska's song
is "this is not a wig,
this is my hair."
- What's the big idea?
- Yeah. (laughs)
All right,
let's play Snatch Game.
Juju, this is for you.
- Okay.
- Those sexy
Kardashian sisters
are starring in a new sci-fi
epic called "Star blank."
Pens down, celebrities.
Okay, Jujubee.
- I'm gonna do it.
"Star Booty."
- "Star Booty."
- Uh-huh, girl.
- Let's go
to the celebrities
and see if you have
any matches on that.
- Zero.
- Joan Crawford.
"Star Booty."
That's a match.
You got it, lady.
- You think you're clever,
don't you?
- (laughs)
- Well, think again.
- Let's go on down to--
Oh, Alaska,
what have you done with
your lipstick, darling?
- Oh, my makeup is terrible.
Now, Ru, I didn't put booty,
but I did put anus,
available on iTunes.
- You know, close,
but not a match.
- Aw.
- Missed it by this much.
- Hi-ee.
- Okay, here we go.
Ariana Grande,
oh, she's got a doughnut.
You're licking the doughnut.
- I love doughnuts.
- You love doughnuts.
- And I love America.
- What's your favorite thing
about America?
- Oh, gosh, the people,
the places, the things.
- Yes.
- Nouns.
- Yeah. (laughs)
So I just, you know,
I drew a doughnut.
- "Star Doughnuts"
is not a match.
All right, let's move
on down to Nancy Grace.
- This just in.
I wrote "Star Injections."
- "Star Injections."
- Illegal injections
of silicone into the body.
- You know,
I'm black by injection.
- Oh! (laughs)
This is going to be
for Raven.
The pit crew have spent way too
much time around drag queens.
Now, before they slip on their
Andrew Christian underwear,
they blank. Raven.
- They take a very tasteful
photo of their nether regions
so that they can post it
online.
They take a selfie.
- They take a selfie.
Let's see if you've got
any matches over here.
- All right,
Tammy Faye Baker.
- As it says in the book,
before thou puteth oneth
a thongeth...
- Yes, uh-huh, yes.
- Thou must pray.
- Pray.
Yeah, I got to pray
before I put on my underwear.
Most of the time
they don't even fit anymore
they're so filled
with God's love.
- Yes, that is not a match,
but a very, very good answer.
It's a very good answer.
- I just--
- You tried your best, darling.
- I tried.
- Moving on down to Bjork.
- Actually, I think
I have the right answer.
- Okay, you have
the right answer?
- I said they remove
their testicles.
- Oh, the judges say, no,
Bjork.
- Oh, I just put mine here.
- You have testicles?
- Sometimes I don't understand
anything about science.
- I'm sorry, Bjork,
but not a match, darling.
- Oh, that's fine.
- (laughs)
Hey, let's move on down
to the Long Island medium.
- Now, we've never met
before,
so I want everybody
to know this.
- Yes.
- I just know exactly what,
you know,
the producers and the background
checkers told me.
- Uh, okay.
- I mean, the spirits
are telling me a selfie.
- A selfie, wow.
- Yes, the spirits are
telling me a--thank you.
- That's uncanny.
That's spooky, isn't it?
- I'm telling you,
I have a gift.
- Yay.
- Let's move on
to Joan Crawford.
What do you say?
- Clean all the wire hangers
out of the closet.
- Wire hangers, Joan?
- No wire hangers ever!
Why?
- Well, that don't make
no kind of sense,
but it sure is
entertaining.
It's just--
- This ain't my first time.
- Yes, yes, at the where?
- At the Snatch Game.
- (laughs)
All right. Jujubee, are
you ready for your question?
- Mm-hmm.
- My play cousin Tornesia
is such a party animal.
When mosquitoes bite her,
they have to go to blank.
Okay, Jujubee.
- The clinic.
- Yes! Good answer.
- Right.
- Let's go to Mae West.
- Well, I'm very happy to say
they have to go to the clinic.
- Oh, we got a match.
- You know, I go to the one on
San Vicente and Santa Monica,
you know what I mean,
Jujubee?
You've been there.
I seen you there a few times.
- Why do you go there,
Mae West?
- 'Cause after your tenth visit,
you get one free, oh.
- (laughs)
Fabulous. All right.
Let's move on down to Bjork.
- I'm pretty excited
'cause I also said clinic.
- You said clinic!
- Yeah.
How many bones do I win?
- How many bones
do you want? Oh.
See you after the show,
bubbles, oh.
Ooh.
- Did you hear that, Bjork?
- I'm down for anything,
especially I'd like
to eat her hair.
It looks like pastrami.
- Something else
looks like pastrami, too.
- (trilling)
- Ow. (gargles) Brrr.
- (laughs)
Let's move on down
to Nancy Grace.
- This just in.
- Oh.
- She had to go to Casey
Anthony's defense attorney.
She partied so hard, RuPaul,
two days after
the child is missing,
she is drinking at the bar.
- Unfortunately,
that is not a match.
- But we do have DNA match,
and that's coming up next
after the commercial break.
Thank you.
- Oh, okay.
Now, Raven, the next question
is a video from Bianca Del Rio.
- Tammy Brown is so unusual,
when she was abducted
by aliens, she blanked them.
- All right, stars.
Write down your answers.
All right, Raven.
- She shaka-buku'd them.
- (laughs)
Let's go on over here
to the Long Island medium.
Are you writing
something down?
- No, no.
- Oh.
Well, yeah, 'cause
you're supposed to match--
- The spirits are telling
shaka-buku them.
- I thought
I saw you writing.
- You didn't seen anything,
Ru, I'm so sorry.
- I didn't anything.
- See, it's the spirits.
- (laughs) All right.
Ariana Grande.
- I put she sang to them?
- Nice try, but no match.
Sorry, Raven.
- Well, that's what
I would've done.
- Let's hear
you sing to them.
- (no sound)
- Oh.
- The last time I went
that high,
one of my dogs died.
- What did you do
to the body?
- Yes, what did you do
with the body?
- (snorts)
I'm sorry. What?
- What did you do
with the body?
- Where's the body
of your dog?
- Tatianna's missing
the mark hardcore.
There's no jokes
coming out of her mouth,
and whatever our jokes
are not landing anywhere.
- Thank you so much.
- Let's move on down
to Alaska.
- She said, hi-ee.
- She said, hi-ee to them.
- Ru is throwing watermelons
down the line,
and, whoo,
swing and a miss.
It's like Little League
softball,
and she has
no arms or legs.
It's sad.
- You still have one more
chance with Mae West.
- Well, Ru, I gotta say,
she probed them
with her tootsie-loo.
- (laughs)
Why dontcha come on up
and fuck me
in the ass sometime?
- (laughs)
You don't beat around
the bush, do you, baby?
- I beat around the bush
all the time.
What are you talking about?
- (laughs)
Okay, kids, our time is up.
The winner
of Snatch Game is...
- Whoo! Hallelu,
I'm back, Ru! Yes!
- She-Angela!
- Hallelu.
- Well, I guess there you
have it, ladies and gentlemen.
Thanks for watching,
everybody.
See you next time
on Snatch Game.
- See you tomorrow, friends.
- Bye.
- Coming up...
- This competition is going
to be even more difficult
because everybody's a judge.
- What do you guys think about,
like, the strategy?
Are you guys still going to
go with the weakest link?
- If I win, I'm eliminating
the strongest competitor.
(RuPaul laughs)
- (sighs)
-  It's a runway day,
it's a runway day
Today is elimination day,
so, girl, you better
bring it to the runway.
And it's going to be
a latex extravaganza.
- Will you shut
all the way up?
- What are you doing?
- Girl,
she is Joan Crawford.
Do you sleep
in a bucket of ice?
- You better get it,
Hannibal Lector.
You look great.
Are you wearing that
down the runway, mama?
- (laughs)
- I can't with you.
- You didn't ever do
a beauty mask, girl?
- Obviously not.
(all laugh)
- What do you guys think
about, like, the strategy
and, like, how you're
gonna vote people off?
Are you guys still going to
go with the weakest link and--
- If I win, I'm eliminating
the strongest competitor.
- Are you?
- Are you being serious?
- No.
- Oh.
(all laugh)
- Now, is it whoever's
weakest in the challenge
or challenge plus runway
or challenge
divided by runway time two?
- That's a great question.
- Whoever accumulates
the most points.
- All right.
- Is safe.
It's an accumulative
contest.
- But that's a really good
question.
What factor
does the runway play?
- If it's a tie, you gotta
work it with the runway.
- Yeah.
- Okay, that's fair.
- This competition is going
to be even more difficult
because everybody's
a judge now.
I would like to think
that I would be Khaleesi,
but I could go over to
the Lannister side, too.
Ugh.
- The only point
in me coming on the show
is to show
that I'm a monster.
- (laughs)
- I'll tell you one thing.
If I win the challenge,
I'm taking all three
of those lipsticks.
Triple elimination.
(snap, snap, snap)
- how did it feel being in front
of Raven and Juju yesterday?
- Right. That's crazy.
- Half of it was, like,
yay, hello, old friends.
And then, the other half
was like,
oh, this is kind of
nerve-wracking.
It's a little bit of dj vu
because Juju and Raven
are also Season 2 girls.
- Were you friends with them
on Season 2?
- Oh, yeah. I was really close
with Jujubee,
and me and Raven
had a splendid relationship.
(all laugh)
- You know what I think
is cool for you
is that, like, there's
potentially the opportunity
for you to gain
a whole new fan base
because the fans
are so fucking young now.
- Yeah.
- And a lot of them,
they've just started
watching the show
at, like, Season 5, 6, 7.
You know what I mean?
So, like--
- 4, 5, 6.
- It's like a rebirth.
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
And that's why I'm kind of
taking this competition
so seriously is 'cause I really
want to reintroduce myself
to the world.
The stakes for me in this
elimination are high.
I need to be here.
I need to be given a chance
to show everyone I'm total
"All Star" material.
- This was not intentional.
- Didn't you hear me
talking about it?
- No, I didn't hear you
talking about it.
I'll show you my notebook.
I drew pictures of it
last night, honey.
- Oh.
- Do you guys think it's worth
winning the lip sync
and the 10 grand
to send someone home, Katya?
- Yes, definitely.
- I have to do it.
- Thank you. Me, too.
- Definitely.
- Me, too.
- I have to do it and--
- It's a competition.
- Thank you. Me, too.
- That's it.
- Give me a high five.
- But you know what, you guys
are, like, high fiving stuff,
but everybody
feels different about it.
Like, for me--
- No, it's not.
- But we're here to--
- Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Can I finish?
I'm so sorry.
We're gonna get this money
afterwards.
Let's be real.
For me, I just couldn't--
It's hard 'cause I wouldn't
want to be, like,
well, sorry, girl.
You know what I mean?
- Well, it's not about
the cash tip, though.
It's about the end
of the finish line.
- Thank you.
- And I guess that's why
we're all different.
- We all have different feelings
about different things,
and I guess
that's how that is.
I don't know.
I feel like my words are getting
twisted, but never mind.
- Just take a deep breath
and go, it's gonna be
a lovely runway, gal.
- (laughs)
- Oh!
(RuPaul laughs)
-  Cover girl, put the bass
in your walk
Cover girl, put the bass
Head to toe,
let your whole body talk
Cover girl
- Whoo!
- Girl, what?
(applause)
- Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul's
Drag Race All Stars."
Michelle Visage,
what's new, pussycat?
- You, my darling,
are the supreme All Star.
- Style superstar
Carson Kressley,
are you feeling judgy,
darling?
- I'm feeling joodgy.
Is that okay?
- I love it.
The incredible
Todrick Hall.
Are you ready for more?
- Ru, I was born ready
and the rest...
- Is draw.
And he's back.
Ross Matthews,
how you doing?
- Oh, honey,
you know I'm back.
I am a sucker
for the Snatch.
- (laughs)
This week,
we challenged our queens
to give us
imitations of life,
and tonight,
in latex eleganza,
they're ready to burn rubber
on the runway.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
First up, Phi Phi O'Hara.
Oh. She's got all her ducks
in a row.
- I'd hate to see the bill
for that.
- (laughs)
- This costume
is totally me:
fun and, like,
almost pinup-y.
And I wanted the jewelry
to speak for itself.
I feel super skinny and then
the booty is, like, on point.
I feel so adorable.
- I wonder if you put her
in a bathtub, she'll float.
- Well, if it quacks
like a duck...
- Yeah.
- Quack quack.
- Roxxxy Andrews.
Look at that body!
- Look at that
hourglass shape.
- It's inner tubular.
- I am fixing to sell
this garment, darling.
I've got
my big nineties hair on.
I'm feeling
total gothic glam.
very Violet Chachki,
but the plus-sized thick
and juicy Violet Chachki.
- Well, if a tire
goes out on my car,
I'll know who to call.
- She's ribbed
for your pleasure.
- Yes, she is.
- Alyssa Edwards.
Ooh.
- Her lips don't lie.
- No.
- That dress is a roadmap
for her man.
- Oh, I can read her lips
from here.
- Yeah. (laughs)
Pow, right in the kisser.
- I am living.
I'm colorful, I'm vibrant,
ferocious.
I got my dress on
with the lips
'cause you know
I got plenty of secrets.
I got to hold back some
I keep in the vault
just in case.
- I want to kiss her
all over.
- Or just kiss her ass.
(all laugh)
- Up next, Katya.
She's into water sports.
- Oh, it's Esther Williams'
cousin, Fister Williams.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Wow. Look at those
breast strokes.
- Our cycles
are synchronized.
- I'm giving you a skin tight
sea foam green
Esther Williams
underwater fantasy.
My waist is cinched,
my nose is pinched,
and my body
is absolutely drenched in sweat.
- Her look is making me wet.
- Take a dip
in the cool waters of Katya.
(all laugh)
Tatianna.
- She's a tramp, a scamp
and a bit of a...
- Vamp.
- Uh-huh.
- That girl is poison.
- My latex look
is real dark lady,
and I'm feeling
a little sexy.
Also, it totally
shows off the fact
that I haven't eaten in a week,
so I'm feeling cute.
- She's like
Johnny Gill said,
you better rub her
the right way.
(all laugh)
- That's her chastity dress.
- Alaska, fashion.
- Yes.
- Just gotta do something
about that uni-brow.
- She's gotta
get that plucked.
- This is totally
Blade Rubber.
(all laugh)
- Yes.
- I'm wearing head to toe
rubber latex
geometrical severe fantasy.
I'm nine parts super model
and one part robot
and ready for insertion.
- Why are her gloves so--
oh, oh, I get it.
(all laugh)
- Bye-ee.
Designed for your pleather.
Ginger Minj.
- She's gone platinum.
- I like the mermaid cut
or is it uncut?
(all laugh)
- I'm just walking
so eleg-wently down the runway.
This gown hugs every
single curve in my body.
I have never felt more beautiful
in my entire life.
- Yeah, girl.
- Yes, you better rub
that lamp, honey.
- Something's
gonna come out.
(all laugh)
- Detox.
(gasp) Yes, mama!
- Raccoon eleganza.
- Now, that is a thigh gap,
Beyonce.
(all laugh)
- My whole vibe
for this look
is, like, this Amazonian
warrior goddess,
and I feel really fierce.
My tuck is right.
I'm brilliant.
I'm beautiful.
Because why?
I'm Detox.
- Now, that's what I call
an apple bottom.
- Red delicious.
-  Sexy, sexy drag queen
- Coming up...
- Unbelievable,
like breathtaking.
- I loved this runway look.
- Um, it was a little
Nancy Gross.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Welcome, ladies.
I want to remind you
why we are all here.
I invited you to "All Stars"
because I believe you are
the best of the best.
With this invitation
comes great responsibility,
and I've fought
my entire life
to not only grow my career,
but to build something that
could help launch others.
Every week that you're here
is another opportunity
to build your brand and legacy.
But there are no
free passes, ladies.
This is still a competition.
And now,
I need to hear from you.
Ladies, are you in it
to win it?
- Yes!
- Good. That's what
I wanted to hear.
Now, when I call your name,
please step forward.
Alyssa Edwards, Ginger Minj.
You are safe.
Please step
to the back of the stage.
The rest of you represent
the tops and the bottoms
of the week.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
First up, Phi Phi O'Hara.
- Tonight,
on an "All Star" stage,
coming out in a latex swimsuit
didn't make me very happy.
- Okay.
- Your makeup is a little off
tonight, too.
Your contouring's
so severe for you.
- I was there for your Gaga,
so I was looking at your
Snatch real close, okay?
My face
was right up in there.
Teresa Caputo
is the perfect kind of person
to pick for the Snatch Game,
and you did a great job with it.
So consistent
all the way through.
- Yay.
- All right.
Up next, Roxxxy Andrews.
- Hey.
- This whole runway look,
like, when I first saw you
come out, I was like, eh.
I don't know.
Like, it's maybe a little too,
like, dead on and literal
when you think of latex.
But the way
you put it all together
made for a better outfit
than just what this dress is.
- It was a bumpy
Snatch Game for you.
It's like, ooh, it just didn't
feel like a yay kind of thing.
- Yeah.
- The thing about Alaska,
she's funny, quick, snappy.
There's a lot
of little surprises
that you get with Alaska
that I didn't get
from that performance.
- In the work room, you said
you were gonna do Sofia Vergara,
but you changed your mind.
- I changed because
something told me
I would've bombed Sofia,
like, worse than
I would've done Alaska.
- When you come into
this competition,
you already know that you're
going to be doing Snatch Game,
so maybe
it would've been wise
to really think about that
before yesterday.
- Up next, Katya.
- I love this runway look
so much.
I like
when people do something
that's what
you're not expecting.
And what you gave us
was, like,
this Esther Williams moment
with the full cap.
And you have, like,
the nose thing,
which is a genius little touch
that I expect from Katya.
So right on.
Snatch Game.
I loved the Snatch Game.
When I think of Bjork,
I think of, like,
an Icelandic toddler on LSD,
and you gave me that.
- You're just brilliant.
You're an artist and all of your
answers were just so psychotic,
and I just love everything
that you do.
- Whether people knew
who Bjork was or not,
we all understood
exactly what you were doing,
and that's what makes
a really good characterization.
It was fabulous.
- Thank you so much.
(all laugh)
- Up next, Tatianna.
- Tonight on the runway,
it's kind of basic.
It's something you'd see in a
Fredrick's catalog or something.
- Okay.
- To me, it doesn't scream
Tatianna in any way.
Your look for Ariana Grande,
spot on.
So the characterization
was there for me.
I think where you lost it
were the comebacks.
- There were moments where
Ru would totally set you up
and you just had to, like,
spike it back over the net,
and that didn't happen
for me.
I can't believe I just used
a sports reference.
That's never happened.
- I'm sorry.
(sniffles)
This means so much
and I fucked it up.
- Don't be sorry.
Be fierce because
you are an "All Star."
Thank you, Tatianna.
- Thank you.
- Up next, Alaska.
- I loved this runway look,
and I think
what's so great about you
is that you're versatile.
I know. Big surprise.
But yes, the details.
The dress, the makeup,
the dye line of the hair,
it's chic and glamorous.
The only callout
on the look,
I would've loved,
like, a cooler shoe.
- Me, too.
- Right? I know, I know.
- The Snatch Game.
It was brilliant from
the beginning to the end.
It was just an amalgamation
of sheer genius.
- You did something
really smart.
You not only entertained us,
but you educated
our audience out there,
who may not know
who Mae West is.
- Mae West now, for me,
is you doing Mae West.
Every time I go through
a drive thru now,
I'm gonna go,
oh, I want a number one-uh.
- Drive up
and see me some time.
- Super size me some time.
- Up next, Detox.
- Let's talk about
this look right now,
which I'm living for.
It's like the epitome of,
like, latex glamour.
- Unbelievable.
Like, breathtaking
when you walked out.
It was just like
an oil painting.
Like a perverted
oil painting.
- You just look phenomenal.
You killed it.
- Thank you very much.
- And I just want to know,
where did you put it?
- Oh, you know where it is.
(all laugh)
- The Nancy Grace.
At first, I was like,
oh, my God,
Nancy Grace
was from Staten Island?
You're, like, listen to me.
- In the beginning, it was
a little Nancy Gross, you know.
It wasn't really there yet,
but you found your way.
- It wasn't the right voice, but
it was kind of the right person,
so I'm gonna give you
a C on that.
- Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
I've made some decisions.
Katya, Alaska,
you are the top two
"All Stars" of the week.
(applause)
Congratulations.
You've each won
two VIP tickets
to Cirque du Soliel's
sexy adult cabaret "Zumanity,"
including airfare and deluxe
Las Vegas accommodations.
- Wow, cool.
- Phi Phi O'Hara,
you lucky duck, you're safe.
That means Roxxxy Andrews,
Tatianna, Detox,
you are in the bottom three.
Katya and Alaska,
each of you needs to decide
which of the bottom three
you'll eliminate
if you win the lip sync.
So while you queens
deliberate in the work room,
the judges and I
will enjoy root beer floats.
You may leave the stage.
Coming up...
- I know that we're looking
at this Rolaskatox situation,
but that was
a long time ago.
- She can say that
all she wants to,
but in the end,
she's not going to send home
her best friend here.
- Now win this lip sync.
- Okay.
(RuPaul laughs)
- It's an odd feeling
being in the top,
and then coming into
the work room for deliberation.
- Thrilled.
- Because
I'm one of the people
who has to make a decision
about some other people
in the room.
- Tatianna, Roxxxy and Detox
are in the bottom.
I don't necessarily agree that
Detox should be in the bottom.
Her runway destroyed.
"National Geographic"
meets "Italian Vogue"
meets
"Better Homes and Gardens."
Flawless.
- One of y'all
is about to get $10,000.
- Yeah.
- When you win a challenge,
it's just so,
like, exciting.
And now it's sort of,
like, much heavier
because there's this huge
responsibility attached to it.
I would like to have a moment
with each of you
on the other sofa.
So whoever
wants to come first.
- Well, I'm here, I guess.
- Hi.
- Hi, honey.
I wasn't expecting
to see you in the bottom.
- Neither was I,
but at the same time,
I feel good enough
that I wasn't the worst
and I looked the best today.
(laughs)
- Hallelu.
- Do you know what I mean?
- And it's crazy
because it's like
this, like,
Rolaskatox-esque moment.
- I know. I was
just about to say. Mm-hmm.
- But whatever decision
is made,
that is not
going to be favoritism.
- Right, and I respect
whatever decision it is
that you come up with.
- Well, it's such a shame
I fucking hate you.
- Should I start
packing now or--
- (laughs)
You probably should.
- Shall I send over
the next clown?
- Yeah, sure.
- Are you sure
you're gonna wear that?
- I'm gonna see
if I can get changed,
because this little
hobble dress
is not gonna be
very enter-tainting.
- Do you need help?
- Yes. Would you, please?
- How are you doing?
- Um, I expected it.
- You did?
- I definitely know I was
one of the weaker links, so...
- Whatever decision is made,
it's not coming
because of favoritism
or anything like that.
- Just do
what you feel is right.
But congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Now win this lip sync.
Win it.
- Okay.
- Win it.
I'm hoping we're gonna
stay true to what we said,
because I feel like
the girl who got the harshest
critiques was Tatianna.
So if we're sticking
through to our plan,
I should be good to go.
- Hi, how are you?
- Um, not good.
- I'm sorry
that you're in the bottom.
I know that we're looking at
this Rolaskatox-esque situation,
but that was
a long time ago,
and I want you to know
that whatever happens,
it's not based on friends
and family discounts
or, you know, favoritism
or anything like that.
- Yeah.
She can say that
all she wants to,
but in the end,
she's not going to send home
her best friend here.
- So I just want you
to know that.
- I trust it'll be
a fair decision.
- I think you're stunning
and really cool.
- Sorry.
Stupid. Go ahead.
- Why do you feel stupid,
though?
- 'Cause I just feel like
I didn't do my best.
In something like this,
you can't really fuck up.
Like, I need this.
I really want this.
- Right. You've been here
and you've held your own.
- I just wanted to show more
'cause there's so much more.
And I hope that
I get the opportunity,
but if I don't, I get why.
- I love you a lot.
- I love you, too.
- I'm not gonna lie.
There's definitely
a part of me
that's enjoying
this potential power situation.
- Girl, no!
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's just because I'm
so used to being terrified
and, like, in the grip
of total anxiety here.
And now I feel like...
I have to say
there is a part of me
that is very intrigued
and attracted
and seduced
by this new power.
(laughs)
But I will do
the fair thing.
- I just want to tell you,
you know,
I want to prove how much
I'm a different person
than I am from my season.
- Uh-huh.
- And I feel like my time
is too short still.
I know I am in the bottom,
and I felt like all I could do
was my runway today and--
- It's not personal.
It's just we're all here.
We're all professional
drag queens with careers,
and we can evaluate
what's entertaining
and what's not entertaining.
- It's 50/50.
I could be going home.
You never know how these girls
are gonna play the game,
and I'm terrified.
- Next!
Tell me why you should be
America's next top model.
- Oh, you...
(laughs)
- I know you're feeling
terrible.
- Yeah. I feel like...
almost because
I am from an earlier season
and I was so young
that I do--
and I've been saying
this whole time,
like, I don't have
to prove anything to anyone,
but I kind of do.
I thought I was on
a good roll here last week,
and there's so much more
that I have
that's, like, out of the box
and different for Tatianna
that I want the world
to see
and I kind of need
the world to see.
This competition
means so much to me.
I don't want to go home.
I'm not ready to go home.
I can't go home right now.
- I knew coming in here
that, like, everybody's
gonna be so good
that it's just like you
don't know what the hell.
From week to week, it's going
to be a complete roller coaster.
- I don't want to make it,
like, harder on you,
if you're feeling, like,
towards one way or another.
Don't think that,
like, this is, like,
trying to wane you,
'cause it's not.
- No, no, no.
'Cause I know you.
- 'Cause it's not.
I would like
to really not have that.
- Yeah, I know you.
Here, give me a hug.
- Can we get
a Code 69 progress?
(all laugh)
- Oh, silencio.
Silencio.
Bring back my girls-uh.
- If I win this lip sync,
someone's going home
because of me.
I've made up my mind,
but it's really hard
having that decision
on my head.
- I have to make the decision
about who to send home.
It's really tough,
but it's still a competition
and I have to make sure
that every decision I make
is the right one.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Welcome back, ladies.
Two top "All Stars"
stand before me.
Ladies, this is your chance
to impress me, win $10,000,
and earn the power
to give one of
the bottom queens the chop.
The time has come
to lip sync
(echoing)
for your legacy.
- I'm excited to lip sync
against Alaska.
I am feeling myself.
I am preparing the world
to gag on my legacy,
which involves
a line of platform jellies
in every size,
color and shape.
- I know that I really need
to turn it out.
There's no question that
I want to win the lip sync.
It's another opportunity
to impress the judges.
- Good luck.
Don't fuck it up.
-  Ah, freak out
Le freak, c'est chic
Freak out
All that pressure
got you down
Has your head
spinning all around
Just come on down,
to 54
Find a spot
out on the floor
Ah, freak out
- I am in the bottom with
two-thirds of Rolaskatox.
So if Alaska
wins this lip sync,
the chances are
I'm being sent home.
- Whoo!
-  I said, freak
- I'm terrified.
You never know how these girls
are gonna play the game.
It's so early in it.
Are they gonna eliminate
a bigger threat?
-  Now, freak
All that pressure
got you down
Just come on down
to 54
Find a spot
out on the floor
Ah, freak out
(all laugh)
Le freak, c'est chic
Freak out
Ah, freak out
(all laugh)
- Yeah!
(applause)
- Ladies, I have made
my decision.
Alaska,
you're a winner, baby.
(applause)
Con-drag-ulations.
You've earned a cash tip
of $10,000.
- Thank you.
There is sort of
a bittersweet feeling right now,
because I love
winning challenges,
but it also means
I have to send somebody home.
- Katya, you're safe.
- Thank you.
- You may join
the other girls.
(applause)
Will the bottom three
please step forward?
Alaska, with great power
comes great responsibility.
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
- Like you've said
many times,
"RuPaul's Drag Race" is
a microcosm of the real world.
And in the real world,
sometimes we have to make
really difficult decisions,
and tonight
is one of those times.
I've taken
into consideration
the performances
in the Snatch Game
and on the main stage
and I've most importantly
taken the judges critiques
into consideration tonight.
(exhales)
The queen
that I have chosen...
Is Tatianna.
- Tatianna.
- Yep.
- As it is written,
so it shall be done.
See me with them hands,
girl.
Now sashay away.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
(applause)
The most disappointing part
about being eliminated
this early in the competition
is definitely
I don't have the ability
to show everything
that I have to offer.
Not just
in the way of clothing,
but I have a lot more
personality and talent
that I didn't get the chance
to feature.
- Con-drag-ulations,
"All Stars."
Keep freaking me out
and you could find yourself
in the "Drag Race"
hall of fame.
Now, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen
up in here?
- Amen.
- Now, let the music play.
-  Throw your hands up
Time to get down
Time to get down,
down, down, down, down
- I would say to Ru, thank you
so much for having me again.
It was great seeing you
and your, uh...
(alarm)
- Ooh, girl.
Tatianna, girl,
all is not lost,
so stay thirsty, girl,
'cause you still
have a chance to return
for your revenge.
- Are you serious?
- (evil laugh)
Wait, does this mean
I get to come back?
I can.