- Hello, hello, hello.
- Whoo!
- Critics have called
"Drag Race" the best show on TV.
- Yay!
- When I'm good, I'm good,
but when I'm bad, I get
a serous venereal disease.
- And this season,
the All Stars kept us gagging.
You'll be eliminating...
each other.
- I fucked up this week, man.
I fucked up.
- Party.
- I'm not holding shit back.
Oh, at all.
- And gagging.
- If you thought it was
personal, absolutely not.
- Can I be completely honest?
I am sick of hearing them say
you can wear shit on stage,
but it's okay
'cause you're Alyssa.
- What?
Oh, my God!
- Oh, my fucking God.
- What is going on here?
- Oh.
- And gagging for more.
- Aah!
- What the hell?
- Tonight, the queens
have reunited to pop off.
- If you want to say that
I'm fake, I have this to say.
- And spill the T.
- You think you're clever,
don't you, bitch?
- Adore Delano.
- I believe in free love.
- You do?
- I do.
- Alyssa Edwards.
- Don't say I get a free pass
because I'm funny.
- Coco Montresse.
- It didn't sound like
there was any humility there.
It was like,
I got that bitch.
- Detox.
- It's a pass, though.
It's judged
a little differently.
- Ginger Minj.
- You do play a dirty game.
- Katya.
- No, the second part
was amazing.
The first part
was utter bullshit.
- Roxxxy Andrews.
- You're going to regret this.
Don't do this.
- Tatianna.
- Oh, she pretty.
We've seen what she's got.
- And she's a winner, baby.
Alaska.
- I did it.
I would do it again.
- ¶ RuPaul's Drag Race ¶
¶ Start your engines ¶
¶ RuPaul's Drag Race ¶
¶ May the best woman ¶
¶ Best woman win ¶
- Welcome to a good
old fashioned reunion,
celebrating the queens
of "RuPaul's Drag Race
All Stars 2."
Welcome, ladies.
- Hello.
- Yo.
- And congratulations,
Alaska.
(applause)
Oh, and in case any of you are
questioning my qualifications
towards tonight's reunion,
I have one thing to say.
Talk to her.
(cheers and applause)
Now, it's fun
to snatch trophies,
but the proudest achievement
of my career
has been to provide
a platform
that has launched
the careers
of 100 queens
to international stardom.
Now, what you decide to do
with that platform
is up to you.
And tonight, one queen
decided not to join us.
Or as Tatianna would say,
choices.
- (laughs)
- One thing before we start.
If at any point tonight
you think one of your fellow
queens is not telling the T,
feel free to raise
the paddle provided
and call bullshit.
- (laughs)
- For example,
if one of you were to say,
"I blame the edit,"
I'd say, bullshit.
- (laughs)
- See how it works?
Good.
So first, let's start
with the All Star twist
that changed everything.
This season,
you'll be eliminating...
Each other.
- Okay.
Welcome to "All Stars."
- Now, when I revealed that
you'd be eliminating each other,
what did you think?
- Fuck
- (laughs)
That's my first thought
was like, fuck.
But you know, I think that
because it was "All Stars"
and because
we're the best of the best,
we should have expected
there was some kind of twist.
- It was like
a mustard gas bomb went off.
- I've heard of those.
- When it happened, yeah.
I've had mustard gas before.
- Oh, really?
On a hot dog?
- Yeah, totally.
- (laughs)
Now how did you guys
come up with this idea
to base your eliminations
on what the judges said?
- That was my way
of making sense of it.
We were sitting there and we
were all like, this is terrible.
I don't want to do it.
And I was like, well,
we have to do it.
We have to do something.
- Right.
- So I wanted to do it
as though I was sitting
in your position
when you have to
send people home.
- Right.
- Did we all agree to it?
- No.
- I would not have agreed
to that.
That is setting
yourselves up
for a fucking bitch fight,
low key.
Like just watching.
- Which we did.
Because we're stupid.
(laughs)
- Watching the show,
it felt like you guys
were trying
to defer the blame--
- Back to the judges.
- Back to the judges,
and not take responsibility
for the decisions you made.
Is that a fair statement?
- Of course. Yes.
- You throw me the potato,
I'm throwing it back at you,
bitch.
- And I think,
in retrospect, yes,
it does
come across that way.
But in that moment,
it seemed that first day,
like, well, this is fair.
- Right, as
the competition progresses,
friendships and all that
shit comes into play,
and it's tough.
- Well, exactly.
- It's a mother fucker.
- Because Alyssa was accused
of breaking the pact.
Did you ever make the pact?
- Baby,
nothing was notarized,
no contracts were signed,
my attorney was not present.
That was hog wash.
Let me get this gig.
Hold on.
(all laugh)
- Now, the first queen to get
the chop from a fellow All Star
was the legendary
Ms. Coco Montresse.
So, Coco, what was your
proudest moment on the show?
- My proudest moment
was being there.
I didn't want to come--
Before I got the call from you
to come back to the "All Stars,"
I had just gotten out
of the hospital.
I was--
my lungs were failing,
and I fought my way back
to being able to live.
- Oh, my goodness.
- And I didn't want anybody
to know that.
I didn't want to get
any sympathy from anybody.
I wanted to come back
and prove who I was.
And...
(sobs)
I just don't want
to let the people down
who believe in me.
- Well, you haven't
let your fans down.
You haven't
let yourself down.
How are you doing now?
- Much better, much better.
I'm probably about 98%.
I was traveling so much,
I wasn't eating,
and I'm thinking,
oh, I'm invincible.
I've never gotten sick
or anything like that.
You've just got to take care
of yourself.
- Yeah, you need to all
take care of yourselves.
- Yeah, you have to.
- Now, this is a question
from our "Drag Race" super fans.
Do you think that your
elimination was fair?
- The girl that I chose
was Coco.
- And who do you think
should have gone home?
- No, I don't.
I don't think my elimination
was fair.
This is "All Stars,"
and, no, I wasn't my best.
I can be honest
and say that.
It wasn't my best.
But there was one person
in that bottom three
that's not here,
that didn't sing
that great that day,
but that wasn't taken
into consideration.
- Mm-hmm.
- And that hurt me more
than anything in the world.
- I know that
if I was in the top,
I would not have sent you home
that first challenge.
And if you roll back
the tapes,
you can see
who I would have sent home.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause I don't think
she did the worst.
And I would say that
if Phi Phi was here,
and she's not here, but, yeah,
I don't think she did the worst.
- I remember you
saying that.
- Now, after you left,
you tweeted
that some people sell out
their family and friends
for fame
and a little fortune.
Do you still feel that way
about Roxxxy?
- Yes,
to a certain extent, I do.
- Everybody has their right
to their own opinion to me,
and whatever they feel.
As far as the tweets go,
we all get mad,
and we say things
that we don't want to say.
There is a line,
and I've crossed
that line before.
I think a lot of people have
crossed that line before,
and when you put something
out there,
sometimes you want to say,
shit,
I should have thought about
this twice before I did it.
- And sometimes, maybe we
shouldn't say those things
on social media.
Maybe we should pick up the
phone and talk to each other.
- So Roxxxy,
are you cool with Coco?
- I will always be cool
with Coco.
Girl, she could say
the nastiest thing to me,
and the next day I'll be like,
girl, you still my sister,
I love you, ain't nothing
ever going to change.
- I still love you more
than anything in the world.
You will never
lose a friend in me.
- All right,
so we'll be right back.
Coming up....
- What are you feeling
right now?
- Embarrassed.
- You said that I played
a dirty game.
- You do play a dirty game.
- Yep.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Now, the Snatch Game
episode
featured one of the most
shocking moments
in "Drag Race" her-story.
Why are your eyes all red?
- Um...
I didn't--I just didn't expect
it to be like this, I think.
I'm thinking of going home.
- Of tapping out?
- I think so.
I'm sorry.
- What are you feeling
right now?
- Embarrassed.
I just shouldn't--I just felt
like I shouldn't have done that.
I didn't want
to let anybody down.
Nobody goes on "All Stars 2"
and is, like, peacing out.
Like, that's like, whack.
It's not even my style.
Like, I walk and I see how
beautiful and statuesque,
like, Detox and Roxxxy
looked,
and I was just like fuck.
My outfits
that I got made for me,
like, don't even
stand up to this, man.
And I didn't prepare myself
to bring myself back to
the whole elimination process,
the critiquing process,
the goddamn runway.
And, like, I wasn't
mentally prepared
to hear that
from Michelle, either.
- Girl, this is
a 14th Street dress,
like, that doesn't fit you.
I don't care if you're going
to give me your hot body line
or whatever it is.
It's just
I expected more for you.
Do you care?
'Cause, like,
everything's like blasé.
- We just got off tour together
around the world,
so the aerodynamics
are completely changed,
and you have to be brought back
to like, not Kiki home girl,
like, you know,
roadie, homey,
back to like, you know,
you're Michelle Visage,
so you're going to tell me
what the fuck you think.
You know, before, I could
just be like, girl, bye.
I'm going to my
dressing room or whatever.
But here, I have to sit there
and fucking take it,
and I wasn't prepared
for that.
I don't even think
I'm still prepared for that.
- I just got to say,
as an All Star,
you can't really wear something
off the rack.
You have to wear something
that's special
that other people can't get.
That's really
what the meaning
of being a superstar is,
you know?
- Yeah.
- And if it is off the rack,
it has to be altered in a way
that no one else can do it.
- Got it.
- And you know, having seen
your, sort of, melt down,
I could totally relate.
In January, I'll be
doing this for 35 years.
- Jesus Christ.
- And what happens
is you have to build up
that dialogue with yourself
to sit yourself down,
center yourself.
Everything is cool.
You're here
because you earned it.
Don't get it twisted.
You are
the cream of the crop.
You are all All Stars.
So one last question.
Adore, "All Stars 3,"
are you in?
- (laughs)
(evil laugh)
I have no idea.
(all laugh)
I'm probably down.
- (laughs)
Now, the next
shocking moment
was after the Snatch Game
when Tatianna got the chop.
- The queen
that I have chosen...
Is Tatianna.
- So, Tatianna,
do you feel Alaska
based her decision to
send you home on the critiques?
- Which time?
(all laugh)
- Oh, damn!
- The first time,
I think so, yeah.
I did poorly
in the Snatch Game,
and I wasn't the best
on the runway.
The second time, no.
I didn't really get
that negative of a critique,
I didn't feel like.
Choices.
And I think that my runway
was one of the most
entertaining, and like, best.
- Now, Alaska, tell me what
was going through your mind
when you had to eliminate
a girl.
- Well, it was really hard.
- Were you thinking about
the audience looking at you
or were you thinking about
your friendship with the girl?
- If I was thinking about
the audience's reaction
and if I knew what that was,
then I would have probably
made different choices.
- #Choices (laughs)
- But I had no idea.
How could I know?
I had no idea
the way people would be so
galvanized behind Tatianna,
and I'm so happy
that they have.
And if you want to say
that I'm fake,
if you want to say that I'm
a snake, I have this to say.
The only thing fake about me
is this.
- Yes!
- (laughs)
- Oh, little Debbie
Scooter snack.
- Scooter, bitch.
- Medic!
(all laugh)
- She is the queen.
- All right.
(laughs)
So, Ginger,
in coming to "All Stars,"
did you accomplish
your mission?
- Well, no,
because I didn't win.
But I didn't feel
like myself.
I didn't feel like
I could find my groove.
I didn't feel like I knew
where to jump back in,
because I felt like I was
still doing it from Season 7.
And I also felt like
we were at maybe an advantage,
but mostly a disadvantage--
- Disadvantage, girl.
- Because we literally
came right back
into that workroom.
I had just lost.
- Uh-huh.
- And so your mind just starts
playing tricks on you.
- Do you feel that Alyssa broke
the pact when she sent you home?
- Wait, hold on.
Can we break the pact down?
What was the pact?
- It was a blood oath...
(all laugh)
Administered by the members
of Rolaskatox.
- Rolaskatox formation.
- Well, the pact was
that the eliminations
would be based on
the judges' critiques.
And do you feel that
she broke that pact?
- If she had been a part
of that pact,
then, yes,
she would have broken it.
But she wasn't part
of that pact.
- You said in your
sign off interview
that I played a dirty game.
- Yes.
- You do play a dirty game.
- She just won
the Snatch Game.
She got one point.
You were safe,
episode one, two points.
You were in the middle
of the road both times.
If I was being strategic,
I would have packed your ass.
(all laugh)
- All right, kids,
we'll be right back.
- Coming up....
- You have to also sit back
and say,
well, yes,
because it's Alyssa,
it's judged
a little differently.
- Don't say I get a free pass
because I'm funny.
- Utter bullshit.
- Errr.
(RuPaul laughs)
- ¶ And beyond,
you'll always be a hero ¶
- Let's talk
movie she-quels.
Alaska kicked Alyssa
in the challenge.
- ¶ Camp town ladies
sing this song ¶
- ¶ Doo-dah, doo-dah ¶
- Dead!
- Aah!
- And then kicked her again
right out of the competition.
- The queen I've selected
is Alyssa Edwards.
(sobs)
- Alyssa, what do you think
was behind Alaska
giving you the chop?
- (clicks tongue)
(all laugh)
Well, let me ask you.
Do you feel that any of it
was strategy?
- No.
- Do you think you based it
on judges critiques?
- Yes, and I was there
in the scene with you.
(all laugh)
Girl, I'll send you home
again right now.
Does anyone have a lipstick
with Alyssa on it?
I did it.
I would do it again.
- You sent her home solely
based on the challenge.
Is that what you're saying?
- I felt like
she did the worst.
I mean,
we barely got through it.
We barely
got it all on tape,
all the words from the pages
on the scene.
So it was like, I was afraid
are we even going to get
through this one time?
Of course, watching
the episode at home,
everyone in the bar is like,
yeah, she's hilarious.
But it was not hilarious
there.
It was serious.
And then the camera dress, I
thought, that's not two in one.
It was like, I'm holding
the camera dress,
and now here's
the camera dress!
- Well, wait, you didn't
have a two in one at all.
- Um...
- A funeral shroud,
cloud of black trash bags?
- I thought it was lovely.
- No, it was--
the second part was amazing.
The first part
was utter bullshit.
Bitch, utter bullshit.
- Errr.
- Alyssa,
some queens have said
that the judges were easier
on you in the critiques
than they were
on the other girls.
- I totally disagree.
- There were several times
that all the judges were like,
it works because it's Alyssa.
It's the Alyssa-isms.
And Alyssa-isms
is a pass, though.
- You have to also sit back
and say, well, yes,
because of my Alyssa-isms,
because of how infectious it is,
it's judged
a little differently.
- Girl, no T, you had one
suitcase it looked like.
You had a bra and a panty
and a paint for the first one.
You had a little strappy outfit
and paint for the second.
And I couldn't do that.
Your body is flawless.
- Right.
- She's wearing combat boots
on the runway,
and she's wearing
flip-flops.
- Don't you come
for my flip-flops.
- And jellies.
We all have our own drag.
- Everybody
has their own drag.
- Don't say--yeah, don't say
I get a free pass
because I'm funny.
- Well, Jeremy Scott
said you are fashion.
- You know what? Coco Chanel
says take off two.
Alyssa Edwards says add 22.
- I love playing dress up.
This is a drag show.
This is
the ultimate All Star show.
Girl, reach in that caboodle,
that's your shit.
(all laugh)
- On that point, Alyssa, I have
a fan question for you.
On a scale of Gila monster
to beast,
how well do you think you slayed
the runway this season?
- I think
I was...a wildebeest.
- Okay.
- Because it was wild,
bitch, it was all out!
- Right after Alyssa
was sent packing,
the mirror cracked.
- I am sick of hearing them say,
you can wear shit on stage,
but it's okay,
'cause you're Alyssa.
It was sloppy.
It was like she kept saying,
like, you shouldn't send me home
because I've only been
in the bottom once,
and she was too concerned
about saying
this is your second time
in the bottom.
You should go home.
It seemed to me
she was more concerned
about throwing you two under
the bus during deliberations.
- What?
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, fuck my God!
- What is going on here?
- Trust the duchess.
It ain't over just yet, baby.
- Oh, my goodness, child,
that mirror had four faces.
- Oh, God, it was the best
feeling in the world.
- None of us knew
what was happening.
We were just told get into drag
and stand here,
and I felt a lot of pain,
because this one was pissed off
and had her claws digging into
my arm for about 30 minutes
while y'all were talking
in there.
- Well, I was trying to fix
my hair and shit,
and I was like, girl,
she's mad.
- We were there...well,
we were behind the mirror
for like an hour.
- Jesus Christ.
- But we heard everything.
- Everything.
But when it literally turned
into that fresh wound,
just salt all over it.
That good organic sea salt.
- Honestly, I was happy
that I might have a chance
to come back.
But then it was like
hearing everything in the room,
it just sounded so dark,
and it was like--
- Do I want to want this?
- I want to be here
and I want to compete,
but, girl, I don't--why you
got to be dark-sided, girl?
I was already eliminated.
- There was a lot
of aggression, for sure.
- It didn't sound like
there was any humility there.
It was more so, it was, like,
I got that bitch.
- Right.
- You know?
- So what was
your first thought
when you saw these bitches
appear in the mirror?
- I thought they looked
fucking sickening.
They looked so correct,
but then I was, like,
now what the fuck
are you going to do to me?
- That was epic, though.
That mirror scene,
y'all did that.
You think you're clever,
don't you, bitch?
(all laugh)
- The fashion this season
had everybody,
including the "New York Times,"
gagging.
Now I want some
queen on queen critiques.
When we love an outfit,
we toot it.
And when we don't,
we boot it.
Katya, top two.
- Roxxxy Andrews final outfit,
stunning from head to toe.
- Oh! Oh, my God.
- Smashing wigs,
colostomy bags
and toenails out of
every living room in America.
- Every single thing that Roxxxy
Andrews wore down the runway.
- Yes.
- It was incredible.
- I couldn't pick just one.
- I want to say
it's Phi Phi.
- I was obsessed
with her futuristic look.
- Honestly, Phi Phi's
future of drag look
was probably
one of my favorite looks.
I thought it was brilliant.
- Top boot.
- Ginger's space look.
- Oh, yes.
- Space ho and robot chicken.
- My top two of the season
was the top four.
Visually,
they're just super stunning.
They looked like a bunch
of fairies up there.
And then boot me, I look like
a fucking shiny sack up there.
(laughs)
- Alaska?
- Top two, definitely Detox.
The latex red bellbottom
pantsuit thing.
It was beautiful.
it looked like
it was painted on your body.
It haunts me forever.
Top boot,
the fucking camera dress.
So stupid.
- Hey, you got--girl, you got
cockroaches on your dress.
(all laugh)
- They're my pets.
- All right, stay right there,
we'll be right back.
Coming up....
- Tell me about the hug
that never happened.
- It was, like,
oh, just chill out.
- I just don't think that
she wanted to hug Alyssa.
(RuPaul laughs)
- Now, Alyssa Edwards
and Tatianna
made All Star her-story
when they both lip synced their
way back into the competition.
When you strutted
onto the runway,
we knew
we were in for something.
- You can look into our eyes.
We were fighting
to get back in.
- Yeah, we were.
- I was like, damn, I really
wanted this so bad.
- Now, tell me about the hug
that never happened.
- Bye, love you.
Phi Phi, I tried to hug you,
though.
- What was going through
your mind at that time, Alyssa?
- I didn't vote Phi Phi
because of anything
other than her behavior.
It was starting to feed off
on everyone,
and it was like, girl,
just chill out
and take a deep breath
and laugh.
So when I tried to hug him
at the end,
I wanted to say, look,
you know what?
We came, we saw,
we conquered.
It's okay to be a little bitter
and a little disappointed.
That's life
when you fall short.
But always tell someone else,
good job and congrats.
It's harder to be
the bigger person in life.
- I just don't think that
she wanted to hug Alyssa.
(laughs)
Because she walked up,
dissed her,
but then gave everyone else
a hug after her.
So that's why
I don't necessarily believe
that it was 'cause
she was going to cry.
Um, also, she did not cry
after hugging everybody.
- When I saw it, I was like, no!
Bitch, hug her!
Like, you're going to regret
this is what I felt.
- It was
an authentic moment.
She was angry and pissed.
Don't pretend to be
something you're not.
If you want to recoil from
the hug, that's a moment.
- But you already pretended
in the dress--in the workroom.
- Right, but what you see
isn't always the truth.
- Right. (laughs)
- Now, the family makeovers
challenge
may have been my all-time
favorite challenge.
- Mine, too.
- Now, Detox, how did
putting your sister into drag
bring you closer together?
- I mean, we're pretty
inseparable to begin with.
Having her share that moment
and being here,
and as being my rock
to begin with,
and to be such a rock
during that challenge
was one of the most
amazing experiences ever.
- Yeah.
- I will never forget it.
- What about you, Roxxxy?
Now, that was your grandmother
who raised you as her child.
- She's always wanted
to be in front of cameras,
so this like
her shining glory, like--
- Couldn't tell.
- You couldn't tell?
- She's gorgeous.
- Thank you.
- How, Alaska, did putting
your mom into drag
affect your relationship
with her?
- Well, I've always considered
my mom a drag queen anyway.
And I have so many memories
of my mom,
like, being in the bathroom
and getting ready
and doing her, like,
face and her hair.
So she knows what it's like
to be a drag queen.
- And Katya, your mother
seemed like a real natural.
When you put that--
- Upstaged me.
- When she put
that lace front on--
- Put that Marilyn on
and hit it.
- Yeah. Has she changed
since that challenge?
- I told her, you know,
you could be recognized
on the street, mom,
and she was like, oh, my God,
I didn't think of that.
So I pray for her.
- Yes, yes.
Well, I got to say,
Alyssa Edwards,
we've seen the crazy nut,
you know, tongue popping Alyssa,
but to see you so human
and so vulnerable,
it felt like Alyssa Edwards
came full circle.
- Mom would have loved
to do this.
She would have.
- Yeah.
I'm glad we're together,
because it's
a sensitive time for us.
- (sobs) Well,
thank you for coming.
The day that they closed
my mother's casket,
I just shut down.
- What was your takeaway
in being there?
- When my mom died,
it was just like,
I packed my suitcase
and I left.
I did a show that night
of my mother's funeral,
and I could tell that
I was running from something.
When she came into the room, I
just, I didn't know what to say.
I didn't know
if I should say I'm sorry.
When I looked at
the hurt in her eyes,
I knew that they lean
so much on me.
You make time for a booking,
you make time for a family.
Because they're
going to be the ones
that are going to be there
for you.
- Yeah.
All right,
we've got a fan question.
What is your freakiest
fan interaction?
Adore,
I bet you've got some.
- I sleep with
a lot of my fans, so--
- You do?
- I do.
- Uh-huh.
- I believe in free love.
- Sure, why not?
- Like, cuddle?
- No, I sleep with my fans,
like full on.
Like, if they're attractive,
yeah, like, I make babies.
- Girl, if you can't fuck
your fans, who can you fuck?
- Exactly.
No, I believe
if you have an attraction,
like, why not?
Nothing shocks me
with a fan.
- What about
you girls back there?
Have you had carnal knowledge
with the fans?
- Um, no, I--
- Oh, shut up, Tatianna.
You're a whore.
- You know what? They might
be a fan of me after our--
- Okay.
- No, I had a dude lick my foot
in Chicago, though.
- That counts.
Now, Detox, have you had--
- Oh, you know we've
had this conversation.
- You've had relations
with the fans.
- I've had very carnal relations
with very many a fan.
- Uh-huh.
- And I feel like some of us
have, like, shared--
- We've shared fans.
- We've had--I've shared
Courtney's fans.
- And I usually get
the pictures after.
- There was one time
I was in my hotel room
and there were like
these two boys in there,
and I was like,
uh, go see Adore.
She's just down the hall.
- Oh, my God, I was scared.
I was like, no!
I don't want--
- You did, though.
- Yeah, I did, yeah.
- We had fun, us girls.
- We'll be right back.
- Coming up...
- It was heart wrenching,
sending you home,
because I knew
that it was not right.
- Do you hold a grudge?
(RuPaul laughs)
- Now, in the family
makeover challenge,
we learned that
global warming is real.
Let's take a look
at Alaska's meltdown.
(all laugh)
- I fucked up this week, man,
and it really sucks.
It fucking
really fucking sucks,
and I need to be
in the final four,
and now I'm potentially
looking at I'm not going to be.
I'll give you $10,000
if you let me stay.
I'll transfer it to you
via PayPal,
because I need to stay
in this competition.
- What was going through
your mind
when you saw Alaska do this?
- I thought
it was ridiculous.
For someone who to me
is so talented and brilliant
at what they do
and is so together,
to have one, to me,
small minor misstep
affect them and shake them
so much,
it was very alarming.
- I thought
it was strategic.
- Oh.
- But it was fun
to watch her crumble.
(all laugh)
- That's so rude.
- I think for me,
I seen it differently.
I seen someone that it
really meant a lot to them.
And it was like, bitch,
I have hustled,
I have worked,
I have fought,
I have cried,
I've stood back up.
And if you were judging,
you probably would
have sent yourself home.
- Yep.
- That's a good point.
That's a very good--what
was going through your mind?
- Going in to "All Stars 2,"
I was, like,
I didn't want to do anything
that could be perceived
as weakness,
because I watched Season 5
and I saw someone
who was really insecure
and who let
that insecurity
affect their performance
in the competition.
And I didn't want there to be
a single frame of camera
of me stumbling over a line
or doing anything
they could play
that bumbly
stupid music behind,
the ¶ doo-doo-doo-doo ¶
(all laugh)
And, Detox, if you want
the $10,000,
I'll send you
my PayPal later.
Thank you
for not sending me home.
- Now, Detox, in the family
makeover challenge,
explain why you sent Alyssa home
over Alaska and Roxxxy.
- There was no way that
I could have sent her home,
because
she had been killing it,
and when it came down to
choosing between these two,
I knew that Roxxxy
should have gone.
And I went to go get
that lipstick,
and there was just something--
my stomach was turning.
I know I'm making
the wrong decision,
but it's a decision
I had to stand by.
It was heart wrenching
sending you home,
because I knew
that it was not right.
- Do you hold a grudge?
- No. Mm-mm.
No, because I've learned
if you hold a grudge,
it only eats away at your
success and your happiness.
- Sure, yeah.
- I had to let go of that.
- Now, one gorgeous
All Star queen
taught us all some new
wig tricks this season.
Let's take a look.
- Thick and juicy is back,
bitches.
Dear, what seems
to be going on?
- Roxxxy, my dear...
- (sighs)
- You are an All Star.
- I'm walking away so proud.
I got to show
who I truly was.
- I will forever
be thick and juicy.
Bye-bye.
(all laugh)
- So, Roxxxy,
you made it all the way
to the final four
of "All Stars."
How does that feel?
- It felt bittersweet.
I was in the bottom
so many times,
I felt like, I shouldn't have--
I didn't earn my way there.
And that's--
It's bittersweet.
I was happy to be there
and to continue to compete,
but I felt like...
like, I don't know,
like I wasn't
supposed to be there.
- I think
you should have won.
Girl, you were in the bottom
six out of seven episodes,
and you made it
to the finals.
That's how "Big Brother
Survivor's" won.
I think you should have been
in the final three.
- Now, a lot of you girls were
in Roxxxy's original season.
How well do you think
she did in this competition?
- Burned it.
You have such a respect for
the fucking art of what drag is,
and every detail
is thought about.
- I could just tell how
happy she was to be there,
which was a nice departure
from the first time around.
- Well, also this was a chance
for you to redeem yourself,
and you absolutely did that.
And let me say this.
You know, you're not given
a redemption.
It's something
that you earn.
I just wanted
to clear that up
for people who don't understand
how that works,
and you earned it, Roxxxy.
Con-drag-ulations.
- Thank you.
- Right on.
(applause)
We'll be right back
after this.
Did you pop a nail, girl?
(laughs)
Coming up...
- Is there anything you'd change
about the season?
- Oh, God,
that sounds ominous.
- (laughs)
(RuPaul laughs)
- Now, when the time came
to crown our queen,
these next two queens
came so close, it hurts.
First, there was Detox.
- ¶ D to the E to the T
to the O ¶
¶ To the--hold it ¶
- Oh!
- ¶ X ¶
Everyone's favorite trash
talking transvestite.
My tuck is right.
I'm brilliant.
I'm beautiful.
I've never felt more...dead?
- It left us gagging.
- Thank you very much.
- Now, Detox, maybe more
than anyone else this season,
your runway looks slayed,
officially.
- Yes! (laughs)
- What was
your proudest moment?
- The entire thing.
Like, I feel such,
like, validation.
Season 5,
I was not in the game.
I was, like, so not present,
but still had that, like,
grandioso attitude,
and coming back and still having
my signature grandioso attitude,
but slaying it.
- Why were you out of it
in your season?
- My dad just found out
he had cancer
right before I came to film,
and he kind of encouraged me
to go ahead and do it,
but the whole time
I was just thinking, like,
I shouldn't be here.
Even though, like, it was
something I wanted for so long.
And it sucked, because it was
like, I was finally there,
and like, not really being able
to perform to my best abilities.
And to get back here
and to be able to share
with people who I admire
and respect so much,
I was like, yes, this is
what it should have been
the first time around.
- Give me your favorite
Detox moments. Anybody?
- I think that last episode,
there was just something
so angelic about all of them,
but because I've known you
for so many years,
it was just really
a big proud moment.
Like, as a friend, just to see
how beautiful you looked.
Oh, I'm like
getting emotional.
I'm all super proud of you.
- Thank you.
- Every moment of Detox's
is a wonderful moment.
She's wonderful
inside and out.
- And she's seen me
inside, too.
- Oh, okay.
Right on, right on,
- Shh, don't tell that.
- All right, and now,
the only high class
Russian whore, Katya.
- My name's Katarina
Petrona Zamalawchickova,
but you can call me Katya,
(snorts)
I am bombarded
by a cacophony
of demonic voices in my head
telling me... (deep voice)
You're not good enough.
Wow.
I'm giving you 1980s
disinterested Ellen Barkin
fantasy,
and I feel...
(deep voice) amazing.
I'm not going to panic
because I don't do that anymore.
- (laughs)
Katya, I'm so happy you were
able to embrace your confidence
and spotlight your talents
in "All Stars."
- Oh, me, too.
You put me
through drag school.
I was going to go
to grad school.
Switch the D and the G.
You have no idea how lucky
I am to be a part of it.
I don't care about winning.
I never did.
I want to be
a part of the family.
- And you are.
- Yep.
Is there anything you'd change
about the season?
- I would probably bring
some better clothes,
but I'm on a style journey
that is still evolving, Ru.
- Yeah.
- We were just plucked out of--
I don't want to harp on it,
but plucked
out of the season
and thrown back
into the skillet.
- Yeah.
- Still scabby.
(laughs)
- Now, I want to talk
about the power of Katya.
- Oh, God,
that sounds ominous.
- Ginger, tell me about
the power of Katya.
- There's not a mean spirited
bone in her body.
I'm convinced there's barely
any bones in her body,
wit the things
she does with it.
- Somebody put their bone
in my body. I'm so lonely.
- Oh, my God.
- Sorry.
- But she's just,
she's just wonderful
and she is a star
and she's just this
big ball of energy.
- Alaska, you also have a left
from center point of view,
Were there any things
that she did
that you thought, mm,
I wish I would have done that.
- Oh, no, I wouldn't have wanted
to do any of that.
- (laughs)
- She's really smart,
possibly dangerous--
I'm not sure--
and she can do
a fucking split.
- Yeah.
- So fuck you.
- You're a pig from hell.
- Fuck you!
They're going to edit that
in the commercial,
and it will look like
I meant it.
(all laugh)
- Now, "Drag Race" is truly
the Olympics of drag,
and this next queen
brought home the gold.
- ¶ Who's that bitch
that on the top? ¶
¶ Oh, wait, that's me,
hey, porkchop ¶
Bam.
(all laugh)
Nobody can do Alaska
except Alaska.
¶ I'm campy and classy
and cunty and mean ¶
Why don't you come on up and
fuck me in the ass sometime?
Aah!
Totally.
- I think you've done
a pretty amazing job
this journey.
You've come a long way since
auditioning for Season 1.
- Con-drag-ulations, Alaska.
- Thank you.
- What does the future hold
for Alaska, hall of famer?
- Well, I'm going to have a
giant picture in a hallway.
- Uh-huh.
- I got a new hat.
- Yes.
- I like it.
- Yeah.
- I just put out a new CD.
- Yes.
- A new tape.
- It's a new tape.
It's called "Pound Cake."
- Exactly.
- Now, as your first
official duty,
I'd like your opinion
on an audition tape
made by a young
up and coming queen
just getting started
in drag.
Let's take a look.
- Certainly.
- Three words to describe
Alaska Thunderfuck
Drug addicted whore,
batshit crazy,
hot mess city.
Because I have class,
I have grace,
and I have sophistication.
- Yes.
(applause)
- I'd say put her on "Drag Race"
in five years.
(all laugh)
- Now, that was
the second audition.
- Yeah.
- And then you sent in a third.
- Uh-huh.
- And a fourth.
- (laughs) And a fifth.
- Uh-huh.
(all laugh)
I'm going to send one
next year, too.
(all laugh)
- Now, all you other ladies,
you got to admit
that Alaska
was stiff competition. Oh.
- (imitating Mae West) Oh.
- What are your favorite
Alaska moments?
- Snatch Game, for sure.
- Yes.
- I farted laughing so hard.
- "Executive opulence,
anus-thing is possible."
- It was always good, but it
became perfect in "All Stars."
- Charismic beauty,
disturbing talent,
I think you define that.
- Alaska,
from the very beginning,
I saw in you perseverance,
a sense of fun,
a sense of intellect,
a sense of being
a marketing genius,
which is really
the future of drag.
And I'm so happy
for your success.
Very happy.
- Thank you.
This is amazing.
Everybody turned it up,
turned it out,
and like, made this the best
season of "Drag Race" ever.
- Yes, this was absolutely
the best season
of "Drag Race" ever.
And you all have been so
gracious to share your stories
and your heartbreak
and your dignity.
And I am so proud
of each of you.
(applause)
Now, remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna
love somebody else?
Can I get an amen
up in here?
- Amen.
- All right,
now let the music play.
- ¶ Throw your hands up ¶
¶ Time to get down ¶
¶ Throw your hand up ¶
- Come on.
- ¶ Time to get down,
down, down, down, down ¶
- Oh, my gosh.
(laughs)
Mwah.
- Chad, do you ever
get lonely in here?
- Snap out of it.