RuPaul: Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
We're having a bag ball.
Joey Jay.
Michelle:
I can tell by looking at this
you're not the sewer.
RuPaul: LaLa Ri.
Carson: It's some bags that
were glued onto a bodysuit.
Yeah, that's not gonna work.
RuPaul: Utica.
You have continuously
upped the fashion,
and I think tonight
was no exception.
RuPaul: Gottmik.
You have a really good
taste level
that transcended
all three of the looks.
Con-drag-ulations. You are the
winner of this week's challenge.
[applause] Oh, my God.
LaLa Ri, shantay you stay.
Joey Jay, sashay away.
- Whew!
- My Lord.
That was a long runway.
Category is our clothes.
What a day.
My boyfriend-to-be
was just sent home, Joey Jay.
I'm so sad!
"I'm a gay-ass bitch. I'm who?
- Joey Jay."
So, LaLa, I'm not
gonna come for you,
but you sent my man home.
Listen, bitch, Joey's cute,
and I definitely have
a big-ass crush on him,
and I most for sure
will sleep with the bitch
when we meet again
after I win this competition.
[all laugh]
When all of us were in
Untucked, it got crazy.
There's a lot
of unfinished business.
So Untucked, ladies,
was really eventful.
- Girl.
- Bitch, it's about to be
like an Atlanta strip club
up in here, bitch,
with bottles flying
and fists flying
and wigs everywhere, baby.
I think there's a difference
between being arrogant
and being confident
who the fuck you are.
There's a difference,
but you ain't...
You're not being confident,
you're being arrogant.
Girl, get the fuck out of
here with that bullshit.
That's not bullshit
that's a fact.
You literally walked in here
and said, "I don't like
some of you girls
because you arrogant
and got nasty attitudes."
I said what I said.
If you don't have star quality,
get the fuck outta here.
Girl, star quality?
Bitches in here
is motherfucking trying me,
and I'm to pop the fuck off.
I don't give a fuck
what any of the bottom girls
have to say about me,
because I'm staying here safe.
Suck it, bitch.
Take me out right now!
How's everybody feeling
about that now?
I guess I felt defensive.
I guess I was going
the fuck off.
I was mad, I was upset.
I thought we was cool,
and then out of nowhere
you don't like me,
which is, like, news to me.
I feel like it was blown
out of proportion.
Tamisha is honest,
she is who she is,
and if she has a problem with
someone, she's gonna tell them.
Whereas with Kandy,
she can dish it
but she has a difficult time
taking it,
and she gets very defensive.
She came in, was nasty,
and got what she deserved back.
I said y'all are doing amazing,
even though it's some girls
I don't care for.
That's what I said.
No, what you said was
I don't like some of you girls,
but you girls did good
in the ball challenge.
Because I've been doing drag
for just so long...
That's not what I said.
That's what you heard,
but that's not what I said.
I'm making fuck up, girl.
Roll back the fuck tape.
That's literally what you said.
It's a couple of you girls
I really don't care for,
but I have to commend you
on your drag.
I'm one to give props
where props are due.
And I still say it's a couple of
girls in here I don't care for,
because you have some really
nasty attitudes or whatever.
But that's just me personally.
She just said, "I don't care
for some of y'all,"
- but that was in...
- That's what I said.
That's what I said.
And then I said,
"Who are you talking about?"
- And then you said, "You."
- What you mean, bitch?
Don't ask a question
you don't want an answer to.
May I ask,
where did it come from?
What was that about?
Since we have entered
the werkroom
with the girls
that all eliminated us,
what I have seen and what
have been discussed...
Even if the other group that
was eliminated and came back
was talking about us,
whatever the other girls feel
some type of way about me,
two of them is already gone and
our entire group is still here.
That is what I'm talking about.
Kandy just showed me
point-blank, period
that you feel like
every member in the A team
is better than B team.
Last week, Kandy stood up
and said, "Symone
is my biggest competition,"
like we wasn't in the room.
You're only gonna rank yourself
amongst your girls,
and that's the thing
that's disheartening,
because it's a competition
amongst all of us.
Like I said, we don't gotta
kiki, we don't gotta talk.
Girl, we don't even
gotta be sisters,
just we're in
the same competition.
Don't look my way,
I won't look your way.
Don't speak to me,
I won't speak to you.
I don't need you
to tell me that.
I'm a grown-ass woman.
You don't need to tell me that.
But nevertheless,
what I said is what I said.
So with that being said,
I wanna get out of drag,
so let's end it.
Goodbye, good night.
- What's for dinner?
Atlanta people
don't take no shit
and Brooklyn people
don't take no shit.
It's about to get real
interesting from here on out.
At the end of the day,
the pageant has started.
We gonna see the best man win.
At this moment,
Tamisha's dead to me.
I don't wanna hear about it.
All of my girls
that are rooting for me,
I love them to death.
For everyone else that has
something to say about me...
Kandy's cockiness is going
to bite her in the ass.
So just like you
in the winner's circle,
it's easy to get in
the loser's circle, so, heh.
Bitch, I said what I said.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
RuPaul: The winner
of RuPaul's Drag Race
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
and a cash prize of $100.000.
With extra-special
guest judge Loni Love.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
[all laugh]
- Go on, bitch, get outta here.
- Oh, my God.
Today is a new day,
and the mood in the werkroom
is hella awkward
because we fully had the bad
girls club brawl last week.
And I don't think
we ever really found,
like, a happy place
to go back to.
So can we just say, like,
it's a brand-new week
and we can just, like,
leave everything in the past
that we went through last week?
Absolutely.
Can we just start fresh?
I mean, wishful thinking.
[alarm]
RuPaul: Ooh, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
- Let's go, bitch.
- Let's go!
Hey, bad girls.
Whether you're hot stuff
or a superfreak,
if you wanna stay alive,
you betta shake
that groove thing, girl,
or this could be
your last dance.
Toot-toot, hey.
Oh, my God.
Hello, hello, hello!
[cheering]
- Hi!
- Come on, ascot!
I'm your host,
RuPaul Charles Nelson Reilly.
[imitates Charles Nelson Reilly]
Oh!
[all laugh]
America's next drag superstar
must never fade
into the background,
so for today's mini-challenge,
you'll be working in pairs
to create eye-popping
designer dresses
using wallpaper
provided by Spoonflower.com.
Now, to prove your design
doesn't blend in,
one of you will be
modeling the dress
in front of a wall
of matching wallpaper.
[all laugh]
And the other will provide
fashion commentary.
Now, I need you all to pair up,
but choose carefully,
because whoever you choose
will be your partner
for both today's mini-challenge
and this week's maxi-challenge.
Now, Gottmik, you were
our winner last week,
so you get to wait and join
the pair of your choice.
Oh, my.
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Now, raise your hand.
Do you know who
Charles Nelson Reilly is?
No, no one. Okay.
Fuck all of you.
[all laugh]
Okay, queens, pick a partner.
Oh. Olivia was first. Sorry.
Sure, yes.
So at the bottom of the barrel
is myself and Tamisha.
Same shit, different day.
All right, Gottmik,
which couple will you
be turning into a throuple?
Oh, I think I'm gonna go
with Kandy and Tina.
- Ooh!
Oh, my God, drum roll.
Who is Mik gonna pick?
Oh, my God,
this is so nerve-wracking.
Of course you're gonna
fucking pick me and Kandy.
Don't even try it, sis.
Okay, queens,
you have 30 minutes
to create
your wallpaper dresses. Go!
Oh, we're sickening now.
Okay, good to know.
Okay, does this cover my hole?
Yep.
All right, time's up,
wallflowers.
First up, Tina Burner,
Kandy Muse, and Gottmik.
From a drag queen
who likes it raw,
everyone looks fishy
in this design we're calling
Catch of the Day.
You'll never blend
into the background.
You'll tuna roll all over it.
That last joke made me feel
a little eel.
Aah!
Up next, Rosé and Denali.
Here's Button Foster.
Zipper? I hardly flipper!
I like big buttons,
and I cannot lie.
Up next, Tamisha Iman
and Elliott With 2 Ts.
What's the matter,
Carole Baskin got your tongue?
- Did you say Carole Baskin?
- Carole Baskin.
Oh, that bitch. I hate her.
[all laugh]
The Tiger King has nothing
on the House of Food Stamps.
This is the same dress
Carole Baskin wore
when she kidnapped
her husband... allegedly.
[laughs] The one-of-a-kind dress
smells like
Joe's exotic bedroom.
This dress
is giving me jungle fever.
Rawr.
Up next, Olivia Lux and Utica.
Just in time for allergy season,
it's Utica Queen
in our growing new dress design,
photosynethe-sis.
This bitch is crazy.
[all laugh]
Bitch, where are you going?
Jesus, take the bouquet.
And finally, LaLa Ri and Symone.
Fresh from the oven,
here's LaLa Ri
in the perfect design
to fire up your pepperoni.
Oh, I can tell
she's a meat lover.
Easy, cheesy, peasy. Pizza girl!
Okay, I'll take a slice.
Oh! [laughs]
Nice work, ladies,
but one team really
sheetrocked this shit.
Tamisha Iman and Elliott
With 2 Ts, con-drag-ulations.
You've each won
a $2.500 gift card
to spend on customized
home decor at Spoonflower.com.
Werk!
Bitch!
Okay, queens, now that
you're already partnered up,
it's time to hit
the dance floor.
For this week's maxi-challenge,
you'll be making
a dancing documentary
about the beat that defined
a generation of liberation.
I'm talking disco, baby.
[cheering]
Now, in the seventies,
disco was about freedom, divas,
and bringing
funky people together.
Aow!
Kinda like Drag Race does today.
So to bring the world's first
disco-mentary to life,
you'll need to learn
choreography,
and more importantly,
embody the spirit of disco.
Now, each team will be covering
a different chapter.
Tina, Kandy, and Gottmik,
you're covering
the birth of disco.
Elliott and Tamisha,
you've got disco and sex.
Oh!
Olivia Lux and Utica, Studio 54.
Denali and Rosé, disco fashion!
- Oh, cute.
- Ooh!
LaLa Ri and Symone,
you've got disco sucks.
Okay. [all laugh]
You know how to suck, don't you?
- Sho' do.
- Oh, my.
Hey, are y'all ready
to boogie-oogie-oogie?
- Yes!
Racers, start your engines,
and may the best
dancing queen win.
[cheering]
Yay, dancing challenges!
This is what I do.
I feel very underestimated
in this competition
by the other girls,
but this is my moment
to let them know
who they dealing with.
Girl, come on, disco inferno.
I think, like, finger dancing.
This week's maxi-challenge
is a disco-mentary.
And then roll it.
I love disco, I love dancing.
It is my challenge to win.
So we gonna be telling
the story of disco
through dance, baby, yes.
This just feels like home.
When I hear disco,
it just sends, like,
a little sensation through
my body, like, ooh, hah!
Baby, she make you
wanna move. [laughs]
Jeez, that hair actually
makes Tina look small.
[laughs]
Tina, your hair
finally makes you look small.
[laughs]
I mean, if I stand next
to LaLa, I'll be good.
[all laugh] Huh?
♪ Ooh-ee, ooh-ee ♪
- Hi!
- Yay!
Who's got boogie fever?
- Yes!
- Boogie-woogie!
All right, Denali and Rosé,
come on down.
- Hi.
So what made you
gravitate together?
You know, we both come
from dancing,
choreography backgrounds,
so we just really get
counts and music
and everything like that.
Right.
Not only can we show off
what we can do,
but we can really push it,
because she's at
a similar level to me.
So you all are representing
disco fashion.
Yes, we are.
I used to work on cruise ships,
and they would make us spotlight
and work on a lot
of the production shows.
And one of them was
Saturday Night Fever,
so I'm very versed
in Bee Gees and their music.
So you worked on a cruise ship.
There's no ice skating
on cruise ships.
There is, actually.
- Ice skating?
- Yeah.
Oh, you fully ice skated
on a cruise ship?
I did, yeah.
There were ice rinks,
and they would employ 10 skaters
from all around the world,
and we would do production shows
for the guests on board.
It was a lot of fun.
But the boat is rocking
while you're performing,
and it's hard to do a spin.
Yeah, we would spin,
we would jump, we did it all.
Wow. Now, Rosé, you came
very close last week
to actually winning.
How are you gonna make sure
that you win this week?
Fuck. Let go.
I think I'm holding on
a bit too much.
And I'm doing well.
I've been in the top
three weeks in a row now.
But, like, I still feel like I
haven't let my guard fully down
in front of you all.
You know, I think
you're absolutely right.
- Yeah.
- Because there's a feeling
that you're saying
to the judges,
you ain't gonna get me.
You ain't gonna break me down.
And it's a strategy,
but it doesn't allow people
to fall in love with you.
You're clearly very talented,
but people fall in love
out of honesty
and vulnerability.
I can't make it perfect,
so I gotta stop trying
to make it perfect.
- Yeah, perfect is overrated.
- Yeah.
Perfect is actually
kind of boring.
- Yeah.
- When you are in a disco
and you've got the lights going
and you're dancing around and
you're connecting to that beat,
something magical happens.
This is an opportunity for you
to just let it all hang out.
All right,
I can't wait to see you.
- Thank you, Ru.
All right, Symone, LaLa Ri.
[laughs]
So, now, you all are
representing disco sucks.
- Disco sucks.
- Okay.
So what do you know about disco?
I don't know much about disco.
- Uh-huh.
- Of course, Sylvester.
What do you about Sylvester?
I think he was, like,
a gay pioneer.
And what do you know
about disco?
There's a lot
of movin' and groovin',
a lot of colors, big hair.
What do you know about
the disco sucks movement.
I have never heard of it
until today.
The disco sucks movement
happened in Chicago.
A deejay in Chicago
had everyone bring down
a pile of disco records
to this stadium and set
these disco records on fire.
- Really?
- Wait, I didn't know that.
It was this revolt that
signaled the "end" of disco,
- but disco never really ended.
- Right.
People, the powers that be,
they get scared
by uncaged, unbridled passion,
which is what disco is about.
You know, with rock music,
you dance to rock music
like this.
Mm-hmm.
But you don't do this.
Right. [both laugh]
That is a revolution.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
And also, it's
associated with gay,
Black music, freedom,
and that scared a lot of people,
because they couldn't
control it.
So that is why
disco sucks happened,
and that's what
you are representing
in this disco-mentary.
And just for the record,
disco does not suck.
Okay. [laughs]
All right, kids, can't wait
to see you out there.
All right.
All right, Gottmik,
Kandy Muse, and Tina Burner.
- Hello!
- Hi!
So who knows
anything about disco?
You know how the Pussycat Dolls
had that one music video,
Hush, Hush,
and then it goes into that...
I Will Survive? I will Survive?
That's, like what I know.
If you were closer to me,
I'd slap you.
[all laugh]
This bit that you all are doing,
it has to do with the roots
of disco and New York City.
Every disco had people
from uptown, downtown,
gay, straight, Black,
white, Latin, men, women,
everybody was there together,
and it is such an expression
of love and soul and unity.
So, Tina, if I say name your
top three disco records,
what would they be?
Knock On Wood, Thelma Houston.
That's not Thelma Houston, but...
- Or, um...
- Amy Stewart.
- Yeah.
- Don't Leave Me This Way.
- Thelma Houston, yeah.
And I Will Survive, Diana Ross.
Well, you know, she covered it.
- Yeah.
- It's Gloria Gaynor's song.
- Well, yeah.
- Yeah.
You got me good.
You got me real good.
Do you have three favorite
disco songs, Gottmik?
Hmm. Probably
somewhere in there.
But I think I might keep them
to myself for right now.
Kandy, what's the difference
between Diana Ross
and Donna Summer?
- Did you know the difference?
- No, definitely, yeah.
"No, definitely?"
No, no, like,
no as in, like, yes.
- [laughs]
- Like, no, definitely, yes.
Like, no, yeah. Like, yeah.
Uh-huh. That's definitely no.
- Please, give a synopsis.
- [laughs]
[gasps] Okay.
[laughs]
I know the difference.
One has big, curly, bouncy hair,
you know, Mahogany.
And the other one's dead.
So listen, I will see you
on the dance floor.
Yes, you will.
It's gonna be fabulous.
Oh, it's gonna be good.
This is gonna be good.
All right, ladies, gather round.
Gather round, queens.
Now, in a few minutes
you'll head to the main stage
to turn the beat around with
choreographer Miguel Zarate.
So good luck, my disco ducks,
and don't fuck it up.
[cheers and applause]
[sighs] I wanna be
in the top this week.
After fucking up that first,
like, group challenge, girl,
I need to, crk-crk-crk-crk.
You'll be okay.
Do y'all think it's gonna be
judged on group or individual?
I'm not sure, because, bitch,
if there's, like,
some partnering bullshit
and then, like,
one person fucks up,
like, you know, who knows?
Imagine it's, like,
you'll be judged as partners,
and then your partner and you
are in the bottom
and you have to lip sync
against your partner.
See, that could be what it is.
[gasps] Uh-uh!
Don't tell that to the universe!
I can see a three-way lip sync,
and then double elimination.
Um, I'm in that group.
That's fucked up.
This is a dancing challenge,
and I should have picked
a dancing queen.
Had I known,
I wouldn't have chosen
two bitches with two left feet.
And now here I am. Fuck my life.
[laughs]
Hi!
How are you guys?
- Hi!
- Hello!
It's time to learn choreography.
I wanna feel transported
when I move my body
to the disco beat.
Hi, ladies.
My name is Miguel Zarate,
and I'm here to teach you some
moves for the disco-mentary.
Don't take yourself
too seriously.
Disco's about
having a lot of fun,
and that's really
what I'm looking for.
So we should just get to it.
Let me start with the trio.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
So you guys start it off.
It's the birth of disco,
so we're gonna start
with a little dance
called the Seat belt.
Sounds gorgeous.
One, two, three, four.
[humming]
Right now, it looks
a little up and flighty.
It's gotta be down and dirtier
and a little grimier.
All together, from the top.
Hit and the top.
Hit and a boom
and a boom and a boom.
Our mean girl trio,
they look cute.
And I say that facetiously.
[laughs]
That's strong, woom,
strong, woom.
And a boom and a boom
and a boom and a boom.
Much better except for Mik.
[all laugh]
Grrr.
Okay, your song is Disco Sucks.
It's about your pussy
being on fire,
serving it hot,
and not apologizing for it.
Shuffle low, shuffle low.
Shuffle high, shuffle high.
Okay, you're going hip,
and I'm going dick.
Let's work on that.
Let's just stay in place
and then go...
down, pop it up,
down, thrust it.
Don't hurt yourself, LaLa.
[all laugh]
You're still competing
tomorrow, girl.
Ooh, hah!
Elliott With 2 Ts and Tamisha,
your category is sex.
- Yes.
- I want you to think hot,
- I want you to think heavy.
- Yes.
And I want you
to think hula-hoop.
Hula-hoop?
Yes.
I don't want
no damn hula-hoop-a!
Keep it going, keep it going,
keep it going, keep it going.
Thrust it forward, thrust it
forward, thrust it forward.
Wow, that's a lot.
Sexy is cute,
but the hula-hoop part,
what the hell?
And-a push and-a push
and-a push. relax the face,
Have fun, aow.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Elliott's like, one, two,
three, four, five.
And I'm like, one, four...
No, wait a minute, one... five...
Okay.
- You got it, babe.
- I hate it.
I'm trying, but at the end of
the day, I have another problem.
It's not just the cancer.
I'm here with an ostomy bag
on my stomach.
It's an open wound,
and it limits my mobility.
I can't do the things
that I normally could do.
Here we go, one more time.
Five, six, seven, have fun.
Funk it up, funk it up.
Having the ostomy,
and I didn't even mention this
to the other contestants.
I haven't asked
for special treatment.
I'm gonna always try
to rise to the occasion
off of my abilities.
Yes, werk! That's nice!
You guys, that's awesome.
It's a lot, but, you know,
at the end of the day,
everybody know fame costs.
[laughs]
All right,
your theme is fashion.
You have the most dance-heavy
of the sections.
♪ Hey ♪
You're gonna do pas de bourree,
pas de bourree.
Turn, out, step, touch.
Do you want that to fan,
or do you want it to break?
Not that, bitch.
[all laugh]
- I'm open to either/or.
- Let's do fan.
Pas de bourree, pas de bourree
bring it in.
This is the strongest technical
team when it comes to dancing.
Me and Rosé, we're killing it.
I'm really hoping that
I can win this challenge.
Beautiful, ladies.
Thank you guys so much.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Miguel.
Great job, great job, great job.
Our choreography is definitely
the most challenging
out of all the girls.
My biggest concern
for this challenge is...
winning. [laughs]
All right, we have
Olivia and Utica.
Studio 54, it's like
confetti in a can.
And what we're gonna do
is bring that confetti
to life using this flag.
Here we go.
Go, one, two, three, four,
and five, six, seven, good.
And outside and up. Lay out.
[laughs] Utica!
Olivia and Utica, I mean, one of
them is doing the choreo wrong,
and by the looks on Olivia's
face, it's not Olivia.
One, two, three, four,
and five, around. No chainé.
five, six, seven, eight.
- And then out.
- Oh, my God.
[laughs] Miss Utica and this...
Yeah. Whoo!
Miss Utica and this little
piece of fabric, girl.
This little piece of fabric
is tearing her up.
Utica, get out of your head,
because your creativity
is amazing.
When you let
your creativity flow,
like, I can't stop
looking at you.
But the second you don't,
I don't wanna look at you.
Ooh.
I'm telling myself,
I can do this, I can do this,
I can do this.
I am a great dancer,
I am a great dancer.
Like, I can do this!
But Olivia is full-on
disco inferno
happening in partnership-land.
So I have, like,
some big shoes to fill
if I'm gonna compete with her.
Let's go. Yeah!
[laughs]
[shouting nonsense words]
Today we are gonna be performing
our disco-ography
on the main stage.
And I'm gonna feel disco
right up into my tuck, honey.
How are we feeling?
Here's the thing.
Like, we just have
strong personalities,
so we have to show
the personality on the stage.
- Yeah.
I know that everyone looks at us
as, like, the loud bitches
in the room.
But, baby, can we deliver?
That's the real tea.
And I think we can.
Yeah, no, we're gonna kill this.
- We're gonna fucking slay it.
- Yes, hands in the middle.
All right.
Mean girls on three.
One, two, three.
- Mean girls.
Oh, is that the clique?
Some people think we're bitches,
but guess what?
Drag queens are very loud,
outspoken.
We push buttons.
You wanna call it mean,
call it mean.
Move over, Dream Girls,
it's the Mean Girls.
How do you feel, Olivia?
I feel really good.
Yeah, you was up there
twirling with that flag, and...
Right.
I always wanted
to be in the color guard,
you know what I mean?
- Really?
- Yeah.
I mean, I was in marching band.
I played the piccolo, and
it was the smallest instrument
for the biggest kid
on the field.
I used to be almost 300 pounds.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I just remember kinda getting
teased about my weight.
I was so insecure because
I was still in the closet.
And I was battling
with, like, my identity,
and it just was, like, a lot.
It just was a really dark time
that I felt like
I just couldn't be myself
and couldn't be a kid.
Like, going through
what we went through
and the rehearsals and stuff
just reminds me
that I wasn't able to do
what I'm able to do now always.
You know, I remember
going to the amusement parks,
and there was one time where
I got turned away from a ride.
- Oh, my God.
- I couldn't fit in the seat
to even secure myself, so...
When did you lose weight?
In high school, my mom...
We went to the doctor,
and the doctor said, like,
the dreaded "O" word to my mom.
- Like, your son's obese.
- Obese?
And my mom was just, like, we
gotta do something about this.
And I was on, like,
strict diets,
and that's when I found,
like, theater and drama
and that kind of all ended up
turning into, like, drag.
Yeah. Olivia Lux, darling.
Olivia Lux.
It took a long time
for me to be confident
with my own body, myself,
and now I don't even
look at the scale.
As long as I feel amazing,
that's all that matters.
I guess in a way, drag saved
my well-being and my health.
Drag is the new diet.
Right. Try it sometime.
You really have no idea
what people have gone through,
and when you learn about it,
it really shows why they are
that person that they are.
Her journey created who
she is today, and I love her.
I admire you a lot, Kandy,
because you are very much
yourself at all times.
And your personality
is so infectious.
And, like, the thing is
I know sometimes, like,
it comes out
a little bit abrasive
and too loud to some people.
Tell us about your favorite
fight you've ever had.
My favorite fight I've ever had?
Girl, the one with the battle
of my inner demons, baby.
Ooh, tell us about that.
Well, I mean, all my life
has just been, like, a battle
with just, like, myself.
My mother was, like,
in and out of jail,
and just, like, you know,
all I knew was the streets.
And on the streets,
you have to be, like,
you know, girl, hood-smart.
I've always felt like
I've had to defend myself,
whether it was, like,
at a job or in school
or in a relationship,
whatever the case may be.
If I was, like,
faced with an obstacle,
girl, I was gonna go ham.
Growing up,
everyone always told me,
like, "You're not good enough,
and you're not gonna
amount to anything."
And, like, even, like,
last time on Untucked,
when I was, like, going off,
like, in that moment I felt like
I needed to defend myself.
And I try not to be that way.
When me and Tamisha
had that little debacle,
it felt like it was definitely
a setback for me,
because I've worked so hard
to not be that angry person.
It took me 10 steps back,
because I haven't been like that
in a very long time.
Learning and growing every day.
Learning and growing
every day, diva.
You have lived, like,
five different lifetimes.
Okay. But, you know,
I look back on it often,
and I wouldn't trade it
for the world.
I grew up in the projects.
Did you really?
Oh, I didn't know that.
Yeah, I grew up in the projects.
We had members in the community
that tried to keep the kids
out of trouble and whatnot.
There was this one particular
lady named Ms. Kemp.
She started, like,
a little cheerleading group.
We didn't have no football team
or nothing like that,
but she gave the girls
something to do.
Dance, cheerleading,
whatever your talent is,
Ms. Kemp wanted
to bring it out of you.
I would always go to practice
with her and whatnot,
and my nickname was Booty.
- Booty?
- Booty.
I've seen it.
So she was like,
"Booty can flip."
When she figured out that
I could flip, I could split,
I could do all those things,
but no one had ever
allowed me to do it.
Mind you, I'm up there
just having fun,
not knowing
what the hell's going on.
My grandmother got wind
that I'm up here doing gay stuff
or whatever, whatever.
And she was like,
"No, boys don't do this
and boys don't do that."
Ms. Kemp was actually the one
who gave me my foundation
and let me know that
I was talented, you know?
I'm grateful for the lady
in my community
that took a chance on me.
That's why I became,
you know, who I am:
the mother of the House of Iman.
I always wanted to actually
make it to Hollywood.
Well, you're here now, babe.
I said, like, I'm
actually living my dream.
Who would have ever thought?
I know I wouldn't
have never thought.
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
And what?
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
It's my favorite Soul Train
dancer, Michelle Visage.
Do you have
a favorite disco song?
Yes, it's the story of my life
and my sex life,
More, More, More.
[all laugh]
Style superstar Carson Kressley,
what's your favorite disco song?
Ru, I really enjoy Shaft.
The 12-inch version.
[all laugh]
She's back.
Everybody say Loni Love.
- Loni Love!
Loni, do you have
a favorite disco song?
Yes, Don't Leave Me This Way,
the Teddy Pendergrass version.
- Yes, that's the original.
- Yes.
I love it.
When he said,
"Don't leave me this way,"
I didn't want him
to leave me. Ooh.
This week we challenged our
queens to dance, dance, dance
in the world's first
disco-mentary.
And on the runway, category
is Little Black Dress.
- Ooh!
- Racers, start your engines,
and may the best drag queen win.
Buckle up, because these queens
are about to take us
to Funkytown.
[changing radio stations]
RuPaul: Hey,
all you foxy people.
This is Mama Ru on the radio,
and, ooh, do I have
a story to lay on you.
Announcer: Mama Ru on the radio.
Chorus: ♪ Mama Ru on the radio ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
RuPaul: In the early 1970s,
a new sound was bubbling up
from the street,
a hot mix of rhythm and blues,
salsa, and funk,
with a undeniable beat.
Disco was born,
creating booty-shaking anthems
for gay liberation, Black power,
women's rights, and the dance
floor would never be the same.
[disco music plays]
♪ Freedom on the dance floor ♪
♪ Won't stop till we get more ♪
♪ Freedom, oh ♪
RuPaul: Disco celebrated sex,
a throbbing beat
that made you wanna
shake your groove thing.
Meet a stranger, feel the beat,
and let's get it on.
♪ Everybody say love ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Everybody say love ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Everybody say love ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Everybody say love ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Everybody ♪
♪ Hey, everybody ♪
RuPaul: Disco brought
different worlds together
at the legendary Studio 54.
Liza, Halston, and Warhol
did the double-bump
with drag queens, bus boys,
and hot studs on roller skates.
In this boogie wonderland,
everybody was a superstar.
♪ Superstar, you know you are ♪
♪ Feeling free, on the move ♪
♪ If you please ♪
♪ In the balcony ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
RuPaul: Disco ignited
a fashion explosion.
Skin was in, baby,
and so were spaghetti straps,
feathered hair, designer jeans,
and damn,
those pants were tight.
♪ Ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Gucci, Pucci, Susan Lucci ♪
♪ Ooh, touch me there ♪
♪ My designer derriere ♪
RuPaul: Disco gave us divas:
- Donna Summer.
- Hot stuff.
- Diana Ross.
- She's the boss.
And there was no shade
in Evelyn Champagne King's day.
But one disco queen paved
the way for the rest of us.
The fearless
and flamboyant Sylvester
showed the world how we could
all feel mighty real.
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ From Fire Island ♪
♪ To San Francisco ♪
♪ Queens are queens are queens ♪
♪ We are the queens
of disco, oh ♪
RuPaul: By the end
of the seventies,
the disco revolution
was under attack.
Haters shouted, "Disco sucks!"
They set our records on fire,
and our dreams
became a disco inferno.
[siren]
Disco sucks!
♪ Fire, yeah ♪
♪ My pussy's on fire, yeah ♪
♪ Burning, burning, burning,
tables are turning ♪
♪ You will soon be learning
that you can't kill our fire ♪
♪ My pussy's on fire ♪
[siren]
Shame, shame,
you can't put out our flame.
RuPaul: They tried to kill
what we loved,
but disco never died.
It just changed
its name and address.
Today, disco reminds us
that our souls are connected
through spirit,
and how together
we can do anything.
It do take a village, people.
[laughs]
♪ Sing it to me ♪
♪ We are family ♪
♪ Oh, I can hear you, y'all ♪
♪ Get up everybody and sing ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ We are family ♪
♪ And the things you do,
hey, hey ♪
♪ I got all my sisters with me ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ We are family ♪
♪ Get up, get up, y'all ♪
♪ Get up everybody and sing ♪
♪ Oh, hey, hey ♪
[laughter and applause]
♪ Bring back my girls ♪
Category is Little Black Dress.
First up, Tina Burner.
Loni: Gimme more.
Benjamin Moore.
Tina: It is time
to bring some color
into the drab
little black dress.
I am serving you a what?
Ru-veal, and all of a sudden
I am serving
paint splattered fantasy.
I feel like
all the boys in the yard
were painting
the motherfucking fence,
and they came up and grabbed
my titties and my ass.
Because I am what?
I'm looking that good.
Michelle: All hands
on deck... and my ass.
RuPaul: Paint misbehavin'.
[Loni laughs]
RuPaul: Kandy Muse.
Michelle: Oh, I'm noticing
a pattern here.
[all laugh]
Carson: Very sketchy.
Kandy: Baby, I have on my
Christina Stambolian creation.
This dress is made
out of canvas paper
with a hand-painted
little black dress.
My hair is wet with oil paint,
and if you look real closely,
this is the revenge dress
that Princess Diana wore.
Thank you very much.
Michelle: No more wire hangers!
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Gottmik.
Loni: Ooh!
Carson: Mm, the LBM:
the little black merkin.
RuPaul: You know, I used to go
to that dry cleaner,
but no more.
[all laugh]
Gottmik: I'm giving you
the littlest black dress.
I'm full naked.
A year ago, I would never
have done this.
I couldn't be happier
with how I look right now.
Loni: Wow.
There's a cold,
naked Barbie somewhere.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Elliott With 2 Ts.
Michelle: The Real Housewives
of Paramus.
Elliott: This look is just
full-on rich, opulent woman.
[laughs] Every once in a while,
someone will have
to double-take at me
and go, "Is that
a man or a woman?"
It is the complete
transformation,
it's the illusion,
and that's what I love
about my drag.
RuPaul: The funeral home
is her pickup bar.
[all laugh]
Tamisha Iman.
Come on, Dominique Deveraux.
This champagne is burnt.
Tamisha: I wanted to bring
a nice, clean black dress.
One of my many creations.
Any time I hit the runway,
I'm doing a classy lady walk.
I want them
to see Diahann Carroll.
I want and need them to see
a Black, classy woman,
and I need them
to see Black excellence.
Michelle: Our lovely
Black butterfly, baby.
RuPaul: Olivia Lux.
Loni: Oh, this old thing?
It's just a Sunday afternoon.
RuPaul: Uh-huh.
Carson: She is working
the micro-berkin.
RuPaul: Ooh.
Olivia: This is not
your ordinary walk,
ladies and gentlemen.
This is a strut.
I am giving you
supermodel vibes.
My little black dress
fits every curve of my body.
I feel beautiful.
Michelle: Bring back my curls.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Utica Queen.
Who the queen?
You the queen.
Utica: So my little black dress
is inspired by Audrey Hepburn,
and these beautiful
little earrings that I have.
I wanted to become the earrings,
so I have my earring
back on my hat,
and I am strutting down
the runway in shades of gold.
I'm definitely feeling like
my true, authentic self in art,
and I'm really excited
about this concept.
RuPaul: Her head says,
"I'm a hooker."
[all laugh]
RuPaul: Denali.
She's starring in
the Queef of the Spider Woman.
[all laugh]
Carson: My, what a tangled web
we weave.
Denali: I am serving you
Mommy Longlegs
in my arachnid-inspired
little black widow dress.
The back of my dress
has gorgeous beading.
Call me Charlotte,
because I am spinning webs
and turning heads.
I am widowed, but plot twist:
I killed that motherfucker.
Oh.
RuPaul: Michelle,
her eyes are up there.
[all laugh]
Rosé.
Loni: If you squeeze her dress,
her tulle pops out.
[all laugh]
Rosé: Simply showing up
to RuPaul's Drag Race
with a little black dress
would be boring,
so I've got this
beautiful grey tulle
framing my truly
little black dress.
This look is definitely
a little bit camp,
but it's also very sexy,
and I feel like a million bucks,
so I'm soaking up every minute
on this runway.
Carson: Anyone else hungry
for a Hot Pocket?
[all laugh]
RuPaul: LaLa Ri.
Michelle: Read my lips.
[all laugh]
LaLa: Any time
I'm given the chance
to wear something small
and little and sexy,
oh, bitch, sign me up.
Showing a little
piece of ass for the class.
Let me use everything I got
to get everything that I want.
Let's go, little black dress.
Carson: Little black tube top.
[all laugh]
RuPaul: If that dress
were any shorter,
they'd have to arrest you
for dealing crack.
[all laugh]
Whoo!
RuPaul: Symone.
- Whoo!
Michelle: Somebody's going
to Miss Charles' hair salon.
[all laugh]
Symone: I am giving you
Black hair is a revolution!
And if you don't know where
that's from, let me tell you.
This hair is a reference
to RuPaul's music video,
Back To My Roots.
So this little black dress
is made of braiding hair,
and I am here to model.
Straight from the beauty shop.
RuPaul: Michelle,
the hair show is in town.
Michelle:
Honey, Miss Hair Show 1982.
[all laugh]
Carson: So good. Damn.
♪ Bring back my girls ♪
Welcome, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
When I call your name,
please step forward.
Gottmik.
Denali.
Rosé.
LaLa Ri.
Symone.
Queens...
You are safe.
You may leave the stage.
Ladies, you represent the tops
and the bottoms of the week.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques...
Starting with Tina Burner.
This look, you obviously
give us a big dash of camp,
and I love that.
I would like the hair bigger
to balance everything out.
It squashes you.
It should lift you up.
Yeah.
Your performance, though,
was out of this world.
I love that homage-
to-Bob-Mackie beaded number.
I think that beaded short dress,
with all that movement,
was really fantastic.
You took control of the stage,
and you were a disco queen
to me tonight.
Well done.
Thank you very much.
Up next, Kandy Muse.
This look, I think
it's really fun.
I like the ode to fashion,
but I do find the hair and some
of the paint details on the face
are a little distracting
and a little messy.
I do wanna say about your outfit
in the disco thing, too,
it was a little too plain
for RuPaul's Drag Race.
In your performance,
you are from the boogie-down,
you're from
the south South Bronx,
and you keep it real,
so we get a lot of talk
to the hand
and a lot of...
I love that about you.
The one comment that I'm
gonna say about them, though,
is it's always the same,
and it kind of
doesn't go anywhere.
Sometimes
when we're big and bold,
we think we gotta be
"Whoo, chile, lawd have mercy."
You don't have to be that
all the time.
So it's a matter of giving us
other sides of Kandy Muse,
so we can see that
you've got more than that.
- Thank you.
Up next, Elliott With 2 Ts
for your pleasure.
I love the little black dress,
but it's too... regular.
Okay.
And then in the challenge,
you can move.
- Thank you.
- You killed that shit.
You looked like
you could have been Halston
or Norma Kamali's muse.
I wish I would have
gone to Studio 54
when I was 10 years old
with Drew Barrymore,
but, alas, that wasn't
in the cards for me.
But you gave us that experience.
It was lit-lit.
Elliott, I know
you're a trained dancer.
What was it that attracted you
to dance in the first place?
I always, as a little kid, would
spin around in the living room,
and so my mom saw it,
and at five years old
put me in dance class.
It was my escape from
the bullying and the torment
that I received
in that small farm town.
It healed me, it protected me.
I've said this before
and I'll say it again.
If you have a child,
put your child in dance class!
Yes! [laughs]
Up next, Tamisha Iman.
This outfit, for me,
I'm always looking
for that twist.
- It's a really gorgeous garment.
- Thank you.
Just think about
always elevating it.
- Is that neoprene?
- It is.
It's not easy to work with that.
But I think what's happening
a little bit with the pleating
is it's so much gathering up top
that it kind of
takes away from your figure.
In the challenge,
it was a little bit off.
You're kind of thinking
about what's coming next.
I think if you just have
a little more fun and exhale,
I think you're gonna perform
better and also enjoy it more.
Like with anal sex.
[all laugh] Exactly. Exactly.
I'm still getting a little bit
of fear in your eyes
when you're performing.
Six months ago, I couldn't walk.
I'm trying to get back
to the old Tamisha.
So I'm fighting,
but at the same time,
like you said, I'm in my head.
And I'm not making excuses.
I'm just being honest.
- Thank you, Tamisha.
- Thank you.
Up next, a disco queen,
child, Miss Olivia Lux.
Tonight on the runway,
I think the hair
is what's speaking here,
and we are listening.
And then you gave us
a little twist
with the micro-berkin I call it.
[all laugh]
I had a good time watching you.
I thought I was back
in the disco days.
It just... everything worked.
Your disco hair was the first
thing that caught my eye.
That is your hair.
That's, like, your trademark,
and it was so gorgeous
the way it moved.
It was just amazing.
You exude positivity and joy,
that disco vibe that
was so happy about that time.
I think you have
what they call "It factor."
I mean, it's just
you are radiant.
Thank you.
Up next, Utica Queen.
Tonight in the challenge,
I felt like I was watching
Mary Hartman, Mary Hartman
meets Carol Burnett.
There were so many faces
being made,
I felt like I wasn't in a disco.
Camp is great,
but there is a line
where it becomes caricature
of a caricature.
Tonight on the runway,
I wanna know how you
came up with this look.
I'm my earrings.
Your earrings?
Yeah, yeah, I'm my earrings.
And then the thing
on top is the earring!
- Oh, my God, you guys!
- Get it?
Thank you
for explaining this look,
because before, I was like,
what the fuck is going on here?
[all laugh]
I mean, I loved it.
I just didn't know what it was.
Sometimes you have to think
to yourself, you know,
are they really
gonna understand this?
Because it's a competition.
Put you, but make sure
that they can understand it.
Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
While you untuck
in the werkroom,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right, now, just between
us squirrel friends,
whaddaya think?
Tina Burner.
When she came out
during that performance,
the other two, I forgot them,
and I was looking at Tina.
She's a real showgirl.
That dress was fantastic.
Gangbusters when she came out
on that stage.
Kandy Muse.
I feel like her content needs
to catch up to her personality,
if that makes sense.
I want her
to go above and beyond
what comes naturally for her.
I want her to push herself
out of her comfort zone.
It would have been funny
if she played
almost like a dumb blonde,
which is total opposite,
and it could have been
really fun
and we wouldn't have
taken our eyes off of her.
Kandy Muse did not capture
the spirit of the disco-mentary.
Elliott With 2 Ts.
Elliott could dance,
and she let us have it tonight.
And she sold the story
with her body movement.
As good as the disco was,
the runway
was kind of disappointing.
It was Sex in the City.
I love it.
If the city were Albuquerque.
[all laugh]
Oh, my goodness.
Tamisha.
She has the chops
to be competing with every one
of these girls up here.
Timing was off, props were off.
We have to critique her
on what we saw.
In this challenge she was timid,
and you could see in her eyes
that she was unsure of herself.
The pros for Tamisha
is that she is a survivor.
It's a tough one, because she's
still finding her sea legs.
Do we judge her like anyone else
who enters this competition?
Olivia Lux.
Olivia's like
Michelle Visage: easy.
[all laugh] Yes!
Everything is easy for her.
I was just, like, looking at her
and enjoying the radiance
and the good energy
that is Olivia Lux.
You couldn't take
your eyes off of her
because she is a frickin' star.
There's a warm feeling
that she projects on stage
that you can't buy that.
Utica Queen.
We shouldn't have had to dig
and ask to know that
it was a two-inch-long earring
that none of us would have
ever been able to see.
- Drag is a visual medium.
- Yeah.
We need to see it
and get the joke.
I love the kind of queen she is,
but when she was performing,
she does this thing
with her body
that she's almost making
a joke out of everything
in a way that is distracting
from the piece.
She would not
have gotten in Studio 54
with that outfit
that she had on.
She would have been
on the ropes.
Crimped, long hair,
yes, that was a seventies thing.
But when you pull it back
into, like, you know,
an Eleanor Roosevelt low pony,
it's not hot. Sorry.
[all laugh]
Silence! Enough is enough.
Bring back my girls.
- Where they at?
- [laughs]
Get 'em back.
[laughs]
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Tina Burner,
That's the way,
uh-huh, uh-huh, we like it.
You're safe.
You may join the other girls.
Olivia Lux.
This week, you gave us
a sweet love hangover,
and I don't want no cure.
Okay.
Con-drag-ulations, You're the
winner of this week's challenge.
[cheers and applause]
You've won a cash tip of $5.000.
I won?
I won my first challenge.
And it feels so amazing.
You're finally seeing me.
I am a force
to be reckoned with.
Elliott With 2 Ts, you're safe.
Thank you so much.
Tamisha Iman.
This week, you looked
a little panicked at the disco.
Kandy Muse.
You gave us earth and wind,
but we needed fire.
Utica Queen.
The judges wanted you
to feel more mighty real.
Syracuse, Schenectady, Utica...
- You're safe.
- [gasps]
Thank you.
[applause]
Kandy Muse, Tamisha Iman,
I'm sorry, my dears,
but you are up for elimination.
Kandy and Tamisha
literally just fought it out,
and now they're in
the bottom two together.
Kandy cannot go home right now,
so she better slay this shit.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come... [thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing] for your life.
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
[music plays]
♪ While he was scheming ♪
♪ I was beamin' in the Beemer,
just beamin' ♪
♪ Can't believe that
I caught my man cheatin' ♪
♪ So I found another way
to make him pay for it all ♪
♪ So I went to Neiman Marcus
on a shopping spree-uh ♪
♪ And on the way,
I grabbed Soley and Mia ♪
♪ And as the cash box rang,
I thought everything away ♪
♪ Oops, there goes the dreams
we used to say ♪
♪ Oops, there goes the time
we spent away ♪
♪ Oops, for all the lies
you told ♪
♪ This is what you owe ♪
♪ Hey, ladies ♪
♪ When your man
wanna get buck wild ♪
♪ Just go back
and hit 'em up style... ♪
Kandy is giving me
so much life right now.
There is so much passion
in her face.
Come on, Kandy!
♪ While he was braggin' ♪
♪ I was coming down the hill
just draggin' ♪
♪ All his pictures and
his clothes in the bag and ♪
♪ Sold everything else till
there was just nothin' left ♪
♪ And I paid all the bills
about a month too late... ♪
Tamisha Iman is giving you
good, old-school drag down.
Baby's giving you, like,
the, you know, boom-boom,
and I'm loving it.
♪ All of the dreams you sold ♪
♪ Left me out in the cold ♪
♪ What happened to the days ♪
♪ When we used to
trust each other? ♪
♪ And all of the things I sold ♪
♪ Will take you
until you get old ♪
♪ To get 'em back without me ♪
♪ 'Cause it might be better
than money or sex ♪
♪ Hey, ladies ♪
♪ When your man
wanna get buck wild ♪
♪ Just go back
and hit 'em up style ♪
♪ Put your hands
on his cash and ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Hey, ladies ♪
♪ Hey, ladies, hey, ladies ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Oh ♪
[cheers and applause]
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Kandy Muse, shantay you stay.
[cries]
Thank you so much.
You may join the other girls.
Tamisha Iman.
You're a fighter,
a survivor, and a star.
Thank you for
the amazing opportunity.
I'm truly grateful.
Thank you to each
and every one of you
from the bottom of my heart.
Thank you.
I never can say goodbye,
so until we meet again,
I'll just say sashay away.
[applause]
Tamisha!
Come here, babe.
Kill it.
No tea, no tea, no deal,
no deal, no deal, no deal.
Do what you do.
I'll see you on the road.
[all laugh]
It's not the end.
It's just till we meet again.
[cheers and applause]
I don't want anybody to feel sad
that Tamisha's going home.
I was so worried about
are they gonna find out
that I got an ostomy?
Is it gonna hold me back?
Every competition,
you don't have to win.
Sometimes you just
have to show up,
and this is part of my legacy.
This gave me the drive,
determination that I needed
to return back
to the art form that I love.
Going home is not a bad thing,
because I can go home
and actually heal
to get ready for All Stars.
[laughs]
And I'm gonna
start working tomorrow,
so whenever the call come,
I'm ready.
Con-drag-ulations, ladies.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an "amen" up in here?
- Amen!
All right,
now let the music play!
♪ I'm a winner ♪
♪ I'm a winner, baby ♪
RuPaul: Next time
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
You need to improv for your life
on the trashy talk show
Bossy Rossy After Dark.
[cheering]
No, I will not!
Woman, get your ass
out of my face!
Oh, no!
- Shut up!
- Aah!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! Aah!
You did great!
You gave us over-the-top,
stupid and ridiculous.
This is Season 13, girl.
Listen, you got to go hard
or go home.
I am genuinely frustrated.
Aah!
♪ I'm a winner ♪
♪ I'm a winner, baby ♪
♪ Losers, weepers ♪
♪ Finders, keepers ♪
♪ I'm a winner, baby ♪
♪ Losers, weepers ♪
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org