- Previously on
"RuPaul's Drag Race"...
It's time to play
The Snatch Game!
- How you doing, RuPaul?
- Hee hee!
- Uzo Abu-boo left the stage.
[laughter]
- What do you do for bunions?
- Well, I was told that you can
get them shaved off.
I'm about to get that done.
- Naomi Smalls.
- It's becoming
quite predictable
to come out in lingerie.
Maybe you should
switch it up now.
- Acid Betty.
- I need, like, a nasal,
angry Southern voice.
And she leans in like she's
in your living room.
- I wish I had you as a coach.
- Okay.
- Bob The Drag Queen,
you are the winner
of this week's challenge.
Naomi Smalls,
shantay, you stay.
Acid Betty, sashay away.
[electronic music]
- What a day.
- I'm really glad
that Naomi's still here.
If Naomi had gone home,
I would've lost a great friend.
And Acid Betty's gone.
- "Ladies, you have been
touched by fierceness.
Bob, love you.
See Jew in New York."
- Betty has
the most iconic looks,
and that's my Brooklyn girl.
But she was always just,
like, in a bad mood,
putting things down.
She deserved to go.
- It was literally the worst
feeling I've ever felt.
I'm just very embarrassed
and disappointed in myself.
I let Ru down, and I know
that he's disappointed in me,
and that's like
the worst feeling ever.
I'm so scared now.
Feel like I have to wear, like,
a fucking turtleneck
that's to the floor.
- Was everything else you
brought here a bra and a panty?
- No.
- Two piece and a biscuit?
[laughter]
- I mean, I work hard
for my body and I love my body.
- I don't think the judges
are telling you
to be ashamed of your body.
I think they just
want to see one time
where you show them
something different.
- Where you wear clothing.
[laughter]
- The other queens
think that what I do
doesn't take a lot of effort,
and that's totally not true.
I put tons of work
into my drag aesthetic,
so it's frustrating.
Well, Bob, congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, congratulations, Bob.
- I had a lot of fun.
- Yeah.
- My reaction to Bob's win
is this...
Always.
I'm just, like, sick of it.
- I came in a close second,
though--they really liked me.
- I'm the first one to win two,
I won two!
I'm gonna try to get three.
Has anyone ever
won three before?
- Bob, shut up.
- I'm really proud of myself
and I feel like the other girls
are really gunning for me now.
They're like, "Oh, you think
you all that, bitch?"
But I don't mean
to come across that way.
I'm just having fun.
I'm just, like, living my dream,
making people laugh,
which is me being me.
- Have you ever played Jenga?
That's Bob.
Like, slowly he's being
built up,
but sooner or later,
the foundation is gonna crumble
and he's gonna take a big fall.
[dramatic music]
- Whoo!
[car engine starts]
-  RuPaul Drag Race
- The winner
of "RuPaul's Drag Race"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia
Beverly Hills cosmetics
and a cash prize
of $100,000.
With extra special
guest judges
Todrick Hall
and Marc Jacobs!
-  RuPaul Drag Race
-  May the best woman
Best woman win
[upbeat music]
- [chuckling]
- Now that we're in
the top seven,
I have no idea
who could go home next.
You can have
your ugly purse back.
- Damn.
[alarm sounds]
[all cheering]
- Ooh, girl!
- Girl!
- She done already done
had herses!
My queens, are you
a friend of Dorothy's,
or just plain wicked?
Just click your tongue
and repeat after me.
There's no place like
"Drag Race."
[clicks tongue]
[all click tongues]
Okay?
Hello, hello, hello!
[overlapping greetings]
We've got company.
Close the door behind you.
What you think this is?
Ladies, say hello
to Marc Snetiker.
Snetiker, please.
[laughter]
He's a writer
with "Entertainment Weekly."
- Oh.
- I'm so excited to be here, Ru.
Our "EW" readers love to read
the "Drag Race" recaps
every week.
- Well, I'm glad
you brought up reading.
Because in the great tradition
of "Paris Is Burning"...
[dramatic music]
The library is about
to be open, darling.
[all cheering]
Because reading is what?
all: Fundamental!
- That's right.
First up, Chi Chi DeVayne.
Come on down, honey.
[cheering]
- Chi Chi!
- Yeah!
[laughter]
- All right, Thorgy Thor.
Girl, I love you so much,
I don't know whether
to give you a hug
or put some change in a cup.
[laughter]
Bob The Drag Queen.
You may be from New York, honey,
but those feet
are still from Mississippi.
[laughter]
- Love it.
- Chi Chi, your drag is just
like turkey neck.
Cheap, and no one wants it.
[laughter]
- Wow.
- Naomi Smalls.
Your wardrobe reminds me of
a legendary "Drag Race" queen.
Nicole Paige Brooks.
[laughter]
- Nice.
- Shade!
Who knew that was lurking
underneath that--
- We all knew.
- Simple.
I mean Derrick.
I mean Britney.
You know, you are pretty
attractive.
I'd hit that baby one more time.
[laughter]
Bob.
Please shut up.
[laughter]
- Naomi.
No one knows whether
to call you "Ny-omi"
or "Nay-omi,"
but judging from
your runway looks,
no one's gonna be
calling you at all.
[laughter]
Bob The Drag Queen.
I had no idea
that there are different shades
of ashy.
[laughter]
- Kim Chi.
You are stomping
for the gods on the runway.
[laughter]
I just wish your drag
would get raptured.
[laughter]
Naomi. I'm gonna give you some
advice, darling.
No one's gonna
take you seriously
if you were born
after Windows 95 came out.
[laughter]
- Robbie Turner, we know
you're a vintage queen,
but do you have to smell
like mothballs too?
- Oh, fuck off.
[laughter]
- Derrick Barry.
You say it takes you an hour
to do your face.
Why does it look
like five minutes?
[laughter]
- Beauty.
- It is a known fact that
Derrick Barry is not very smart.
When she heard "Britney Spears,"
she said, "Does she?
I prefer fencing."
[laughter]
It is very hard to have
an intelligent conversation
with Derrick Barry.
The only thing harder
is Robbie Turner's wig lines.
[laughter]
Rob-bie Turn-ter!
I know you're a huge fan of
classic movies and television.
May I recommend one of my
favorite classic TV shows?
"Flipper."
[laughter]
- Oh, my goodness!
Y'all went in deep!
- I feel like I'm a lot
shadier just by being here.
[laughter]
The winner of today's
mini-challenge...
is Bob The Drag Queen.
- Whoo!
[applause]
- Bob just won, again.
Ugh.
- You've won jewels valued
at $1,500
from Fierce Drag Jewels.
- Oh, wow!
- And to see more reads,
go to logotv.com.
Let's say good-bye to Mark,
everybody!
all: Bye, Mark!
- Ladies, since you love
reading so much,
I want to share with you
my favorite book of all time,
"The Wonderful Wizard of Oz."
[applause]
This week's maxi-challenge
is your chance
to strut your stuff down
the yellow brick road.
But you won't be doing it alone.
Please welcome some
"Drag Race" super fans.
[cheers and applause]
The cast of Lifetime TV's
"Little Women: LA."
Say hello to...
And last but not least...
Now, for this
makeover challenge,
you need to create
original drag couture
for you and your partner
inspired by
one of the characters in
"The Wonderful Wizard of Oz."
#WizardsofDrag.
[laughter]
Little women of LA,
you choose the queen
you want to be your partner.
Briana, which character
do you have?
- I have the Wicked Witch,
and I actually picked Kim Chi.
[chuckles]
Hi!
- Hi!
[laughter]
- I have
the citizen of Emerald City,
and the queen I picked
is Thorgy Thor.
- Whoo!
[cheers and applause]
[laughter]
- I have the Cowardly Lion,
and the queen I picked
is Robbie Turner.
[laughter]
- Yes!
- I'm gonna be
Glinda the Good Witch,
because I'm good,
and sometimes I'm a witch.
[laughter]
And I'll take
Bob The Drag Queen.
[laughter]
- I have Tin Woodman,
and I am
100% going
with Mr. Derrick Barry!
- Whoo!
I love Terra!
I've met Terra in the past,
and she impersonates Britney.
She's Mini-Britney.
It's a perfect match.
- I have the Scarecrow,
and I'm taking Naomi Smalls.
- Okay.
[laughter]
[applause]
- How are you?
- Hello.
- I am Dorothy.
And I have Chi Chi!
- I love you!
[applause]
You don't play no games, baby.
I watch you
all the time.
- Now, there should be a strong
drag family resemblance.
- [laughs]
[upbeat music]
- Ooh, these are cool!
- Yeah!
- This week's maxi-challenge
is to make over
the cast of "Little Women: LA,"
inspired by the characters of
"The Wonderful Wizard of Oz."
- So, I'm open to anything,
because I love fashion,
and makeup,
and I'm a hair stylist.
- Me too. Yeah.
- Are you?
Whoo!
This is gonna be bomb.
- I'm so excited I get Jasmine,
because she's gorgeous,
and I'm gorgeous, and--
Like, you literally just, like,
are, like, posed like that.
- Oh, like--
- Yeah.
- Like a Scarecrow
'cause they're very still.
- Exactly.
- Oh, shoot!
- I'm excited that we
get to do some designing.
I could seriously look
at fashion magazines
from the time
Barnes & Noble opens
to the time
Barnes & Noble closes.
I really want
to show the girls
that I'm not just
a walking bra and panty
and I'm talented.
[chuckles]
- So tell me, like, what's
your personal style like?
- It's very vintage.
- Me too.
- My wedding was a 1940s
vintage wedding dress.
- Fabulous!
I love that.
- Yeah.
- So, the Cowardly Lion.
We're gonna make, you know,
a cute little dress
or maybe a leotard
or I don't know.
I'm thinking.
- You have a big challenge.
- I do have a big challenge,
yeah.
- Oh, Robbie.
I agree with Christy.
I think he's gonna
have a challenge,
because based on
his poodle challenge
a couple episodes ago,
Robbie's not the best
at construction,
and especially with somebody
much smaller.
- So how do you fit
into your group?
'Cause here's the thing.
They're sick of me winning
all the time,
so they're all like,
"Ooh, Bob wins everything.
Everyone loves Bob."
- The bitchy one.
- The one right here?
- Yeah.
- I can hear you.
- I mean, I'd be lying if I said
I wasn't a little nervous.
I don't know if there's anyone
in "The Wizard of Oz"
more the opposite of who I am
than Glinda the Good Witch.
And I think, honestly, a lot of
the girls want to see me do bad.
I am nervous!
- Why?
- You know you guys are all
fucking gunning for me to lose.
- Well, of course we are.
We just want you
to trip and fall, that's all.
- Ooh, hoo, hoo!
- Sometimes it's funny to watch
other people, like, squirm.
Especially Bob.
Too real?
- Our resources
are very limited.
- I'm just worried about
being efficient.
I'm feeling a little pressured
about the outfits today
because so far the judges
seem to not like my style.
I keep saying that
I'm like the broke queen,
you know what I mean?
I just cannot get out
of my head.
- See, you can't do that.
Don't even claim that.
Don't even have that energy.
It ain't no "if."
It ain't "I'm trying,"
or "I can't."
No.
"I am,"
and "I'm doing it."
'Cause if I could do it,
you sure could do it.
- Mm-hmm.
- I didn't let
my height to get in my way
of my dreams.
Don't think small.
- The lesson in "The Wonderful
Wizard of Oz" for Dorothy
is that she's searching for
something that she already has,
so maybe I have
everything I need
and I am a real-life Dorothy.
- Whatever you do,
I'ma wear it,
strut it,
and be confident in it, okay?
'Cause you know that's how
I roll.
[both laugh]
- Hello, hello, hello!
both: Hi!
- Hello!
- Hi, Kim Chi.
Hi, Briana.
- Hi, Ru.
- Hello.
- Now, Kim Chi, you're known
for really high concept,
Leigh Bowery style.
- Yeah.
- How does that translate
to a little person?
- Well, I ask her, like,
what are some of
your style inspirations?
And she said Jessica Rabbit
and...
both: Betty Boop.
- Cartoon makeup is
what I love doing,
so it's a match
made in heaven.
- Because of your
knowledge of design,
there are high expectations.
Does that make you nervous?
- It doesn't make me nervous,
'cause I feel like the first
challenge, I won,
and then I was in the bottom
right after that
and I've been safe since,
so I want to knock
this one out of the park.
- Good, good.
I'm looking forward to this.
- All right.
I'll not let you down.
- All right, kids.
Hey, guys.
- Hi, Ru. How are you?
- Hi, Brittney.
- Hi!
- Now, Brittney, have you
ever been made over before?
- No, I have never, but I was
on tour with Miley Cyrus--
- Miley Cyrus?
- Yeah!
She thought of the outfits,
and she made everything.
So we had cones
coming from our boobs,
all crazy stuff.
- Wow.
Thorgy, do you have any sketches
or anything?
- Actually, I just--that was
the stage we just got to.
- Okay.
All right.
Time is running out.
- I'm feeling the pressure.
- All right, Thorgy.
- Thanks a lot, Ru.
- Thanks, Brittney.
- Thank you.
- Cool.
- Hello!
both: Hi.
- So what do you have planned?
- Well, we are the Tin Woman,
and the Tin "Whoa, Man!"
- [laughs]
- So I was thinking
of creating
elements that can
go onto a body suit
or something like that.
- That's great, but haven't
you done that before?
Wearing a body suit
or a bathing suit,
and then putting something
on top of it?
We're looking for couture,
something inspired
by the Tin Woodsman,
so take it from there.
- I don't handle
losing very well,
so I will give this 120.
- Well, you say that while
you have a hatchet in your hand.
That kind of scares me.
[laughter]
All right, well, I'm gonna
let you get to it.
- [sighs]
Now I have to rethink ideas.
That really scares me.
Oh, God.
- All right, ladies,
gather round.
Gather round, ladies.
Now tomorrow, in addition
to your runway presentation,
I want each duo to perform
a dreamy interpretive dance
set in a poppy field.
Of course.
[laughs]
- [laughs]
[upbeat music]
- This week's maxi-challenge
is makeovers
for the cast of
"Little Women: LA."
- They're looking like they're
getting creative over there.
- Which one?
Oh, the Tin Man?
- Mm-hmm.
- I wouldn't be too worried
about Derrick.
- All right, let's do it.
- Okay.
- We're sleeping.
- Are we gonna lay down?
- Yeah.
- This whole time?
It's finally time to rehearse
our interpretive dance routine.
To ask the question "Do I
understand interpretive dance?"
is to ask "Do I know
the entire pi formula?"
And the answer is no.
- I woke up with a nightmare.
His face looks like
he's going for a dental checkup.
- Oh, my God.
Terra, you belong here with us.
- [laughs]
- Pow!
- Girl, what the hell
are you doing?
Like, she's just slapping
her little lady around.
- Fucking bitch!
- You gonna get a charge, girl.
You beating up on a little lady.
- Oh!
- I'm guessing we should
just play up the fact
that we're scarecrows.
- Okay.
- And maybe we can, like,
do like a cross, like--
- Should I go in front of you?
- Sure.
- And then it looks like
you put that leg out.
- I don't know what to do.
What's interpretive dance?
- Uh...
- Uh oh.
The Scarecrow people.
- Are they practicing?
What they doing?
- No, they both staring
at each other,
trying to figure it out.
[laughter]
- He ain't no choreographer.
He don't dance.
He was in the bottom last week.
- Uh oh.
- This is his time
to, like, step it up.
- I have no idea what the fuck
we're supposed to do.
- "What do you think?"
"What do you think?"
[both laugh]
- Y'all better stop
thinking and start doing.
[laughs]
- I love you.
[both laugh]
[machine stalling]
Why is this machine
being a dick?
[machine stalling]
Oh, my God.
Do you want to see
something completely insane?
- [gasps]
What the fuck?
Why did you sew
it like this?
I don't even know
how you did this.
- No, I don't either.
Isn't that bizarre?
Apparently this fabric
cannot be sewn on.
So we've gone from a
beautiful, regal cape,
to making bustles to give us
sort of a regal flair.
I want to scream.
My brain just exploded.
- [screams]
Oh, shit!
[laughter]
- Yes, indeed.
Our little hot glue skirt
turned out good.
- [laughs]
- I'm pretty much done.
I have a complete product
and I'm feeling good today.
- This working?
- Yes, ma'am.
It's not gathering?
- I'm right on track.
- Okay.
- Yeah, it's done.
- What?
We're all working,
and she's done.
Do something more
to your outfit.
Because it doesn't
look that great.
- Come on, Disco Dorothy.
- [laughs]
- I almost want to go over
there, like, "Hello?"
You have, like,
a challenge to do."
[hums]
Somebody in this competition
should not be
wasting their time but using
every single second
to create every
single thing perfect.
- Needless to say,
I was pissed off.
- Chi Chi is the next to go.
She's not ready
for this competition.
[dramatic music]
[electronic dance music]
- Let's do it!
- Oh, my goodness.
- Let's throw this hideous
purse away.
- I know.
- Did you just throw
Purse Purse?
How dare you?
- We're gonna have,
like, a fucking blast.
We just have to, like,
kill the runway.
Like, we have to kill it.
- Got it.
- Oh, Lord. Bob, how much do
you have to do still?
- Way too much.
- I thought you were
almost done yesterday.
- I was.
My outfit fell apart.
- He had to remake
a new outfit.
- So I get to
the workroom this morning,
and try on my couture look,
and the zipper
just like flies off.
It falls apart, basically.
Like, it is just non-functional.
So I need to make
a new outfit.
And on top of that,
I still have to do my makeup,
I have to do Elena's makeup.
I'm like F-M-L.
Oh, my God.
This is madness.
- So do you kind of
find it hard
being a, you know,
a little person?
- It was hard.
- I am made fun of
all the time.
-I get personally offended
by the word "midget."
Because "midget" doesn't
necessarily mean,
like, a person.
- Mm-hmm.
- It just means something small.
It's such a derogatory,
ugly word.
It, like, makes me cringe
when I hear it.
- Do you think it's
because people are just
afraid of what
they don't know?
- Yeah.
- You know what trips me out?
Is if I'm literally
at the mall walking,
and somebody's like, "Oh,
my gosh! Look at that midget!"
I'm like, "Are you serious?"
- People have
a long way to come.
- Yeah.
- I think that's why I feel so
comfortable around gay people,
'cause they get how I feel
because, you know,
they get treated
the same way.
- Right, exactly.
You can't stop being the height
that you are, you know?
- Yeah.
- It's like who you are.
- And you love
who you love.
- Right.
At the end of the day,
everybody just
wants to be loved.
Everybody just wants to fit in.
- Exactly.
- My confidence
didn't really build
until I had a child.
- So you could be strong
for your baby.
- Yes, and I had to
help her deal with it.
- Mm-hmm.
- I had to be an example.
She's average height,
and so
I was really hard on her, 'cause
I had to gain that respect.
- Yeah.
- At an early age,
because I knew by the time
she was seven or eight,
she was gonna be
taller than me.
And I refused to be
on somebody's talk show
saying "My kid
is whooping my ass."
- Yeah. [laughs]
- That was not gonna happen.
[electronic music]
- There we go.
Oh, my God.
I don't know how I'm gonna
get any of this--
any of my shit done.
So Elena's done, but then
I look at myself in the mirror
and I'm like, "Oh, my God,
I don't have time
to get myself pretty."
- Okay, face.
Face, face, face.
I'm not wearing
any makeup at all.
- It's not possible.
It's literally not possible.
- [laughs]
[car roars past]
[RuPaul's "Cover Girl" plays]
Cover girl
Put the bass in your walk
Head to toe
Let your whole body talk
- And what?
[cheers and applause]
Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
Michelle Visage.
- My darling,
there's no place like home.
- He's back!
Ross Matthews.
- I'm so excited, I'm clicking
my heels under the table, honey.
- [laughs]
And the world's
biggest "Oz" fan,
Todrick Hall.
- Ru, my life has been
black and white until now,
and now all I see
is amazing color.
- Oh, you gonna
play the race card?
[laughter]
And fashion's coolest designer,
and a supporter
of the drag arts,
Marc Jacobs is here.
- Can't be happier being
somewhere over
the rainbow with you.
- Thank you, darling. It's a joy
to have you here with us.
- Thank you.
- This week,
we challenged our queens
to drag up the cast
of "Little Women: LA."
And tonight, they're ready to
ease on down the runway.
Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best woman win.
[RuPaul's "The Realness" plays]
The realness
First up,
serving Dorothy couture,
Chi Chi and Ti Ti DeVayne.
- Come on, Disco Dorothy.
- We look good.
I mean, you can't go wrong
when you're serving up
Nubian Dorothy realness.
- Come through, Dorothy.
- Zbornak?
- Zbornak, yes.
Serving Glinda the Good Witch
couture
is Bob The Drag Queen
and Rob The Faux Queen.
Glinda Evangelista!
[laughter]
- I'm really shocked that
I dressed as fast as I did,
but we look good.
Me and Rob The Faux Queen
are, like,
living our dreams
on the runway.
- I think I wore
that outfit to prom.
[laughs]
- Serving Scarecrow couture,
Naomi Smalls and Jazzy Jems.
- I ain't scared of her.
- [laughs]
- Very Oz-mopolitan.
- I'm trying to give the judges
a different side of Naomi.
Vivienne Westwood
meets Scarecrow
meets Vidal Sassoon
and we look amazing.
- Thank God her pussy's
not on fire.
- We're all eating crow now.
- We are.
- Serving Tin Woodman couture,
Terra and Derrick Barry.
- She brought her own lube!
- [laughs]
- I knew that I wanted to
make the Tin Woodman sexy,
so we're showing leg,
we're showing body,
- Ooh, girl, you better axe
somebody.
- [laughs]
- Not a girl,
not yet a tin woman.
[laughter]
- Serving Cowardly Lion couture,
Robbie and Hedda Turner.
Nobody mention Cecil.
- [laughs loudly]
- Rowr!
Christy and I,
we are giving you
king of the forest.
Serving courage and fearfulness
and elegance.
- This is the mane event.
- [laughs]
- Paws up.
- Serving Citizen of
Emerald City couture,
Thorgy Thor and Thorgeous.
I think it's 4:20
in the Emerald City.
[laughter]
- We're giving you artistic
Fifth Avenue
meets "Fifth Element."
Everyone wants to be us and
everyone wants to know
where we purchased
these fabulous green outfits.
- Always been seen
in emerald green.
- Oh!
Wow!
Serving Wicked Witch couture,
Kim Chi and Miso Chi.
You know, the Chi dynasty.
- [laughs]
- My concept for this runway
is Isabella Blow
going to a funeral realness.
And Briana is definitely
selling the garment.
She's feeling all sorts
of fantasy.
- Water won't melt them.
- Now it's time for
"The Wonderful Wizard of Oz"
dream sequence.
[RuPaul's "Night After Night"
plays]
Night after night,
I close my eyes
And I wonder
when the sun will rise
Day by day,
I live my life
And I try my best
to do what's right
A moment of hope
is all I need
To keep me moving on
Through the dark,
till I see
- [laughs]
[car roars past]
- Welcome, ladies.
It's time for
the judges' critiques.
First up, Chi Chi
and Ti Ti DeVayne.
- I thought your performance
was really sweet.
And the two of you
look really pretty.
But I would like to
see it all pushed further.
- I have something to ask you.
I know you're not
a breast drag queen.
Do you ever
consider contouring?
- Yes, I tried to kind of
contour tonight.
- With what,
translucent powder, girl?
[laughter]
Because your waist
is not cinched.
We gotta balance out the man.
- Next up,
Bob The Drag Queen--
not to be confused
with Bob The Court Reporter--
and Rob The Faux Queen.
- Elena, do you feel gorgeous?
- Yeah. I feel like
I'm in "Hunger Games."
[laughter]
- Totally.
Well, I thought
you really shone tonight,
and, Bob, I don't think
that's good for you.
Elena looks inspired
by the Good Witch,
and yours, I feel like I could
get that in a mall.
- I guess I thought
that was the challenge.
I was really wanting
to make sure that Elena
felt like a beautiful goddess,
you know what I mean?
- But you're the one competing.
- Okay.
- Next up, Naomi Smalls
and Jazzy Jems.
- Everyone should take a look
at Naomi right now.
This is how you win
this competition.
- Yeah, you did
an amazing job.
I mean, it just gave me
Scarecrow
in the most gorgeous way.
The look, the details,
the makeup.
I just thought
it was perfection.
- And you could not have asked
for a better partner--Jasmine,
with these straw leg warmers on.
[laughter]
It was just phenomenal.
- Thank you.
- Next up, Derrick
and Terra Barry.
- It just looks so homemade,
in the worst way.
- Uh, I'm not a seamstress,
but I did sew everything
on here.
- It's a piece of fabric.
We're, like, pretty far in
to the competition now.
You have to give us more.
That is not
a Britney reference.
- I have watched you in Vegas.
I know what
you're capable of,
and it just sort of saddens me
because you're better than
what you just did up there.
- Next up, Robbie
and Hedda Turner.
- I literally don't even know
what to make
out of what you're wearing.
Bustles can be flattering
when they're on a big gown.
This looks like just a bunch
of ruched up fabric stuck--
And we have to work
on that hairline.
- I guess I'm a little
more old school.
I come from big ol'
Christian hair women.
- Even Jan Crouch
found a way to blend.
- [laughs]
- Robbie!
We're at this point now.
It's, like, so frustrating,
because you are so talented
and all we want is
for you to bring it.
And we're missing it.
- All right, Kim Chi
and Miso Chi.
- I got a Kimbra, Feller,
"Voluptuous Horror of
Karen Black" sort of vibe,
and the look was fantastic.
- I loved the beginning
runway walk,
even though it was
a little wobbly.
You had a complete concept.
Great job tonight.
- Next up, Thorgy Thor
and Thorgeous.
- What I was
charmed by, really,
was when you eased on down
the road into your dance moves.
- Your look tonight,
I thought it was cohesive,
but it didn't wow me.
I'm not gonna remember in a
few weeks, driving in traffic,
thinking "Oh, God,
remember that look?"
You know?
- Ladies,
one final question:
who deserves to click their
heels and go back to Kansas?
Starting with Chi Chi DeVayne.
- [blows out air]
I'm sorry, Derrick, but
your outfit to me, was just...
a train wreck.
- Bob The Drag Queen.
- Based off this challenge,
I would pick Derrick as well.
- Naomi.
- Based on execution, I would
probably say Derrick's too.
- Derrick.
- Well, I would say
all three that said me,
but I know I have
to pick one.
I would say Chi Chi's.
It's hot-glued together.
It's cut fabric
with no detail.
- What say you,
Robbie Turner?
- Chi Chi's didn't
scream "Dorothy" to me.
- Kim Chi?
- I love her,
but I'm going to say Chi Chi,
only because
yesterday, when everyone
was just working hard,
she was just sitting there,
and that was a time
that she could have
spent on her outfit.
Sorry.
- Thorgy Thor, you're up.
- Kim Chi, you literally said
every word that I was gonna say.
I think in this competition
you have to apply
every single second
and I'm here to win,
so people like
Chi Chi piss me off.
- Yes, I did have extra time,
because I did hot glue
my outfit,
but I did what was
in my range of doing.
But that's how they feel, so
I respect y'all's opinion.
- All right, I think we've
heard enough, ladies.
While you untuck backstage,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
Just between us
friends of Dorothy,
what do you think?
Chi Chi DeVayne.
- I really didn't care about
the hot glue gun conspiracy,
issue, whatever.
[laughter]
Like--
- Gluegate!
- You know, there's a lot of
hot glue gunning going on,
even at the Met Ball.
- Really?
- I don't want
to name names, but--
- Please name names!
- Please do!
- Who's mad at a hot glue gun?
BenDeLaCreme won
a fashion challenge
with a hot glued dress.
- But here's the deal:
that outfit, at this point,
is nowhere near good enough.
- Bob The Drag Queen.
- Well, Bob The Drag Queen
made the biggest mistake
you can make in show business:
you don't let someone
outshine you!
- But Elena looked beautiful,
so he did his job there.
- I know that that was part
of the challenge,
but I wasn't looking at
Bob The Drag Queen tonight.
I was looking at Elena.
- Naomi Smalls.
- Told her last week
I was getting bored
of seeing her in underwear,
so when she came out tonight
the way she did with something
creative, it was amazing.
- The look, from head to toe,
was flawless.
The choreography was amazing.
- I could not have
been more proud,
and I don't even know her.
[laughter]
- Derrick Barry.
- I'm banging my head against
the wall with Derrick
because you're just giving
me a bathing suit
with something wrapped
around your waist, again.
And putting two horse penises
on your shoulders...
- Oh!
- [laughs]
- Doesn't change it.
- I cannot.
- She's amazing as Britney.
And we still haven't
gotten past this, episode six!
- I know that
Britney's frustrated.
- She seems lost to me.
- You said "Britney."
Did you say "Britney"?
- I sure did, yeah.
- That's hilarious.
- But that's the point.
- Robbie Turn-ter.
- Yes, we've seen
way better looks before.
even this hair thing done better
by Kim Chi in episode one,
but I just can't make myself
hate it.
I would be so angry to see
Robbie go home.
- But how many times
is he gonna be excused?
She is holding herself back.
You saw it in
the acting challenge
and you're seeing it again.
- Kim Chi.
- I loved the look,
but the performance
was a little out there.
Didn't understand
the laying of the brooms...
[laughter]
The collecting of the brooms.
But, you know--
- The trading of the brooms.
Returning of the brooms.
[laughter]
- Thorgy Thor.
- [laughs]
[car roars past]
Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Thorgy Thor.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
[applause]
- Oh!
- Kim Chi.
Your witch couture
slayed the house down.
You're safe.
- Thank you.
- Naomi Smalls.
This week, you spun straw
into gold.
Condragulations, you are the
winner of this week's challenge.
[cheers and applause]
You and Jasmine have each won
$1,000 worth of spa services
from The Spa on Rodeo.
- Thank you.
- Awesome.
- It feels amazing that
the legendary RuPaul
is saying my name
in a positive way.
I am freaking out.
- Bob The Drag Queen.
Your Glinda was not bewitching.
You are safe.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
[exhales]
- Derrick Barry.
Your tin couture
was rusted.
I'm sorry, my dear, but
you are up for elimination.
Robbie Turner.
This week you are
not queen of the forest.
Chi Chi DeVayne,
your Disco Dorothy
did not inspire oohs or ahhs.
Robbie Turner.
I'm sorry, my dear, but
you are up for elimination.
- I'm pissed off.
Like, this is so unfair.
- Chi Chi.
You are safe.
You may join the other girls.
- Thank y'all so much.
- Yes!
- I guess I was hoping
for a miracle.
Like they were gonna
pluck Chi Chi
and put her back in the bottom
two where she belongs.
Fuck.
- Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
The time has come...
[thunder rumbles]
For you to lip-synch
for your life.
[voice echoes]
- This is it--I'm gonna have
to take Robbie down.
I love her,
but I will send her home.
- Good luck...
and don't fuck it up.
-  I got this feeling
on the summer day
When you were gone
I crashed my car
into the bridge
I watched,
I let it burn
I threw your stuff
into a bag
And pushed it down
the stairs
I crashed my car
into the bridge
I don't care
I love it
You're on a different road
- I feel confident.
I feel powerful.
I feel like I am killing
this performance.
-  You're so damn hard
to please
We gotta kill this switch
- I'm nailing it.
Connect with my audience.
Make 'em laugh.
Make them want more.
And then don't give it to them.
-  I don't care
I love it
I don't care
[cheering]
I love it,
I love it
I don't care
I love it,
I love it
[laughter and applause]
- Whoo!
That's awesome!
- [sighs]
- Ladies, I've made my decision.
[suspenseful music]
Derrick Barry,
shantay, you stay.
- [exhales]
[sobbing]
I'm sorry.
This is the most emotional
roller coaster
I've ever been on.
I'm so outside
of my comfort zone here,
and it just crumbled down
on me today
because I had put myself
in a Britney box.
And I'm doing my best
to get out of that,
so thank you for allowing me
to continue to make it happen.
- Thank you.
- [sniffles]
May I leave the stage now?
[laughter]
- [inhales deeply]
Yes.
- Thank you all.
- Robbie Turner,
I'm reminded of a quote
from "The Wonderful Wizard
of Oz."
"Now I know I've got a heart
because it's breaking."
Now...
sashay away.
- Thank you, guys, so much.
Love you. Love you. Love you.
- Bye. We love you, Robbie.
- Love you. Mwah!
Good morning.
Guess right now I think
still a little stunned.
I'll probably get back
to Seattle and be like,
"Woe is me,"
and eat some peaches
and then I'll be okay.
Oh, fuck.