- Previously
on "All Stars... "
- It's time to play
Snatch Game!
[cheering]
- What's an appro-ho?
Who you calling ho?
[laughs]
- Carson, I've been meaning
to get these back to you.
[laughs]
- Winner, winner,
chicken...dinner.
- Crickets.
- What's this?
- From Thorgy.
It's says fuck
this shady bitch Shangela.
- I didn't show it to you
'cause I thought it was
not helpful or appropriate.
- But you decided
to hang it on the wall?
- Trixie Mattel.
- I didn't laugh,
like, the whole time.
- Kennedy Davenport.
- The green leaves
on the bottom.
Maybe up
the sophistication level.
- Chi Chi DeVayne.
- You spelled
your name wrong.
And it was like tumbleweeds.
- Shangela.
You're a winner, baby.
- Yay!
- BenDeLaCreme.
You are also a winner, baby.
- Oh!
- There's two lipsticks.
It's bad.
- Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
- I chose Chi Chi.
- Shangela?
- This person left
"RuPaul's Drag Race"
not winning the crown,
but definitely
going forward as a winner
and creating a career
for themselves.
And I know they will do that
long after this
because I believe
in their talent.
I also chose Chi Chi.
- Chi Chi, sashay away.
- $5,000!
- Oh, my gosh!
That was crazy.
- Oh, Chi Chi.
- "Love all of you gals.
Remember to keep it fair,
Chi Chi."
- I haven't seen
a polite mirror message
since Morgan, okay?
She has
such a heart of gold.
- We love you, Chi Chi.
- My boo.
- Chi Chi's
almost like my daughter.
I am gonna miss her spirit
in the workroom.
- Let's buy Shangela
a round of shots.
- Well, I'll take that.
But you know I'm watching
your station, mama.
If I see another note,
it's a wrap. [laughs]
I can't believe
I get a second chance.
I guess I didn't know
if she would be able
to put aside
with the whole drama
about something Thorgy wrote.
But Shangela made a decision
based on the competition,
and I, like,
really respect that.
My heart's yours.
I'll never forget it.
You'll never
have to buy drinks
at the same bar
as me again, girl.
And I will PayPal you
$10,000.
- Oh, I've got 5K right now
for me and BenDeLa.
I just want to clear the air
with Trixie.
I hope that she sees
that by my decision
that I am someone
who could be trusted
and who could possibly
be an ally for her.
Me and Trixie actually
have things in common,
and I would love to focus on
those more
so that we could help each other
get to the top.
- While we're all sad
to see Chi Chi go,
if we're just looking
at track record,
today was actually
a fairly clear decision.
And now we get to the point
where being fair
is going to be more muddy
than it was today.
We're halfway through,
and the criteria for how
we want to eliminate people
is getting more confusing
because some people have
been safe the whole time.
Some people have been in the top
and the bottom.
It's really hard to know
what to judge things on.
- I mean, we would like to
all go on a group criteria
that we all decide upon.
But, honestly,
just letting y'all know,
that ain't really
what's gonna go down.
- We all are at the top,
so our job
gets harder every week.
- Just be respectful with
the mirror messages, people.
[all laugh]
- Everyone
is making these jokes,
but you never know who will
pull the stunts here and there.
There have been surprises
in the past.
It's All Stars, girl.
Anything can happen.
- The winner of "RuPaul's
Drag Race All Stars"
receives a one year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
a coveted spot
in the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize
of $100,000!
With extra special guest judges
Shay Mitchell
and Tituss Burgess.
- ? RuPaul's Drag Race
- ? May the best woman
? Best woman win
- Oh!
- Oh, the girls.
Back in the mix
with the top six. Whoo!
[alarm]
[imitates alarm]
- She done already
done had herses.
- You wanna be an "it girl"?
A real super star?
Your 15 minutes of fame
starts now.
Hello, hello, hello!
[cheering]
- Oh, my God!
- Ladies, this week,
in tribute to my hero,
we're throwing ourselves
a little Andy Warhol Ball.
- Yeah!
- Yes!
- Warhol's celebrity portraits
are worth millions,
but many started out
as Polaroid snapshots.
So for today's mini challenge,
you'll pose
as I take a picture
that we'll transform
into a pop art portrait
that will be worth pennies.
[all laugh]
You've got 15 minutes
to get into quick drag.
Get famous!
- Sis!
- I look like I'm in
an albino cast from Chicago.
- [laughs]
- Ladies,
you're not a real woman
if you don't have perfume on!
- All right, super stars,
time's up.
First up, Kennedy Davenport.
Ooh.
What story
are your eyes gonna tell?
- Dreamy.
- Oh, that's nice,
that's nice.
Why don't you show
top teeth like...
But don't look like
I'm gonna hurt you or anything.
- [laughs]
- That's beautiful.
- Hey, sis.
I know a thing or two
about old glamour.
I got my Dita Von Teese hair.
I'm gonna look good
in this Polaroid.
Ooh, I feel like a model
right now.
- You look like
Linda Evangelista.
- One, two, three.
I'll see you at Studio 54.
Can you lean into it
like that?
Yeah. Oh, nice. Lovely.
Oh, that's nice,
that's nice.
Oh, I can see this
hanging in the Louvre.
- Is that the bathroom?
- [laughs]
- Oh, my God!
I didn't even know
this was happening.
- Oh, look at Miss Trixie
looking all soft...
softish.
- I'm gonna do, like,
a punk rich woman.
- Okay. All right.
- Oh, my God.
There's so much going on.
- Ladies, one of you
is a true pop tart.
Aja.
- Ooh, bitch!
Yes!
I have never won
a mini challenge.
Bitch, I earned it.
- You've won a year's worth
of hamburgers...
- Ooh!
- From Hamburger Mary's.
- I'm so hungry.
- Plus $2,000 cash money,
honey.
- All right.
- And we'll be posting all
of your portraits on VH1.com.
Now, ladies,
our Warhol Ball
is just getting started.
For this week's
maxi challenge,
you'll need to create
two Warhol-inspired looks
from scratch.
- [inhales]
- First look, in homage to his
iconic Campbell Soup can series,
I want you
to become souper models.
That's right. You need
to design a soup can
that captures the true flavor
of your charisma, uniqueness,
nerve and talent.
Now, for your second look,
inspired by Andy's
favorite nightclub, Studio 54,
you need to design
disco queen couture.
Now, to give you a sense
of how wild Studio 54 could be,
Bianca Jagger
was once photographed
entering the club
on a white horse.
God, I miss quaaludes!
[all laugh]
You can use fabrics
provided by Mood
and hair
provided by RockStar Wigs.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best All Star win.
- The maxi challenge
is to create a soup
that reflects who you are
as a drag persona.
Last week, I believed
I was going home,
and this week,
I love sewing.
I love making costumes.
And I'm actually really good
at branding and selling stuff.
So I'm feeling really good.
I wanna win
a fucking challenge.
Is anybody else
doing energy?
- Well, I'm not doing energy.
I'm doing sugar.
- Aja's making something
really sweet
because she's sweet?
- Like, sweets, like,
come get your sugar rush.
Like, I want my soup
to be a candy soup.
- A candy-flavored soup?
It's not interesting and doesn't
really brand you at all.
That's, like, crazy.
- Mine is spicy.
Mine is hot.
And it's call "Achoo."
- Achoo?
- Yeah, it's like spicy,
kind of very flavorful.
It's called "Achoo."
- What the fuck is achoo?
Achoo.
Shouldn't soup help a cold,
not cause one?
You don't hear no soup
being called... [coughs].
- I'm writing my ingredients
right now.
- Uh-huh.
- It's like, you know,
like a peanut soup.
- You're buying ginger,
garlic, onions,
ground peanuts.
That's soup.
That's soup!
- It has some kick to it.
[laughs]
- This isn't "The Chew."
We're not making food.
- What do you think?
"Achoo."
- Honey, if she names
that soup "Achoo,"
that soup is gonna be a recipe
for the bottom two.
- Coming up...
- I took two months
of sewing classes.
Aah!
- Do anybody have a lampshade
that Shangy could borrow?
- Girl!
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Can you trace me a pattern
real quick?
This is my body, girl.
- You're stupid.
- For this week's
maxi challenge,
we have to drag up
a life-size soup can
and also come up with
a seventies disco queen look
for the Warhol Ball.
I don't know how to run
a sewing machine,
but I have won
a design challenge
with a glue stick before,
so I'm hoping
I can do it again.
- I wanted to do
something black.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, this'll work.
- So what do I need to do
right now?
Do you need
to cut anything?
- What do you want me to do? You
want me to cut it out for you?
or sew it for you?
- I can cut it,
then if you wanna sew it.
Because
I don't know how to sew.
Well, you can tell me
exactly what you need me to do.
- Okay. Just get some fabric
and double it,
and then just, like,
pin this onto it.
I'm helping Bebe sew
her little base of her outfit.
She's making fringe
out of sequins.
I think Bebe feels like
she's very seasoned,
but she hasn't won
any challenges
and she just really
has a lot to prove.
Work for your sister,
please.
- Oh, mother fucker.
- ? There's a hot glue gun
- Does anybody have a lampshade
that Shangy could borrow?
- Girl!
Look, it ain't no secret.
I'm not a super seamstress.
Oh, come on, work with mama,
work with mama.
Work, Bertha. Oh, fuck.
However, I'm not
a person that gives up
or throws in the towel.
Come on, Bertha.
I've gone away
and I have learned
at least how to work
the sewing machine.
Bertha's not gonna
beat me today.
Please, sir,
help me and Bertha.
Here we go.
Oh! [laughs]
Aah! Why does the top one
keep coming out?
- Let me tell you
who's not gonna win.
- Girl.
- Shangela, what you do--
Can I help you?
- I don't know what I did,
but I didn't do right.
- Oh, that is wrong.
- [laughs]
- This is
an opportunity for me
to at least in a small way
thank her
for saving me last week.
This is what you're gonna do.
Put this on your body.
'Cause if this fits,
this could be really cute.
- Mama, it ain't gonna fit
over my body, though.
- Oh, is it too small?
- It doesn't stretch.
Go lower, go lower.
- It doesn't stretch?
- I didn't know the fabric
doesn't stretch.
- Oh, bitch.
- [laughs]
- Did it fit?
- No, bitch. [laughs]
I know
y'all think I'm lying,
but I took two months of sewing
classes, and for what?
I guess I should've taken
some fabric picking classes.
That's what
I should have taken.
It's not gonna work.
Maybe if I go over my head.
I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
I'm basically back at square one
at the drawing board.
Goddog it!
- Happy New Year, everybody!
- It's elimination day.
We're going to present our looks
and our soup cans to the judges,
and one of us
is gonna get canned.
Soup can.
- Oh!
- I feel so proud
of my outfit.
Like, making that
felt so, like, nostalgic.
You know, I'm on the machine
like mmm, yeah.
I'm very excited
for this runway
because the judges
have commended me
on boosting not only
my look, but my style.
They called me stylish!
So right now,
I'm living my moment.
Oh, I'm so happy
with my drapey, like,
pearl-back necklace fantasy.
Y'all can't handle it.
- Girl, bye.
I think Aja
is very confident.
Shoot, over confident.
- Y'all can't
ha-ha-handle it.
- I mean, I'm impressed with her
sewing skills and everything,
but she too much.
- Liza would die for this.
Bam!
- How are you guys who are
super confident for today--
because
I'm not in that group--
how are you thinking
if you're in the top
that you're gonna make your
decision on who to send home?
- Let's go down the line
starting with BenDeLa.
- Right now, it feels hard.
Like, how do you, like,
quantify it at this point
where everybody
is performing at a high level?
Something
I really wanted to do
was, like, kind of write
who placed where every week.
Kind of try to, like,
do some math about it
just to be technical.
- Girl.
- Does it help more if somebody
has, like, been in the top
but has also
been in the bottom?
Or if somebody's been,
like, consistently safe?
- Jesus.
- Honestly, I don't want
that responsibility
of, like, figuring it out
or deciding it.
I'd really rather
be, like, okay,
this is, like, the technical way
I've decided to do this.
- Girl, come on.
Get out your head.
If it was me
and I was in Ben's position
and I was winning...
I understand
I have a job to do
and I have to let people go.
Maybe she just
can't handle it.
- If we're basing it
on track record--
- As we should not.
I don't think we should.
It's not like, ooh,
we should do it this way
or we should do it that way.
Just play the game,
and when you end up in the top,
you know what you gotta do.
You been in this profession
long enough
to make your own decision.
For whatever reason it may be,
it's yours.
- But I don't think
we're saying
we wouldn't make
our own decision.
But I still
am, like, interested
in finding different
perspectives to look at.
- Yeah.
Well, I didn't say that.
- Oh, my God!
- I'm not saying that.
- Justify it.
- If you think too much
of the situation,
it's gonna work your brain.
- Hit her!
- Shut up.
- [laughs]
- Coming up...
[horse neighs]
Oh, she's got horsepower.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- ? Covergirl,
put the bass in your walk ?
? Covergirl,
? Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ?
? Covergirl
- Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul's
Drag Race All Stars."
A woman whose cans
are definitely museum worthy,
Michelle Visage.
- [laughs]
- Funny man Ross Mathews.
Now, Ross, do you like art?
- Yes, if it's well hung.
- [laughs]
- She's a pretty little liar
soon to be seen in the film
"Cadaver",
Shay Mitchell.
- I am so excited
to be here.
- Now, "Cadaver" isn't
my life story, is it?
[all laugh]
And the fabulous
Tituss Burgess.
Have you had any good
pinot noir lately?
- For breakfast.
- And by pinot noir,
I mean black dick.
[all laugh]
- For breakfast.
This week,
we challenged our All Stars
to bring it to you
at the Warhol Ball.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best All Star win.
Category
is Soup Can Realness.
First up, Aja.
- I'm Aja,
and I'm moist and sweet.
Mmm, open wide and get a taste
of my sugar tits
because
I'm made of candy, bitch,
and I look good.
- Type 2 dia-booties.
[all laugh]
- Shangela.
- Open wide and get a taste
of Shangie Angie's
caffeinated Halleloops.
Just like my soup,
I'm an all night party, baby.
Heat me up
and watch my loops swell
with loads of heartiness,
guaranteeing
that after one bite,
honey, your friends will be
saying, "Slow down, bitch!"
Ooh, halle-loo!
- She's serving canned fish.
- Oh, no!
[all laugh]
- Trixie Mattel.
- Open wide and get a taste
of nonrefillable,
prescription only,
habit-forming,
heart-slowing goodness.
Just like my soup,
I'm inspired by rainbows,
little birdies,
and the reemerging dark recesses
of a rocky childhood.
Side effects include
drowsiness, nausea,
depression,
and a broken DVR.
- Looks like "Children
of the Corn" chowder.
[all laugh]
- Kennedy Davenport.
- Grandma Kennedy's
Pot Licka Juice.
I'm scrumptious-ba-da-rumptious.
Ask for me by name,
and spoon your way
to a fat bootay.
- I forked my way to mine.
[all laugh]
- Bebe Zahara Benet.
- Don't be scared.
I'm bringing a taste of Africa
into your mouth.
I am Zaza,
Spicy, flavorful, hot,
and I will make you
want to shout Cameroon!
- [laughs]
- The soup du jour is nut.
[all laugh]
- BenDeLaCreme.
- Mmm. Open wide
and get a taste
of CreamDeLaCreme
All Purpose Soup,
an award-winning recipe
of talent, desperation
and dumb luck.
Heat me up and watch me rise
to challenges of any sort.
CreamDeLaCreme's
All Purpose Soup.
Perfect for any occasion.
- She's lactating.
- [laughs]
- Category is Disco Queen
Eleganza Extravaganza!
Aja.
- You can lead a whore
to water.
[all laugh]
- Sis, life is so crazy.
Last night,
I was at the Target,
and I ran into Lindsay Lohan,
who had the nerve to tell me
that I looked like
Linda Evangelista.
The nerve.
Henny.
Who would have thought
that my life would go
from twerking these cheeks
to now telling people that
their smile is beautiful,
and getting paid for it.
- That's a look you can wear
in winter, fall,
Donna Summer.
- Yes.
- Shangela.
Never look
a gift whore in the mouth.
- Dear Diary, last night
Solange Knowles
dragged me to Mariah Carey's
New Year's Eve party,
where she was like,
"Happy New Year, everybody!"
Ha ha! Who would
have thought my life
would go from shucking corn
in Paris, Texas
to now meeting with Tyra Banks
and Miss J. Alexander for lunch
to talk about
shooting photos
for America's Next Top Model,
Cycle Number 276.
Halle-loo.
- She's got a big disc.
- Is that a 12-inch?
- I think so.
- [laughs]
- Trixie Mattel.
A whore by any other name
is still a whore.
[all laugh]
- OMG, girl.
Last night, I dreamed
I was in the front row
of Tiffani-Amber Thiessen's
fashion show
Seated between Karen
from finance and John Wayne,
who's looking
better than ever.
Then I raced to dinner
with Soleil Moon Frye,
Betsey Johnson
and Buffy the Vampire Slayer,
And all they could talk about
was rhinestoning
their lady parts.
Wow, I love life.
- Ru, who needs
a horse toe
when you can have a camel?
[all laugh]
- Kennedy.
Oh, she's got horsepower.
- [laughs]
- Today,
I woke up at 1 P.M.
My phone was screaming.
It was Michelle Obama
yelling at me
that I was late
and was supposed to be
at the photoshoot
for "JET" magazine.
When I arrived,
Miranda Priestly kissed me hello
while London's ambassador
shoved a 20 in my hand
and told me I looked cheap!
Eff that, honey.
- [laughs]
- Well, now I can't even see
her disco balls.
- Hmm.
Bebe Zahara Benet.
If you want to ride,
ride the white horse.
- Yes, Hunty.
- Dear Diary,
life is so crazy!
Last night, I was at
Diana Ross's famous party
at the Moulin Rouge.
The paparazzi swooped in,
and the scene
got really, really crazy.
I had my pepper spray
in my purse,
so I whipped it out
and started spraying
those bitches,
and everybody went crazy.
[laughs]
- Looks like
a homosexual carwash.
- [laughs]
- The best kind.
- Yes, please.
- BenDeLaCreme.
She's arriving sidesaddle,
henny.
- Dear Diary, last night
I was at the Vatican,
and I ran into
the Taco Bell chihuahua.
He tossed me into his limo
and dragged me to Baby Jessica's
party at the bottom of a well.
We got there and Stevie Wonder,
of all people,
had the nerve to tell me
I looked like Michelle Visage.
Real original, Stevie!
- [laughs]
- Coming up...
- All I can say is R.I.P.
to this challenge
because you murdered it.
- Oh, my God,
your face and your hair.
- I really don't have
any negatives to say,
and that ain't easy.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Welcome, All Stars.
It's time
for the judges' critiques,
starting with Aja.
- I'm gonna start
with your can.
- Yes.
- Not that it wasn't fun,
but I found that your can
had nothing about you.
- I was trying to go
for, like,
it's, like, sweet and sexy.
- That's not what
we know you for.
- I think of you
as spicy and fiery.
- And tonight on the runway,
you put it together nicely,
but this is really not disco.
- I was trying to go
for, like,
a Cher meets,
like, Frances Joli, like--
- Frances who?
- Frances Joli.
- You mean France Joli?
- Is that how you say it?
- France Joli.
- Oh!
I just learned that
right now. [laughs]
- And the wig feels like
it's in a different decade.
- For the hair,
I was just trying to go
in kind of like
a Bridget Bardot like--
- Well, she's sixties.
- I'm all over the place
right now with my references.
- You're 23 years old,
right?
Obviously, you weren't here
for a lot of the history
of humans on this planet.
- Yeah. [laughs]
- But we're queens.
It's important
to know pop culture
and things like that.
I just expect queens to do
a little bit more research.
Especially seventies
wasn't that long ago, doll.
- I really do love
the fashion from that era,
So, like, that's why
I'm, like, really, like,
kind of devastated
that I missed the mark.
- Well, Frances Joli
was flattered, wherever she is.
[all laugh]
Let's move on down
to solid gold Shangela.
- Whoo.
- The warm fish soup
kind of turned me off,
but you still looked fish.
- I'm glad you know
what fish is. Halle-loo.
- I do, I do.
- I loved your can.
I thought it was branded
right away.
Halleloops!
Oh, Shangela.
I've heard that before.
You sold it.
- But Shangy,
this runway look.
- Yes, ma'am. I know.
- [laughs]
First of all,
you came out here.
We couldn't see
any part of your face.
I bet you looked real pretty
under that dish on your head.
- Oh, hello!
- Hi! Look at that!
I don't know what's going on
under the tinsel.
I don't understand why
there's three giant records
on the front
of your tiny little body.
It's a little crazy tonight.
- It is big disco,
but it looks
a little homemade.
- It is, and with
a hot glue gun and a staple gun,
you could do it, too.
[all laugh]
I did make an effort
on the sewing machine,
and I broke every needle
and had a friend
to help me to thread it.
But, you know,
it's just not my gimmick.
And I can hold my head high
in saying that, you know,
at least I didn't bow down.
Halle-loo.
- Thank you, Shangela.
Up next, Trixie Mattel.
- Hi, guys.
- All I can say is R.I.P.
to this challenge,
'cause you murdered it.
- The can came out.
You could have been backstage,
and I would have known
that was your can.
- This is definitely
giving me disco Barbie.
I mean, the whole look
is so great.
- It tells me a story
of a country girl
who decided I have to fit in
at Studio 54.
And the best part about it
is you made it.
- I did.
- You know what
your body shape is.
The arms, the legs,
the width.
Even the camel toe.
It's all good.
- There's not enough money
in the world
for me to put tape
on my dick.
- You have a dick?
[all laugh]
- I think it's in the back
somewhere.
- I don't know if you got
the invite late or what,
but you RSVP'd
and you showed up today.
- The Trixie that I wanted
has finally arrived.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
- [laughs]
Kennedy Davenport.
- Listen, I know you're quirky
and you do fun things,
but when you came out, I was
like why is she a grandma?
This is a branding challenge,
so you want to brand
what you're known for.
- Right.
- It didn't work.
I didn't get the story.
I didn't get the connection.
- It was more
branding the booty.
- I would have led with that.
But, oh, my God,
your face and your hair.
- You have my favorite
disco queen look,
and you would definitely
be catching
everybody's attention
at Studio 54.
- Your mesh looked regal
like a super hero
and seventies
all at the same time.
You look absolutely beautiful.
- Thank you.
- Up next, Bebe.
- Hi, Mother.
- Is peanut soup
a thing in Cameroon?
- It is. It's one of,
like, our delicacies.
- Ooh, it sounds delicious.
- [laughs]
- I thought your can
was beautiful.
Artistically,
it was very understated.
If it was a print,
I would hang that.
- And because
you represent a country
and you're very proud of it,
the branding
worked beautifully.
And, baby, when baby Bebe
walked out got on this runway,
I about lost my mind.
Absolutely stunning.
You made this?
- I did.
- So beautiful.
I really don't have
any negatives to say,
and that ain't easy.
- Everything
from the accessories,
to the jewels on your face,
it's 10 out of 10
for this look.
- Thank you.
- Up next, BenDeLaCreme.
- Hi.
- So your can tonight
was fantastic.
- Thank you.
- The colors were you.
Your hair was adorable.
It was terminally delightful.
That's your brand.
- I like this look.
I don't love this look.
It doesn't scream
disco queen.
- You're definitely
not the queen.
You're probably in line
trying to get into the club.
- I feel like I'm in the alley
behind the disco.
- Listen, it does not suck.
But it's simple, basic.
You can do better and more.
- And I don't know if you're
tired tonight or something,
but we are at the edge of our
seats every time you walk out
just because of the level
you've been performing.
So if it's not at 120,
if it's just at 100,
we're like, oh, 100. Okay.
- Thank you, ladies.
Based on
the judges' critiques,
I've made some decisions.
Bebe Zahara Benet,
Trixie Mattel,
Con-drag-ulations.
You are the top two All Stars
of the week.
[applause]
You each won
a two-night escape for two
at the W Hotel,
Fort Lauderdale.
BenDeLaCreme,
Kennedy Davenport.
You are safe.
- [exhales]
Thank you, Lord.
- Thank you.
- That means Aja
and Shangela,
you are the bottom two.
Trixie and Bebe,
each of you needs to decide
which of the bottom two
you'll eliminate
if you win the lip sync.
Thank you, ladies.
You may leave the stage.
- Coming up...
- I'm just trying to smile,
and sometimes
it's just so hard.
- My mood
just changed to fear.
- Someone's feelings
are going to be hurt.
- Ah, bitch.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- ? Oh, my God
- I've never been
in a position
where I had to choose
who to eliminate.
And it's like are you going to
be honest about the situation?
Are you going
to play the game?
How do you choose
who's gonna go home?
- Shangela and Aja,
how are you guys feeling?
- I mean, this is my first time
in the bottom,
and it's just...
We know what it is.
- I've never felt
more drag scalped,
like, murdered.
At that moment,
I was like, whoa.
- I just cracked.
And to see her being cracked
when just this morning
she was, like,
I'm gonna win the challenge.
It's a testament to how
you can't be too confident.
- I wanna talk.
Do you wanna talk?
- Yeah. It really helps.
- Do you wanna talk?
- Yes.
- Let's do it.
- Well, TYA.
- TYA?
- Tell your ass.
[all laugh]
- Hi, sister.
- Hi, sis.
Oh, my gosh.
How you feeling?
- I'm hoping that this moment
won't define
how much I can bring
to this competition.
You have
a hard choice to make,
and regardless of what else,
you are always my sister.
- I do feel like Shangela
has shown amazing work,
but Aja is a fireball.
Aja is somebody
who has shown a lot of growth
compared to Season 9.
So it's really, really hard.
Oh, bitch.
- Maybe I can't
pronounce names right,
but, like, I really
made this with the intent
to, like, really be couture
and high fashion
and still give disco.
- On one hand, I think Aja's
runway was the most beautiful.
On the other hand,
the judges didn't.
And her can
was, like, terrible.
It had nothing
to do with Aja.
- I fucked up so bad
on my season,
and I want to go
as far as I can.
- I know you do.
- When Ross was like
"I sort of feel bad for you
because
you perform so well,"
it's, like, we need to see
120% every time.
And, like, I don't know whether
you're just tired or what.
I was, like, yes, I'm tired!
I am exhausted every minute!
You just happened
to notice this time.
- I noticed, too.
- What?
- I noticed, too, this challenge
was working you.
- Oh, my God, yeah.
- You let this challenge
work your ass,
and then it kind of like
spewed a little onstage.
- Wait. What does that mean,
spewed a little onstage?
- Like you kind of
let it show.
- Oh, really?
When I was walking--
- That you were not like
your usual self, you know.
- Kennedy's saying that
I seemed like my energy
is a little lower,
and it's like, duh.
I just won
a million challenges
'cause I was working
super hard.
I have had to not only
pull it out
in everything that we've done
as we all have,
I have also
had to decide every week
who is gonna walk out
of this workroom.
And that emotionally
is enough.
- It is trying. Mm-hmm.
- I don't wanna be
on the judges panel.
I wanna be one of the girls.
So, anyway,
blah-blah-blah. Poor me.
- BenDeLa is relieved
that she has been taken off
of this high horse, honey.
Some people are not made to deal
with that type of pressure.
But, listen,
if you don't want to win,
stop playing to win.
- We were just here, bitch.
- Yeah.
- Do you want
this chair back?
- Mama, it's a whole
different dynamic now.
- If the tables were turned,
I wouldn't expect Shangela
to save me
just because
I saved her once.
That falls into more
of a RuPaul's Best Friend
Race category,
and it should be judged on
did you do the worst?
She knows her outfit
was the worst outfit.
It's maybe the worst thing
I've seen on "Drag Race."
It's getting hard. It's getting
really hard, you know.
But she has one of the best
track records here.
Look how many weeks
she's hit homeruns.
But I don't know
if those homeruns
outweigh the fact that there's
a record glued to her head.
I don't know.
- I know you have
a rough decision,
but I could see us next week
top five, top four, top three.
I see that for you.
I see that for me.
I wanna stay.
- I know you do.
- Whatever choice you make,
you'll forever be a top three
kind of person to me.
When Daenerys is creating
alliances on "Game of Thrones,"
she's creating them
out of mutual respect,
and that's what I hope I've done
in this competition.
But I love you.
- You're a real life All Star.
- I've done my best
at creating these alliances,
and now I'm just
gonna leave it up to them.
- First of all,
I'm going to let you know
that you look
really beautiful today
and you're very authentic.
and I like the fact
that I can see you
just blossoming right here.
And I watched you tonight.
- I just wanna make it
to the top.
- Yeah.
- So I'm not, like...
- No matter what,
you've made it.
You're here.
- [sighs]
I'm trying to tell her
why I think I should stay,
but Bebe
is not letting me talk
and she's just going on.
- It's just how far
you have made--
You have made it, girl.
- And I can't even
plead my case.
- I just want to say
I'm very proud of you
because you are just a star
in my eyes
and I really love you.
So let's go back
to the group, honey.
I love you, my sis.
- My entire mood
just changed to fear.
[sighs]
- What's going on, sis?
Because I know
how you feel, so...
- Yeah. I just feel
so numb right now.
I'm just trying to smile,
and just have a good time.
Sometimes
it's just so hard.
- It hurts me
to see her so broken.
But I get it.
This is scary.
One of us is going home.
- I'm thinking about
who did the worst today?
Who did the best today?
Who has the best track record?
Who can save my skin
tomorrow?
I could stare at these
two lipsticks all day,
but it's one resounding
gut feeling.
- I have to kind of
look at everything.
I can't look at just
the judges' critiques.
I have to look at
the whole picture.
But I do believe that I have
made the right decision.
My decision is honest.
But I know in spite of that,
someone's feelings
are going to be hurt.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Welcome back, ladies.
Two top All Stars
stand before me.
Ladies, this is your chance
to impress me,
win $10,000,
and earn the power
to give one of the bottom queens
the chop.
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing] for your legacy!
- I want to win the lip sync
for once.
On Season 7, I'll lost
a lip sync to Pearl.
Do you know what it's like
to lose a lip sync
to a partially sedated twink
from Brooklyn?
- Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
[music plays]
- ? I defy
? Anyone who claims that I
? Didn't control
? Whatever moved
? In my soul
? And I could touch
? Touch delight
? Just because
you fell for me ?
? Why should I
feel uptight? ?
? Love had to show me
one thing ?
? I was so right
? So right
? Thought I could turn
emotion ?
? On and off
? I was so sure
? I was so, so sure
? But love taught me
? Taught me
? I was so right
? So right
? Thought
I could turn emotion ?
? On and off
? I was so sure
? So sure
? That love taught me
? Taught me
? Who was,
who was the boss ?
? Love
? But love taught me
? Taught me, taught me
- Whoo!
- Yay!
[cheers and applause]
- Ladies, I have made
my decision.
Bebe Zahara Benet...
You're a winner, baby.
[applause]
Con-drag-ulations.
You've won a cash tip
of $10,000.
Trixie Mattel, you are safe.
You may join
the other girls.
Aja and Shangela,
please step forward.
Bebe, with great power
comes great responsibility.
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
- [sighs]
- When I was coming
to this competition,
I didn't know what
my relationship was going to be
with all of you girls.
I had no clue.
And I came here
and I bonded so much
with every single one of you.
I just hope that we
stay as family.
I'm going to send Aja home.
[sighs]
- As it is written,
so it shall be done.
Aja, you are
and you will always be
an All Star.
- Thank you so much.
I'm just grateful to have lived
this experience twice.
That is some shit.
- Now sashay away.
- Sis, I gotta go.
Bye-ee.
I was a little surprised.
I helped Bebe
make her outfit.
Sis...
The tea, the tea, the tea.
But then again,
this is All Stars,
and bitches gonna send
whoever they want home.
And I respect her decision.
And I just want to thank
all my supporters
for believing in me
and, like--
[bell rings]
- Blessed be, kitty girl.
The day of reckoning
is upon us.
[evil laugh]
- Somebody gonna die
or something's happening.
I don't know.
Y'all scaring me.
Aah!
- All right,
we're alone now.
You can come out.
Blessed be, kitty girls.
How many
of my eliminated girls
were you able to capture?
- We think
you'll be pleased.
- Under his eye.
- Under his eye-ee.
- Let yourselves be known!
The time has come
for your revenge.
[evil laugh]
- Next time
on "All Stars..."
You'll be auditioning
to be part
of my new super group,
the Kitty Girls.
- Ow!
- The look is straight
out of Baby Spice's wardrobe.
- You nailed it.
- I was blown away.
- Wait a minute!
I've decided to audition
a few other girls.
- I think this is
a crock of shit.
- I'm not here for drama.
- Oh, it's about to go down.