- Previously
on "All Stars..."
- You'll be performing
our very own VH1 Divas Live.
[ cheering ]
- Happy New Year, everybody.
[ all laugh ]
- ? Should be criminal
? Don't make sense for a bitch
to be this endowed ?
[ all laugh ]
- Kennedy.
- Janet is a very
specific kind of move.
You could have worked
a little harder.
- Thorgy Thor.
- I felt like I was looking
at Thorgy with a blonde wig on.
- I was in character
the entire time.
It's stupid. [ sobs ]
- I think that's a lot
of emotion for safe.
- Shangela,
you're a winner, baby.
- Yay! Thank you.
- Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
- I know what it's like to
come back to this competition
and be sent home again
without getting the crown.
The person I've chosen
to send home...
Is Thorgy.
- Oh, Jesus.
Gross.
- Thorgy, sashay away.
- Whoo!
- Oh, my God.
- Halle-loo,
am I right, ladies?
- That is not
a halle-loo moment.
- Oh.
- [ laughs ]
- Oh!
She put a penis and balls.
- Ms. Thorgy drew the--
a very like, you know,
a picture of what the...
[ laughs ]
She drew a picture.
- Wow.
- I don't like that.
No, that--
see, that makes me mad.
I don't like that.
That's just not right.
- She's a clown.
She's--
It's a joke, obviously.
- No, I don't get it.
- But because
you're not a clown.
Well, you look like a clown
right now, but--
- No, no, no.
That's not right at all.
- I'm devastated because
I don't quite see Kennedy
taking drag
to an all star level
quite like
I thought Thorgy could.
That just means, I guess,
Kennedy will have to be
sent home next week.
- Maybe her feelings
are hurt right now,
so, you know,
if that's how she feels,
I don't hold it
against her at all.
- I do.
- Here's to Thorgy,
everybody.
We love you, Thorgy.
- Love you, Thorgy.
- Drag is fun!
Drag is fun.
Thorgy was a sheet
in the wind, Mama.
Whatever way it could've blown,
she would've gone.
I need loyal people
on my team,
because, baby, if Daenerys
is gonna conquer
the seven kingdoms,
she's gonna need allies.
Me and my dragons
can't do it alone.
- All right, Ben.
Show us some lipstick.
- I also chose Thorgy.
- What did you base
your decision on?
- [ sighs ] It was
a really hard decision.
I mean, it was, like,
at the final moment,
like, the final
determining factor, um...
- Oh, BenDeLa,
I see the wheels turning.
She's calculating.
She's careful about
every word she says
because she has a reputation
to uphold.
- I don't know.
Did you even say what your
determining factor was?
- Oh, why it's gotta be me?
I was happy it was on you.
- You get $10,000, so you
have to say it first.
- There's a lot of reasons,
but, Thorgy, yes,
she did have a smaller role,
but there was opportunity
for her, in my eyes,
like mine, I had Mariah--
- But--
- Let me finish.
When I saw what I had, I put
my own elements in there.
- Stevie is not current.
It's difficult
to compare that to Mariah.
- Oh, I'm not comparing her
to Mariah.
- I feel there were no gags
in the music part
of Stevie Nicks.
- Oh, Miss Big and Milky,
honey.
Season 3, Shangy would have
picked up my cocktail
and threw it on that ho,
but as Beyonce
has taught me,
I should be a more evolved,
grown woman.
I just feel like
I'm having to defend,
not explain, my decision
specifically to you.
Correct me if I'm wrong.
Just let me know.
So tell me what choice
would you have made?
- I think I would have
chosen Thorgy to stay.
I find Thorgy's concepts
and her looks
much more exciting.
- I mean,
let's just not sit here
and act like
I didn't do shit
to deserve to be called.
- I'm not saying that.
- Fuck my drag, right?
Because basically
that's what you saying,
and you talking
like I'm not even here.
If I'm not your cup of tea,
then, baby, don't drink it,
Miss Milk.
- Everybody's gonna go home
basically,
and we can't be sitting here
getting mad
about who's going home,
who's not going home.
- It's not about mad,
it's about being an adult.
- Step your pussy down,
Kennedy.
Take a breath. [ inhales ]
- The tension on this sofa
is tight.
I'm so happy
I'm not in this feud.
It seems like this divas' battle
ain't over yet.
- The winner of "RuPaul's
Drag Race All Stars"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
a coveted spot
in the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize
of $100,000.
With extra-special
guest judges
"UnREAL's" Constance Zimmer
and Jeffrey Bowyer-Chapman.
- ? RuPaul's Drag Race
- ? May the best woman
- ? Best woman win
- Happy New Year, everybody.
- Hi, there.
- Oh, I guess
we're going this way.
- Another day
in the workroom.
You get up, you walk in,
you step over the body
of a dead friend,
and you just move along.
- Who's sore?
I am so sore.
This is what a two-time winner
looks like, people.
- Two.
Two in a row, Ben.
- Well, but this
is what I've learned
from my first
experience here
is that every time you hear
that you're in the top,
that is the sound
of that rollercoaster
click, click, click, click,
click, click, click.
And you never know when
it's gonna go like this.
[ siren ]
- Hey!
- Whoo!
- She done already
done had hers.
- Hey, um, can I steal you
for a second?
I'm starting to feel
a real connection with you.
- Me, too!
- But for this relationship
to go to the next level,
I just really need you
to open up.
[ all laugh ]
- [ whispering ] Rosebud.
- Oh, my God.
- Aah!
- [ laughs ]
- Hello, hello, hello!
- Hi!
- Hi, ladies!
- Hi, Ru!
- Oh, my goodness.
- Now, for this week's
maxi challenge,
you'll be improving your way
through a funny
little dating show
we call "The Bitchelor."
[ all laugh ]
- You'll be doing unscripted
comedy with our bitchelor
played by the dreamy star
of "UnREAL,"
Jeffrey Bowyer-Chapman.
- Ooh, yes!
- Oh, yeah.
Now, to make things
extra twisted,
I'm going to assign
each of you a date partner
and a funny personality type
to play.
Aja and Kennedy, you'll be
going on a two-on-one date.
- All right.
- Kennedy,
you'll be the party girl,
and Aja, you'll be playing
the super needy girl,
so insecure it hurts.
- Oh.
- Trixie and Milk,
you'll be working together.
Trixie, you'll be
the fake bitch.
- All right.
- Milk, you'll be
the psycho stalker.
- BeBe and BenDeLa, you'll
go on a date with Jeffrey.
BenDeLaCreme,
you'll be the cougar.
- Naturally.
- BeBe, you'll be
the shy virgin.
- Oh.
- You tell everybody
you're pure,
but you secretly
want to lose it.
And finally,
Chi Chi and Shangela,
you are our polyamorous duo.
[ all laugh ]
- Chi Chi, you're
more into the bitchelor,
and Shangela,
you're more into Chi Chi.
- Hi, Boo.
- Now, remember,
the first rule of improv
is to always agree,
to say yes to everything.
For example, when I ask "Does
this Klein Epstein Parker suit
make my ass look juicy?"
You say...
All: Yes.
- You got it.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may
the best All Star win.
[ cheers and applause ]
- How do you feel
about improv?
- I do not consider myself,
like, a comedian per se.
I'm excited.
In Season 1, we never had
the opportunity to do improv.
The character I'm playing
is the virgin,
and I was, like,
what about
if this girl
is an African princess?
Come on, now. You can
just make her really funny.
I would like to approach
my character
like somebody fresh
off the boat from Africa.
- Yeah.
- Because in our culture,
it's like you have to be married
to be able to, you know--
You have to be married
to be able to have...
[ laughs ]
I mean, it's--
I can't even spell out
the words
because
it's like this girl--
- But how would you establish
the idea specifically
of virginity other than
that you're not married?
I think that what they're
gonna be looking for in here
is gonna be like being
so over the top with it.
- Right.
- What they want here
is like campy, you know?
- Yeah. But this is hard
to go extreme
being a virgin
and being shy.
- I'm feeling
really worried
about BeBe's choices
around her character.
BeBe, up to this point,
has just been
kind of poised and regal,
so we'll see if she can
get down with being goofy.
If it were me,
I would go with the more
traditional kind of like...
like, buttoned-up Catholic,
kind of like,
"I only do anal
because that still makes me
a virgin" kind of thing.
- That would be very funny,
honey, but no.
- I want my character
to be so fucking crazy
that she's like
bat shit crazy,
that she will do anything.
- And don't forget
insecurity, too.
- Well, yeah,
she's insecure.
- Yeah.
- But that's the point.
You're so insecure
you become crazy.
- Okay.
- Like I will fake cry.
I will put some
Visine tears. [ cries ]
A needy girl
is easy for me.
My strategy is to give you
a lot of moaning,
aww, and a lot of, like,
crying sounds.
Aah!
I'm just gonna be crazy
and needy,
kind of like a rich bitch,
like, vibe.
- Ugh. I don't think
she understands her character
not one bit.
- Rich bitch,
religious fish.
I used to be a Christian
for attention fish.
- [ sighs ]
- We don't know
what he's gonna give us.
But whatever he says,
we will think of the right
response.
- Right.
And he's super dreamy.
- Oh, my God.
- And so I would stalk him,
actually.
- Yeah. No kidding.
- Psychotically.
I feel good about playing
the stalker bitch
because it's sort of like
an easy transition
into this role,
because before I started
dating my boyfriend,
I stalked him on MySpace,
and just, like, check out
who his friends were,
and that sort of
led me to, like,
becoming friends
with his friends,
and then being friends
with his friends
led me to meeting him.
So I'm very confident
about my role
as psycho stalker number one.
- Hi, what's your name?
- Hi, I'm Chi Chi DeVayne,
and, yeah.
I mean, I'm just--girl,
I don't know how to do it.
- Come on,
you got it, you got it.
- I don't consider myself
to be a comedian
or an actress and all that.
So looking at the other girls,
I'm getting so intimidated.
Like, girl, are you going to be
able to perform at that level?
- How are you gonna
play your character?
- What do you mean?
You--I mean--
- How's she gonna talk?
How's she gonna act?
- I am shittin bricks.
I don't know if I can come up
with that kind of funny
just right off the bat.
Hi, I'm, you know,
Chi Chi DeVayne, and--
- Oh, she's
the proper English.
- She might be from England,
but she still sound like
she from Crenshaw, too.
- Shangela's super funny
and good at improv.
If anything, I can see her
bulldozing Chi Chi.
I would not want to be
in a group with Shangela
to be honest with you.
- Yeah.
Do you think people say that
about you and I?
- [ laughs ]
Probably not.
When Celine doesn't win,
she cries.
- After last week,
I think I've learned
that being safe
is clearly not okay for me.
Even though I thought I was
really impressive last week,
I'm--now is the time
to prove myself,
and if I don't,
and if I'm safe,
then I'm probably
gonna cry about it again.
- Coming up...
- Are you ready for the romantic
adventure of your life?
- Oh.
- Ooh, we here.
- Ooh.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Okay, places, everyone!
Places, everyone!
fuck it up.
Oh, and don't
- I'm Jeffrey, and I'm here
to find the love of my life.
This is not gonna be easy,
but it never is
in this game we call love.
- Jeffrey Bowyer-Chapman,
are you ready
for the romantic adventure
of your life?
- Oh, I just want this to be
real, you know what I mean?
- Oh, yeah. I know
exactly what you mean.
- Do I have something
on my face?
- Oh, look, here comes
the first girl.
Good luck.
- Thanks, Ru.
- My name
is BeBe Zahara Benet.
- Hi.
- And I'm all the way
from Africa.
And I came to America
to find my prince.
Hi, Jeffrey.
- You can look me
in the eye, you know?
- [ laughs ]
Ooh, he's a handsome man,
and I bet you
he has the big...
[ laughs ]
Oh.
Can I tell you
a little secret?
- Please, yes.
- I'm still a virgin.
I have a special flower.
- Well, maybe I can take
a little sniff later.
- [ chuckles ]
- We'll see you inside.
Thank you.
That's totally unnecessary.
Wildly unnecessary.
Thank you very much, BeBe.
- Well, hello there,
handsome.
- Whoa. Wow.
- My name is BenDeLaCreme.
Who's a big boy?
You're a big boy.
And I'm here
to land me a boy-man.
I'm BenDeLaCreme.
- Nice to meet you BenDeLa.
Thank you.
- You don't have to call me
BenDeLa.
- Okay.
What should I call you?
- My friends
call me Bedtime BD,
because I like to tuck
a big boy in night-night.
- [ laughs ]
- You can just go on inside
to the house.
I'll meet you inside
in a few minutes, all right?
- Thank you so much!
You're a beautiful driver.
I really appreciate it.
Oh, my God,
that taxi was disgusting.
It smelled like a barn.
He was gross, he was late,
he drove like a maniac.
Hi, I'm Trixie Mattel.
I'm 27 years old,
and I'm from
sunny West Hollywood.
And some people
might say I'm fake,
but those people
are alcoholics.
He's not even
that good looking.
I have to go. Hi.
- Hi.
- Oh, my God, you're even cuter
in person than you are on TV.
- Oh, that's
very sweet of you.
- You kind of have,
like, this sexy,
like, Denzel,
like, Gilbert Godfried,
like, but, like, sensual,
do you know what I mean?
- Uh...
- I like my men
like I like my coffee...
incapable of loving me back.
[ sighs ]
Bye, Jason!
Sorry, it's Jared.
- Jeff. Jeffrey.
- I'm Milk.
I'm from New York City.
I kind of move around a lot
in life for legal reasons.
Is it okay if I step out?
I know
this is less than 500 feet.
Some people say
I'm, like, psycho,
but I just say I'm really
passionate about love.
[ giggles ]
- Nice to meet you--
Ooh, okay.
- I'm his biggest fan,
and it's unreal
to see the star
of "UnREAL."
I'm in love.
- I have to open it myself.
My name is Aja,
and this is Woofy.
Woof. Oh.
He's the only person who
actually stays by my side.
Oh, my God!
When I first saw Jeffrey,
I just knew from that moment
that I would do anything
to have him.
I will kill someone.
Can you believe they made me
open the door by myself?
I didn't even close it.
Should I go close it?
- I think maybe
you better close it.
- I don't do anything
for myself,
but for you
I'll do anything.
- Thank you, Aja.
It's a pleasure.
- You don't love me.
I'm gonna make you love me.
- Ooh, we here.
Ooh! Ooh, it's big.
Ooh, I hope he cute.
[ bleep ]
[ laughs ]
- Hi.
- My name is Kennedy.
I'm from West Dallas,
and I'm here to meet my man.
Ooh, you is fine.
- Thank you.
- Ooh, yes, honey.
I love to party, too.
Hold on one second.
- Okay. Okay, all right.
You come prepared.
- As I'm looking
into Jeffrey's eyes,
I just get so moist inside.
I gotta have his baby.
You better be watching.
Keep watching.
- [ laughs ]
- Mm!
Honey, look at the sperm count
on this one!
Come on out here, baby.
- Ooh.
- I'm Shangela.
- And I'm Chi Chi.
- I am looking for love
with my partner
because we like
to be polyamorous.
- I love limos.
- This is a very progressive
coupling that's going on here.
- Oh, you have insurance?
You said "Progressive."
- No, I do.
- Now look at the size
on this one.
- Ooh, he look like
he got a big one, too.
- Yes, he does.
Let's measure it.
Yeah, she likes big heads.
- [ laughs ]
How is your head,
by the way?
- Oh, you have
to ask my wife.
- Chi Chi and I usually
have very good luck.
I mean, look at Chi Chi.
She's stacked
like a brick house.
- I like bricks.
- We'll see you inside.
- It's nice to meet you both.
- Uh-huh.
- [ exhales ]
- Coming up...
- No, those are balls.
- [ laughs ]
- Have you ever taken out
a catheter?
- [ laughs ]
- My dream date is...
whatever mother
wants me to have.
- Ugh.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- All right, ladies.
It's time for
your two-on-one dates.
Stay in character,
go with the flow,
and don't talk
over each other.
- This is the weirdest group
of girls I have ever seen,
and I like it.
I like weird.
- So how you feeling?
- Well, I'm scared
and a little bit horny.
- Nice.
Mm.
So are you ready for
your two-on-one date?
- I'm as ready
as I'll ever be, Ru.
- Well, good luck.
- Ladies, are you hungry?
- Oh, my goodness.
- I thought we could get to know
each other over a couple snacks.
Oh, that's totally
unnecessary, but thank you.
Would you like to try
a chocolate-covered strawberry?
This is one of my favorite
delicacies.
- Let me just
pull off my shoes,
because a man cannot feed me
with shoes on.
- Oh, right, right.
Oh, oh, that's beautiful.
- I'm just insatiable
tonight.
I can't get enough.
- Oh, I can tell--
Oh, wow.
That looks delicious.
- [ laughs ]
- Oh, my gosh. Oh!
- This is perfect
for a widdle baby wike you.
All pre-mashed.
- Jeffrey, look at me.
You like it?
- Yes, you're beautiful,
absolutely.
- [ giggles ]
- Gorgeous.
- Thank you.
- BeBe
is just kind of there.
It's...meh.
- Have you ever taken out
a catheter?
- [ laughs ]
- I can't say that I have.
- BenDeLaCreme, she is old.
That is a dirty woman.
Mm-mm.
I don't know if you're
looking for a woman like me,
like the woman
who is clean,
clean down there.
- Are you looking
for a woman that's clean
or are you looking for
a woman that's dirty?
- Um...
- Remember, I already
ate this once before.
- Yeah.
- [ laughs ]
- If Jeffrey
needs a warm bosom
to press himself against
at night,
I'm the wrong gal
because these
don't feel temperature.
We'll have
a lot more opportunities
to get to know each other
later.
- I can't wait.
- Just don't come after 9:30
because that's when
my Xanax kicks in.
- [ laughs ]
- My God, you are so funny.
Stop.
- Oh, ladies.
- Stop. I said stop!
You're literally killing me,
you're so funny.
- I want to get to know you both
a little bit better.
- [ laughs ]
- Is this your house?
- Yes.
- Wait, Jeffrey,
Jeffrey, Jeffrey.
- This is, like,
the prettiest refurbished,
like, Cheesecake Factory
mall kiosk I have ever been to.
- Thank you very much.
- Do you remember when you wore
these shirts on "UnREAL?"
- Uh...
- You know this style.
- Wow.
- Yeah. I've seen
every episode of "UnREAL."
I have like every--
- You don't know Jeffrey
like I know Jeffrey.
[ whispering ]
The date's
going really well.
Like, Jeffrey seems,
like, really into me.
[ laughs ]
- Hold on. I have
to have to take this.
Yeah, I'm here now.
No. She's like
a weird forest girl.
- Do I come across
as, like, crazy though?
- Oh.
- Like, do I look crazy?
- That's just
a really strong word.
- He's like five--
- I can't handle it
right now.
I can't handle it.
- You look different.
- Yeah?
- I know Trixie
is playing a fake bitch,
but, baby, those facial
expressions are real.
- Don't--
- [ laughs ]
- No, he's like a five.
He's like an L.A. two.
- Stop talking to me.
What? [ sighs ]
Oh, my God.
- If steam
could come off a wig,
she would have those
little lines above her head
where the heat is rising.
Miss Thing is hot
that Milky
is cutting her off.
[ laughs ]
- People call me psycho,
but I don't think
I'm psychotic.
I just think I'm really
passionate about finding love.
- Yeah.
- While the leaves--
- And that's why I'm here.
- Me, too.
- The leaves in your hair
are so fun,
I wish you would leave.
- Milk is just going
way overboard.
- It's been great, ladies.
It's been
an incredible pleasure.
- [ sobs ]
Bye, Jerald.
- It's Jeffrey.
- We're gonna go on a date.
- This has been so much fun.
- Well, this ain't no party.
- No.
You know what , ladies?
I thought we could take
some time to chill out.
- That's so nice.
- Yeah.
- But you know what?
I got the party right here.
Hold on.
- I don't get it.
- She does
a lot of partying.
- Hold that.
- Yes, ma'am.
- You have one too, crazy.
- All right.
- [ babbles ]
- Don't be looking, boy.
- Oh.
- She brought drinks.
Oh, my God.
You're good for something.
- Hey, we have a party.
- You are a girl
who knows how to party.
- We're gonna get drunk
together.
- Can we propose to me
finding the love
I couldn't find within myself?
Nobody's ever loved me like
you before, and I'm so happy.
- That's really,
really, really sad.
- [ cries ]
You think it's sad?
- Oh, my God.
It's supposed to be insecure.
It's like a needy girl,
not just crying.
- [ cries ]
- The only thing Aja's
insecure about is this scene.
- We gonna make
a toast to love.
- Yes.
- And your nice ass.
Jeffrey is so sexy.
Oh, my God.
If this doesn't work out,
I'm probably gonna
whoop the bitch that won
and just take Jeffrey.
You is fine, boy.
Just being honest.
Baby, hold on.
- Your hands are greasy--
- You do this.
- Aah!
- Oh.
- That's how you do that.
- [ laughs ]
- What about
your past relationships?
- All I had was a--
he turned out
to be a crackhead.
And he stole all my shit
out of my apartment,
but I found him, though,
and shot his ass.
- [ Michelle laughs ]
- Ladies,
I wanna know something.
- What?
- What's your favorite part
of my body?
- That dick.
- [ laughs ]
- That's so vulgar.
My favorite part of your body
is your everything.
- Hey, baby.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
- Kennedy
is blowing my mind.
She is doing it.
- It's hot.
- Don't you have
another bottle of alcohol?
- It's hot, bitch.
It's hotter than shit.
- Then get out!
- Is she okay?
- I'm a man.
- [ laughs ]
- Ladies, I thought
we would just take a little time
to relax and unwind
and take our clothes off.
- Are you into the whole
polyamorous thing?
- I'm open to everything.
- Oh, are you?
We've been looking for somebody
to be a little more open.
- I mean, how wide
are you willing to go?
So how did you two
come together?
- I think it was fate,
right, Chi Chi?
- Well, Mama found me,
you know, at a strip club.
That's Mama.
Mama found me
at a strip club.
- You've heard
of sister wives?
- Yeah.
- We are sister wives.
- Sister wives.
- Yeah, how about that?
- Oh, my God,
you just so...
- Here, touch me, too,
though.
- Yeah, yeah.
Go for it.
- Mama said
I could have real meat now.
- Oh. [ laughs ]
- Let's see what's going on
down in the meat department.
My mission while I'm here
is to get me a nice,
strong, firm plastic cup
and get me some
of that Jeffrey sperm in it
so Chi Chi and I can make
the family we've always wanted.
- [ laughs ]
- I ain't seen nothing
that big and black in the water
since I took you
to Sea World.
Whoo!
- Shamu.
- Oh, now those are balls!
Those are big balls!
- Shangela is so over the top
with her persona, you know,
and she's
cracking her jokes.
- One of y'all
needs to shave.
Nobody told me
Bush was back in office.
- [ laughs ]
- Chi Chi's just drowning
in the tub, honey.
- My dream date is...
whatever
mother wants me to have.
- Ugh.
- We're a two-piece combo
over here.
- All right.
- You wanna hang out with Sugar,
then you gotta
come through me.
- [ laughs ]
- If Jeffrey
gets me and Shangela
in the fantasy suite,
it's going down.
[ laughs ]
- Chi Chi had
a special question for you
that she wanted to ask you.
- Go for it, Chi Chi.
- Chi Chi?
- [ deep voice ]
Do you wanna have my baby?
- Hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
- Ladies, it's time
for the most dramatic
eggplant ceremony in herstory.
- Ladies, I just really
want this love to be real,
and, frankly, most of y'all
scare the hell out of me.
Which is why I've decided
to give this eggplant...
To Ru.
Will you accept
my eggplant, Ru?
- I will take
all your eggplants.
- What?
- No!
- Way to go, RuPaul,
way to go!
- Bye-ee!
Finally, this is
my happily ever after.
Next stop,
"Good Morning America."
We'll do
"Dancing with the Stars,"
and then we'll get divorced.
- Coming up...
- Milk, Milk, Milk.
It's just hurtful
because I thought we were
all better than that.
But y'all feelings
is really hurt.
- I'm paying no attention.
That's dumb.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
Hi, guys. Good morning.
- This week's runway
is Wigs On Wigs On Wigs,
inspired by Roxxxy Andrews.
- Welcome to another day
at the office.
Aren't you feeling gorgeous?
Aren't you feeling
technically amazing?
- Milk someday wants to have
a challenge inspired by her,
and I bet you next season
there will be, like,
this week on the runway
you'll be crying
because you're only safe.
[ laughs ]
- New day.
- New day, sis.
- Y'all can't handle
all this cuteness.
I'm about to feel real cute.
- I'm going through it.
I'm going through it
in my head.
I mean, yesterday was bad.
On Season 8, I just
doubted myself so much.
I often asked myself, like,
what the hell
are you doing here?
And, like, how could I compete
with girls like this,
you know what I mean?
These bitches
have fabulous costumes,
and I'm gonna walk out
in a neon bathing suit.
So if it seems like
I'm a little worried, I am.
That's why I'm quiet.
I'm distancing myself
from the girls.
I thought that
I had elevated my drag,
but here we go again.
Like,
what are you gonna say,
like, what are you gonna do
to, like, match these girls'
energy and funniness?
I'm just trying
to keep a positive head.
I'm trying to keep smiling,
but at the same time,
I am nervous.
I don't want to go home.
I'm gonna show them that,
you know,
I have what it takes
to go all the way.
- How are you?
- I really, really
wanna win a challenge.
I've never even
been in the top,
so I really hope today
it can happen.
The first time
I was on "Drag Race,"
I kinda just floated
until I got flushed.
All people knew about me
was that I did not excel
at "Drag Race"
and didn't win
any challenges,
and I never had
my star moments.
This time I, like,
have to change that.
I don't really, like,
need validation,
but, like, to have
one good week here
would really help the momentum
for the rest, you know.
- I feel you.
- Being safe all the time
you start to feel invisible.
In the real world,
I'm Beyonce,
but in the "Drag Race" world,
I'm just a LaTavia.
It doesn't matter
on "Drag Race"
what you've done
in the real world.
In these four
fake brick walls,
you are garbage
until proven otherwise.
- Is there anybody
that either of you
are, like, concerned about?
It's kind of hard to figure out
who the bottom two are.
Like. I feel like--
- Oh, let's say three.
Who would you think
the three are?
- I mean,
if I were gonna say three,
I would say Aja, Chi Chi,
and possibly BeBe.
- What do you feel, Milk?
- I'd have
to agree with Ben.
- I feel like two out of three
of those are correct,
and my third variable one
that I kept going
back and forth on
was between Aja's and yours.
- I'm not fazed by Shangela
thinking that I may be
in the bottom.
That's dumb.
So I'm just gonna turn my
hearing aid down a little bit
and just, like,
let her speak,
but I'm paying no attention.
I thought I killed it.
The idea of being in the top
is so exciting.
- Well, halle-loo.
Oh, Miss Thing,
I'm looking at her, like,
you don't see
the writing on the wall?
Mama, she really thinks
that she's in the top two
on this one.
I'm cracked. [ laughs ]
- Shit.
It's just hurtful
because I thought
we were all better than that.
- I think I would've chosen
Thorgy to stay.
I find Thorgy's concepts
and her look much more exciting.
- Fuck my drag, right?
- Bitch, your feelings
is really hurt.
- Yep.
- Kennedy is really upset
because it wasn't right
for Milk to say
that Kennedy
should have gone home
because her looks
weren't on point,
because this is a competition
about more than just your looks.
And Kennedy proved this week
that she deserves
to be here 100%.
- If you don't care about me
and you don't care
about my style of drag,
you're entitled to that.
I'm upset at the fact
that we work together
a lot of times,
and what's hurtful
is when you feel like
you have
this certain relationship
with your so-called sister,
and you come to find out
it's something else.
And they end up reading you
like a dog and stuff,
throwing you under the bus.
We stopped conversation
after that.
- No.
Not even talk to me.
That's how I know
when people ain't real.
I've worked
with Milk before.
We've been on tour together,
and I've never had a problem
with Milk ever.
I've always liked
working with her,
but now you're treating me
like you don't even know me.
I value people's friendship,
I value sisterhood,
and when
I really like a person
and then they really show me
who they are, it's hurtful.
- What goes around
always comes around.
- And that's what I believe.
You're right.
- I also feel, like,
she's been, like,
the most, like,
kind of rude.
I just feel like sometimes
she just doesn't give,
like, some of us
the time of the day,
you know what I mean?
- Mm-hmm.
- And I'm just like--
like, I think more so,
like--
- Well, at least you notice it
and saying it and not me.
- Yeah.
- I look at it like this.
I'm gonna still walk this runway
in my dated as shit
and my dated as shit is gonna
help me go on and win this.
- Yeah.
- And that's how I see it.
- Ooh.
- Coming up...
- I laughed so hard I cried.
- Your character
was so spot on.
- If you're gonna be a bottom,
at least be a power bottom.
- [ laughs ]
[RuPaul laughs]
- ? Covergirl,
put the bass in your walk ?
? Covergirl,
? Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ?
? Covergirl
- Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul's
Drag Race All Stars."
My wingwoman,
Michelle Visage.
- Oh, my God, isn't everything
better with wings?
- Yeah.
Funny man Ross Mathews.
Are you a romantic?
- In a power top
kind of way, yeah.
- [ all laugh ]
- Jeffrey Bowyer-Chapman,
did you survive
a night with my girls?
- Ru, I just got back
from the free clinic,
and we are good to go.
[ bell dings, all laugh ]
- And from "UnREAL,"
the fabulous Constance Zimmer.
Hi-ee.
- Hi-ee.
- This week
we challenged our queens
to make fools of themselves
on a fake dating show,
and tonight
on the main stage,
category is Wigs On Wigs
On Wigs.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may
the best All Star win.
First up, BenDeLaCreme.
Oh, Michelle Visage.
[ all laugh ]
Oh, my goodness.
- What's a better way
to reveal a wig under a wig
than to reveal a wig
that's three feet
under the wig on my head?
- Miss Rapunzel.
- Ooh!
- What?
- Somebody forgot to shave.
- Stroke it, honey.
- It's the natural look.
- BeBe Zahara Benet.
Oh, the Miss Thing dynasty.
- [ Michelle laughs ]
- Is that a Bump It
in your hair,
or are you
just happy to see me?
- She went
all the way to Asia.
Yes, she doesn't only do
goddess beauty.
She is a well-traveled gal,
honey.
- Uh-oh,
something's happening.
- Ooh!
- I love a queen with big,
black, hairy balls.
[ all laugh ]
- Who doesn't?
- Trixie Mattel.
- Ooh, look who's here, Ru.
- It's Lady Bunny.
- Yes!
- I'm Lady Bunny passed out
on a deck chair in Palm Springs
getting a sunburn,
and then boom!
- Ooh!
- Oh, my God.
It's a Tatiana, same part,
Dennis the Menace fantasy.
- Take another little piece
of my hair now, baby.
[ all laugh ]
- Milk.
- Milkshake.
- Yeah.
- More like a creamsicle.
- Made entirely
of little post-it notes.
- So the look
I'm bringing to the runway
is very sixties inspired,
and the cut of the dress--
aah--my legs are killer.
- Yank it like a troll doll,
honey.
[ all laugh ]
- Michelle, is that
a good hombre or a bad hombre?
- [ Michelle laughs ]
- Aja.
Ani-mazing!
- I think she used
too much hairspray.
[ all laugh ]
- Sis, I'm just feeling
real kawaii.
That's "cute" in Japanese.
Like, you can't tell me
[ bleep ] right now
because I feel like
I just walked out
of a Manga comic book.
- Ooh!
- Oh!
- Third wig's the charm.
- Don't take your wig off
unless you've got
another one underneath.
- That's right.
- And another one
underneath that.
- Yeah.
LaGuardia, Newark,
Kennedy Davenport.
? Ch-ch-ch-chia
[ all laugh ]
- That's a hair situation.
- Yeah.
- Ooh!
- Take that, Carol Brady.
[ all laugh ]
- Let me tell you,
I feel fine, honey.
I got on these three girdles,
Miss Thing,
and my waist
is cinched, boo.
- What?
Damn, girl.
- Somebody just graduated
from the Lace Front
Institute of Technology.
- Yes, LIT.
- LIT.
- It's lit.
- [ laughs ]
- Up next, Chi Chi DeVayne.
- Do I have something
on my face?
- If you like it, you better
put a ring through it.
[ all laugh ]
- This outfit
totally represents
the new direction
that Chi Chi is going.
- Hey.
- Oh, maintain.
- Oh, okay.
- I'm bringing you
all this bayou princess.
I just hope the judges
are eating it up.
- These have always
brought me luck.
- Eyes up here.
- Where do you go?
Oh, okay.
- Bye-ee.
- She's going that way.
- Shangela.
- Corn.
- Ru, is it me,
or is she looking a bit husky?
- I don't remember
eating corn.
[ all laugh ]
- Corn is something that will
forever be associated with me.
Look, I'm from the country,
and I keep it real.
Nothing says that
better than corn.
- Ooh.
- Oh, my goodness, popcorn.
- You want some boy butter
on that?
[ all laugh ]
- You don't have
to ask me twice.
- There may be a kernel of truth
to this dress.
- That's right, honey.
You better pop the corn
and feed the children.
- G-M-Oh, no,
you better don't.
[ all laugh ]
- Oh, that's so stupid.
- Coming up...
- You were constantly
overshadowed.
- You were terrifying.
- What I got
was a whiny brat.
- Those are really lovely words
of encouragement.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Welcome, All Stars.
Based on
your improv performances,
and your "unbeweavable"
main stage presentations,
I've made some decisions.
Now, when I call your name,
please step forward.
Shangela.
BeBe Zahara Benet.
You are safe.
Please step
to the back of the stage.
- Thank you.
- The rest of you
represent the tops
and the bottoms of the week.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
First up, BenDeLaCreme.
- Hi.
- I loved the surprise
wig skirt reveal.
It's tough to, like,
shock us
when we know it's Wigs
On Wigs On Wigs.
We know what's gonna happen.
There's gonna be
a wig under there.
But somehow
you managed to shock me.
- Every piece
you stripped off
revealed another layer
and another layer,
and that's what you did
in your performance, too.
You gave layers.
I laughed so hard I cried.
- As an actor, you gave me
a lot to play with.
I had so much fun with you.
I was equally disgusted by you
as I was turned on.
- I keep waiting for you
to drop the ball,
and you haven't
dropped it yet.
- Those are really lovely words
of encouragement.
- I wish nothing more than
you shutting me up each time
by not letting that ball
or balls drop.
- Thank you, DeLa.
- Thank you.
- Up next, Trixie Mattel.
- Hi, guys.
- When you came out,
I was feeling immediately
like if Lady Bunny
and Kesha had a baby.
- Were you doing Lady Bunny?
What was that about?
- I thought, can Lady Bunny
become Naomi's balls?
Turns out yes.
[ all laugh ]
- In "The Bitchelor,"
your character was so spot on.
It was basically
Paris Hilton.
- I was very impressed from
the second you walked out.
You were on the phone and
you weren't paying attention,
and it was like, oh,
we know exactly who you are,
and it was
everything I wanted.
- But I felt like
you were getting talked over
a little bit.
- We were advised to try
not to talk over each other.
It was kind of like
jump roping.
I was kind of waiting
sometimes for the moment.
- I felt you waiting.
- However, when you did
get those lines in,
they were hilarious.
- All right,
well, thanks Trixie.
Up next, Milk.
- Hi.
- You look gorgeous tonight.
- Thank you.
- This is a great look
for you.
- Thank you.
- In the wig reveal,
I liked that there was
another sort of reveal
when you pulled the pony,
like those dolls that
I always that I always wanted
that my parents
wouldn't get me.
- Crissy Doll.
- Yeah, Crissy Doll.
- Crissy Doll's
my favorite doll of all time,
but we could see
the black cup holder
underneath the blonde hair.
- Yeah, it's dark root.
- In the challenge,
you were terrifying.
- I know. [ laughs ]
I was--
I was actually psycho.
- But it was the same note
the whole time.
I kept hoping that
you were going to pretend
like you weren't a stalker
and there wasn't anything wrong
with what you were doing,
and you're just
a really nice, friendly person
who happens to know
everything about you.
Because there are times
when less is more.
- Your foot was on the gas
the whole time.
You were going so fast,
you weren't sharing the stage.
- Up next, Aja.
- Hi.
- Tonight on the runway,
I'm going to go
out on a limb
and say this right now was
the best Aja has ever looked.
- Oh, thank you.
- From the second
you walked out,
I just said, what is that,
and I need more.
- You're giving me
street fighter couture,
and it's incredible.
Yes, hyah.
- Win.
- So in "The Bitchelor,"
I didn't get needy girl
at all,
not even a little.
- Oh, my God.
- What I got
was a whiny brat,
and that
is not the character.
- You were giving me
more Cher Horowitz than Tai.
- Oh. To me, needy
has always been spoiled,
but maybe I guess
there is a difference.
- Needy is not spoiled.
- Yeah.
- They're
two different things.
Needy is constantly needing
somebody to be approving
or to tell you
how beautiful you are.
- Please love me,
please tell me I'm pretty,
that kind of insecure girl.
- It's exhausting
to the person.
- Mm-hmm.
- I feel like
I need to reevaluate
the definition of needy now.
I was trying to give you,
like,
a little bit of, like,
Farrah Moan
meets, like, Kim Kardashian
meets, like, kind of like
crazy girlfriend. Wah.
Like, that's
what I was going for.
- Up next,
Kennedy Davenport.
Helleer.
- Hi.
- On the runway tonight,
it was gorgeous,
and I think
it was truly Davenport.
- It was spectacular.
The absolute polar opposite
of the character
you played on the show.
- The challenge,
out of all of the girls,
I had the hardest time keeping
a straight face with you.
From the teeth to the tits
to the ass,
you were
absolutely hilarious.
- I never think of you
as like really a comedy queen,
but you are.
- Well, she did win Snatch Game
on her season.
- That's right.
- Why don't I think of you
as comedy?
- It's probably because
of her criminal record.
[ all laugh ]
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Up next, Chi Chi DeVayne.
- Hey, y'all.
- You look beautiful
tonight.
You took my breath away
from the moment that you
stepped out on the runway.
You just have an aura
about you
that is just so bright,
it's really quite stunning.
- You have presence just
standing here right now,
but then in "The Bitchelor,"
you were constantly
overshadowed.
- Shangela had joke
after joke after joke,
but you sort of were
a spectator in the scene.
- In that hot tub,
I wouldn't even have noticed
that you were there
until you were kissing up
on his boobies.
- You gave it all away
to Shangela.
I understand
you were playing the bottom,
but if you're gonna be a bottom,
at least be a power bottom.
- Uh-huh.
- When you did have
a moment,
when you leaned over
into his ear and said...
- [ deep voice ]
You wanna have my baby?
- I mean,
that was incredible.
Where was that
for the rest of the show?
- I don't know.
I don't--I don't know.
I went
and I just felt like crap
compared to
all of these comedy queens,
and I let it get to me.
I just got so intimidated,
and it's frustrating
because I don't want you
to think
that I don't want to be here
and that I'm not trying.
I don't want to upset you
for bringing me back.
I'm sorry, y'all.
I'm just so sorry
that I'm not giving my 100.
I'm letting
what they're doing affect me
and just me not thinking
that I'm worth it.
- Chi Chi, you're worth it.
You're worth it.
- Thank you, Chi Chi.
Now, based on
the judges' critiques,
I've made some decisions.
Kennedy Davenport,
BenDeLaCreme,
you are the top two All Stars
of the week.
[ applause ]
Con-drag-ulations.
You've each won
a suite of jewelry
from Fierce! Drag Jewels
and a $1,000 gift card
from Nailed by Cristy.
Trixie Mattel,
you are a totally fake bitch.
- [ chuckles ]
- And I loved it.
You are safe.
Milk, Aja, Chi Chi,
you are in the bottom three.
DeLa and Kennedy,
each of you
needs to decide
which of the bottom three
you'll eliminate
if you win the lip sync.
So while you queens deliberate
in the workroom,
the judges and I will be
twisting balloon animals.
You may leave the stage.
- Coming up...
- I did not see this coming.
- Girl...
- I just don't think
it's my time to go.
- Every week is just like...
[ imitates bomb dropping ]
turd city.
- I know what I have to do.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Lord. Lord.
- A cocktail, please, Jesus.
- I've never been an alcoholic,
but today I'm going in.
- Oh, I'm full on.
If I could black out
right now, I would.
Well, here we are again
with another elimination,
and it's always
a difficult decision.
I can attest to that
more than anyone.
- I thought I would win,
but that's okay.
- You thought
you were gonna win?
- I did. I thought
I would be in the top,
and I was ready to do
my little lip sync,
do my little song,
but I'll get, you know.
I thought
I would be in the top,
so I'm kind of trying to
wrap my head around that.
I'm not gonna be safe
and cry
because that would be,
you know, inappropriate, but...
- [ laughs ]
- Kennedy,
the full redemption, sis.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Cheers.
- Ben, you're also
in the top two.
- Ben has won every single
challenge since we got here.
- She going home next week.
[ all laugh ]
- Milk,
you seem really quiet.
What's going through
your head?
- I'm crying about--
now I'm crying
for a legit reason,
being in the bottom, but I did
not see this coming at all.
- Girl...
I think, like, Milk
in a weird way,
she works
so much in her mind,
almost like you convince
yourself of something
even if
it's not the reality.
I don't know,
maybe that's how she copes.
I mean, that performance,
it's, like,
how can you not tell?
- I'm being penalized
for going 100% full throttle,
and I don't 100% agree
with the critiques.
I thought Trixie and I had
an amazing back and forth.
I really thought
I killed that challenge.
- I don't know
how she's this delusional.
How--somebody put something
in her cocktail.
Cosby? [ laughs ]
- My question
to the top two,
we have three now
in the bottom.
That's the gag
of the season.
- They did it
last season, too.
- Well, to me this is a gag.
[ all laugh ]
How are you going to assess
the situation?
The two of you, are you guys
gonna do one on ones
with the girls?
- I decided not to.
I'm just gonna do what I've said
from the beginning,
and that's just
assess the whole thing.
- Right.
- And just make my own
professional decision.
I do feel like
playing a fair game,
and y'all already been crying
and shit.
- That sort of
comes as a shock.
Is it 'cause she's
already made up her mind?
Is it 'cause
she doesn't want to allude
to what she's about to do?
I mean, it doesn't scare me
because she's a smart individual
who sees it as a whole.
- M'lady, how you feeling?
- You know, it doesn't
feel great to be in the bottom,
but I feel like I've been doing
well in the competition so far,
so I feel like this is
just, like, a minor slip,
and it happens.
- Yeah. I mean, I think
you've been phenomenal.
- I just don't think
it's my time to go.
I think DeLa is going
to judge the bottom three
based on our track records.
So I know I'm safe because
I won the first challenge.
Milk has been safe
the whole time,
but Chi Chi has been
statistically doing the worst
every single week.
I mean, you put it together.
- When I got here,
I thought I had this in the bag,
you know what I mean?
Like, ain't none of these
bitches gonna to upstage me,
you know what I mean?
Like, I got these looks
together, baby.
I'm going back in this thing,
you know what I mean?
And every week is just like...
[ imitates bomb dropping ]
turd city.
I let this challenge,
like, diminish my spark
and question myself
whether I can do this or not.
I know shit bring me down,
you know what I mean?
- But it happens
to all of us.
You just gotta--
it's how quickly
you can turn it around
and get back up.
- I've been in the bottom
three times,
and I'm beginning
to question
is this
the right time for me?
Maybe I should have
been on All Stars 4,
you know what I mean?
Or maybe I should have
popped out of a box
like Shangela on Season 10.
I don't think I'm ready
to be here at All Stars.
- Hi, Chi Chi.
How you feeling?
- Girl, I mean--
- Here we are again.
- Here we go again,
you know,
and, like, I don't know.
I don't know if I have
what it takes to go all the way.
- Yeah.
- And I hate to say that,
you know.
I want to be here just as bad
as everybody else does.
- Yeah.
- But I'm so friggin'
intimidated right now.
I feel like the life
has been sucked out of Chi Chi,
and, like, me personally,
I don't care what they say,
don't say this
and don't say that,
but to me, the right decision
is to be fair,
you know what I mean?
- The reality is
that the only thing
that dampens
your confidence is--
- Accepting what
somebody else is saying.
- Exactly.
- [ sighs ]
Just make
the right decision.
- Deciding who to send home
is always super hard.
No matter what anybody says
about whether they're ready
for their time to go,
there's nobody who didn't
fight very hard to be here
and doesn't
continue to fight
once they walk through
that door.
- Big and Milky.
- Fire me up.
- Well, the thing is,
I'd like to be very honest
about the whole
situation, guys.
Like, everybody just trying
to be so, like, sugar coat,
coo coo coo,
woo woo woo woo woo.
Milk is saying, like, I thought
I was going to be in the top.
To me,
I thought that the top
was going to be
you and Kennedy.
- Yeah.
- But you are
the fakest bitch alive.
- Yeah.
- And to be fair,
you probably would have
been in the top two
had you been able
to land all the things
that you were looking
to land.
- Right.
- Yeah.
It was so hard, you guys,
because he was just--
he was, like,
yelling the whole time.
- Yeah.
- He's, like, big
and I'm like, ba da ba da.
It doesn't, like--
And I could feel you guys'
energy in the moment.
I was, like, fuck.
- How are you?
- I'm in the bottom three.
Like, what the fuck?
- Yeah.
- It's--I don't know.
It's a shitty, shitty
situation.
To be in the bottom three
with two queens
that didn't give a 100%,
that were bulldozed
by their scene partner,
and then there's me.
I haven't made sense
of it all yet.
Obviously
this isn't my thing.
I'm not super into comedy,
and so I thought
that being that way
and succeeding in a way,
that it would be, like,
wow, Milk, you did it.
Just know
that I want to be here,
know that
I want to continue.
The judges actually want me to
continue in this competition.
The other queens respect me
and they want me to be here.
I am not on the level
of these bottom queens,
and to be compared to them,
it pisses me off.
But I'm feeling confident.
Make good decisions.
- Nope.
Never have, never will.
- Oh, my God,
this is so much fun.
- Oh, my God, I love it.
I made a dog.
- [ laughs ]
- I got lip and I got lips.
- Oh, wow,
that is hilarious.
- [ normal voice ]
Whee, this is so fun.
- I didn't know the balloons
had helium in them.
- They don't.
- Well, that's awkward.
Silence.
[ pop ] Oh.
- Bring back my All Stars.
- Having to eliminate somebody
is not a good feeling,
but this
is part of the game.
I look at the whole picture.
I just don't look at
the performance
or just
what the judge's say.
You gotta take everything
into account,
so I know what I have to do.
- Tonight the decision
is between three people,
and that just
complicates things more.
There are reasons
that every girl has to stay
and there are ways
in which every girl
didn't show up for
the competition this week.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Welcome back, ladies.
Two top All Stars
stand before me.
Ladies, this is your chance
to impress me,
win $10,000
and earn the power
to give one of the bottom queens
the chop.
The time has come...
[ thunder ]
to lip sync...
[ echoing ]
for your legacy.
- I know that
I shouldn't camp this one up
because I need
to show the judges
that I can do
different things.
This is my third lip sync,
and if I don't win this one,
then I'm at a negative
two to one ratio.
- Good luck
and don't fuck it up.
- ? I do my makeup
in somebody else's car ?
? We order different drinks
at the same bars ?
? I know about
what you did ?
? And I wanna scream
the truth ?
? She thinks
you love the beach ?
? You're such a damn liar
? Those great whites,
they have big teeth ?
? Oh, they bite you
? Thought you said that
you would always be in love ?
? But you're not in love
no more ?
? Did it frighten you
? How we kissed when we danced
on the light up floor? ?
? On the light up floor
? Sometimes I wake up
in a different bedroom ?
? I whisper things,
the city sings 'em back to you ?
? All those rumors,
they have big teeth ?
? But I hear sounds
in my mind ?
- Whoo! All right.
- ? Brand new sounds
in my mind ?
? But, honey, I'll be seein' you
down every road ?
- ? I'm waiting for it
? That green light,
I want it ?
- ?'Cause, honey,
I'll come get my things ?
? But I can't let go
- ? I'm waiting for it
? That green light,
I want it ?
- ? 'Cause, honey,
I'll come get my things ?
? But I can't let go
- ? I'm waiting for it
? That green light,
I want it ?
- ? Yes, honey,
I'll come get my things ?
? But I can't let go
- ? I'm waiting for it
? That green light,
I want it ?
? I'm waiting for it
? That green light,
I want it ?
[ cheers and applause ]
- Ladies,
I've made my decision.
Kennedy Davenport...
you're a winner, baby.
- Whoo!
- Whoo-hoo!
- Con-drag-ulations.
You've earned a cash tip
of $10,000.
- Thank you.
- BenDeLaCreme,
you are safe.
[ applause ]
- Good job, Ben.
- Will the bottom three
please step forward?
Kennedy, with great power
comes great responsibility.
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
- Oh. It was very hard.
I had to really think about
everything that was going on
on and off screen
to make my decision,
and I take that wholeheartedly
as a professional.
So I chose...
Milk.
- Milk, as it is written,
so it shall be done.
You are and will always be
an All Star.
Now sashay away.
- Thank you so much
for bringing me back.
I will continue
to make you proud.
I will do things that
nobody else has ever done.
[ applause ]
At this point in the game,
me holding this...
It's stupid.
The fact
that I was eliminated
even though another queen
had been in the bottom
three times...
dumb.
I know a lot of girls
think it's unfair for
them to be going home, but...
[ sighs ]
I just don't see
how this was my week.
Watching the episode--
[ bell rings ]
Ding.
- Milk!
- Oh, gosh.
- Blessed be, kitty girl.
You haven't seen the last of me,
Wagon Wheel Watusi.
- What does that mean?
Is somebody gonna tell me?
Damn it.
[ chuckles ]
- Next time
on "All Stars..."
It's time to play
Snatch Game.
[ cheering ]
Look who's here!
- Hi, guys.
[ cheering ]
It's Marc Jacobs.
- You look like a fudgsicle
dipped in flowers.
- You and I will meet
in a back alley somewhere.
- Oh, face crack.
- Well, can I trust you,
bitch?
- Ooh, this is so juicy!
- At the end of the day,
that type of shit
don't supposed to fly.
The struggle was real
on my end.