♪ See the super queen ♪
[RuPaul] From the most sickening
reaches of the Ru-niverse,
I searched among
my most legendary children
to find queens
with the superpowers
of charisma, uniqueness,
nerve and talent,
to join forces
with the super queens
that rule the Drag Race
Hall of Fame.
But remember, my All Stars,
with great power
comes great responsibility.
[evil laugh]
♪ See the super queen ♪
Honey, the face, the look,
the me.
Miss Monique Heart,
reclaiming my time,
reclaiming
my crown.
RuPaul, where's my check at?
Hello, America. Your girl
is back: Monique Heart.
The heart of Season 10.
And honey, she is what?
Brown cow stunning.
And I'm the first one!
Now, facts are facts, world.
When Beyonce
walks into the room,
you know she's there.
I know I'm that girl,
and I'm gonna win.
♪ Ah ooh ah ooh ah ah ♪
My issue on Season 10
was not talent.
Bitch!
My issue was money.
Where other queens
had a large repertoire
of drag to choose from,
I came to this competition
with glitter and Jesus.
There's my giraffe.
You said giraffe,
but I got brown cow.
Stunning.
[all laugh]
Since Season 10,
the good Lord made sure
that I shimmied good enough
to pay the designer, honey.
And now that money and costumes
are not the issue,
that crown is mine.
Who's the next bitch?
- Yes!
- Aah!
The body is back!
I'm Trinity Taylor,
top four from Season 9.
[laughs]
Did I say Trinity Taylor?
Sorry.
I just felt like
Trinity Taylor's so boring.
I am Trinity The Tuck,
and this tuck has teeth.
Chomp!
Before Season 9,
I was old school,
pageant, the body girl.
♪ My name is Trinity
and can't you see ♪
♪ I've got a lot
of plastic parts up in me ♪
It was a huge surprise to me
that I could do comedy.
My name is Stanky the Starfish.
I'm addicted to speed, too.
- Aah!
This time I'm confident
that I'm the whole package.
I made it to Top Four
the last time,
and now I'm here to win.
I am a super queen.
So tell me what this look is.
This is all zip ties, bitch.
Come through
the house down, bitch.
I'm made of plastic.
Might as well wear plastic,
bitch. [laughs]
Trinity is ultra fierce
competition.
I thought she was winning
Season 9.
I really did.
So the pressure is on again.
You can't spell legendary
without...leg.
M name is Naomi Smalls,
the legs of Season 8.
Come on, legs.
You know when this tall bitch
walks in the room
exactly who she is.
She's glowing, she's shining.
She's flexible.
She's on the stilts.
[laughs]
Naomi is a fashion girl.
She's fucking fierce.
Very Oz-mopolitan.
I just thought
it was perfection.
America's first drag president
must speak at-- fuck.
Cut.
It's all about attitude.
Now, when I look at you
as a model--
You're gonna take
great photos,
but that does not take talent.
Even though I made it
all the way to the Top Three,
a lot of people still think
I'm just a tall,
pretty fashion model.
- You're gorgeous!
- A goddess!
So I'm going to seize
this opportunity
to show the world
that I'm not just
this beauty queen.
There's only one crown
and it's mine.
- Damn her waist.
- Thank you.
I don't really know
what to expect of Naomi.
she's beautiful, young,
creative.
But Naomi doesn't have
a very big personality,
and you either stand out
or you get out.
Thank God you're pretty.
Guess who's black
in the house, bitch. Yes!
I am Monet X Change
of Season 10,
your current reigning
Miss Congeniality.
I am here to slay,
and until I snatch that crown,
a bitch brought her own. Ooh.
Soak it up, bitches!
Monet X Change.
Monet is on a roll.
Maya Angelou
ain't no punk bitch.
In Season 10, I thought
I was going all the way,
and I was really surprised
that I didn't win
any challenges.
The look seems homemade.
Really sloppy.
If I could go back in time,
the one thing that I would
change from my season
would be my rickety-crickety
runway girl
so I could have
some challenge wins.
I want a challenge win.
- Yes! Yes!
- You are a nasty queen.
I'm excited to see
my Season 10 sister.
I feel like both of us
have something to prove.
But this is "All Stars" 4.
A black jumpsuit
like a leotard?
It's not stunning.
Hail Mary.
Step aside, boys,
'cause the real queen is here.
My name is Gia Gunn,
I'm from Season 6,
and this fresh tilapia
is now seasoned.
Ch-ch-ch-chia.
He is CCC:
crazy cuckoo cunt.
Are you
in a White Snake video?
I'm feeling my oats.
I'm Darienne Lake.
My God,
there's room for everybody.
I could tell
that you're the feisty one.
Absolutely.
There's still a big percentage
of the world
who thinks that Gia Gunn
is the "absolutely, let me
feel my oats," shady character.
But since Season 6,
I did a huge self discovery
and drag was the gateway
for me to realize
that I am not a man
that dresses up as a woman.
I'm a woman that participates
in the art of drag.
Y'all got the same look.
Uh-uh. She got
a crown of thorns on.
That means we about
to crucify her real soon.
It feels amazing
to be back in the workroom
as the proud trans-woman
that I am.
So get ready,
because she's here.
Yes, God.
Thank God I didn't add
any more roses.
[all laugh]
Her look
may be similar to mine,
but, honey,
there's a big difference.
Mine is couture
and hers is just hot glue.
I saw you on "Botched."
- Yeah, girl.
- Yes, yes, you did.
I just saw a monster.
I said, that's my sister.
Ooh! No!
Girl, Gia's
gonna let everybody have it.
She is shady.
She's not the same person.
She's worse.
[all laugh]
Oh...
The crybaby's back.
[laughs]
I'm Farrah Moan
from Season 9,
and I'm here to moan and groan
my way to the top, honey.
Oh.
- Farrah Moan.
- I like the peek-a-boobs.
Are you feeling lucky?
On Season 9,
I felt prematurely cast
only because I was so young.
No. I don't want
to do this.
She whines
like a six-year-old.
She knows she's a cute girl,
but there's nothing more
than that yet.
Oh.
I think a lot of people
still see me
as this scared, whiney,
little 22-year-old girl,
But I just want to show people
that I am now
a ferocious, fierce
25-year-old. [laughs]
Oh, my God, it's
Christina Aguilera, girl.
Girl. [laughs]
Farrah Moan is one of the most
stunning queens I've ever seen.
She has more Instagram followers
than a lot of these bitches do.
Aah! Oh, my God,
y'all look so good.
Miss Farrah is gorgeous.
Let's tell facts.
But, America,
if you gonna have your ass out,
it's supposed to look like J-Lo,
not like Mr. Rogers.
I see that they went
straight from 8 to 6,
so we're skipping 7.
Let's all praise the Lord
for that.
- Pages.
- Oh.
I am Jasmine Masters
and I have something to say.
Oh!
I am back for "All Stars 4,"
you junky whores!
For those of you
who don't remember me,
I was on Season 7.
Jasmine Masters, your
personality is off the hook.
Where did you get
a loaf of bread?
[all laugh]
Watch out, sisters. Oh.
- Head cheerleader.
- Head--head cheerleader.
I've never seen a car crash
like this before.
I don't want to hear
any goddamn excuses?
Be prepared!
- Aah!
- Oh, my God!
- How you been?
There's a lot of queens,
a lot of fans out there
who don't believe
that I'm a great drag queen.
But since I've been on the show,
I became the mean queen,
and I'm always in
somebody's video or clip.
You know, I don't understand
why people's breath
be motherfucker's stink
and they don't taste it.
Because when you go... [chomp]
you don't taste that?
The mean queen is back
to snatch the crown.
Oh, look at you,
You're still beautiful.
You tall bitch,
get out of my face.
I'm glad to see
Jasmine Masters back
because she did so poorly
on her season.
But that bitch fucking
dug herself out of a grave
with those Vines
and Instagram videos,
and the bitch is so funny.
- So you were Season 7.
- Yes.
That's the season
you wanted to skip.
- Oh, really?
- Well, what I--
But if anybody,
at least we got Jasmine.
- You know what I mean?
- What is there from Season 7
that we were not
looking forward to seeing?
Season 7 was a pretty boring
fucking season,
and Season 9,
y'all were next on the list.
Wait a minute.
No. No, bitch.
I call shade, bitch.
Everyone thinks
that their season
was the best of the best,
but Monet
ain't got half the talent
that the girls
from Season 9 have, honey.
Season 9 is about to slay.
Season 9 was just fine, okay?
Fan favorite is here.
Oh, shit.
- Ha!
- No.
Brbrbrbrbr.
I'm back.
It's you, Valentina.
I'm glamour, high fashion,
a Latin-American diva.
And this is the Valentina
confessional look 2.0.
Shush.
We have a beautiful
designer beret by Dior,
and look at this manicure.
I'm ready for my closeup.
- Aw...
Linda Evangelista.
I like it.
Stop. Take that thing
off of your mouth.
I'd like to keep it on,
please.
It's a lip sync. What part
of that do you not understand?
After my elimination
on Season 9,
I felt the weight
of being a failure.
But eventually
I took it as motivation.
And since my season,
I've had the opportunities
of working with
a man from "Vogue,"
"Vogue Mexico."
And I don't really intend
on being known forever
as the person that
doesn't know how to lip sync.
Let's do a conga line.
♪ Dee dee dee dee dee da ♪
I'm surprised you know
the words to that song.
- Oh!
- Well, girl, whatever.
I feel good.
We were a close-knit season,
despite the reunion.
[all laugh]
We were such close friends,
and you have not spoken to me
in almost five months.
Text me, call me.
Let's talk about it.
I have texted you.
You ignore my texts.
I respect you and love you.
You don't love me.
I know that everybody wants
the fun little telenovela,
"Valentina vs. Farrah,
You Don't Love Me" fantasy.
However, she's apologized,
I've apologized,
and I feel like
we're on the route
to a better relationship.
Do you even have
her phone number?
Yeah.
She's texted me back now.
[laughs]
In the eyes of some,
I am Miss Congeniality.
And in the eyes of other people,
I'm a snake.
But I just know I'm both
because I know
I can be really nice,
but I've always loved
the villain.
[evil laugh]
So wait, you guys.
Do you think
this is all of the cast?
No, there's more girls.
How many trophies is it?
Eight is too little.
There's no way there's
just eight of us girls.
[alarm]
Uh-oh.
You bullshitting, you
bullshitting, you bullshitting.
Ooh, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
- Aw...
- Come on, bitch.
Hey, hennies.
The moment
you strutted through that door
your fate changed forever.
You're no longer mere mortals.
You're super queens,
and if you can harness the power
of your charisma, uniqueness,
nerve and talent,
you'll rule
the Drag Race Hall of Fame
from here to eternity.
Now, who the fuck is Heather?
[all laugh]
Hello, hello, hello.
[cheers and laughter]
Hey, super queens, welcome back.
- Hey!
Now, out of all the queens
in the world,
I've invited the eight of you
to return.
- Ooh!
- Whoo!
Because each of you possess
a unique super power
that puts you
in a league of your own.
Yes, ma'am.
All Star rules
are in full effect.
Each week, the top two queens
will lip sync for their legacy,
and the winner will receive
a $10,000 tip.
- Whoo!
- $10,000, yeah!
Plus, the power to eliminate
one of her fellow All Stars.
Now, this is your chance
to prove
that you can compete
with the best of the best.
And at the end of the day,
if you slay,
you'll earn your way
into the Drag Race Hall of Fame
and a cash prize of $100,000.
[cheering]
Now, there may be a twist.
Of course.
- Or two.
- Oh!
So without further ado,
please welcome Team...
Latrila.
Oh!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
[cheering]
Latrila is back in the house.
The bitches
are handcuffed together,
and I'm like, not teams,
not teams, not teams.
We all saw how "All Stars" 1
turned out.
Everyone competed in teams,
and if this is teams again,
I'm done.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I know I'm stunning,
but just 'cause I'm fabulous
don't mean I'm gonna be paired
with somebody fabulous.
Twist, honey.
Why y'all gagging so?
I still don't get
what's going on.
Me, neither. Oh.
♪ "RuPaul's Drag Race" ♪
The winner of "RuPaul's
Drag Race All Stars"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
a coveted spot
in the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize of $100,000.
With extra special guest judge
Jenifer Lewis.
♪ "RuPaul's Drag Race" ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
Please welcome
two legendary queens.
- Whoo!
- Oh!
Team Latrila.
- Ooh!
- Aah!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
[cheering]
Yes!
Aah! Everybody screaming?
I know you're screaming. Stop.
I'm the large, in charge,
chunky and funky
Latrice motherfucking Royale.
Eat it.
Look at Manila-nila-nila.
I'm Manila Luzon.
I'm the runnerup from Season 3,
and something-up
from "All Stars" 1.
On your own,
none of you
were able to reach the top.
So this time around,
you'll be competing
as teams of two.
- [laughs]
- Shit.
When we did "All Stars" 1
in teams,
it was the gagger
because we weren't expecting
to have to work with someone
the entire season.
Latrila.
This has been like
the best pairing in the world
because like you always know
how to take it
that extra step beyond,
and I love that.
Manila and Latrice,
sashay away.
This time
is gonna be different.
Now, ladies,
Latrice and Manila
competed as a team
in the first "All Stars."
But I invited them back
to compete as individuals.
[cheering]
[laughter and applause]
- [sighs]
- Whoo, girls!
I am very relieved
that it's not a team situation.
But at the same time,
having Latrice and Manila here,
things literally just got
three times harder.
They are two of the most
fierce competitors
in "Drag Race" history.
Game on.
Now that all 10 All Stars
have arrived,
I'd like to celebrate.
- Ooh.
- Yay!
Oh, Pit Crew.
[cheering]
Oh, yes!
And the bulge is real. Yes.
In the great tradition
of "Paris Is Burning," darling,
the library
is about to be opened.
Because reading is what?
[all] Fundamental.
That's right,
especially with fabulous frames
from l.a. Eyeworks.
All right, first up,
Monet X Change.
Ooh. RuPaul,
but I'm Miss Congeniality.
I could never...
[deep voice] Here we go, bitch.
[all laugh]
Tiffany The Tuck,
you've had so much plastic
in you,
you won't be buried in a coffin.
You'll probably be buried
in a recycling bin.
[all laugh]
Manila Luzon.
Emphasis on lose.
- Oh...
- Twice.
[all laugh]
Monet X Change.
The sponge queen.
Yes.
Too bad
you couldn't soak up a win.
[laughs]
Oh!
Ru, thank you so much
for bringing someone here
that's going to make me
look smart.
What's up, Farrah Moan?
[all laugh]
Farrah Moan is so dumb,
she thought Valentina
was her best friend.
Ooh!
Oh, my God.
Naomi Smalls,
legs you are known for.
However, you should
be known for toes,
'cause they're always
hanging out.
Oh!
Just like you
in that nineties video, Ru,
you know, when you
were in the bodega?
Oh!
Security.
[all laugh]
Monet X Change.
Now I know why
you have your name.
You look so cheap,
it looks like
you've broken your piggy bank
for some change.
[laughs]
For workshopping,
good to know.
Trinity Taylor.
When is the second
nose job planned?
I think you could still cut
a little bit more of her off.
You should tell that
to your ass.
[all laugh]
[laughs]
G-G-G-Gia Gunn.
I guess you can
buy a Gunn at Walmart.
[all laugh]
Jasmine Masters,
you know what--oh!
- Oh, my God.
- What is it?
I'm sorry. I was just
looking for her talent.
[all laugh]
Monique Heart,
you brag so much
about how you make
your own clothes,
but your dresses are so ugly,
they hang themselves.
[all laugh]
Tell.
Manila Luzon, I loved you
so much on your season.
But who's a booger now,
bitch?
[all laugh]
It's me, guys.
All right, all right,
you janky whores.
Latrice Royale.
You are my sister, bitch.
I liked it better
when you was my bodyguard.
[all laugh]
- And Ru.
- Uh-huh?
Thank you
for having me back, bitch.
I want my suit back.
[all laugh]
Trinity The Tuck, was that
legal or illegal silicone,
and whose kitchen table
did you get done on?
I'll give you
my doctor's number.
I don't wanna die.
Thank you.
[all laugh]
Miss Farrah Moan.
Sweets, if I was as untalented
and unoriginal as you are,
I too would invest
everything I had
in looking like somebody
more famous than I.
Okay.
Naomi Smalls,
legs, legs, legs.
Could we get
a side of brains with that?
[all laugh]
Valentina, take that thing
off your face.
Oh. It is your face.
[all laugh]
Your other one.
Oh! Damn.
[all laugh]
Jasmine, say it's true.
You got a key
to my house, bitch.
Girl, welcome to a season
that somebody
will give a shit about.
[all laugh]
That's how it's done, ladies.
That's how it's done.
Monet X Change,
I'm sure you get compared
to Bob the Drag Queen
all the time.
And in this competition,
that's a good thing,
because at least you know
you'll beat Naomi Smalls.
Oh-ho-ho. [laughs]
A two-for-one read.
Monique Heart,
do you remove your makeup
with flushable toilet wipes?
Because you're an ass
and your makeup is shit.
[all laugh]
All right now.
The library is closed
officially.
And, ooh, child,
I'm gonna need some aloe
for all them burns.
But the winner of today's
mini challenge is...
Latrice Royale.
[laughter and applause]
Con-drag-ulations.
You've won a $2,500 gift card
from l.a. Eyeworks.
I'm the ultimate reader,
bitch.
I won it on my season,
and I won it here.
So if anybody had a doubt
of why I am back,
here's your answer.
And I'll be posting
more of your reads
at RuPaulsDragRace.com.
#AllStars4.
Ladies, since appearing
on "Drag Race,"
you've served
as ambassadors of drag
around the world.
Now it's time to see
how your charisma, uniqueness,
nerve and talent has grown.
For this week's maxi challenge,
you'll be headlining an All Star
Spangled Variety Show.
[cheering]
And you'll be showcasing
your best talent
to entertain a patriotic mix
of LGBTQ veterans
and active service people.
- Oh.
- Ooh.
Maybe I'll find
my straight military husband.
Except for it's LGBTQ.
Oh.
That was the key word.
So my fellow drag Americans,
start your engines
and may the best All Star win.
- Whoo!
- Ow!
- Oh!
- Whoo!
Claim!
Bitch, my nails
is there already.
My nails is on the counter.
I lost a nail.
It's okay, it's okay.
That's not the only thing
you're gonna lose.
[laughs] Oh, my God.
Heave!
Latrice and Manila.
That's the gag of the season.
It really is.
It's so wild
being on the same season
with legends,
but I can't let that admiration
get in the way
of my performance.
Because I know I can outperform
these bitches
who've been at this shit
since before I was born.
[laughs]
It's so nuts to be here
on the same season as you.
You are a legend.
- Yeah, girl.
- Thank you. That's so cool.
I mean, I remember
when I first met Lady Bunny
when I first moved
to New York City.
You're my Lady Bunny.
[all laugh]
Oh, my gosh.
Lady Bunny is old
as a dinosaur, okay?
Uh, thank you, I guess.
That's okay.
I have longevity, okay, girl?
Read between the lines.
We'll talk to you
in a couple years
and see where you at.
Read between the lines
on your forehead, darling.
[all laugh]
You know what?
You are the reason why
I wear highlight now.
- That should be your talent.
- It is.
Oh, my God. That's great.
I wanna show something
that's my brand,
so I've put together
a tucking tutorial.
[laughs]
I want to show you
that I can be funny
and still teach you
how to tuck.
That's never been done
on the show.
You do have to take risks
if you want to win.
No. Well, just the song,
'cause it's
"Brown Cow Stunning."
This is for something else.
For my performance,
I decided to debut my song
"Brown Cow Stunning,"
and sing live
because last time
I went home right before
the singing challenge.
So this time, oh, honey.
trust I'm gonna give you
the ooh-ah-ah sensation.
Trust.
[clicks tongue]
♪ La vaca, moo ♪
- What does it mean?
- La vaca means the cow.
♪ Moo, the cow, moo ♪
Aah, yes!
Brown cow stunning.
Uh, I don't know how stunning
it's really gonna be.
I'm excited to see
what we're all doing.
I know.
We're gonna find out.
Hopefully it's not comedy.
I doubt that.
I'm uncertain about how I feel
with Farrah here
in the competition.
I'm a little bit worried for her
because I don't really think
that she's an All Star.
I don't think that she
is anything more past Instagram,
and this is a place
for legends, okay?
Okay!
Here we go, girls.
Here we are!
Today we're getting ready
for our first maxi challenge,
an All Star
Spangled Variety Show.
All right, y'all.
Yes, get into the outfits.
Yes!
- Model.
- Always being a diva.
[all laugh]
[laughs]
Latrice!
You guys are interrupting
my outfit moment.
- Are you excited, bitch?
- I am!
I'm nervous. Very excited,
but nervous, girl.
What are you
most nervous about?
I don't know.
What if the judges don't think
that what you think
is your talent is your talent?
- You know what I'm saying?
- Yeah.
"All Stars"
is a very different game.
The stakes are higher.
The chances
that you can go home
for a tiny fumble
are greater.
I'm trying to put these on
so I don't slip and fall, girl.
You know
that is the kiss of death.
Like you're done.
Game over. Career's ended.
Goodbye.
Honey, "Brown Cow Stunning"
is gonna get debuted.
- Yes.
- I'm so excited.
- Good for you.
- I am gonna do standup.
Yes?
Yeah. It's just like,
bitch, gimme the mic.
I'm gonna talk some shit.
We gonna have a good time.
I have always been told,
from very young,
"Ha ha, you're so funny."
Just saying
whatever I need to say.
But I've just been myself.
The women love me,
the men love me,
the kids love me,
the cats, the dogs, the mice.
Everybody love me, so...
Guess what?
Up in the ring, bitch.
Did you write or are you
just gonna go off the cuff?
I'm just gonna go off of it.
I figure
if I write something down...
- Uh-huh.
- I will forget it,
'cause I'm trying
to stay here.
Oh.
You know, this is not like,
oh, you gotta learn this script
and these words.
But what if it's
more like a skeleton?
You know what I mean?
An outline.
So that way you always know
where you wanna go.
You shouldn't try to wing it.
You're in a competition.
This is not
your little Facebook videos.
Honey, this will send you home.
Beyonce rehearses.
Oh, my God.
You look like a turtle.
Bitch, commitment.
Oh!
My eyebrows!
Valentina,
how you feel over there?
Y'all know me.
I run so damn late
that if I get carried away
in these conversations,
I'm never gonna be ready.
Oh, we know.
Is that your tactic,
Valentina,
to not get kicked off
by just never getting ready?
[laughs]
The energy in the room
is so focused.
We're all ready
to deliver an attack.
Who thinks
that could be in the bottom?
Gia, if you ask
the shady question,
why don't you answer first?
I'm a little bit worried
about yours
'cause I don't think tucking
is a talent.
That makes me nervous for you.
Okay, but just because
you're dressing up in kabuki
doesn't mean
you're talented, either.
Well, honey, I'm
actually doing something
that I've studied for 15 years.
Okay, Well, I've done drag
and tucking
for 15 years, too.
Okay.
Oh, God, this got really real
really quick.
Baby, those are some balls
getting pushed out.
The important thing is
I'm not worried,
so you'll see
when I'm out there.
I sure will.
I'm conflicted with Gia.
I don't remember her
ever being this shady.
I don't know if she's got
something up her sleeve
and this is her strategy.
You better believe
if that continues,
she will be gone.
Hasta la vista, baby.
Since I checked,
tucking is not a talent.
That's not a talent.
And that's why today's
really gonna set apart
the All Stars
from the drag queens.
Amen.
Who the fuck
is going home today?
[RuPaul laughs]
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
♪ Cover girl ♪
And what?
[cheers and applause]
Welcome to the main stage of
"RuPaul's Drag Race All Stars."
Michelle Visage, are you ready
to get all-started?
If you stay all-started, you
don't have to get all-started.
- Oker.
- Brrr!
Style superstar
Carson Kressley.
Now, do you like a man
in uniform?
Oh, I love them in uniform,
but even out of uniform
is better.
[all laugh]
I'm not picky.
The hilarious Ross Mathews.
You're back.
Well, my neck, my back,
but you know the rest.
[all laugh]
And black Hollywood
calls her mother.
The insanely talented
Jenifer Lewis.
Yes, I am the mother
of black Hollywood.
I'm so happy to be here.
[all laugh]
This week,
we challenged our queens
to gag us
with their many talents
in an All Star Spangled
Variety Show.
Ladies and gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best All Star win.
To the brave LGBTQ veterans
and service members
from the bottom of our hearts,
thank you.
And welcome to our All Star
Spangled Variety Show.
[cheers and applause]
How now, brown cow?
It's Monique Heart.
Hello, world.
Hello, America.
Quick question.
♪ Are you brown cow stunning? ♪
♪ When you wake up
in the morning ♪
♪ When you walk
through the room ♪
♪ Slaying all day every day ♪
♪ Serving face to Mother Ru ♪
♪ Giving you
your ooh-ah sensation ♪
♪ Brown cow stunning
in formation ♪
♪ Brown cow ruling the nation ♪
Hit it!
♪ Brown cow stunning ♪
♪ Giving ooh-ah sensation ♪
♪ Brown cow stunning,
coming to every nation ♪
♪ Brown cow stunning, giving
ooh-ah sensation ♪
I didn't know
this bitch could sing.
She is turning it out, girl.
♪ Are you brown cow
stunning yet? ♪
♪ Are you, brown cow?
Are you, brown cow? ♪
♪ Are you brown cow stunning? ♪
[cheers and applause]
Here to close the house down,
Naomi Smalls.
[cheers and applause]
Hey, sweeties.
Let me introduce you
to my friend.
Her name's fashion.
What was that? Fashion.
And what do we do
with fashion?
♪ Oh, so ♪
♪ And strut ♪
Work, girl!
♪ Oh, so ♪
♪ A little strut ♪
♪ Oh, so, right strut ♪
♪ Go down ♪
♪ Go up ♪
♪ Oh, so ♪
♪ A little strut,
oh, so ♪
♪ Right there and strut ♪
♪ Go down ♪
♪ Fashion ♪
Yes!
♪ Her name's fashion ♪
♪ Shoulders back,
hips forward ♪
♪ Oh, so ♪
[cheers and applause]
Fantastic.
- Love it!
- Great!
Can you feel her oats?
It's Gia Gunn.
[cheers and applause]
[gong, Japanese music plays]
[singing in Japanese]
[cheers]
Bitch, how do you do that?
Because that was magic to me.
[singing in Japanese]
[cheers and applause]
The look and feel of real.
Trinity The Tuck.
[lively music plays]
♪ For the perfect tuck ♪
♪ You'll need
some spray adhesive ♪
♪ Give a little spritz ♪
♪ To both your front and back ♪
♪ Put some tissue paper there ♪
♪ Just below your derriere ♪
♪ With your junk pulled
distinctly to your crack ♪
Sorry, Mom!
♪ Then clear vinyl tape
should do quite nicely ♪
♪ To give that mean tuck
a helping hand ♪
♪ At least three strips
is wise ♪
♪ Depending on your size ♪
♪ From chiquito
to el chalupo grande ♪
See, that's Spanish.
♪ Now, go and get your
sturdy tucking panties ♪
♪ The ones that look like hell
and smell much worse ♪
♪ Get those straps
around your thighs ♪
♪ As you pull them
to the skies ♪
♪ Till you're tucked so tight
it makes you want to curse ♪
Motherfucker!
♪ A little airbrush spray ♪
♪ To hide the razor burn
and welts ♪
♪ And your perfect tuck
is finally in the groove ♪
♪ You can dance
and you can stun ♪
♪ But it's gonna take a ton ♪
♪ Of industrial-strength
cleanser to remove ♪
♪ It's just a tip to save ya ♪
♪ To hide
what God done gave ya ♪
♪ The perfect tuck
to keep your junk away ♪
I can't sing,
but you get the point.
Go tuck yourself.
[cheers and applause]
I think I've been tucking
wrong this whole time.
- [laughs]
- Look at that ass.
Welcome to burlesque.
It's Farrah Moan.
[stripper music plays]
[cheering]
[cheers and applause]
I'm gagged.
Farrah's setup is fabulous.
It looks expensive.
Interesting.
[cheering]
Oh!
Whoa.
She fell.
And she fell hard, bitch.
[cheers and applause]
America, she might
be in the bottom
'cause it's not stunning.
[cheers and applause]
Welcome back
to "RuPaul's Drag Race"
All Star Spangled Variety Show.
So perk up.
It's Monet X Change.
[R&B music plays]
♪ People hating undercover ♪
♪ Without knowing
what you're all about ♪
♪ But when they try
to turn ♪
[deep voice]
♪ You under ♪
- [laughs]
- ♪ Find a way to turn it out ♪
♪ I'm feeling fierce and free,
unbothered ♪
♪ Bitches, take my sponges ♪
♪ Come on and soak it up.
♪ Let these bitches
take my sponges ♪
♪ S-s-soak it up ♪
♪ And let these bitches
take my sponges ♪
♪ S-s-soak it up ♪
♪ And let these bitches
take my sponges ♪
♪ S-s-soak it up ♪
[all laugh]
When the girls
come at you, honey,
you gotta be a sponge.
♪ You soak it up,
turn it out ♪
Girl, soak what up?
I mean, maybe some of that sweat
on that forehead.
♪ Tens across the board ♪
♪ From Kenya to Alaska
to Venus and beyond ♪
For real!
[cheers and applause]
All right, y'all.
Let's get this party party
started.
It's Manila Luzon.
[Grieg's "In the Hall
of the Mountain King" plays]
What's she doing?
[tempo increases]
[cheers and applause]
Go, girl. Very nice.
Push, push, get your jush.
It's Jasmine Masters.
[cheers and applause]
Hello.
I am Jasmine Masters,
and I have something to say.
I went on a date with this guy,
and when he called me back
for another one,
I said, "Hell no."
And he asked me why.
I said, "'Cause, baby,
your breath smells
exactly like your ass.
Your breath stinks."
[exhales and inhales]
Honey, I don't know
what you been doing,
what you been eating,
but your breath smells like
you have been doing nothing
but eating on asshole.
I need you to fix that.
Where are the jokes?
Don't eat no more asshole.
Go see a dentist
and then come back
and say hello to me.
I am Jasmine Masters,
and I have something to say.
Thank you.
[cheers and applause]
Jasmine can have all
the viral videos she wants.
That don't make an All Star,
girl.
A lot of people
have viral things.
They go to the doctor for it
and get rid of it.
[cheers and applause]
She's large and in charge.
It's Latrice Royale.
[gong, music plays]
The royal queen has arrived!
Latrice Royale,
give them life!
♪ Tens, tens
across the board ♪
♪ When I hit the door,
they clear the floor ♪
♪ Excuse the beauty ♪
Whoo!
♪ Eat it, eat it, gag ♪
♪ Choke and come back to life ♪
- ♪ Excuse the beauty ♪
- Come on, baby!
♪ Excuse the beauty ♪
♪ Sorry those fries
don't go with this shake ♪
♪ If you're a Big Mac,
then I must be steak ♪
♪ Excuse the beauty ♪
♪ Tens ♪
Latrice singing,
yes, yes, yes.
Everything is yes.
♪ Bitch, I--
bitch, I-- bitch, I can ♪
♪ Bitch, I-- bitch, I--
bitch, I can ♪
♪ Bitch, I--
bitch, I-- bitch, I can ♪
♪ Bitch, I-- bitch, I--
bitch, I can ♪
♪ Bitch, I--
bitch, I-- bitch, I can ♪
♪ Excuse the beauty ♪
[laughs]
[cheers and applause]
Yay!
¡Escandalo!
It's Valentina.
[music plays]
This is a story
about the power of your words.
Valentina, it's time.
I'd like to take it off,
please.
[singing in Spanish]
Whoo, Valentina's
a fierce competitor.
There's no doubt that
she's supposed to be here.
[singing in Spanish]
[cheers and applause]
Welcome, All Stars.
When I call your name,
please step forward.
Gia Gunn.
Valentina.
Manila Luzon.
Latrice Royale.
You are all safe.
Please step
to the back of the stage.
Thank you.
Ladies, you represent the tops
and bottoms of the week.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques,
starting with Monique Heart.
Happy to see you in brown cow.
Real brown cow,
not giraffe print.
Yes! No!
[all laugh]
Way to start a show.
Really got our attention
from the beginning
and held it
the whole performance.
You're ferocious.
I love that word,
and you're an entertainer.
It's udder-ly great.
[all laugh]
And you were milking it
for all it's worth.
[all laugh]
This is a great way to enter
this competition with momentum.
You need to keep it up.
Didn't you mean moo-mentum?
[all laugh]
Thank you.
Up next, Trinity The Tuck.
You had a minute to do
something, and you told a story.
It just was so enter-tainting.
[laughs]
In your season,
you didn't think
that you were funny
until we had Sister Mary Koont,
and then you started
to break out of your shell.
So I am so grateful
that you chose tonight
to start with comedy.
Just one directorial note.
You had that great prop
of going behind
that little dressing screen.
And when you come out,
I would have liked
a bigger bang.
Okay.
I kind of enjoyed
the late reveal.
It was unpredictable.
I got it and I liked it.
You're wearing an outfit now
that doesn't require a tuck.
Have you maintained the tuck?
Oh, no, girl.
She's still there.
- Oh.
- Oh, wow, okay.
Is that uncomfortable,
darling?
If you only knew.
[all laugh]
God bless you all.
Up next, Naomi Smalls.
The world is starved for fun,
and you gave it to us.
I found the whole thing
very beautiful to watch.
But beautiful can get kind of
boring after a while.
The best part about this
wasn't how gorgeous you looked.
It was the weird part
when you popped that wig off
and you had like
my Uncle Lenny's hair.
[all laugh]
That intersection where drag
and glamour meets comedy,
for me, that's great drag.
Up next, Monet X Change.
- Soak it up.
- Hi, Michelle.
Glad to see
you're on the sponge.
- The same.
- No pregnancies here.
[laughs]
You had your own voice
in the beginning of that song.
- Yeah. ♪ Undercover ♪
- That's interesting.
Yeah, it wasn't
a good vocal day.
Mm.
That sponge thing,
yes, is part of your brand,
something we know you for.
All designers have their
kind of their bread and butter
and what they're known for.
But then each season,
they try to take it forward.
We've seen it before.
- This is "All Stars."
- Yeah.
So I'm going to push
for you to be on par
with everybody else.
Yeah.
Up next Farrah Moan.
Hi.
This look tonight
is delicious.
It is like sparkly rock candy.
I want to come over there
and lick everything--
well, on your clothes.
[all laugh]
Everything
just looks gorgeous.
So feel good about that,
because I know
you were so nervous.
It just didn't really happen
how I had dreamed of it.
Like I just wanted everything
to be perfect,
and it just...it just wasn't.
You have everything it takes
to win this whole thing,
but not if you can't
summon the confidence.
Yes.
Leave that nervous shit home.
It's boring.
Can I get an amen up in here?
- Yes.
Up next, Jasmine Masters
in that pantsuit.
Hi.
Oh, my goodness.
Very Liza Minnelli.
[all laugh]
It was a smart choice
to do comedy for you,
because you are very funny.
Those jokes just kind of
weren't landing.
Did you prepare that at all?
Well, I knew
what I was going to say
because I went off
my bad breath video.
But was it planned
when you did the video?
- No. No.
- No.
I know exactly what happened
with you tonight.
I'm a funny person, too, right,
and I think I'm funniest
when I'm off the cuff.
That's why that video went viral
because it was hilarious
and it was so authentic.
But doing standup
is a different thing.
- Mm-hmm.
- It's gotta be flawless,
because one little stumble
and you lose us.
Now, based on
the judges' critiques,
I've made some decisions.
Trinity The Tuck.
Monique Heart.
You're the top two All Stars
of the week.
[applause]
- Thank you.
- Con-drag-ulations.
- Yes, children, yes.
You've each won
a seven night's stay for two
at the Sand Castle
on the Beach Hotel
in St. Croix,
U.S. Virgin Islands.
Yeah!
Naomi Smalls,
Monet X Change,
you are both safe.
That means Farrah Moan
and Jasmine Masters,
you are in the bottom two.
I came here with such
high expectations for myself,
and it's hard for me
not to feel like
I just don't have it in me
or something.
How can you go from being so
confident and proud of yourself
to feeling so small?
Monique and Trinity,
each of you needs to decide
which of the bottom two
you will eliminate
if you win the lip sync.
So while you queens
deliberate in the workroom,
the judges and I will be
tooting our own horns.
You may leave the stage.
- Oh, girl.
- I'm getting a drink.
It feels great
to be in the top two.
This shows right out the gate
who is competition
and who is not.
Girl, this is
the first elimination.
- I know.
- I want to win,
but then again, like, winning,
you have to send someone home.
Someone's dreams are
about to be crushed forever.
- Not forever, honey.
- No.
We're on "All Stars"
because we're All Stars.
- Yeah.
- That's never going to go away.
The real T, you can say
we're all All Stars,
but when you are going home,
packing up your stuff,
it doesn't feel like that,
you know what I mean?
It feels like shit.
How do you feel, Jasmine?
You can't say
that I wasn't funny.
You may not like
what I was saying,
but you cannot say
I wasn't funny.
Jasmine does not get it
at all.
She refuses to take any
responsibility for her faults
and fucking up her talent.
I was so excited
about this number.
Like, I've literally dreamt
of this number
ever since I started doing drag.
Maybe one day
I'll be able to afford
to be as sparkly and beautiful
as I've always dreamed of.
I'm going to cry again.
This crying,
let me get her lipstick,
'cause I'm not doing it.
You a grown-ass man.
Girl, I'll talk to you
over there, honey.
I love you,
but your crying annoys me.
If you continue on, sis, like
you gotta be, like, do or die.
Like in that fall,
I would have loved
if you would have just posed.
I get it.
We all have those moments.
Beyonce. We saw the video.
Ring the alarm, bla-ka-ka-ka,
she fell down them stairs.
But you get up.
You hold it.
It's not that you fell.
It's how you fell.
All I want
is to just be the best.
And I want
to fucking just...do it.
That's what I want.
That right there,
I would like to see her
more often.
Sis, if you are here...
Because if you fuck up again,
I'm going to send you home
personally.
I'm telling you that
to your face.
Why should you stay
and not your counterpart?
She breaks down too much.
Every little thing go wrong,
she just gonna
keep breaking down
and breaking down
and breaking down.
- Right, okay.
- And this is "All Stars."
I want to eliminate
the weakest link,
because if I'm going
to be the best,
- I want to beat the best.
- Beat the best.
Well, if you want
competition, bitch,
I'm gonna bring it to
your ass, though. [laughs]
If you were in their position,
who would you send home?
- Ooh.
- Oh.
I'm not as confident
in Farrah's skills.
Honestly, girls like her,
to me, they're not showgirls.
They look good on Instagram,
and they hope that the clothes
and the jewels and the--
Make up for talent.
But it doesn't.
And tonight proved that.
I'm just disappointed
that Jasmine didn't even think
to like write down an outline.
At least Farrah Moan, she had
a fully realized concept.
I mean, we could tell some
preparation went into it.
Right.
My mind is not made up.
Why should you stay?
I have come to "All Stars" 4
with something to prove.
If you choose me to stay,
I'm going to fucking fight,
because I never once felt
like I could be a winner,
and like for the first time
in my life,
I really feel like
I could win something.
Ugh.
If you stay or you go,
you've got to stop crying.
You've got to pull it together.
Sis, I think
you are stupid funny.
Right.
And I think that
if you just had a skeleton,
it would have went by
just a lot smoother.
Recently, within
the past couple of years,
I've been doing
the Laugh Factory.
I have got nothing
but great reviews.
I can go down a list,
oh, you know, this happened,
this happened, this happened,
that happened.
But it's not about that.
If I stay, I stay.
If I go, I go.
There's no love lost,
because it's a game.
Things happen,
you know what I mean?
You know how the girls
don't want to beg.
But there's a difference
between like begging
and saying if you keep me,
trust and believe
you won't see me here again.
Where's that extra fight, girl?
If you keep me, you keep me,
then we gonna ride it out.
If you don't,
we still gonna ride it out.
Right. I can't with her.
Like if you can't fight
for yourself,
there's a whole lot
of other girls who will.
Now that I have the power,
can you send both?
I don't know.
So...yeah.
[playing a Sousa march]
- Jesus.
- Sorry.
Silence.
Bring back my All Stars.
I'm coming from an excitement
that I'm in Top Two
to, oh, shit.
I have to send
one of these girls home.
And I wasn't expecting
the emotional side of this
to be as hard as it is.
Feelings are not fact.
We cannot let the way we feel
determine how we act.
They know I'm not malicious,
whatever, da-da-da-da.
I'm not really worried
about them.
I'm here to take the crown.
Period.
Welcome back, ladies.
Two top All Stars
stand before me.
Ladies, this is your chance
to impress me,
win $10,000,
and earn the power
to give one of the bottom queens
the chop.
The time has come...
[thunder]
to lip sync...
[echoing] for your legacy.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
[all laugh]
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ You've got me
feeling emotions ♪
♪ Deeper than
I've ever dreamed of ♪
♪ Oh, you've got me
feeling emotions ♪
♪ Higher
than the heavens above ♪
♪ I feel good ♪
♪ I feel nice ♪
♪ I've never felt so satisfied ♪
♪ I'm in love ♪
♪ I'm alive ♪
♪ Intoxicated ♪
♪ Flying high ♪
♪ It feels like a dream ♪
♪ When you touch me tenderly ♪
♪ I don't know if it's real ♪
♪ But I like the way
I feel inside ♪
♪ You've got me feeling
emotions ♪
[laughs] Bitch.
The saying goes what comes up
must come down.
And she is what? Bald.
Why can't you keep
your hair on, girl?
♪ Oh, when you're looking
into my eyes ♪
♪ You make me feel so high ♪
[all laugh]
♪ Oh, oh, baby ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, hey, hey ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ You've got me
feeling emotions ♪
♪ Higher
than the heavens above ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ You've got me
feeling higher ♪
[all laugh]
♪ You've got me
feeling higher ♪
[laughter and applause]
All right.
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Trinity.
Con-drag-ulations.
You're a winner, baby.
[applause]
Yay.
It makes me emotional
because I want this.
I want to win "All Stars,"
and it's a great start.
You've earned a cash tip
of $10,000.
Monique, you are safe.
And I think you should invest
in some duct tape.
Maybe Trinity
can give you some of hers.
Because you know the other girls
duct tape their heads.
Yes, ma'am.
Or a stapler.
Stapler. [laughs]
All right, you may join
the other girls.
Stunning.
[applause]
Will the bottom two
please step forward.
Trinity, with great power
comes great responsibility.
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
You picked a great song
for the first episode,
'cause this is very emotional.
Unfortunately, I have
two friends that are here,
and I'm trying to give
the fairest decision
that I can make at this time.
And, um, the person
I've decided to go with...
is Jasmine.
It's okay.
You're going to be good.
Just do what you do
and prove all your haters wrong,
'cause you have a lot of talent.
Jasmine, as it is written,
so it shall be done.
You are and will always be
an All Star.
Yes! [laughs]
Sashay away.
Thank you.
I still love you, sis.
- I love you.
- Bye, girls.
- Love you.
I love you, too.
[applause]
I don't really believe
I should have eliminated
for this one,
because if they went
by mistakes,
I had nowhere near big
of mistakes as anybody else.
I don't do the whole crying
situation and woe is me
and all this and all that,
because I'm just not about that.
But you have not seen
the last of me yet.
[laughs]
Because I'm coming.
I am coming.
Con-drag-ulations, All Stars.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
- Amen.
- All right.
Now let the music play.
♪ I'm telling, I'm telling ♪
♪ I'm telling the truth now ♪
♪ We're all born naked
and the rest is drag ♪
Next time on "All Stars"...
I'm holding auditions
for my new super group
called Henny featuring
Stacy Layne Matthews.
[cheers and applause]
Wow!
[singing in Spanish]
Coochie-coo.
I don't know what
the fuck she's saying,
but, girl, I am living.
♪ I am not the first ♪
[cheers and applause]
My spot's already right here.
So then fake it
in that one spot then.
Farrah is plucking
my last nerve, America.
According to your team,
you're the weakest link.
Yeah, well, some of us
don't have to force storylines
to get their air time.
God, I can't stand her.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]