- Previously on "All Stars"...
10 of my fiercest queens
return for a spot
in the Drag Race Hall of Fame.
- The energy in the room
is so focused.
They're all ready to attack.
- This got really real
really quick.
- Who the fuck
is going home today?
- Welcome to our All Star
Spangled Variety Show.
It's Monique Heart.
- This is a great way
to enter this competition
with momentum.
- Didn't you mean moo-mentum?
- Trinity The Tuck.
- Is that uncomfortable, though?
- If you only knew.
[all laugh]
- It's Jasmine Masters.
- Your breath smell like
you have been doing nothing
but eating on assholes.
- Did you prepare that at all?
- No.
- It's Farrah Moan.
Oh!
- Leave that nervous shit home.
It's boring.
- Trinity The Tuck.
Con-drag-ulations.
You're a winner, baby.
[applause]
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
- The person
I've decided to go with...
is Jasmine.
- Jasmine, sashay away.
- Whew.
Poor Juj.
- Oh, Jasmine.
- Oh...
- The first queen has gone home.
Our beloved sister,
Miss Jasmine, chopped.
The honeymoon phase is over.
Stuff just got real real, y'all.
The goopery, the gaggery,
it is real.
- "Hey juj, much to you all.
Kick faith, love Jasmine."
- I mean, she's "Drag Race"--
- Legend.
- Royalty.
- Right.
- Legend.
- How do you feel, girl?
- This you can't
prepare yourself
for how you're going to feel.
I'm not a crier,
and it made me think
of, like, how I feel
about this competition.
What I want.
It was hard.
So just prepare yourself.
It's not gonna be easy.
- Trinity needs to get over
this feeling
of regret and remorse
and "Woe is me,
I had to send someone home."
It's part of the game, girl.
Like, you might lose
a friendship here or there,
but you know what?
You're $10,000 richer,
girl, you know.
You can buy friends.
[laughs]
Well, congratulations, girl.
You guys were
the top of the week.
- I felt good in my lip sync.
I'm happy that my hair loss
was iconic in the rafters.
[all laugh]
- She was in
the stratosphere, bitch.
- Girl, if you have a wig
come off your head,
some other something better
be up underneath your wig.
And this ain't the first time
I'm looking at your bald head.
Brown cow's thing?
Not so much.
- Who's lip syncing your kitty?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yours.
[all laugh]
I chose Jasmine.
Farrah, I love you,
and I told you--
When you started crying,
I was like she's getting it.
I'm sending her home.
And it wasn't until
you stopped crying
and you were like
I want this so bad,
and it threw me all the way back
to my season
when I got eliminated,
and I was like
this is not supposed
to be my time, I'm sorry.
If someone could have
given me grace in that moment
for a fumble, then I would
like that same grace.
- Thank you.
I can't even begin to express
how thankful I am
that I am getting a second
chance in this competition.
I'm not a fuck-up
and I'm not untalented.
I just messed up.
I'm excited
to have a second chance,
and literally, like, watch out,
I'm about to fuck this up.
- That little beautiful bitch
was lucky today.
But this is a show about talent,
and looking pretty isn't enough.
If she's just
going to rely on that beauty,
somebody's gonna serve it
to her soon.
So let the games begin.
[laughs]
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- The winner of "RuPaul's
Drag Race All Stars"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
a coveted spot
in the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize of $100,000.
With extra special guest judges
Ciara and Kacey Musgraves.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman ♪
- ♪ Best woman win ♪
- Gentlemen.
[all talking]
- Why did y'all go
without me?
- [speaking Spanish]
It's a new day
in the workroom,
and--Mreowrr--I'm here.
- Valentina, what is the story
about this look?
- I just wanted to be dark,
sleek, and chic.
- Can we talk about
how great your ass looks.
- Valentina.
- Aah!
[all laugh]
- ♪ Da-da-da-da-da-da-da ♪
- Valentina's bare ass?
I'm sorry.
No ass at all.
When they was passing out
Little Debbie snack cakes,
she missed the line, honey.
[all laugh]
[siren]
- Oh!
- Ooh, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
- Hey, All Stars.
If you want to earn your place
in the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
you better put your henny
where your mouth is.
So everybody say love.
- Love.
- And don't funk it up.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, yeah.
- Hello, hello, hello.
Ladies.
[cheering]
Hey, All Stars.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Now, for this week's
maxi challenge,
I'm holding auditions
for my new super group
called Henny.
[all laugh]
#AllStars4.
Now, performing in two teams,
each of you will need
to write your own lyrics,
and then record your vocals
with singer/songwriters
Leland and Freddy Scott,
who've worked
with superstar artists
like Troye Sivan
and Selena Gomez.
[cheers and applause]
- Okay. Come on.
- Plus you'll be creating
your own group choreography
and then you'll style
your individual looks.
Trinity The Tuck
and Monique Heart,
since you were the top two
All Stars last week,
you are the team captains.
- Aah!
- Yeah! Okay.
- Here we go.
- Trinity,
you get to choose first.
- Oh, goody.
Valentina.
- Ahh. Brrrrr! Ow!
[purrs]
- [laughs]
- Monique, you're up.
- The sponge queen,
Monét X Change.
[applause]
- Brrrr.
[all laugh]
- Come on, Latrice.
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
- Come on.
- Miss Naomi.
- Yes, ma'am.
[all laugh]
- Come on, Manila.
[cheers]
- All right, that leaves
Gia Gunn and Farrah Moan.
- I actually thought I was going
to be the first one picked.
I don't think any of these girls
really know what I do
other than look gorgeous.
Maybe they're just intimidated.
- Monique, who do you choose?
- Miss Farrah Moan.
- Oh.
- All right,
that means Gia Gunn,
you are Team Trinity The Tuck.
- Aw.
So you got stuck with me
anyway. You see?
- We are happy.
We are happy.
- Now I'm going to show you
how the real tuck is done.
[all laugh]
- Team Trinity,
you'll be performing the track
"Don't Funk It Up."
- Yes, honey.
- Team Monique,
you'll be performing the track
"Everybody Say Love."
- Everybody say love.
- Love.
- Now, ladies, Henny is not
your average girl group.
In fact, it's a collaboration,
featuring one of my
all-time favorite queens
in "Drag Race" herstory.
I'm talking
the original Henny-Henny.
[cheers]
That's right.
From Backswamp, North Carolina,
please welcome
Stacy Layne Matthews.
[cheers and applause]
- The Henny, like,
the motherfucking Henny.
Oh, my gosh, a fucking legend.
- Wow.
- Now that's
the "Jingle Bell Rock."
- I'm gonna go tell her, Henny.
- Henny is in the house,
Henny.
- Who the fuck is here
that I'd want to know?
Is Precious back there?
She better be cooking me
something to eat.
I feel like it's couture.
- That meme of her
in the Season 8 finale,
it'll be ingrained
in everyone's brain forever.
- Shake it. Ooh!
- I really love her.
Like, when I see her,
it does something to me.
- Mmm. Mmm.
- [whines]
- Now, ladies, Stacy is our
artist in residence this week.
You will be judged
on how well you feature
her extraordinary talents.
Stacy, darling, are you ready
to share the spotlight
with my All Stars?
- Well, you know
what they say, Ru.
Never work with animals,
children, or drag queens.
[all laugh]
- But for you, Mother Ru,
I'll do anything.
- Oh, good.
- Henny.
- All right.
[laughter and applause]
- All right,
ladies and gentlemen.
Start your engines,
and may the best All Star win.
[cheers and applause]
- "Everybody Say Love."
- Oh, my gosh, you can--
do it again.
- All right, girl.
- [laughs]
- She didn't do that, you know,
the white-girl twerk.
When you do this.
- With the shoulders.
- All right, Farrah Moan.
- She was that one white girl
that can twerk at the club.
As team captain,
I just need to make sure
that my team
can come out on top
with lyrics and choreography.
I know I'm going to be stunning
at whatever I do.
We need to shine together
as a group cohesively,
but also make sure
that we shine individual.
And no tears.
- No tears. Hell, no.
- Farrah allegedly has a fire
under her booty to work better,
but just last week,
the bitch could barely dance
to her own fucking number
that she knows all the moves to.
How's she gonna do
a choreographed challenge, girl?
Sabotage.
- Three, two, one, say love.
- Three, two, one.
- Love.
- Oh, my God,
it would be so cute
if we can harmonize
that last note.
- We can add in
a little unh-aiy.
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
[all laugh]
- Rrrrap on, rrrrap on.
- The song that we are assigned
is "Don't Funk It Up."
And I feel good about this team.
- I'm thinking more
inspirational message.
- Right.
- So right here, I've said,
for those of you
who don't know me,
I put the "T" in the LGB.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- Okay.
- Mine's going to be more about
if you do funk it up,
get back up and keep going.
So if you Farrah on your ass,
you just gotta keep going.
- I was just so nervous
that me and Farrah were
going to be in the same group.
I don't know if y'all knew this,
but me and Farrah had a big
falling-out a couple months ago.
- No.
- At one point,
I considered Farrah
to be a close friend.
But she tried to go about
patching up a relationship
between me and another person
in an inappropriate way.
And while I'm at work,
they showed up drunk,
and so I kind of
let her have it,
and the other girl have it
at the same time.
I texted her and she
just didn't respond to me.
So seeing her
walk into this workroom,
I was a little gagged,
because I did cherish
our friendship,
but she kind of
fucked it up a little bit.
- Man.
- She funked it up.
- She funked it.
And bitch,
I was kind of hoping
that you were gonna
vote her off.
I just don't want our drama
to be a distraction for me
during this competition.
- I think that while you guys
are stuck here
in this workroom together,
it's a perfect opportunity
for you to address it.
- I agree. Without
the outside influences.
- Yeah.
- Just me and you, baby.
What's going on?
- I am not trying
to get in the middle
of all of this bullshit.
Girl, figure it out.
Move on.
Sounds like high school
bullshit to me.
I just don't think you should
even worry about it.
- Oh, honey,
I'm not worried about it.
I don't know if "All Stars"
is the place
to be focused
on our unfinished business,
but I hope that we can
kind of talk things out
because I'm sure that
she'll get the chop soon.
- Hi.
- Hello, gentlemen.
- Welcome, everybody.
- This week's main stage
challenge is girl groups.
So now it's time to record
our hit single,
"Everybody Say Love."
- My name is Leland,
and this is Freddy.
And we put these two songs
together.
You're singing along with Lizzo.
Lizzo is on these choruses.
- Yes!
- How fun is that?
- Her lip sync sent me home,
so I feel a little shaded.
But we'll work it out.
- Shredded.
- Hello.
- So as a team, who do you feel
is the strongest singer?
[bell dings]
- There have not been
a lot of good singers
out of the "Drag Race" family.
You know, there's Adore,
she's a good one.
There's Jujubee. I think
she's a really good one.
Me.
- Okay, here we go.
- ♪ Took some time
to love myself ♪
♪ And embrace this melanin ♪
♪ And now I thank God
for the beauty of this skin ♪
- I've never worked with Monique
in terms of a group,
but I do know that Monique
has very grand visions,
but her thoughts are way more
grand than her execution is.
- ♪ 'Cause now that--
'cause now that I've got-- ♪
Oh, crunchy monkey.
Can I just get
that one part out?
It's supposed to go...
♪ 'Cause now that I got-- ♪
- ♪ I got love,
I'm free and deep ♪
- Oh.
- Everybody.
- ♪ 'Cause now that I got love,
I'm free and deep ♪
- ♪ Everybody ♪ Okay.
We've got time for one more.
If you don't nail that,
I'm going to be
personally offended.
[all laugh]
- ♪ Da-da-da ♪
- This is your moment.
- This is what Eminem
was talking about in "8 Mile."
- Okay.
- Here we go.
- ♪ 'Cause now that I got love,
I'm free and deep ♪
- Boom!
[applause]
- Awesome.
- ♪ Ooh ♪
Aah!
- Monét X Change.
- Yes.
I went to school
for opera performance,
and being a musician
and a singer,
I really fucked up last week.
So I definitely feel a lot of
pressure to show that, bitch,
I'm like a fierce vocalist,
girl. Like, get into it.
- ♪ If you cancel again,
I'll call The Vixen ♪
♪ And she'll read that ass
from one to 10 ♪
♪ For a frou-frou recipe
to rise above ♪
♪ It's real simple: self-love ♪
- I think we're working on
like the third "Sister Act"
right now.
[all laugh]
It feels really special.
- Farrah, you ready?
- Okay.
This is my first time ever
actually recording vocals
for a song,
so I'm a little bit nervous.
- Tell me about
your singing experience.
- So I did phone sex
operating for a while,
so right now we're going to
take things really slow, boys.
- Oh, do you wanna unbutton
my blouse?
Maybe I can distract you from
your depressing life, beebee.
- If she can really pull off
sexy, it could be fierce.
If she's not sexy, car fire.
- Here we go.
- ♪ Love, it's crazy, right? ♪
♪ Never, ever had somebody
love me right ♪
♪ Forget, forget,
and hold on tight ♪
♪ And if they can't, then you
say you don't love me anyway ♪
[all laugh]
- I think Farrah is living
her Britney Spears fantasy.
- ♪ Oh ♪
[stifled laughs]
- I'm a little gagged.
- Aow!
- I am obsessed with you.
[all laugh]
- That's a wrap.
- Oh, cool.
- Hi, guys.
- Hi.
It's really important
for me to win the super girl
group challenge
because I was safe last week,
and I feel that
I should have been on top
for once in my life.
- Do you want to do
some scales to warm up?
- I don't want to,
but if I need to, I sure will.
[all laugh]
- Let's just dive into it.
- ♪ For those of you
who don't know me ♪
♪ I put the "T" in the LGB ♪
♪ I'm a woman who does drag ♪
♪ But don't confuse me
with those hags ♪
- Wait a minute,
is she calling me a hag?
Is she calling me a hag?
- ♪ Don't worry about
what you call me ♪
♪ 'Cause I know who I be ♪
- Girl.
We're lucky the show
has "lip sync for your life,"
not sing for your life.
- ♪ Be the best you,
and I'll be ♪
♪ The best that I can be ♪
- Okay.
- Its kind of like a mosquito
that gets in your ear
and goes eeeee.
Eeeeee.
[mosquito buzzes]
Ugh.
- It's not landing quite yet.
- She's not landing
like fresh tilapia yet.
- You said it.
- ♪ Be the best you ♪
♪ And I'll be
the best that I can be ♪
♪ Yes, honey ♪
- Great.
That was the best by far.
- Yes, that was good.
- Okay.
- Miss Valentina, why don't you
tell me about your verse
and what you're saying.
- It's kind of like
very telenovela.
It's about a boy,
and it's like saying,
"I'm vulnerably giving you
my heart,
I'm giving you my coochie-coo."
- What did you call it again?
- My coochie-coo.
- Okay.
- So don't fuck it up,
because it's a precious thing,
and you want to take care of it.
[all laugh]
- I'm excited to hear that.
- ♪ Yo te amo a ti, mi amor,
so much I want to die ♪
♪ Eres mi amor,
y te regalo mi coochie-coo ♪
- I don't know
what the fuck she's saying,
but, girl, I am living.
- ♪ When loving you, baby,
don't make me go crazy ♪
♪ 'Cause I am not the first ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Get out!
- Aah!
- Oh, yeah,
we're winning this one.
- Girl.
[all laugh]
- I knew what I was picking,
bitch.
- Okay, Manila, tell me about
your singing experience.
- I love to sing.
I like to make records
and I like to make music videos.
I do this a lot.
I have many songs.
And I perform all the time,
so this should be easy for me.
- Let's get into it.
- ♪ Give it everything you got ♪
♪ You rock
when things go wrong ♪
♪ Might not go the way I want ♪
♪ [mumbles] no Luzon ♪
- ♪ If you fail, girl,
so what? ♪
♪ So you fail, get back up ♪
- Oh, God, my sister Manila.
[mocking] ♪ If you fail,
you fail, uh ♪
- ♪ If you're in love ♪
What?
- I feel like you've got
a good instrument,
but now you just
have to sell me on it.
- Okay, all right, so I'll give
it a little bit more Jackson.
- Here we go.
- ♪ Give it everything you got ♪
♪ You rock
when things go wrong ♪
♪ Might not go
the way you want ♪
♪ Uh, blblblblblblbl ♪
- Yeah, I think you need to
just push harder on personality.
- ♪ If you fail, girl,
so what ♪
♪ If you fall, girl-- ♪
♪ Gotta try, try, try again ♪
- On a scale from 1 to 10--
- I'm a 4 1/2.
- I was going to say 3,
3 1/2.
- Oh, girl.
- Oh.
- I'm a little worried
because when it comes
to team challenges,
you're only as strong
as your weakest link.
- I think that's a wrap.
- ♪ Everybody say love ♪
- Who's that?
- Yes!
Bitch, girl, how are you?
- What's going on, Henny?
- Hello, darling.
Ready to do some splits
and stuff?
[all laugh]
- Yeah, some death drops?
- It's time to rehearse
the choreography
for our super girl
group performance
featuring the one,
the only Henny.
Stacy Layne Matthews.
- So have you guys been
working on choreography?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- We have. We know
that you are the feature,
so we want to make you
the most beautiful Beyoncé
that works like Kelly.
[all laugh]
You know what I mean?
- Okay, honey.
The judges are looking for
how well the group
incorporates me into the number.
Wait, I'm not doing the splits.
Honey, I'm not doing
a death drop
because that would be the end
of Stacy Layne Matthews, honey.
And I promise you, this studio
would have a basement.
- [laughs]
- So you won't turn around
until the song goes
♪ Oh, honey ♪
- Where do I start?
- You're gonna start
right here, sis.
'Cause we want you
to have a good pooch.
As team captain, I have
to come up with choreography.
Then I have to
teach the choreography.
We have to perfect
the choreography
and then perform
the choreography.
So the pressure,
oh, my gosh, I feel it.
♪ Love ♪
You step out. ♪ Love ♪
- So my first one
I'm stepping out.
- You step back
and to your spot.
One, two, ready, go.
- I still go this way?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- So you just bum-ta-da-bum,
bum-ta-da-bum.
One, two, three, bang.
- Pressure, honey.
- When I thought girl group,
I thought
I was going to be doing
some fun little Britney-isms,
some hair flips.
I didn't really think
we were going to be all,
you know, getting down.
[laughs]
- Du-du-du-du-du-du-du.
I'm here...
da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
- See, I end up like all the way
over here with that.
- But you can't go
too far, my love.
Because see I was here,
and I just go.
It's all in the movement.
You don't have to go.
- Take smaller steps.
- Yeah, smaller steps
so you don't travel as far,
you see what I'm saying?
- My spot's already
right here already.
- So then fake it
in that one spot.
Miss Farrah is plucking
my last nerve, America.
Okay, so let's just say
sorry, sorry, sorry,
for the sake of time.
We're trying
to do a whole lot.
- Yeah.
- Whoo, honey.
Too many things.
- I think Monique
kind of receives ideas
and just moves on.
She doesn't give people
time to process things.
Well, your brain
has to process shit, girl.
- Say love, say love.
Farrah, Farrah, come over here.
- Oh. So we're not doing
the leg kick anymore.
- No, because we need
to get you on this side.
- Okay.
The choreography
is coming off super messy.
I keep wanting
to like simplify it,
and I'm kind of
getting shut down.
But I will just shut up
and let Monique do it,
and if this all
crashes and burns,
she's the team captain,
and I guess she can take,
you know, the fall.
- You look stressed.
- I am a little bit stressed
with this.
- We'll work it out.
- No stress.
- ♪ Don't funk it up ♪
- Hello.
- Hey.
- Henny!
- Being on stage
is what I do best,
and I need to show
these other bitches
what real talent is about.
- Well, let's see what
we're working with, honey.
- I'm what, here?
- No, you are...
you are here.
Here, Manila, and then Henny.
- No, but like
we're making a "V", right?
- Let's just walk
to our places first
before we even start
doing the choreography.
- Three, two, one.
- ♪ Don't funk it up ♪
♪ Don't funk it up ♪
♪ If you're going to funk it ♪
- Oh, honey.
- And da-da-da.
- Start with the right foot?
- Yes.
- So once we get
to the first position,
then we start doing our...
No, no, no.
The march thing.
So we can march here,
turn, get back to your spot.
- I think we should
start it off here.
- Who's team leader?
- Her.
- Oh, okay.
- Why don't we just do do-do-do?
- What if the simple idea is
♪ If you want to funk it,
don't funk it up ♪
- No, because
we should be in a square.
- Basically there was
17 cooks in the kitchen.
All the servers done quit,
honey.
I was like, girl,
who's cooking this cake, honey?
Chaos, honey, chaos.
- So if we're getting there
really early,
then we need to figure out
something to do.
- That's why I didn't like
the marching idea.
- I'm trying to like
sift through all this
without seeming like a dictator.
- Why don't we just do
do-do-do-do?
- Deep breaths.
- ♪ Ahh ♪
- Yes.
♪ God ♪
- ♪ Don't funk me up ♪
Today we're getting ready
for our super girl
group performance.
And I'm feeling my oats, wheats,
grains, thins, and oatmeal.
One, two, three.
- Oh!
- [laughs]
- That is not good, girl.
- No.
- Today's look giving you
cocktails in Palm Springs.
- We need to get you
some human hair wigs
so you can whip it around
for real.
- Yeah.
My girl group character
is kind of based off Aaliyah
for a little bit.
So I'm really inspired
by Aaliyah's look
from "Dust Yourself Off."
But I think it'll be good
because--
- Team leader.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Are you feeling your oats
over here?
- Yeah. I'm really excited
for our, like, girls
to get out there
and do what it is that we do.
You know what I mean?
Love her. She, uh--
- Uh-uh, bitch, don't lie to me.
- No, no, no, I didn't.
She triggers me,
but she didn't--
♪ Uh... ♪
- Just be honest.
- I would say, yeah,
but she is fighting.
She's doing it.
- It's clear that Farrah's
teammates think that she
is probably going
to fuck this up for them.
And in case she gets sent home,
I just want to make sure
that I did my part
in terms of reaching out to her
and trying to squash this drama
so that I can have closure.
- You getting ready already?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, do your makeup
and get ready, sweetie,
'cause according to your team,
you're the weakest link.
- Oh!
- Oh, shit.
- Oh, here we go.
- Listen, I'm like way less
concerned about everybody else.
Like, you don't see me,
like, going around
and trying to get in everybody's
head and focusing on me.
If my team thinks
that I'm the weakest link,
then obviously I need to be
doing exactly what I'm doing
and getting centered, balanced,
and my makeup done.
And so maybe
you should do the same.
Because I feel like
only insecure people,
like, go around and try
and do what you're doing.
- Oh, sweetie, I'm very secure.
Are you secure?
- Okay. It is taking everything
in my power right now
not to completely go
the fuck off on this bitch.
- Clearly you don't really
care about our friendship
or anything that we had.
- [sighs]
- So I was just trying to--
- Gia, I'm trying to get ready.
- Okay.
- I don't have time
for your drama.
I feel like you're
not coming over here
as a friend right now.
I feel like
you're coming over here
trying to stir the fucking pot,
and it's like--
- Well, honey, coming up
to my job drunk...
- Oh, here we go.
- ...wasn't really being
a friend, either, babe.
And when I texted you
months ago
and you didn't answer me,
that didn't really show me
that you cared, either.
- Just in her tone of voice
I can tell that she is trying
to get under my skin
and psych me out, because
I guess she sees me as a threat.
But now she's trying
to backpedal
and say that this is
about our previous drama
that happened
like six months ago.
And it's like Gia,
stop trying to make this
about something that literally
isn't even a thing.
Honestly, that night
has been nothing in my life
since that night.
None of that was public.
And I don't really understand
the whole point
of bringing this in
in the workroom
while we're getting ready.
It seems opportunistic of you.
- Call it what you want.
It is what it is.
- Opportunistic.
- Sure. Honey, I'm here
for an opportunity
just like you are.
- Yeah, well, some of us
don't have to, you know,
force storylines to get airtime.
- [laughs]
Cutthroat Farrah.
- I was just trying to see,
in case today's your last day
here in the competition,
how you feel about
our friendship and our past.
- You are taking up
my time right now,
and I don't have time for it.
- Because you can't multitask.
- Sure, Gia, whatever
you want me to fucking say.
- Can you not bully my teammate?
- I'm not bullying her.
- I'm saying, but she
just asked you to step away.
- Literally, like,
just please get out of my face.
- I'm not bullying her.
- Seriously, sister.
She just said
she wants to get ready.
- Gia, you know you're over here
trying to stir shit up,
so, like, why don't you
go to your station
and put your makeup on, girl?
- Ooh, bitch, girl.
Farrah's clapping back.
She's like leave me alone.
She gonna get to cracking
her neck.
I'm like, yes, Farrah,
let that bitch know.
Leave you alone, girl.
Bye.
- Don't be so sensitive.
- Sis, no one
was being sensitive.
You literally went over there,
and you was trying
to gas her up.
Now I catch your game,
and you're trying
in get my teammate's head.
No, ma'am.
If that was your girl
and you was really concerned
about that friendship,
why didn't you address that
day one?
- Because it's taken a while
for things to boil up.
- No, you--
No, you found an opportunity.
- I like Gia, and I see
some of myself in her.
But, girl, don't pick on
the weakest one.
If you go to prison,
on the first day,
you don't shank the weakest one.
You have to shank the biggest
guy to show your dominance.
That just makes you
look like a bully.
Trust me, I tried that
on my season.
It doesn't work out.
- Just in case
it's her last time here,
I wanted to make sure--
- Oh, my gosh, sis!
That is fake-as-fuck.com.
- Call me what you want.
- America,
Gia is fake as fuck.
- Thank you, Monique,
for sticking up for me.
- Farrah, I hope
that this, like,
lights a fire under your ass.
- Baby, this is a competition.
If you can't take the pressure
of your other competitors,
then you don't deserve
to be here.
Get into it or get out.
[RuPaul laughs]
- ♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
- Walk?
- ♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
♪ Cover girl ♪
- And what?
[applause]
- Welcome to the main stage of
"RuPaul's Drag Race All Stars."
Michelle Visage, are you live
or lip syncing tonight?
- You will never know
because I have the best
lip sync in the game. [pop]
- [laughs]
And the hilarious
Ross Mathews.
Now, I've always wondered,
are you related
to Stacy Layne Matthews?
- She's my sister.
- Really?
- She's my daughter.
- What?
- She's my sister
and my daughter!
[all laugh]
- Sorry I asked.
The incredible Ciara.
Now, are you ready
to see my girls' goodies?
- I want to see
all of the goodies.
[all laugh]
- And Kacey Musgraves,
welcome to my house.
- Giddy up, y'all,
I'm moving in.
- [laughs]
This week, we challenged
our All Stars
to funk it up
in a girl group collaboration
with the Stacy Layne Matthews.
And now they're ready
to let us have it, Henny.
Ladies and gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best All Star win.
First up the world debut
of "Don't Funk It Up, Henny."
[all laugh]
- ♪ Don't funk it up ♪
♪ If you're gonna funk it,
don't funk it up ♪
♪ Don't funk it up ♪
♪ If you're gonna
funk it up ♪
♪ Now here I come,
ooh, henny ♪
♪ Don't funk it up, whoo ♪
♪ If you're gonna funk it ♪
♪ Don't funk it up ♪
♪ If you're gonna funk it,
whoo, whoo ♪
- ♪ For those of you
who don't know me ♪
♪ I put the "T" in the LGB ♪
♪ Don't worry about
what you call me ♪
♪ 'Cause I know who I be ♪
♪ I'm a woman who does drag ♪
♪ But don't confuse me
with those hags ♪
♪ Be the best you and I'll be
the best that I can be ♪
♪ Yes, sir ♪
- ♪ This is what get,
you're feeling down and low ♪
♪ In times like this,
you gotta let it go ♪
♪ Got you all uptight
with the same damn fight ♪
♪ Just know everything's
gonna be all right ♪
♪ And you can't always
count on your friends ♪
♪ If it's not right there
with them ♪
♪ Oh, people be strong,
get your life, go on ♪
♪ Don't let Henny dim your
light, shine, stay bright ♪
- ♪ Don't funk it up ♪
♪ If you're gonna funk it ♪
- ♪ Well, here I come, ooh ♪
♪ Don't funk it up ♪
♪ If you're gonna funk it ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Give it
everything you've got ♪
♪ You rock
when things go wrong ♪
♪ Might not go
the way you want ♪
♪ Take it from me,
my name is Luzon ♪
♪ If you fail, so what? ♪
♪ If you fail, get back up ♪
♪ Gotta try, try, try again ♪
- ♪ Clap back,
time to say no more ♪
♪ Hear the people's voice
that you can't ignore ♪
♪ We're here to fight
for our equal rights ♪
♪ Girl, nothing new,
gotta tell the truth ♪
♪ No time for hate,
so let's go, uh ♪
♪ They say shut,
tell them no, huh ♪
♪ Where's the love? ♪
♪ Standing up,
it's time to fight ♪
♪ Inside, get high, spread
the love, cut the strife ♪
- ♪ Love you so much, mi amor,
so much I want to die ♪
♪ If you were
to hurt me, baby ♪
♪ I'm leaving tonight ♪
♪ Eres mi amor,
y te regalo mi coochie-coo ♪
♪ When loving you, baby,
no, let us go crazy ♪
♪ Because I am not the first ♪
- ♪ Funk it up ♪
- ♪ Don't funk it up ♪
♪ If you're gonna funk it ♪
♪ Don't funk it up ♪
♪ Whoo, don't funk it up ♪
♪ If you're gonna funk it,
don't funk it up ♪
♪ Don't funk it up ♪
♪ If you're gonna funk it ♪
♪ Whoo, whoo, wow ♪
♪ Don't funk it up ♪
[applause]
- I love it.
- Up next, the world debut
of "Everybody Say Love, Henny."
- ♪ Love, love, love ♪
♪ Oh, Henny ♪
♪ Everybody say love ♪
♪ Everybody ♪
♪ Say love, say love ♪
♪ Legs that you know me for ♪
♪ And believe there's more
walking through that door ♪
♪ I'm here, yes, I know that ♪
♪ And I'm hung like
a mother-tuckin' baseball bat ♪
♪ Strutting all night,
getting it all tight ♪
♪ What the hell
is an appetite? ♪
♪ Fashion love is what I crave ♪
♪ Bitch, I'm here,
yes, I'm brave ♪
- ♪ Took some time
to love myself ♪
♪ And embrace this melanin ♪
♪ And now I'm paying comps
about the beauty of my skin ♪
♪ No longer stand for lies
and accusations ♪
♪ 'Cause now that I got love,
I'm free inside ♪
- The other team
is sh-sh-sh-shaky.
They're all just
kind of bopping around,
but, God,
Farrah just cannot keep up.
- ♪ Say love ♪
- ♪ Love is crazy, right? ♪
♪ Never ever had somebody
love me right ♪
♪ With love,
you always have to fight ♪
♪ Forget, forget,
and hold on tight ♪
♪ You gotta be wise
to compromise ♪
♪ Sometimes you pay
the ultimate price ♪
♪ And if they can't,
then you say ♪
♪ You don't love me anyway ♪
- ♪ What's the T,
you're coming over tonight ♪
♪ So we can cuddle, chill,
start a pillow fight ♪
♪ If you cancel again,
I'll call The Vixen ♪
♪ And she'll read that ass
from one to 10 ♪
♪ You're tired,
you're fired, expired ♪
♪ If you text me,
you're blocked, sire ♪
♪ For a foolproof recipe
to rise above ♪
♪ It's real simple: self-love ♪
- ♪ Everybody say love ♪
♪ Everybody ♪
♪ Everybody say love ♪
♪ Say love, say love ♪
- Love.
[laughter and applause]
- So good.
♪ She's a super queen,
super queen ♪
- The category is
eleguance after dark.
[Michelle laughs]
- First up, Gia Gunn.
Her colors are blush,
but she ain't bashful.
- Mm-mm.
- I've heard of two in the pink,
but two pinks on one dress,
that's new.
[all laugh]
- I am serving you cherry pie
on a platter,
and I just feel like
a Japanese Barbie doll.
- Serving face and tail.
[all laugh]
Up next, Latrice Royale.
Black gold, serving T.
- She's in mourning
with morning wood.
[all laugh]
- Baby, I'm serving
old Hollywood glam,
feeling my eleguance, eleganza,
extravaganza, realness.
- Ciara, see, that's
some goodies right there.
- Yes, honey.
- That's some good goodies.
[all laugh]
- Manila Luzon.
- 50 shades of gay.
[Ciara laughs]
- I'm a silver fox.
I'm an old bitch
and I'm coming here to show you
how you do drag, girl.
- Are those stones
in your armpits,
or are you just happy to see me?
[RuPaul laughs]
- You know, her gray is showing.
She needs Just For Men.
- Yeah.
- Or, you know, Just For Queens.
- That lean back is mean.
- Trinity The Tuck.
[Michelle laughs]
- If she was in Nashville,
they'd call her Canya Tucker.
[RuPaul laughs]
- My dress
is cut out for you, bitch.
I am feeling the fantasy,
and you can't tell me
I am not real, bitch.
- They call me Rusty.
Rusty Nail.
[Ross laughs]
- Up next, Valentina.
Hy...drangea.
[all laugh]
- That's a flower
I wouldn't mind plucking.
- Oh, Ross.
- Curses, I've been soiled.
[all laugh]
- I'm giving you
a Mexican in Paris.
You know in your heart
that it is not
a flaw in sight.
- She's blossoming.
- She certainly is.
- You know how you plow
a garden?
- No, how do you plow a garden?
- With a hoe.
[all laugh]
- Naomi Smalls.
- Everyone, let's just take
a moment to reflect.
[all laugh]
- This is Naomi Smalls
serving you very VIP
heavy metal reflective.
- Now I know where my car
sunscreens went.
- Naomi, can you just
stand still for a second?
I'm trying to check my hair.
[Ciara laughs]
- Monique Heart.
Look at those violet tchotchkes.
[Ross laughs]
- I am serving high-fashion,
regal glamour.
And-- [gasps]
- Oh.
- It's milking time.
[all laugh]
- I feel great, honey.
I feel expensive.
I'm giving it.
- Like I've always said,
who needs a top?
[RuPaul laughs]
Michelle: Well...
[Ross laughs]
- Farrah Moan.
- Those earrings are lit.
- It took
all of Bea Arthur's wigs
to make that boa.
[all laugh]
- She's slinky.
Good for a girl and a boy.
- Everyone loves a slinky.
- I am feeling
absolutely gorgeous.
I have a giant
.5-ply ostrich boa.
My hair is slayed.
And I'm feeling like
a million bucks.
- She's from Vegas.
Clearly she plays the slits.
I mean slots.
- Monét X Change.
She is serving
Sheryl Lee Ralph eleganza.
- Yes!
- I've got this horrible knot
in my right shoulder.
- Oh, no.
[all laugh]
- I feel royal,
I feel elegant,
and I feel that I'm giving
the judges fashion, girl.
And I smell good, too.
- I don't bring my dress
to the red carpet.
I bring the red carpet
on my dress.
- You just wear it.
- She's from the hood,
the Little Red Riding hood.
♪ She's a super queen ♪
- Welcome, All Stars.
Now based on
your Henny performances
and your elaguant
runway presentations,
I've made some decisions.
Now, when I call your name,
please step forward.
Valentina.
Monét X Change.
Naomi Smalls.
You are the tops of the week.
[cheers and applause]
Bet you don't hear that
often, do you?
Manila Luzon.
Monique Heart.
Farrah Moan.
You ladies are the bottoms
of the week.
Latrice Royale.
Gia Gunn.
Trintity The Tuck.
You are safe.
Please step
to the back of the stage.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques,
starting with Manila Luzon.
That...getup.
- Get into the armpits.
- Did you stone those armpits?
[all laugh]
- On the runway,
you looked stunning.
This is what I expect,
and nothing less.
But when it came
to your performance,
almost everything on you
was like little for you.
It was like small hair,
you had these
little wedgie shoes on,
that I was like, Manila?
In a wedge?
And I almost felt you
kind of not knowing the words.
You're a performer.
That's what you do.
So I want to see that in you,
and that's what I expect.
- The performance I honestly
have a giant question mark by,
because I don't feel like
your intentions were super clear
as to what you were
trying to get across.
- Okay.
- I can't pinpoint what it was.
And maybe it's just that
all the other queens
in your group were so good.
- It really, really breaks my
heart that I came all this way
and not just slay it
like I know I can.
- So if you look in that mirror,
if you're lucky enough
to survive, you know what to do.
- Up next, Valentina.
- Hola, Valentina.
- Hola, mi amor.
- Tonight on the runway
is very pretty,
and your performance,
I loved most of all
the nod to Selena, obviously.
You had some Spanish
in your verse, which was lovely.
It was fun, it was catchy,
and it was you.
- Valentina, you gave me
Valentino vibes.
That's how I look at your dress.
I loved the energy,
and I loved
when you hit the high note.
Like, there was something
kind of like "I Love Lucy"
about that ending.
You brought it.
- There's something very special
about you, Valentina.
We saw it in your first season,
and we are seeing it again
here in "All Stars."
- Up next, Naomi Smalls.
- You are a great songwriter.
- Thank you.
- You are.
Your verse
really stood out to me.
- You were one of the few
that actually just slayed
the hell out of your game.
Loved what you were wearing.
It was sassy,
it was fashion, it was hot.
- I actually could see myself
rocking it on the stage.
I was like, I gotta figure out
who made that.
It was just lit in all ways.
And you committed
and you were consistent
from the performance
to the runway.
- I printed out your words
to "1, 2 Step"
so all my girlfriends
in sixth grade,
we could memorize
all the lyrics.
So this is fucking crazy.
- Oh, thank you so much.
- Up next, Monique Heart.
- Hello, hello.
- I loved
the kind of nod to TLC
you were giving us
with your look.
- I was doing Aaliyah.
- Okay, Aaliyah.
I just felt like it was
full nineties
girl group moment.
- Stunning.
- But it got a little bit messy.
- In a performance like that,
precision is key.
Right? The words have
to be precise.
The movements
have to be precise.
And it just was a little messy.
- I would say the coat
I can say was messy,
but I was sweating.
I'm a dude
trying to take it off.
It got stuck.
Get it?
- Sometimes that happens,
but I will say,
when the lights are on, as
performers and just for myself,
we can't even make
an excuse for it.
We just have to like be in
that moment and commit to it.
And that's just the ownership
we have to have.
- Up next, Farrah Moan.
- Everything about your look
is perfection.
Like, everything works
with each other.
It complements each other.
Everything is just right.
- So many women would kill
to look like that.
- Oh, stop.
- But the performance was,
sorry, just like
a little bit white bread.
- I think this is the first time
I've really seen you dance,
and the whitest dancer
I've ever seen in my life
is the nice way to put it.
- Oh.
- You are serving me
vegan dessert.
Like they bring it to the table,
and it looks really good.
And it tastes really good, too.
- But it's not as fulfilling
as you want it to be.
You have it.
We're just seeing you
struggle to find it.
- Up next, Monét X Change.
- Tonight, you were my favorite
performer of all.
You're actually
a really good rapper.
- Thank you.
- You were in the moment.
You were grounded.
- I really enjoyed
the performance, too.
It was another memorable moment
for me for tonight as well.
- But now let's talk about
this runway look.
I love it.
- I was thinking, damn, girl.
- [laughs]
- This is a look that
you never would have served us
on Season 10,
and look at you now.
It's a joy to watch you
really hone your skills.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
And I've made some decisions.
- Monét X Change.
Valentina.
Con-drag-ulations.
You are the top two All Stars
of the week.
[applause]
You've each won a $2,500
gift card from arda wigs,
plus $1,000 gift card
from Coolhaus Ice Cream.
Naomi Smalls, you are safe.
Manila Luzon,
You are safe.
- Thank you.
- That means Farrah Moan
and Monique Heart,
you are in the bottom two.
Monét, Valentina,
each of you needs to decide
which of the bottom queens
you'll eliminate
if you win the lip sync.
So while you queens deliberate
in the workroom,
the judges and I
will toss Ross's salad.
Ladies,
you may leave the stage.
- We have a winner!
- ♪ Dee dee dee dee ♪
- Oh.
- Congrats, mi vida.
- Congrats to you, too.
- I've now won
my first challenge.
It's been an honor.
[applause]
Thank you, thank you.
But when you're in
this position,
it makes you feel
all these feelings
'cause you don't want
to have to send somebody home.
I don't want to have to be like,
all right, I won, bitch, bye.
No.
- Congratulations, guys.
- Yes.
- Cheers.
- Thank you guys so much.
- My first challenge win
in "Drag Race" history, girls.
[cheering]
I never won any in my season.
- But you're a winner, baby.
- Yay!
- No, you're top two.
- No, bitch,
I won a cash prize. I won.
- Oh.
- When can I plead my case,
because I need to stay,
so at what point
does that happen?
Can I plead my case with
one of y'all, because I cannot.
America, I am so gooped
right now.
Like how does a strong,
beautiful,
talented,
fabulous queen like me,
that was in the top last week,
be in the bottom?
Was I really that bad?
Can we talk?
- I think we should
definitely talk.
I would love
that opportunity.
- But not right now?
- Um, I don't know.
I just wanted to share something
with you guys.
- Oh, my God, yes.
- Okay.
- I feel so many emotions
right now.
I should be celebrating,
but at the same time,
I feel like, oh, my goodness,
I have to focus on the lip sync.
Valentina, you are not known
for knowing the words.
- Girl, Valentina is a diva.
She seriously thinks that she
is like this telenovela star.
[Spanish guitar plays,
applause]
- It's just so hard, girls.
- Ugh.
Are y'all gonna talk
to each other, or what?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Y'all got
about 10 minutes, bitch.
- The biggest issue
with being in the bottom
is the fact that
you can't fight for you.
You're in the ocean.
You can't swim.
You're by the boat,
and you're waiting for them
to throw you a lifeline.
That is the most
unsettling thing
about this whole competition.
I cannot go home.
Like, I cannot.
I felt like to come back
and come back as strong
as I came day one in the door,
I think that speaks volumes.
It was just messy
because of a coat.
Fuck.
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
- If you can go back,
I wouldn't have worn the coat,
but I was trying to give homage.
- Monique is very defensive,
but with her Aaliyah outfit,
the fit of that pant
is not okay.
That is so disrespectful
to Aaliyah.
How dare you.
I have to make a decision.
- You do.
- And ultimately, someone's
heart is going to be broken.
- Very bad.
I don't want you to pick me,
but if you do, I would
have to swallow the bullet,
and it's not personal.
It's just what the game
has called for.
Ouch.
- I really am gagged
that you're in the bottom,
because I felt like
our team as a whole--
- Did so well.
- I feel like
we were all so strong,
and that you really went
balls to the wall.
- Yeah.
- Hold on. I just want to say
something to them real fast.
Is that rude
for me to interrupt?
I'm feeling
a little bit responsible
for the way that things
played out today,
and I just don't want that
weighing on my shoulder
if she does get eliminated.
- I'm kind of like
really holding in
a lot of my emotions right now.
- Ladies,
I don't want to interrupt,
but I just want
to say something real fast.
Is that okay?
- This is Farrah's time.
- Yeah.
Real fast, because
you were both on your team--
on each other's team.
I do sincerely want to apologize
to both of you
if I created any type of stir-up
in anyone's emotions
or anything like that.
My intentions were not to throw
you off or throw your group off.
- Gia, this is literally
not the time
for your fake apology
to make yourself feel better.
God, I can't stand her.
- Gia Gunn can't stop talking.
Look at her.
She's over there like buying up
Miss Farrah's time.
- I would have put Gia
in the bottom.
- Would you have?
- Just for her attitude.
Girl, it's time for her to go.
- You know that
I treasure our friendship
and regardless
after what happens today,
I would really like for us
to work on our friendship,
and that's all
that I wanted to say.
I don't want to take
any more of your time, okay?
Thank you.
- Girl, here she comes.
Don't say nothing.
- What did you
go over there for?
- I know. What'd you say?
- I just wanted to tell them--
- Poke the bear.
- Huh?
- Poke the little Care Bear.
- No, no, no, no.
I feel like when
you make a mistake in life,
it's okay to apologize and
let people know how you feel,
in case this is the last time
that I do get to talk to her
before elimination.
That you know what, girl?
I'm sorry if I fucked
y'all's juj up.
- Gia is here
stirring the pot again.
Is that all she does?
'Cause if that was a talent,
girl, you win.
- Girl, I'm just like, what?
You know, I thought
they were gonna get it.
I thought
they were gonna like it.
I thought all the boxes
were checked.
I cannot go home.
Don't send me home.
I don't want to go home.
I have worked too hard
to get back.
It took too much to bounce back.
- Yeah, yeah.
- But I'm not done at all.
- Yeah.
- Miss Monét, that's my sis.
And I hope she would save me.
That's my mindset,
that is my game plan,
that's where I'm at.
- I love you.
- You know I love you, too,
mama.
Now I'm going to go
and change for this lip sync.
- Yeah, I need you to win.
- [laughs]
- Hey, baby.
- Hi.
- I'm sorry that
you're in the bottom.
I could only imagine
how much you're feeling.
- Honestly, it really sucks,
Valentina,
because I came here
to prove something to myself.
And I think you know
deep down in your heart
that I am a bigger star
than going home right now.
- But if I was to eliminate you,
what would that do
to everything that we've built?
We've worked so hard
on this relationship, Valentina.
It's like we've finally got
to such a good place.
And, I mean,
it would be heartbreaking.
I want this
more than I've wanted anything
in my whole life.
If I go home tonight,
it's going to take me a really
long time to get over it.
- I just fixed my relationship
with Farrah.
She apologized
about all the stuff
that happened at the reunion,
and we were able
to move forward.
And now we're excited
to be here together.
So I don't really want
to go there and do that to her.
- I love you so much, Valentina.
- I love you, too.
I really do, okay?
- I can't wait
to watch your lip sync.
Don't let the stress
of this decision
affect your moment right now,
because, Valentina,
this is exactly
what you came here to do.
[laughs]
- Thanks, mi amor.
- Sending someone home
is harder than
I thought it would be.
My Miss Congeniality
crown, girl,
is gonna be a little tarnished.
It's gonna be a little tainted
because someone's dreams
are on a lipstick
underneath my sweaty sock boob.
That ain't congenial.
- This decision sets the tone
about who I am
and what I'm here to do.
There's going to be
so many opinions
about why I decided that person.
Are you threatened?
Are you jealous?
Or are you mean?
Are you empty?
Their entire future
is in your hand,
and it's up to you
to cut it short.
To go, whoosh.
Bye, girl.
Adiós, mi amor.
But that's the game.
- Welcome back, ladies.
Two top All Stars
stand before me.
Prior to tonight,
you were asked to prepare
a lip sync performance
of "Into You" by Ariana Grande.
Ladies, this is your chance
to impress me,
win $10,000,
and earn the power
to give one of the bottom queens
the chop.
The time has come...
[thunder]
for you to lip sync...
[echoing] for your legacy.
- I now have the opportunity
to completely redeem myself
with an Ariana Grande song.
And if I fuck this one again,
it's over, girl.
- Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
[music plays]
♪ I'm so into you,
I can barely breathe ♪
♪ And all I wanna do
is to fall in deep ♪
♪ But close ain't close enough ♪
♪ Till we cross the line ♪
♪ So name a game to play ♪
♪ And I'll roll the dice ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Oh, baby,
look what you started ♪
♪ The temperature's rising
in here ♪
♪ Is this gonna happen? ♪
♪ Been waiting and waiting
for you to make a move ♪
♪ Before I make a move ♪
♪ So, baby, come light me up
and, baby, I'll let you on it ♪
♪ A little bit dangerous ♪
♪ But, baby,
that's how I want it ♪
♪ A little less conversation ♪
♪ And a little more
touch my body ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm so into you,
into you, into you ♪
♪ Tell me what
you came here for ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't,
I can't wait no more ♪
♪ I'm on the edge
with no control ♪
♪ And I need,
I need you to know ♪
♪ You to know, oh ♪
- Yes!
- Oh, my God!
These bitches
are turning it out, girl.
- Come on, bitch.
[cheers]
- Go, bitch!
- ♪ A little less conversation ♪
♪ And a little more
touch my body ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm so into you,
into you, into you ♪
♪ Got everyone watching us ♪
♪ So, baby,
let's keep it secret ♪
♪ A little bit scandalous ♪
♪ But, baby,
don't let them see it ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm so into you,
into you, into you ♪
[laughter and applause]
- Oh, bitch!
- Yay!
- Wow, that was tough.
- Ladies, I've made my decision.
- Valentina.
You're a winner, baby.
[applause]
- To win this lip sync
is a big triumph
for me in my life.
This moment puts
the proof in the pudding
that I am a winner.
- Con-drag-ulations.
You've earned a cash tip
of $10,000.
- Thank you so much.
[applause]
- Monét, you are safe.
You may join the other girls.
[applause]
- Ciara, I love you.
- [laughs] Thank you.
- Will the bottom two queens
please step forward.
Valentina, with great power
comes great responsibility.
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
- I made this decision
confidently tonight,
but with a broken heart
strictly because
the person I'm eliminating
had the opportunity
to prove themselves,
and it simply wasn't enough.
And I hope
this is not the end of us...
But I chose...
Farrah Moan.
Farrah, I'm so sorry,
mi amor.
- It's okay, baby.
You don't love me.
[laughs]
- I do.
- I'm just kidding, baby.
- Farrah Moan, as it is written,
so it shall be done.
You are and will always be
an All Star.
- Thank you so much, Ru,
for this opportunity,
and I'll never forget it.
- Now sashay away.
[applause]
- I love you.
- You actually don't love me.
Bye, guys.
I really didn't think
that Valentina
was going to send me home.
This competition
meant so much to me.
And I really wanted
to prove to myself
that I could do it,
and I'm so disappointed
in myself.
But at the end of the day--
fuck--
don't let anybody
tell you ever
that you're not worth it.
Fuck!
Con-drag-ulations, All Stars.
And remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an amen up in here?
- Amen.
- All right.
Now let the music play.
[music plays]
- ♪ I'm telling the truth now ♪
♪ We're all born naked
and the rest is drag ♪
♪ Who, who ♪
♪ Who do you think you ♪
♪ We're all born naked
and the rest is drag ♪
- Next time on "All Stars..."
For the first time
in "Drag Race" herstory,
we are playing
the Snatch Game of Love.
[cheers and applause]
- Girl, I already got
my outfit planned.
- Well, I already have my outfit
and my hair out,
so, honey, this is
the winner right here.
I mean,
of course I have backup,
but I'd rather do
what I wanna do.
- Well, what you wanna do
is not necessarily
what you're gonna do.
- Let's meet our snatchelors,
Gus Kenworthy
and Keiynan Lonsdale.
- Where's the strangest place
you've ever been naked?
- We back in Season 4
with the "Romper Room" fuckery.
- [laughs]
- We know who is going home.
- But this might be
the chance to get off
one of the strongest competitors
in "Drag Race" herstory.
- Alert, alert, alert, alert.