Previously on Face Off...
The artists competed for
a pirate treasure of their own.
$5,000.
Everybody wants to win
that booty.
Sarah's inventive sea urchin
pirate won her the prize.
- Oh, God.
- Ohh! - Nice.
But CC fell short
and was sent home.
Now ten artists remain.
And tonight,
they'll face a challenge
like never before.
Oh.
If we don't get this mold out,
we'll be totally screwed.
There is no way that
this is gonna get done.
I do think I need
to prove myself.
What the fuck?
Something bad has happened.
There's a lot of blood.
On stage, the makeups
are put to an unexpected test
in an acrobatic dance routine.
It was quite stunning.
I see what you guys
were going for-- Huge mistake.
This could go horribly wrong.
In the end, only one
will win the opportunity
to be a guest lecturer
at Make Up For Ever's academies
in New York and Paris,
a new 2012 Toyota Prius V,
and $100,000.
And for the first time ever,
America,
your voice will be heard
in selecting the winner.
Only one will win Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
I can't believe CC's gone.
It's a little weird that she
wasn't here this morning.
CC will definitely be missed.
There is going to be
an empty bed in our room
and we're going
to have to look at it
every single day
and be reminded
that every challenge could be
the last challenge.
At the end of the day,
they were right.
I guess they could have done
more with the jewels.
Jason and I were both
in the bottom last challenge.
I do think I need
to prove myself.
and we have no idea
where we're going.
Oh, my goodness.
And then we see
this beautiful temple.
Welcome to the Thien Hau
temple in Chinatown.
People come here from all over
the country to celebrate
the Chinese new year
with firecrackers, music,
and my personal favorite,
the amazing Chinese dragon
and lion dancers.
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah!
- We got a show.
- Oh, sweet.
The dragon is cool.
But at this point, okay,
well, that's a giant puppet.
Like, what does that have
to do with anything
that we're gonna do?
All right, guys, so working
together in teams of two.
Yay.
Your spotlight challenge
is to create
a completely original take
on the traditional
Chinese new year dragon.
- Wow.
- Yes!
I draw dragons all the time
for tattoos,
so I'm kind of excited.
Your creations will then be
put to the test
as the head
of the new year's dragon
while performing
in an acrobatic dance
on our reveal stage.
- Wow.
- Oh, yes.
This is not going to be easy.
Once your actor
starts to sweat,
the makeup has a super high
chance of peeling off.
And we also want to give
your dragons
just a little extra
personal touch.
Chinese dragons are influenced
by various animals.
One may have the head of
a camel, the eyes of a wolf,
and the claws of an eagle.
So your dragons should
incorporate traits of each
of the team members zodiac signs
into the final makeup.
All right, so your teams
have been randomly selected,
and they are...
Nicole and Rod.
Excellent.
Eric and Sarah.
Awesome.
I'm excited about working
with Sarah.
She won the last challenge.
With my sculpting skills
and her costuming skills,
I think we can
do something original.
Next team is Alana and Laura.
- Yeah, girl.
- Yeah.
Derek and Tommy.
Awesome.
We were both in the bottom
the first time
and we both really
wanna win this time.
And I think we can do it.
Jason and Roy.
- Excellent.
- We got this.
Jason has fabricating
experience like I do.
We both work in the haunted
house industry
and so we think that
we can create something cool.
Now your sign is tied
to the year you were born
and we have
that information right here.
But before you head back
to the lab,
why don't go ahead
and take some photos
of this beautiful temple
for some inspiration
and get working
on your designs?
Good luck, everybody.
So we have a half an hour
to just look around the temple,
take some reference pictures,
do some sketching to come up
with our concept.
The design is important
because...
if you don't know
where you're going,
it's kind of hard to get there.
I'm gonna draw the bodies out
so you can get an idea
of where everything is.
Even though it's a boar face...
- Yeah, yeah.
- The dragon face...
We can give it that goofy,
monkey type of feel.
One of the things
we both key in on
is doing the boar tusks
and boar jaw with an underbite.
And then we wanna try and do
monkey fingers
and then definitely do
some hair laying
since they both have hair.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
For our concept,
it's the face of a dragon
with a bull ring out
of a baboon nose.
We're just throwing elements
of both of our animals
back and forth
and making one cohesive piece.
That's awesome!
The first thing I see
is a Chinese warrior,
and he's got
this amazing headdress.
And there's
these poles coming out
with flags hanging from it.
- Perfect. I love that.
- Oh, it's amazing.
- Okay, good.
- That's good.
It's one thing to make
a really cool makeup,
but it has to be something
that can look really pretty
with movement.
I can't wait to start
sculpting it.
- Start with the camera.
- Just so much...
I know.
This is gonna be great.
Is gonna be there to play with.
The first thing we do
when we get to the lab
is pick our models
and get right to work.
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
After we get to the lab
from the temple,
I start working
on the sculpture for the face.
Jason decides that he wants
to do the scales.
We want to take a rabbit face
and give it snake skin
and then do like
these really long ears,
and then a chest piece
that's reptile.
I'm gonna start vacuum forming
scales for the back piece.
The vacuform's great
because it gives us a way
to make copies of things.
Scales, scales--
just vacuform after vacuform.
Then I have to sit down and cut
out over a hundred scales.
Alana has goat
as her zodiac sign,
and mine is a rat.
I think a rat
and a goat together
is gonna look freaking fierce.
This or that?
I'm more feeling this.
We could go very theatrical,
but everybody else might be
doing something like that.
So we decided to go more
realistic to stand out.
I haven't even started adding
any of the detail
but roughed out, I got dragon.
I love Chinese culture,
but it's not something
I bring to my aesthetic.
So this is a challenge
right off the bat for me.
I think it's gonna look
fucking badass.
I think it's already
looking sweet.
Me and Derek just click.
He's gonna do the face
and I'm gonna do the cowl.
Well, we're both working on such
a same wavelength,
this could be
a great partnership.
I love his lips
that you're making.
I wanna do the lip
on the top part the same way.
Oh, okay.
Our plan is for me to start
sculpting the face,
and then we had this arm design
that we wanna try to get done.
It's a scaly dragon arm
with monkey hands.
Dude, I am not digging
the scale thing.
I don't like these.
Right away, as we start doing
some of the sculpting,
certain things
that we have in our heads
just aren't laying out
on the clay correctly.
It just seems like
it's time consuming.
What if I start sculpting
a chest piece?
Sometimes, the best things
can come from
having to work on
something different,
but now we could be
falling very behind.
You can do it
while I fabricate the costume.
- You know what I'm thinking?
- What?
To have those snakes and
the rats underneath the skin.
My thoughts are I don't--
You're still
not vibing, are you?
I'm sculpting the face,
and Nicole wants
to have rat tails hanging down
and my mind jumped to
let's incorporate--
instead of them hanging down,
let's incorporate it
into the design.
Wouldn't it be interesting
to have rats as cheeks?
In all the Chinese drawings
that you see,
the dragons have
the flares that come
and they're blowing
in the wind.
And I think
that would be really cool.
I really wanna do
these rat tail flares
and then rod sculpts
the rat tail in,
but he does a mustache.
And that's not at all what
I was talking about.
I just don't think
that he's wanting
to take any of my input
on this one.
We're all working very,
very hard,
when suddenly,
out of the blue...
What the fuck?
There's a scream.
Something bad has happened.
- Did you cut yourself?
- Oh, fuck!
Can I please have a medic?
Alana sliced her finger
really bad
and there's a lot of blood.
This really, really,
really hurts.
We have a face piece, a cowl,
and a hoof that need to be
sculpted today.
I could see in Laura's face
she's worried.
Hmm.
There's no way that this is
gonna get done.
Coming up...
If we don't get this mold out,
we'll be just totally screwed.
Shit.
I see what you guys
were going for.
I have a lot of problems
with it.
This could go horribly wrong.
Can I have please have a medic?
Something bad has happened.
This one really, really,
really hurts.
Alana sliced her finger
really bad
and there's a lot of blood.
Dude, if you gotta sew me up,
sew me up.
Let's go.
Are you serious?
Do you think
I really need stitches?
I feel terrible for Laura.
I'm leaving this girl
with a ton of work to do.
We have a face piece, a cowl,
and a hoof that need to be
sculpted today.
She needs to get stitches.
Yeah, go, go.
You know what, sometimes one
team member has to compensate
and that's okay.
So I just start
speed sculpting.
My brother Derek and I
obviously have
the same zodiac sign.
Of course I want to do
something different.
So I walk up
to my brother's sculpt
because I haven't gotten
a chance to see his design yet.
It's getting there.
I really want to kick his ass.
What do you have, ram?
Boar and a monkey.
I'm gonna win definitely.
I would think
it would be me but, uh...
I would, you know,
let you hang out with me
and share my glory.
That's all right.
Seven stitches.
Oh, my God, seven?
Oh, yeah!
This is looking great girl.
- Yeah.
- What do you want me to do?
Hmm.
We have an hour left
and I can't get this wet
and we use water clay.
How am I gonna work?
Do you want me to get those
bitches on the sander
so they're finished?
- Oh, yeah. Do it.
- Yeah.
At the very least I'm gonna go
make these horns for us.
Seven stitches.
- Really?
- Yup.
That girl's an accident
waiting to happen.
Waiting?
The first day, it's a little
hard to kind of grasp
a non-realistic makeup
and more theatrical.
It takes me a little bit longer
than I'd like
to get it roughed out.
Making this thing even
is such a pain.
We are about done with our
sculpts at the end of the day,
but we're not
where we wanna be.
I think I'm gonna have
to work on this
a little bit more tomorrow.
All right, guys, time's up!
Time is up!
End of the day, we didn't get
our sculpts finished.
I think I'm behind schedule.
We have a long day tomorrow,
but I'm a little worried
I'm not gonna be able to get it
all done in time.
We have ten hours for day two.
Immediately we walk over
to our sculptures
and we start
finishing up the detail.
In the beginning,
me and Rod were kind of like...
on different paths.
Do you wanna incorporate
those ears?
- I like the ears.
- If there's time.
I tell him, you know what,
let's sit at the same table,
and just kind of feel off
of each other's sculptures.
And that starts to work.
That's gonna look nice.
That's gonna look
freaking amazing.
I wanna make sure that
the communication is there.
We're in a good groove.
It's the second day
of the challenge,
we still have a good amount
of fabrication left to do.
This is a ton of work.
Roy has to vacuform scales
and I have to sculpt
the chest piece, mold it.
This is taking a lot longer and
a lot more time and materials
than I thought
it was going to take.
The hoof is gonna
start becoming
priority in the molding process
because we need to start
casting those up...
- Casting those, mm-hmm.
- And slip right away.
All of our sculptures
are pretty much finished.
I really, really need
to start molding.
You make a mold
by putting a cement-like
substance onto your sculpture.
From there you can
pour in silicon or foam
which will eventually
become your prosthetic.
It's not like
it has to be pretty.
It just has to be functional.
Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Here with Glenn to do
a little walk-through.
We're into the day and here
comes McKenzie with Glenn.
Glenn has such a good
poker face,
it is hard to read him.
You're working on the face,
you're working on the cowl
so that they match up?
The thing I'm worried about is
it's flaring pretty well
and I don't wanna flare that.
Instead of a singular,
hard line where they lay,
when I have to do this
I try to get
the line broken up...
So that where the two meld,
the eye doesn't go straight
to the fact
that there's this hard break
between the two.
We sculpted the face
of a rabbit
and give it scales
like a snake.
- So like a snabbit.
- Yes.
This is gonna be very
red and black.
And this is what the ears
are gonna look like
- when you're done?
- Yes, sir.
- I'm looking forward
to seeing it. - All right.
- Thanks.
- Good luck, guys.
Thanks, guys.
Concept-wise,
this is what we're kind
of going off of.
We fabricated these horns to
come up through the cowl here.
We're thinking
of making them shorter,
considering the actors
are rolling around.
You're putting a lot of trust
in the fact that
that little aperture and some
glue is gonna hold that on.
Explain this to me.
Your two animals were what?
A monkey and a ox.
One of the best ways to stand
out from everyone else
is to use
concepts and materials
that not everyone else
is using.
We can only look at so many
foam latex masks and hands.
Right.
So try to find other things
to integrate.
- Okay.
- It's a cool design.
So, yeah, we're going
with more of the boar jaw,
face, nose.
Our colors are an orange,
a blue, and then gold accents
because we thought a lot
of people wouldn't do that.
Here's the thing.
When you're going with all these
stylized, theatrical concepts,
my concern for you
is what are you gonna do
to impress us
when we get up close?
Theatrical makeups are great
from far away.
Yeah.
But when you look at them
close up,
they're gonna be hard,
opaque colors
that fade into one another.
Try to find something else that
you can go in there and detail.
- Thank you.
All right, thank you.
After hearing Glenn,
I'm wondering if we should be
doing it this way.
Sarah seems not as confident
as we were before.
So we're both trying
to figure out
if we're going
the right direction.
With everything
that you've seen today,
who's really thriving?
Design-wise, what Alana
and Laura have going on,
if they can get it to where
it is on paper in real life,
I think they've got a strong
shot at taking it this week.
But with Derek and Tommy,
there's a lot of cool
Chinese dragon or Asian ideas.
I wish more of them were doing
something like that.
Who do you think is maybe
falling a little short,
at least
at this stage of the game?
My greatest concern is
definitely with Sarah and Eric.
What I'm looking at color-wise,
conceptually, and sculpturally,
I don't see any-- a lot of it
changing or morphing
into something successful
in the next 24 hours.
- Hmm.
- Hopefully I'm wrong.
Yeah.
All right, everybody.
We're heading out.
See you tomorrow, guys.
Sarah's molding the cowl piece,
and I don't know what Sarah's
molding skills are.
Oh, my God,
this is the fucking shittiest mold
I've ever fucking made.
This is fucking ridiculous.
What you did is--
Yeah, the weight pushed it down.
Because look at all this.
Like, all this is crap man.
I'm so sorry, Eric.
We're starting to open
the mold and it stuck.
It's a little nerve-wracking,
opening up a mold.
You just don't know if it's
gonna open easy or break
while trying to get it
pried open.
This part's cracking.
It's too thin.
Oh, I didn't make it
thick enough?
If we don't get this mold out,
we'll be just totally screwed.
Shit.
I am not letting you down.
Rod is so cute.
He runs circles
around all of us.
There is no time to waste
with Mr. Rod Maxwell.
He's fast, man.
I've not seen him walk,
I don't think, actually.
Being on the show is like
training for a marathon.
Something that would
typically take you a month to do,
you're asked to do in no time.
So, if it takes a little running,
I'm running to get there.
Oh, my God,
this is the fucking shittiest mold
I've ever fucking made.
I'm so sorry, Eric.
If we don't get this mold out,
we'll be just totally screwed.
We're starting to open
the mold and it's stuck.
It's a little nerve-wracking,
opening up a mold.
You just don't know
if it's gonna break
while you're trying
to get it pried open.
Ugh!
Okay.
So we pull all that clay out
really fast and luckily...
You know, the stuff that needs
to be nice is gonna be nice.
Everything comes out perfect.
Uh, I'm gonna take
this outside.
Okay.
I know we have
a lot of work to do.
So I'm thinking
instead of sculpting
and molding these hooves,
let's sculpt and vacuform them.
That way we'll be able
to bust them out super fast.
All right, ready.
It's like an easy bake oven
for crazy people.
I think this is gonna be good.
Yeah, let's do that.
Alana's got two hooves out.
However she definitely wants
this creature to have four legs.
Really, if I spend like 30
minutes on the hooves, finishing them,
while you're getting
the weight capped down
and prepping them all--
So you want me to do
the application
while you apply these?
I had to say,
"I don't think we're gonna have
enough time for those.
Let's concentrate
on something else."
I know, I just feel like
we have so much done
and we only have two pieces
to lay down tomorrow.
It's five hours.
It's just-- It's just
a risk, you know.
I don't think it is.
I just really don't--
All right.
Well...
My gut is telling me
to keep going.
If you wanna continue.
We got it, girl.
Don't worry.
There's a lot to do still,
so all I'm thinking
about is time.
How quickly can we do this?
Do you have a system going on,
or do you mind if I just
jump right in?
Just jump in.
Rod has a very specific way
of how he likes to mold,
but I don't think it really
works for a time constraint.
You know, you could just like
dip the burlap and just slap it.
That's a way to do it.
Right now
there's no reason for panic.
Actually just take-- Just run
down there and back
just fast as you can.
We are doing the most work
out of any team
by trying to tackle
the entire costume.
This survives the roll,
I think we're good.
I think it will.
So we're hoping that that
gets us some brownie points.
No-- Ian, note to self...
No more scales
on projects ever again.
So...
I get all four hooves done.
They're all finished
by the end of the day.
But Laura only paints
two of them
and the other two
are just hanging out.
I'm not okay with that,
I'm not.
Going into application day,
if we're not on the same page
this is gonna be a disaster.
All right.
That's time, everybody.
Good job today.
It's application day, and
we have four hours in the lab
to get everything done
on our model.
And we still got a lot
of things to do.
Jason starts doing
the paint job.
And I see it and I'm not happy.
There's all these
little black dots
like he has a bad case
of black acne.
I'm thinking though, okay,
if we're on bottom,
hopefully it's
for the paint job.
Because I can honestly say,
without throwing him him
under the bus,
I had nothing to do
with the paint job.
And so I decided not
to even touch it
and let that be
his cross to bear.
- Hi.
- Hey!
Good morning, girl.
Oh, no.
I'm laying down the cowl,
and as I'm putting it on,
our cowl rips in half.
- Did it rip?
- Mm-hmm.
It breaks.
A big gaping hole in the back
of the head.
Can you start working
on that patch?
I just feel like
if we don't patch it,
it's just gonna keep ripping
throughout her dance.
It's just gonna
keep coming undone.
That's okay.
We're gonna cover it in hair
and hopefully, it doesn't rip
during the dance.
What do you have as the flag?
The-the green--
The flowy green stuff that's--
that I made her fan out of.
Okay.
I'm going as fast as I can
and this is a lot to do
in this four hours.
Are you seeing anything you
don't like?
No, that's good.
That's good.
- We'll keep-keep going.
- Okay.
We wanna make sure
that the wires
that are gonna hold the flags
are in place.
Haven't experimented
with this yet.
I say we should bring
some of this color up, though.
'Cause this is, like,
standing alone.
Derek starts painting
the face piece
and I'm gonna focus
on painting the cowl.
- Is this cool?
- Yup.
- Yeah? Really?
- Okay.
It's a huge risk to have
two different paint jobs
on two different pieces
if they're coming together.
You're just really counting on
each other to pull it together.
This could go horribly wrong.
- You like that color or no?
- I don't know.
The orange we have
is looking way too orange.
It's too bright and we wanted it
to be more dull and brown.
We're a little worried
about that.
So I'm just focusing
on the face,
trying to get the color down.
We got 20 minutes.
Is that gonna be too much
of a temperance for you or--
We all have our fabrication
that we're doing.
We're running out of time
to apply the facial appliance.
It is extremely risky to wait
till last looks to do
your appliance.
To me, a last look should be
just for touch-ups.
It's time, guys.
It's time.
- Let's go!
But I don't have that option
right now.
Ooh!
I got so many things
that have to get done.
That last hour at last looks
is gonna kill me.
Coming up...
It's time to put your makeups
to the test
in an acrobatic performance.
- I'm freaking out.
- I don't see the dragon.
It's one of the strongest
collaborations
I've seen on this show.
So we have one hour
for last looks
and I'm running out of time.
We still need to put
on the face prosthetic.
It is extremely risky to wait
till last looks
to do your appliance.
And that is gonna
be very wobbly.
I'm not getting too much
positive reinforcement
from Sarah,
so I'm thinking she's
not really feeling it.
So I'm not confident
with what I'm doing.
Okay, so this is
coming up back here.
We're both working together
to do details.
I'm like, "Nicole, go for it.
Do the makeup."
One minute, everybody.
Let's see how this
all comes together.
That's time.
We walk out on stage
and the whole place
has been decked out
with lanterns.
We have been transported
to a new world.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
First, let's say hello
to your judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
- Hi, guys.
- Hey.
Creature and concept designer,
Neville Page.
Hi, guys.
Hello.
This week your spotlight
challenge was to work in teams
to create an original take
on the traditional Chinese
new year's dragon.
We also told you that your
makeups would be tested here
on our reveal stage
in an acrobatic performance.
But before we put them
to the test,
let's just see
what you've come up with.
First up is Alana and Laura.
That fact the ours does look
so different--
So much less Chinese
than everybody else--
It could help or hinder us.
I'm feeling pretty good.
I love those tassels on the end.
Every time she moves,
those tassels are going.
We budgeted our time
and we executed it as well
as I think we could have.
I'm all smiles.
That guy looks awesome.
I'm not 100% on the paint job.
That's the one thing
I'm really worried about.
But everything else--
I love how the tusks look.
After we put the contacts in,
it looks pretty cool.
Overall, I really like it.
But I'm worried about
the paint job that Jason's done.
Okay, everybody.
It's time to put your makeups
to the test.
They've got this dance stage
set up and all of these
different dragons are like
circling around each other.
Everybody's a little nervous.
I'm so excited to see them
dance and, like,
do all their crazy stuff
with this on,
and I'm really hoping
that nothing falls off.
Awesome!
Wow!
Oh, my God!
Once the music ended,
I was like "Whoo. Okay."
And everything held up.
We did good.
Okay, let's see how well each
of your dragons held up.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look?
From far away,
it looks like our makeups held
up during the dance routine,
but we have a rip this big
in the back of our cowl.
I'm freaking out.
Join the conversation
on Twitter.
Use #FaceOff to tell us
what you think
about tonight's designs.
We have a rip this big
in the back of our cowl.
I hope they don't see it.
The sculpt is a little haggard
but the forms are there.
Oh, yeah.
There's like rats crawling up
the side of the...
- Ooh, shit.
- Feisty.
Yeah.
Actually in profile,
it's just badass.
It's definitely dragony.
That's a good word,
interesting.
Yeah.
Interesting.
The horns were something
I thought of last minute.
So it's something that I'm
a little worried about.
Yeah.
All right, well, the judges
would like to speak
with each of you to learn
more about your work.
Rod and Nicole.
Glenn, why don't we start
with you?
Why don't you begin
by explaining to us
what the astrological
symbols were
that you had to integrate
into your dragon?
Snake and rat.
The characters got sculpted
into the muscle structure.
I liked that right away when I
saw the sculpture that you had,
like, rats and snakes
on a dragon face.
I also would have to applaud
the fact that you added
these wavy flag banner things
to the top of the head.
It looks cool.
It breaks the form up.
It does give it an Asian flair,
and it shows you were thinking
about the movement.
Yours is the one that really
says "Chinese" to me.
I really think you did a great
job of integrating
your Chinese birth signs
into this makeup.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm torn with this one,
because I think you have
a really creative core concept,
but I don't see the dragon.
Thank you very much.
You can both step back.
Jason, Roy.
Guys, tell me
which astrological signs.
I mean, I can get the snake.
Your other one was the...
- A rabbit.
- Rabbit, right?
And who did what
in this collaboration?
I sculpted the, uh,
face prosthetic
and made the cowl area here.
And I sculpted
the chest and hands.
All in all, I'm pretty happy
with this physically.
I'm just not really happy with
this red and black paint job
on the snake-like face.
It's distracting to see
all those black spots in there.
I just thought it would
add more of a theatrical effect.
Okay.
Can you bare your chest for us?
- It's--
- That's cool.
That does so much more
than this costume piece.
Not having the chest out
was a huge mistake.
You know, when you do that
much work, you got to show it.
Also to me, this would have
been the easiest one
to turn into a dragon.
Really wish you would have
elongated the face
and brought the skull structure
closer to a dragon's.
Jason, Roy,
thank you very much.
You can step back.
Alana and Laura.
Tell us about your birth signs
that influenced this.
- Well, I am a rat.
- I'm a goat.
We kind of homogenized
the two together.
Who did what exactly?
I sculpted the face.
Alana did the horns, hands,
and headed up the paint scheme
for the face.
I really love the vibe
of this one.
I do like the fact that you've
got a little bit of muck,
adding a little bit
of weathering
helps to give it a little bit
more character as well.
What I see here
is very successful
in its persistence of vision.
It looks like a sketch.
I think that's awesome
when you can really stick
with a design
and see it all the way
to the end.
I'm really happy with this one.
Thank you.
Alana, Laura,
thank you so much.
You can head back.
Thank you, guys.
Eric and Sarah.
Start off by reminding us
which birth symbols are
in your design.
I am the monkey.
And I have the boar.
I see what you guys
were going for.
I have a lot of problems
with it.
There's a lot of
unintentional asymmetry.
I love asymmetry
but it has to look to me
like it was put there
on purpose,
not because you couldn't
get things straight.
And I think there's a lot of
elements in this sculpt
that are pretty neat,
but if I would have
made those horns,
I would have just said
"oh, screw it.
This guy is not gonna
have horns."
'Cause that's just too nasty.
- Who did the horns?
- I-- At the last minute.
I painted them.
Did you really think that that
was gonna fly, those horns?
I didn't get a chance
to double look at them.
'Cause we were rushing to get it
over here, so--
- But you made them.
You had to have looked at them.
Who did most of
the painting on the face?
Eric did most of it,
and I did some of
the blue work and things
and he finished detailing it
while I continued
working on costume stuff.
It is actually the details
that I have a problem with
and the lack thereof.
We've got really blocky,
solid color
on a blocky, solid sculpture.
- Yeah.
- And that spells trouble for me.
Thank you both.
You can step back.
All right.
Derek, Tommy.
Okay, guys.
What were your
astrological critters?
- I'm an ox.
- I'm a monkey.
Who did what in this makeup?
This is Derek's baby
from the beginning
and I just totally
jumped onboard
so I designed the costume.
I followed his lead.
Let's talk about the head.
Face and cowl--
Two separate people?
Yes.
I sculpted the face...
And from here back--
And painted it and he painted
and sculpted the cowl.
I think it's one of
the strongest collaborations
I've seen on this show.
There is no disparate
difference
between what you did
and what you did.
You worked really well
as a team.
Thank you.
I love the color combinations
that you did on this.
It was quite stunning
when he first came out
and the lights came on.
I also feel that it has
a Japanese aesthetic as well.
And I don't know
if that's intentional.
I'm a tattoo artist
and a lot of stuff I draw
- is Japanese-style.
- That's awesome.
That seems to me like it's
transcending what it is
that we asked you to do.
I'm pretty thrilled
with this thing.
Thanks.
Derek and Tommy,
thank you so much.
You can step back.
- Thank you, guys.
- Thank you.
All right, well, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they make
their decisions.
All right, judges, let's talk
about the top looks.
Let's start
with Rod and Nicole.
- What are your thoughts there?
- They did everything right.
They had the little
flag-type things, the fan.
They were really successful in
getting aspects of the Chinese
traditional new year's dragon.
It's my favorite
from the standpoint of
it's a cool concept.
Alana and Laura,
what are your thoughts there?
That's probably my favorite.
You know, I could see this thing
in a pretty cool indie film.
- It's definitely a cool makeup.
- It is.
There's just nothing about
a Chinese dragon there.
All right.
Derek and Tommy.
I love that splash of color
using a mandrill's snout.
Yeah.
The costume was so spectacular.
When he moved,
it was very flamboyant.
The question that we have
to answer amongst ourselves is
which is more important to us
in this week's challenge--
The team that came up
with something
that more closely echoed
a traditional dragon design,
or the team that came up with
a more successful
and complete makeup?
- Yeah.
- Tough one.
Why don't we talk about
some of the looks
you liked least this week.
Jason and Roy.
If they would have painted it
green and not chosen that red...
Yes.
That would have been a dragon.
- The red was a horrible choice.
- And the dalmatian spots...
- Yeah, that--
- Did not help.
Yeah.
A lot of bad choices
within the challenge.
Yeah.
An easy save
would have been the color.
Let's move on
to Sarah and Eric then.
The horns were unacceptable.
How could you not know
how bad they were?
I would have just not
put the bloody things on.
At least if they would have done
a cool paint job
and done the hair darker
so it wasn't bright orange,
it could have been made
to look really, really cool.
Great, judges.
Have you made your decisions?
I think we have.
Let's bring them back out.
Okay, Glenn,
tell us about the top looks.
This week, there's only
one team that we felt
actually met the criteria
of the challenge.
The top team tonight is...
All right, Glenn,
so why don't you tell us
about the top teams tonight?
This week, there's only
one team that we felt
actually met the criteria
of the challenge.
The top team tonight is...
Tommy and Derek.
Congrats, bro.
Derek and Tommy,
congratulations.
- Thank you.
But as you know, we can only
have one winner tonight.
Glenn.
Our winner
of this evening is...
Derek.
Yay, Derek.
- Thank you.
- Good job, buddy.
Thank you.
Although you both did
a really good job,
we felt that your familiarity
with a specific Asian
design aesthetic
is what allowed you guys to do
what we're asking for
in this challenge.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
Derek, congratulations.
You and Tommy can head back
to the makeup room.
- See you, guys.
- Thank you, guys.
- Thank you so much.
- See you, guys.
It feels good to win,
but my brother's
still out there
and I'm kind of worried
for him.
All right, Glenn,
why don't you tell us
about the bottom looks?
We felt that there was one team
that really missed the mark
in trying to meet the parameters
of this week's challenge.
The bottom team is...
Eric and Sarah.
All right, so that means
the rest of you are safe tonight
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Eric and Sarah,
step to the center.
All right, so Glenn,
who is leaving us tonight?
The person going home
this evening is...
Eric.
Ultimately, we felt that
it was your concept, sculpture,
and paint job that lead to
the failure of this makeup.
Eric, I'm sorry
but you have been eliminated.
Sarah, that means
you are safe this week.
Will you please head back
to the makeup room?
It's okay.
You know you're talented,
we know you're talented,
so all the best of luck to you.
Thank you.
Eric, it has been great
having you here with us.
Please head back to the makeup
room and pack up your kit.
Thanks, guys.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
- Take care.
- Good luck.
- I'm going home.
- Oh.
- Oh, man.
- Yup.
The most disappointing thing
about going home right now
is not getting to show
my best work.
I can't enjoy my win now.
That sucks.
Last looks with Derek.
I definitely don't think
this is the end for me.
Face Off has made me
more confident
because there's so many things
I did on this show
that I've never done before.
Derek just better step up
and keep going for me
and for us.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net