Tonight, on part one of
the season finale of Face Off.
Only three artists remain.
And you, America,
will choose one to win it all.
Laura.
A lot of my work
has been theme parks.
If I win,
I could start my career.
It's so well done,
it blows my mind.
Derek.
I cannot believe that
I've made it this far.
I want to make
my mom and dad proud.
- He's a really good designer.
- Nicole.
I was eliminated,
but I came back with a bang.
I have so much to prove.
I have to win this.
I'm really proud of the fight
from her since she's come back.
- And later--
- What's up, guys?
There's something huge
that I have not told you yet.
This is freaking me out.
Fuck.
I feel like such an asshole.
Rod has to start
working faster.
Why am I gonna win her $100,000
when I should be
winning it for myself?
And then they'll battle it out
in an explosive final challenge.
This is the hardest thing
I will ever do.
I'm about to start crying.
It's the finale.
You know, it's gonna be huge.
Oh, my God.
In the end, only one
will win the opportunity
to be a guest lecturer
at Make Up For Ever's academies
in New York and Paris,
a new 2012 Toyota Prius V,
and $100,000.
And for the first time ever,
America, your voice
will be heard
in selecting the winner.
Only one will win Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Am I missing any strands
in the back?
- Are any of the strands, like--
- Yeah.
- Damn it!
- Right in here.
It's a little odd in the house.
Everybody is gone except me
and Nicole and Derek.
I'm just getting ready
for the day,
and thinking about my husband.
I mean, this is easily
the longest I've been
without talking or seeing him.
So I'm walking downstairs,
and all of a sudden
there's a computer
that wasn't there before.
Oh, my God!
Hi, honey!
- Hey, honey.
- Hi.
Sorry. Sorry.
I just missed you.
Oh, my God! Mom!
Hi!
It's my mom.
My mom and my little sister.
- I made it!
- We are, like, beaming.
- Hey.
- Oh, my God.
I haven't seen you in so long.
- I miss you.
- I miss you too.
It's my wife.
I definitely think about her
all the time when I'm here.
I miss her.
I've been rooting for you
the entire time.
I could not be more proud.
Being without Carlo,
I've really had to dig deep
and find something
to keep focused.
One more challenge.
You've got this.
You are the one.
Back home I told mom,
"if I make it back on the show,
I'm gonna go to the end,
I'm gonna win it."
You know,
"I'm gonna do this."
And she's like, "I know.
I know you're gonna do it."
- Kisses.
- Love you, baby girl.
Bye!
Well, I love you. I gotta go.
And I'll see you soon.
- I'm so proud of you.
- Thanks.
Getting to see her gives me
some inspiration to work harder.
- Oh, man.
- Oh, my God.
Walking into the lab today,
I immediately see,
like, a harvest.
There's tombstones and, like,
gargoyles and skulls.
Oh, it's Halloween.
Welcome to the finale.
Your final spotlight challenge
is inspired by one of
the oldest celebrated holidays,
Halloween.
- Yes!
- Yeah, buddy.
I think we're all
qualified for this one.
Yeah.
I'm really excited 'cause, like,
that's why I got into makeup,
you know, was because
of my love for Halloween.
Each of you will create
two original characters.
The first is a demon
determined to spread chaos
throughout the living world.
And the second is a good witch
who will hunt that demon down
and banish it back to hell.
Now your demons can be created
in any style that you like,
but your witches are elemental
protectors of the Earth.
Ooh.
So each one must be influenced
by one of the
four major elements.
Earth...
air...
fire...
and water.
We drew your names randomly.
Laura, which element would
you like to inspire your witch?
My instincts are telling me
to go with earth.
- Nicole?
- I'm gonna go with water.
- And Derek?
- I'm gonna go with fire.
So some of the biggest names
in makeup history,
like Stan Winston
and Dick Smith,
they not only
excelled individually,
but they also knew
how to lead a great team.
- Guys, come on out!
- Oh-ho-ho.
Yeah, buddy!
- What's, up, guys?
- Hi.
So you will each get to choose
two of your former competitors
to join your team.
Nicole, you get to pick first.
Roy.
My man.
- Derek, your turn.
- My brother.
Aww.
Yeah!
- Laura.
- How's your arm feeling, Rod?
Yay!
My girl, Sarah.
Jason.
- All right.
- And Laura.
Since we worked
together before,
I'm gonna pick Tommy.
Whoa, don't hurt her back.
Alana, CC, we will definitely
see you at the finale.
Yes, you will.
Good luck to you guys.
- I love you all.
- Love you guys.
- Bye.
- Love you.
There's something huge
that I have not told you yet.
Three days from now,
all of your creations
will take part in
a choreographed stunt routine.
- Oh, man.
- Oh, wow.
How in the hell
am I gonna make that happen?
I am scared and yes,
I'm losing color in my face,
'cause this is freaking me out.
Good luck, guys.
I will see you soon.
- Thank you.
So we pick
our stunt performers.
There we go.
And we have ten hours
to work in the lab.
This is probably
the hardest thing
that I will ever have to do.
- Laura, here. This is yours.
- Yay! All right.
If I win, that would make
a ginormous impact on my life.
- I could start my career.
- All right, guys.
I've got a frickin'
great idea for the demon.
When the time starts,
the best thing to do
is just get the sketching
out of the way
and try to get, like,
what I'm seeing in my head
somewhat out on paper.
- I'm thinking those swirly horns.
- Oh, like, the goat horns.
Yeah. But then having spikes.
I want the demon to have
a fish element,
but I also want to throw other
animal characteristics in there
because I feel like
that's what a demon is.
You still want
to maintain some of those
traditional witchy features
on her, though?
- Hmm, I don't think so.
- Okay.
I'm making a headpiece
for the witch,
and then I also want minimal
prosthetics on the face.
So I want her face
to be really soft and pretty
because it's a water creature.
This head piece is gonna
be really hard though.
Just so you also see some
of the stunt harnesses.
Oh, okay.
Is this definitely
what he's wearing?
We are going to have
to incorporate harnesses,
elbow pads, stunt equipment,
into our design.
As far as the demon
is concerned,
the only thing I was thinking
was abominous and grotesque
on one side.
It's a demon whose
whole point in life
is to pollute the Earth.
We're just gonna make the demon
the anti-nature.
You know, when
I'm thinking of her,
I'm thinking maybe
we make her all-white.
With the witch,
since she's supposed to be
the good character, I would
like to do a cherry blossom tree
or a birch white tree.
I'm thinking the witch
is gonna be, like,
cracking with lava in between.
My concept for my witch
is molten rock that starts
cooling down and cracking.
You want to do
any armor on the demon?
I don't even know
if I want to do horns.
My demon is
an underground creature,
almost albino-looking,
which entraps him
with multiple rock chains
fused to his bones.
All right, I think
I'm gonna start sculpting hers.
I'm gonna get some
clays and stuff.
For the first day,
I'm having Roy block out
the face of the demon,
and I'm working on
the witch's face.
And Sarah's working on
the arms and hands.
The stunt show
is gonna be awesome,
but it's gonna, like,
take away a lot of our design.
From here on out, it's gonna
be all soft, nothing rigid.
Safe, but durable.
And I also need to create
the best and the biggest
of anything I've ever done.
How do you think I should do the forehead,
just trying to figure that out soon...
Derek's giving me
a lot of freedom,
but I'm still checking in
with him every now and then.
I'll ask him to come over
and see how it looks.
Oh, you don't have any idea?
You've got nothing?
No comment?
No comment.
So I asked you, and you come
and look at it, like, "um."
I thought you were gonna
give me some advice, and no.
I'd keep this all open because
she's gonna be moving a lot.
Tommy is moving
at this feverish pace.
Rod, on the other hand...
- Do you want multiple eyes or--
- Yeah, we can do multiple eyes.
- I mean, I'm not sure.
- Yeah.
But no, no, no.
That isn't a suggestion from me.
It doesn't seem
as though he knows
in what direction to go.
Trying to do it on this
would be tricky.
Rod is checking in...
Do you have a preference
of how to go with this?
What are your thoughts?
I definitely want
to work with you on that.
A lot.
If you want to hop in there
and rough something out
and I'll go in and detail it?
Or if you want to do it
the other way around?
I'm just trying
to keep my mind focused
on what has to be done.
I have a lot at stake,
and I don't have time for this.
Coming up...
Shattered, gone.
I'm about to start crying.
Welcome to the Face Off finale.
Whoo!
And stay tuned for details
on how to cast your vote
for our winner.
What are your thoughts?
Do you have a preference
of how to go with this?
Rod doesn't seem
as though he knows
in what direction to go.
If you want to hop in there
and rough something out,
and I'll go in and detail it.
I'm feeling a lot of pressure
to make sure that
I deliver for Laura.
Well, I tell you what,
uh, you just keep sculpting.
Whenever you want me
to get to the detail,
I will do that.
We have to do two makeups,
a good witch and a demon.
Rod has to start
working faster,
or I don't see how
we're gonna be able
to do anything
worthy of a finale.
So this is
a test piece of coral.
That's awesome.
Seven minutes, everyone.
All right,
that's time, everybody.
- Let's go.
- All right.
I really would like
to get everything molded
and finished tomorrow.
I'm a little worried,
but I definitely
have a lot of confidence
in my team.
- Oh, wow.
- What?
Walking into the lab today
is awesome,
there is a car there.
This is the Prius V
that's going to be
the prize for the winner.
Oh, it's leather.
- Get away from my car, come on.
- Definitely need a car.
Me and my wife
share one right now,
so it's kinda hard
to get to work.
Oh, my God, this is cool.
You know how many
makeup kits I can fit
in the back of this thing?
Look, there's a thing
for your phone.
It's called Bluetooth.
I don't know
what fancy stuff is.
I need a car that doesn't
constantly need checkups
and replacing
and rusted-out parts.
The whole prize package
would be an amazing new start
to a new life.
Okay, team leaders,
you gotta win it first.
I'm sorry.
And to do that,
we gotta get to work.
Okay. I'm done.
See how fast it is
with wet clay?
Shut up.
Girls, you're both pretty.
We have 10 hours today,
and we pretty much have
all the major sculpts done,
so it's time to make the molds.
These actors are gonna
be running around, sweating,
so all my pieces
are gonna be foam.
Foam is lighter and
a little bit more breathable.
Silicone doesn't breathe
at all.
Hey, Roy, can you do
a couple of those scales
on the face so it ties in?
Yeah, do you--
where do you want 'em at?
Because I don't think
they're gonna match.
I want the demon
to be shrively and, like,
lots of wrinkles
and lots of texture,
and Roy seems frustrated.
I mean, I don't
do wrinkles like that,
'cause they don't
look as natural.
Oh, fuck.
It's, like, a lot of tension
is building between us.
Oh, look at that.
At the end of the day,
everyone is working well
and getting the molds done.
- Whoa. Here we go.
- All right, guys, that's time.
Let's go.
We're in very good shape
for tomorrow.
Let's see what we got.
The third day,
we have a lot of molds.
I've lost track.
It's a busy day.
- But that's all fixable.
- That's all gonna be covered.
And the ear's
gonna be covered as well.
Being in the finale is crazy,
'cause I was sent home.
To win would be the greatest
accomplishment of my life.
Let's get sculpting.
That looks good.
Since we have most
of the prosthetics complete,
we are gonna try and sculpt out
a back for the witch
and for the demon.
You think I should slab
all of them on this?
No.
You can feel the tension
right now.
I'm no longer a competitor.
Why am I gonna win her $100,000
when I should be
winning it for myself?
I just don't know
what I did to upset him,
but I'm hoping
that he looks past it.
Hey, everybody.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I've brought Oscar-winner,
Emmy-winner,
and my dad, Michael Westmore.
- How are you?
- We're gonna take a look around.
Michael Westmore
is an amazing makeup artist.
I mean, he's done
so many different things.
So this is cool.
This is the cowl.
- Wow.
- Oh, wow.
I want to paint it
copper or, like, gold.
You don't have a lot
of depth to work with,
so start with your
lighter colors and build up,
because if you go with too dark
a one to start,
there's no going back.
So here are the--
this is the demon.
Let's see.
Nice thin edges on it.
What are you going to do
to bring out
that there's something
going on underneath?
I really want it to be bright
and maybe some metallic makeup.
They also have
metallic press-on,
which we used on the borgs a lot
to metalize them.
Show us your witch.
Yeah, let's look.
Yeah, there were things I was
thinking about adding to it.
Maybe I can run this by you,
just kind of work them into some
of these crevices and give it
a little bit more dimension.
- What are they made out of?
- Uh, plastic.
Okay, that's fine.
That's flexible.
But you got
a lot of work to do.
So pre-paint as much as you
can pre-paint to prepare it.
So let's start with team Derek.
My main concern with him
was I really want to see
how he's gonna handle
the cracks in that head
so they don't disappear.
Right. So let's
move on to Nicole.
She has a great direction.
And you're happy
with the witch?
That coral head was beautiful.
Yes. With the coral head,
the paint job is gonna
be very important,
or you're gonna look at it
and go, "what is it?"
Right. Let's move on
to team Laura.
Mm-hmm. The one character
I'm concerned with is her witch.
Really?
She's talking about
its vines and its tree,
and there's not enough texture
in her sculpting
to really sell that idea.
All right. Well, let's see
how this turns out tomorrow.
Yep.
Okay, everybody,
we're heading out.
- Good luck tomorrow.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
This is very difficult.
This is taking a lot longer
than I thought it would.
Try this one.
See if that,
like, does anything.
It's really hard right now
because me and Roy
have always been buds,
and there's just something
not right.
And I just don't know
how to deal with this.
It's hard to even look at her,
because I'm reminded that
the judges chose
her work over mine.
There's so much to do,
and there are so many decisions,
and the tension's building.
There's all the stress
of the finale.
I'm hurt that Roy
is upset with me.
I'm about to start crying,
'cause this is my last chance
to show that I have the skills
to be in the finale,
and I feel like I'm screwed.
The Prius V is awesome.
I've never seen a car like this.
Press the bottom and it starts.
Oh, how cool is that?!
The system is really cool.
You can buy movies on it.
You can find restaurants
that are in the area.
What do you guys
want this to do?
It's very spacious.
It's got leather sits.
This is a fancy car.
Oh, this is too cool.
Where do you guys wanna go?
Say "help" at any time
for additional instructions.
It's like the car
from the future.
- Fuel prices.
I'm hoping this will
be my next car.
Check this one.
See if, like, does anything.
I've always wanted
to work with Roy,
and we're working
together finally,
and then there's tension
and that sucks.
I love Nicole,
but every time I look at her,
I'm reminded that the judges
chose her work over mine.
But I have to be professional
and help Nicole win.
So I see Jason working on
the staff for their witch,
and Tommy working on one
for Laura and I'm thinking,
"you know,
we don't have a staff."
So I decided to make one.
I see this acrylic tubing
and I'm thinking,
if I can get that hot enough,
I can take it and bend it
and do, like, a little
water spray on the top,
make a really cool
staff out of it.
- Oh, my God!
- Whoo!
That's so cool!
This is amazing.
It's just gorgeous.
The tension with Roy
just kind of starts
to, like, disappear.
Hug me.
I'm so relieved.
Still working on her costume
and trying to figure out
his rigging.
It is the smallest detail that
makes the entire thing work.
The color schemes,
prosthetics, accents, and props.
These are all essential
to the overall look
of the character.
These teeth for the demon
are tricky.
Finally, we start
trying out feather quills,
and then we get some foam pieces
and put those in the back
and the feather quills
over the top,
and it looks awesome.
All right, that's it.
We have finished everything
that needs to be finished today.
It's all come together,
and it's a good feeling.
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab
and we have one hour
at last looks.
I've never done
this many pieces.
It's kinda nerve-wracking,
but we gotta work through it
and get it all down
as fast as possible.
This is the best bald cap
I've laid since I've been here.
Everything is pretty much
working out on application day.
Roy is painting the staff,
and it's just
looking cooler and cooler.
Sarah has got the cowl on
the witch and applying the face.
I feel like if we
just keep up the same pace,
I think we can pull this off.
I'm gonna be
heading up the witch.
Rod's heading up the demon,
and Tommy is gonna be
helping out wherever he can.
Oh, my gosh,
that's so gorgeous!
I like being the guy
that you have to depend on
when things get hot.
It's fun to play superhero.
Uh, Roy?
My foot hit Roy's totally
awesome plastic-formed staff.
The whole thing fell over
and the bulb fell off.
- Oh.
- I feel like such an asshole.
Tommy accidentally
knocked the staff over.
Which it's my fault
because I left it in a place
where it could be knocked over.
- How are you doing, Roy?
- Uh, not good.
The staff's gone.
Broke, shattered, gone.
You don't want something broken
on finale.
You have to let it go.
- Well, fuck.
- Oh, well, it was a nice idea.
- There.
- It's like birthing.
Yeah.
Black and then
maybe glowing here.
For the lava, I really want
fluorescent colors.
Uh, yellows and oranges.
But for the demon, I want
to work on the paint scheme
with my brother
and get it down.
Lighter paint,
lighter skin--
- however you
started with this.
- I went back and forth.
- So do that.
We have a lot to paint,
so I'm stressed out.
Careful with
getting it on this.
Five minutes.
All right,
that's time, everybody.
I feel like we're behind
a little bit.
We definitely have a lot to do,
but this is my last chance
to impress the judges
and impress America.
As I walk into last looks,
it sets in, like,
how big this is.
Ooh.
So we're around the corner,
and there are these
gorgeous makeup trailers.
And that's awesome.
I'm, like, a real
makeup artist now.
- Come on in.
- Where's the other compressor?
So we only got an hour in here.
In the first, like, few minutes,
I kind of had, like, a moment.
Like, "oh, my God,
what am I doing?"
Like, "what do
I do first?"
Go ahead and set him down
and get his eyes and mouth done.
Roy is the voice
of reason right now.
So we have a lot
of painting detail work to do.
Pucker tight.
Tommy's laying down moss.
Rod still has to
apply all of the hair,
but the majority of the work
is all resting on my shoulders.
I've still gotta finish a lot
of the paint job on the witch,
but we have to get it done
and it's gonna get done.
All right, guys.
That's five minutes.
I don't like her eyes now.
I'm not a fan.
- It's time!
- Whoo!
I am so proud of these makeups
that are walking out
of this trailer today.
He looks frickin' awesome.
I couldn't have asked
for anything more.
I feel on top a little bit,
and it's just a good feeling.
I'm extremely proud
of my team, but you can tell
everyone's nervous
because next is the stunt show,
which is completely
out of our hands.
Coming up...
Welcome to the Face Off finale.
The stunt show
is freaking me out.
My heart's pounding.
This is it.
You did a great job.
- The teeth are really cool.
- Thank you.
And stay tuned for details
on how to cast your vote
for our winner.
Please welcome your host,
McKenzie Westmore.
Thank you.
Good evening, everybody.
Welcome to the Face Off finale.
Tonight, we're gonna
celebrate Halloween our own way.
Our finalists' characters
will have to survive
an epic choreographed
fight sequence.
For their final
spotlight challenge,
we asked each
of our contestants
to create two original makeups.
The first is a demon
determined to spread chaos
throughout the living world.
The second is a good witch
who will hunt that demon down
and banish it back to hell.
So let me tell you
what's at stake tonight.
The winner of the Face Off
finale will have the opportunity
to become a guest lecturer
at Make Up For Ever's academies
in New York and Paris,
a 2012 Toyota Prius V,
and $100,000.
And for the first time
in Face Off history,
you, America,
will have the chance
to vote for
your favorite artist.
So stay tuned for details.
The winner will be announced
tomorrow night, live,
right here on SyFy.
So with that, I would like
to introduce you to our judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
Creature and concept designer,
Neville Page.
And rejoining our panel
this week,
creature designer and director,
Patrick Tatopoulos.
All right, well it is time
to get this started.
Tonight's first creations
are from Laura.
Her witch
was inspired by earth.
♪
My model just
starts using that staff,
and she is looking bad-ass.
Our demon comes out
and everybody loves it!
And when they come out
as a couple,
they definitely
look like they have
come from two different worlds.
The witch comes out
and she's visually
just stunning.
I love that.
The demon's colors
are all popping,
and he's got this great stance
that he does.
He's just striking.
I love that when they
stand next to each other,
they look like they're
from the same world.
He looks like
the evil creature.
She looks like
the good creature.
And they belong together.
I'm loving the paint scheme
for my witch.
The color contrasts
are just popping more
than I expected it to
and I'm really digging
the makeup.
It's looking really cool.
The pinks are popping
where the stone is imbedded
into his skin,
it shows that irritation.
I love it.
Seeing these two together,
it is awesome.
And the crowd loves it.
It's a cool feeling.
Well, that was
just the beginning.
Now it's time
to put them all to the test
in our spectacular stunt show.
The stunt show
is freaking me out,
'cause we're gonna get judged
on how well they're gonna
hold up afterwards,
and that's wracking my nerves.
I'm just--
my heart's pounding.
Then all of a sudden,
I hear a motorcycle revving.
This is it.
Well, that was
just the beginning.
Now it's time to put them all
to the test in our
spectacular stunt show.
Let's check it out.
The stunt show
is freaking me out,
because there's gonna
be these stunt guys
crashing through windows
and jumping off balconies.
Then all of a sudden,
I hear, like,
a motorcycle revving.
Oh, my God, this is it.
Okay.
Awesome.
To our studio audience,
who have helped to make this
such an amazing night,
it is now time
for our judges to speak
with our contestants in private.
Thank you all so much.
Have a good night.
So judges, what did you think
about what you saw here tonight?
I thought it was fabulous.
I love all the fantasy elements,
the witches and the demons.
It was bitchin'.
Everyone did such a great job,
and it really, really
is very impressive.
Yeah.
Well, the judges would like
to speak with each of you now
to learn more about your work.
Laura, you're up first.
Could you tell us
about the concept?
The witch that I chose
was the earth witch,
so that we could do more
vines and textures with bark.
And the whole concept
with the demon was that
he was gonna be anti-nature.
He's very toxic and has
started to disfigure and deform.
Addressing your witch,
I thought that it was
an absolutely
gorgeous execution.
It's not this traditional
idea of a witch.
But I thought that was
a brilliant decision,
when you're dealing
with elemental witches.
It was a stroke of genius
to approach it that way.
I can't say the same
for the toxic demon.
I was disappointed in the fact
that they felt like
they were from
different worlds.
What made you choose the colors
that you used on your witch?
I guess a cherry blossom tree
has white birch in it,
and I thought
"well, wouldn't that be cool
if it was white birch
over the entire thing."
And of course
white being more of
a pure and hero kind of color.
We went with the white.
I loved the way
it all looked like roots
crawling up her body
and all over her.
And as far as your
demon character goes,
I wasn't real hot on the color.
But I did love the witch.
Her profile
was really beautiful.
There were some really nice
lines happening with that.
I'm gonna give you credit
for one thing.
Everybody who's supposed to--
planning to create
a character from earth
is gonna use earth tones,
and you swept
everything around.
Just by doing this,
you took a bit of a challenge,
and I like what you've done.
I think it was very creative.
It was very daring.
- You did a great job.
- Thank you.
Thank you, Laura.
Would you please step back?
Nicole.
Can you tell us your concept?
My element
for the witch was water,
so I wanted to make her
be the protector of the sea.
And this demon
has been sent from hell
to kill her
and to take over the world.
I wanted her
to be very light and airy,
but still look like
she belonged from the ocean,
and him as well.
Well, I think
you were very successful
because they do look like
they both come
from a water element.
And I especially like the teeth
that you put on your demon.
I haven't seen anything
like that in a while.
What did you make them out of?
- Feather quills.
- Nice.
They function so well together.
They really belong
to the same world.
The head of the water witch
has got different textures.
It's very layered.
And you've done
a lot of things like that
that create a very
rich-looking character.
- So you did a great job.
- Thank you.
How exciting is it to have
your makeup doing wire work?
It was really, really elegant,
and that's why I wanted
a lot of that flowy fabric.
The outcome is great
for the witch.
Whereas the demon--
the horns I'm not so sure
that I agree that those work.
Having ram's horns.
In terms of the demon,
it's a bit blocky.
The sculpt of the head suffers
from an acute angularity.
That's not to say that
I didn't like the demon.
The color break between
the face and the chest,
they're actually
very different colors,
and I love that.
Thank you so much.
Nicole, thank you.
Would you please step back?
And Derek, please step forward.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
So tell us about
the concept first, please.
My demon is a soul eater,
and he was imprisoned
underground by the fire witch,
with molten rock
infused into his bones.
The thing I liked the most
is how
her hot lava earthen energy
has been infused
into his flesh.
And the teeth are really cool.
The downside
is it drew attention
to the actor's mouth
behind the teeth.
Yeah, I think those two
sculptures are very beautiful.
Thank you.
But I also love the paint job
on the pink demon.
I usually have a tendency
to not like those two tones,
pink and reddish.
And I think it came out
really, really strong there.
There is a good reason
why you're here tonight.
It's a great job
and I'm very impressed.
- Thank you.
- I really dug the paint job.
- It's sickly and gross.
- Yeah.
And it looks like something
that's been underground
for a really long time
and hasn't seen
the light of day,
which evidently that's exactly
what was wrong with him.
And as far as your witch goes,
I really dug
the whole idea that
she's completely parched
and her skin is breaking apart
and there's fire
coming from inside.
And I thought the concept
was really cool.
Yeah, thank you.
I appreciate it.
Before you leave-- one thing
that I feel went unsaid,
I think your demon
is the strongest silhouette
in profile.
I think that the lines
that you achieve
with the back of the head
and along the back
are absolutely gorgeous.
- Thank you.
- Derek, please step back.
All right, well, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup trailers
while they share their thoughts
with each other
and the viewers.
I'm hoping when the judges
look at tonight's work,
that they're not just
looking at tonight's work.
I hope that they're
looking at my body of work.
And I really hope that
this is the start
of a great career for me.
We're all waiting
to see what happens.
I'm really nervous,
but I'm also really hopeful.
Laura's makeup
looks really good.
Nicole's looks really good.
So it's anybody's game,
I think.
All right, let's talk about
each of our finalists' makeups.
Let's start with Nicole.
Now she chose water
for her witch's element.
- She's the comeback kid.
- Yeah, she is.
She did such a cohesive job
with design and fabrication.
It looked like it was done
by the same artist.
I really loved the way
she colored everything.
It looked like it was glowing.
I loved the headpiece
that was all coral coming out.
That was really a cool idea.
Yeah.
All of that said,
I did have some huge problems
with the demon.
The blockiness
of that sculpture.
Mm-hm.
For me, she could have played
with the horn a little more.
Just give them a more
aquatic look, if you may.
Yeah.
She's done some amazing stuff
since she's come back as well.
Since her resurrection,
she's just gotten better
and better and better.
For me it is really,
really special.
And to see someone
that just basically
almost dropped the ball,
and to become
one of the very, very top
in the group is-- wow.
What do you think
of Derek's work?
He chose fire for his element.
I think that the amount
of work that Derek and his team
accomplished
is quite impressive.
Yeah.
They seem to have
worked well together.
The demon, for me, was cool.
I just thought it was really
a great idea that it was so pale
and looked like
it had been buried.
Yeah. Although I did
really enjoy the lines of it--
Absolutely.
The face, I have
a huge problem with.
It's okay to have teeth
on the surface as a feature
of a creature, but that piece
should be solid and hard.
Yeah.
Looking back at Derek's
career with us, I mean,
the Dishonored thug
was awesome.
Oh, yeah, with
the white dreads.
- Yeah.
- That was good.
He's a very good visual artist.
And that leaves us with Laura.
She chose earth.
- The witch was fantastic.
- Yeah.
It was interesting that
she chose to use a charcoal
to do the coloring on the roots,
it was so terrific.
Oddly, conversely,
the demon was not.
Yes. In this final makeup,
I don't feel Laura's touch.
It doesn't feel
like her work to me.
You know, upon reflection
of Laura's previous makeups,
she's done some
really amazing things
with regard to execution
and the grace of her sculpture.
I think that she has
the best application skills
and the best sense of color.
She's perhaps the best
makeup artist on the show.
Derek is probably the best
at communicating his concepts
because of his drawing skills.
And Nicole's just been able
to knock 'em out of the park.
- Just pull things together.
- Yeah, she--
Create new energy.
Ultimately, we're gonna leave
it up to our audience tonight.
- Yes.
- Yeah. Phew!
They've got a tough decision,
because I'm torn tonight.
- Yeah.
- Exactly.
Well, it looks like America
has a tough decision
on their hands.
Let's bring 'em back out.
Okay, America, you've heard
what the judges have to say.
It is now up to you.
Here's another look
at tonight's makeups,
along with details on how
you can vote for your favorite.
To vote for Laura,
call 1-855-55-FACE-1.
That's 1-855-553-2231.
Or text LAURA to 79391.
To vote for Nicole,
call 1-855-55-FACE-2.
That's 1-855-553-2232.
Or text NICOLE to 79391.
To vote for Derek,
call 1-855-55-FACE-3.
That's 1-855-553-2233.
Or text DEREK to 79391.
Please dial carefully.
These are 855,
not 888 or 800 numbers.
Voting will remain open
until 7:00 pm eastern
on Halloween night.
Please tune in tomorrow
as we crown
the season three winner
of Face Off.
Live, Halloween night,
right here on SyFy.
For more information,
or to vote online,
please visit syfy.com/faceoff.
You can begin casting
your votes right now.
Good night.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net