Previously on Face Off...
The artists created
original zombies
inspired by Alice's Adventures
in Wonderland.
Oh, my God!
Roy's terrifying queen
carried him to victory,
and Nicole was sent home.
Now eight artists remain.
Tonight they'll tackle
a challenge
of heroic proportion.
Yes!
I'm excited
about this challenge.
I do not like this shit.
I don't like
what I'm sculpting.
I need to start over.
The mold cracked.
And I'm gonna be
in serious trouble.
And onstage their work
will be showcased
before an entertainment icon.
Boy, what a bunch
of hard-asses.
You didn't do a good job.
I could be the one going home.
In the end, only one
will win the opportunity
to be a guest lecturer
at Makeup Forever's academies
in New York and Paris,
a new 2012 Toyota Prius V,
and $100,000.
And for the first time ever--
America, your voice
will be heard
in selecting the winner.
Only one will win Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
I miss her already.
Nicole's eliminated,
and I'm devastated.
I don't think
she deserved to go home.
And if it wasn't gonna be me,
it was gonna be Rod.
No way was Nikki going home.
I thought you were
gonna go home too.
Nicole was my best friend
in the house.
It felt terrible.
I thought that I should have
gone home over her.
I just want to get back
in the shop
and not make
another catastrophe.
in front of this huge cave.
Welcome to Bronson Caves.
This location has been used
in countless films.
However, it's probably
best known as the entrance
to the bat cave in the classic
Batman television series.
What?
Superheroes come
in all shapes and sizes.
So, working together
in teams of two,
your spotlight challenge
is to create the superhero
and sidekick that would use
one of these vehicles.
Cars start coming
around the corner,
and they're the coolest ever...
Is that a Lamborghini?
From every genre
and style and time period.
What the heck is that?
- Aw, yeah!
- Yeah!
All right, your teams
have been randomly selected,
and they are...
Derek and Sarah...
Jason and Rod...
Laura and Tommy...
Alana and Roy.
- Yeah, buddy.
- All right.
Alana's sweet,
but she's also very flighty.
So I'm pretty sure I'm gonna
have to take the lead on this.
Okay, if everybody would stand
with their new team member.
All right, so these
are the vehicles you have
to choose from today--
The Dodge Charger,
the Tatra T87,
the AJS Motorcycle,
the Lamborghini Gallardo,
the Space Mole,
and the Humber Pig
Armored Truck.
All right, it is time
to select your vehicles.
Derek and Sarah?
The AJS Motorcycle
with sidecar.
Jason and Rod.
- Tatra T87.
- T87.
- Alana and Roy.
- Let's do the Charger.
And Tommy and Laura.
We'll take the battle tank.
So, before you get started
on your designs,
I would like to introduce you
to a special guest
who knows a thing or two
about impressing our judges.
He also happens to be
a very gifted concept designer
and will consult with each
of you on your designs today.
Come on out!
- Yeah!
- Awesome!
Hey, buddy!
It's Rayce,
the winner of season two.
He has a really good eye
for detail.
Everything he did last year
just was very unique.
So I'm really looking forward
to see what he thinks
of our design.
Everybody please say hello
to the season-two winner
of Face Off, Rayce Bird.
Hey.
What have you been up to
since you won Face Off?
Um, I've been doing a lot
of conceptual-design work--
Anything from the digital stuff
to the makeup stuff.
Of course, tattooing has gotten
out of control as well.
- I can only imagine.
- So, yeah.
All right, guys, get started.
♪
- Just draw, homey, just draw.
- Okay.
What I'm playing with
is a weak, wealthy person
being driven in that great car.
Rod and I decided the Tatra
will inspire our superhero
and sidekick.
- Jason.
Rod.
We don't know
the superhero thing that well,
so the challenge is pretty
difficult for both of us.
Tell me a little bit
about what your plan is.
The idea is the person
in the back seat
is the brains of the operation,
and then the driver
is the muscle.
But the passenger
will be controlling the driver.
Build your story
based off of the vehicle--
The shapes, the way it flows.
It could even be
some kind of a vein pattern
- that flows that way.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, so we decided
to go with a female hero
with a sidekick.
So we came up with
the characters fire and chaos.
Fire is the daughter
of the devil,
and her imp is there
to cause trouble,
but also to keep her
out of trouble.
What's cool
about this specific flame
is the circular pattern,
so play with the small circles.
Also, incorporate
something into him
that creates a cohesion.
It could even be just
the way the shapes move
and flow across the body.
So basically she is
a military experiment
that has escaped.
And she can do whatever
she wants with her body.
Like, it can morph
into whatever it needs to be
and that's why she's looking
a bit more badass.
The sidekick is a soldier.
He's in love with this woman.
He loses it and breaks her out.
He blows a wall
inside the laboratory,
and he blows half his face off.
Now, this is
a very big, black vehicle.
So, even if you put
some blocky stuff on her
or a little more rigidity,
you should be very careful
of how you integrate it.
So tell me a little bit
about what you got going on?
We both want to go
with the superhero
that doesn't have superpowers,
but is more like Batman.
We would like a girl and a guy.
We keep thinking definitely a
female Indiana Jones superhero.
Even if it's a very
normal-looking character
- with normal features...
- Mm-hmm.
It can still have some
of those subtle details
of the bike--
You know, how it's very busy,
it's very dirty.
That can lead
to some kind of a scar.
It's the details that are gonna
help relate to the vehicle
you guys have chosen.
Hey, guys, everything's
looking really good.
Good luck. Go ahead and make
your way back to the shop
and get these things rolling.
- Thanks.
- Thanks, Rayce.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, guys.
I love superheroes.
I grew up learning how to draw
from comic books,
so I'm excited
about this challenge.
First thing I want to do
is start sculpting.
I'm gonna work on the sidekick,
and Sarah is gonna work
on the superhero look.
Our concept is to go
with brains and brawn.
I'm going to attempt
to be the brain,
and Jason's going to be
the brawn.
His skin's
a little rough there,
with the veins
coming out of it.
One here, one here,
and then one on top.
Alana and I came up
with the concept fire and chaos.
I'm gonna work on chaos.
She's gonna work on fire.
My concern is even though
Alana's a good sculptor,
I just don't know
how fast she is.
I look at Laura's sculpt,
and it is very, very similar
to my own.
And I'm confused.
Why does Laura's headpiece
look like fire?
I've just been pushing around
clay for, like, an hour,
and it's just not translating
as a burn for me.
I don't know what
the fuck to do.
- Yeah.
- I do not like this shit.
I've never sculpted
a burn makeup.
It's supposed to look like
he's gotten hamburger-meated.
- I'm just gonna go with it.
- Totally.
It's a simple, simple sculpt.
It took me way too long
to wrap my head around it.
It's taking me way too long
to put the small amount of clay
that I put on the face.
So then I decide to jump over
to make the headpiece,
which is what will give
our superheroes
their superpowers.
I start with foam sheets.
That's not going the way
I want it to go.
So then I decide
I'm just gonna sculpt.
But I'm just not happy
with anything that I'm doing.
And I have a lot
of catching up to do.
One hour, three minutes.
I didn't think this
would be as hard as it is.
Alana's making the flames
way too small,
and flames
are really hard to sculpt.
I'm starting to get worried.
Okay, maybe this
is just a bad way to go.
Fire isn't choppy.
It's smooth. It's flowing.
It's alive almost.
Okay, guys, that's it!
Time's up!
I spent five hours
sculpting a face piece
that I am not happy with.
And, like, that's pathetic.
Let's get this.
It's day two
of the superhero challenge,
and I don't like
what I'm sculpting.
I'm disappointed in myself.
I really need to step my game
up, or else I'm gonna go home.
Bye.
I need to start over.
I'm, like, losing it.
I don't know
what I'm doing here.
I really don't.
I'm disappointed in the way
that this is going.
We could be in serious trouble.
Coming up...
- Fuck.
- Oh, no.
The mold cracked.
Rod, Ve wants to come back
really quick.
I just want to say
one more thing to you.
Wow.
I know I'm in trouble.
Joining our panel this week,
Kevin Smith.
Thanks for having me, man.
I'm ready to judge.
Bye.
It's day two
of the superhero challenge,
and I need to boogie down
and restart the sculpture
because I don't like it.
It's not a winning piece.
It's not something
that's even commendable.
I'm starting my sculpture over.
That's how brave I am.
Changed my whole design.
Alana has this new excitement
about starting this piece,
and I'm starting to feel
a lot better about it.
I can actually see these
characters driving around
in the Dodge Charger.
Starting over.
I'm sculpting faster
than I think I ever have
and I'm loving the way
that this is pulling together.
And I think it
looks more cohesive
with Roy's sidekick.
- I like the bat nose.
- Thank you.
- I love her so much now.
- Good.
I feel so much better
about the situation.
- How many hours we got today?
- Ten.
Awesome.
I'm gonna need 12 of them.
I'm still a little down
about how much work
I got done yesterday,
but I have a ton
of energy today.
First thing I do
is get my face done...
- That works, right?
- It's working.
The headpiece, which
is the device that controls
the brains to the brawn,
and now I'm sculpting
the chest piece.
I'm not happy with the piece
I sculpted,
but it needs to be molded
by the end of the day.
We have a lot of work to do,
so we start molding.
We need to get this ready to go
by the end of the day,
so we have our appliances
ready for the morning.
We're molding together.
I'm helping her out.
She's helping me out.
We're really working as a team.
Yeah.
Derek and I are doing
everything in silicone.
So we need to get all of our
sculpting finished and molded
so that we can get
the silicone run,
and then we can focus
on making the props.
I honestly don't know
where Sarah's spending
all of her time.
Her design is very minimal.
It's an eye patch and a scar.
It seems like Derek is doing
most of the work.
I decide to go
with silicone again.
I'm hoping that it'll look good,
but I'm worried
about the weight of his face
and chest pieces.
Yeah.
All right, thank you.
Derek and I
are fabricating the props.
I'm making some goggles,
and he's making a helmet.
Hmm.
Are you doing
the goggles on it?
I'm thinking I am,
so it saves time.
Awesome.
I ended up spending lots of time
fabricating something
I don't need.
Sarah looks a little frustrated
'cause we're not
on the same page.
Hopefully we'll
get everything tied up.
Hey, everybody,
I am here with Ve.
We're gonna do
a little walk-through
and see how you're doing.
Let's go.
Tell us your concept
of what you're creating
for a superhero and a sidekick.
This character is a scientist.
He's always been
wheelchair-bound.
As the brains of the operation,
he really needs muscle
to do all the harder work.
So the same apparatus
that he would be using
to make himself smarter,
we're going to put
onto the stronger guy,
so it would make him
super strong.
This guy looks very familiar.
He kind of looks like that weird
guy inside that pod suit...
- The queen also.
- And the queen.
Now you got three of them
that are very similar.
No.
Ve says, "it looks like
everything else you've done."
This is not good.
I will take note of that.
'Cause I won't be the only one
that will recognize that fact.
No, no.
She's giving me a hint now.
Change this, or there's probably
going to be trouble ahead.
Thank you.
Good luck.
It's never a good thing
when judges come through
and then say, "you should
probably change everything
about your sculpture."
We're doing minimal
prosthetics on her.
She has a big scar
across her lip.
You might consider taking
the scar down a little bit.
She probably is attractive,
and you don't want to remove
that element
from your superhero.
Try to keep her
as sexy as possible,
especially if she's
in that '40s genre.
I'd actually already
finished casting the scar,
so Derek and I
look at each other.
We're kind of like,
"well, let's pull it apart,
see what it looks like,
and then maybe we can just
quick re-sculpt it."
- We got the Dodge Charger.
- Love that.
Our characters' names
are Fire and Chaos.
Fire and Chaos, all right.
And Fire is
a daughter of the devil.
Chaos is sent along with her
as her guardian/troublemaker.
- What color is she gonna be?
- I'm sticking with reds.
But she's not
gonna be solid red?
- Oh, of course not.
- Good girl.
No, no.
We took the humber.
The giant tank.
The battle tank.
I'm pretty much concentrating
on the hero,
and he's got the sidekick.
Oh, so you did all
the sculpting on this.
- You did this.
- Mm-hmm.
This is her,
and she can morph her skin.
She's gonna have claws
and things that--
She's just combat ready.
It looks like
you're really going for it.
- I'm trying.
- Okay, good.
So what are your thoughts
of Rod and Jason?
They have the brains
and the brawn characters.
Yeah. He's repeating himself,
you know?
- A third time.
- Mm-hmm.
We don't want to see
the same thing every time.
Okay, let's move on
to Derek and Sarah.
I like their concept
and everything,
but they've really got to work
on their female.
Because they don't want to make
that female unattractive.
It's not gonna make
for a good superhero.
Next we have Alana and Roy.
They're really
kind of a cohesive group.
They've got their backstory.
They're trying
to pull off a lot.
I hope they can do that.
All right, so let's
move on to Laura and Tommy.
I think they're
cool characters.
I don't know
if it's a cohesive idea.
A superhero that can morph--
Okay, cool.
Okay, everybody,
we are heading out.
It's looking good.
Good luck tomorrow.
Bye, everybody.
Bye, guys.
Okay.
After Ve's concerns
about my sculpture,
I'm determined to change
everything in this face
so nothing is similar.
So I start to reshape
the entire face.
Rod, Ve wants
to come back really quick.
I just want to say
one more thing to you.
The judges never come back.
This must be worse
than I thought.
Okay.
Ve hinted that I should change
my sculpture.
So I'm determined to change
everything in this face
so nothing is similar.
Rod, Ve wants
to come back really quick.
I just want to say
one more thing to you.
Wow.
Ve coming back is serious.
I know I'm in trouble.
I like the fact that
you've taken off some wrinkles,
but it still looks
like the same guy.
So start thinking
about doing something
a little bit more aquiline,
to change the look
of the character.
I don't want to say too much,
but no droopy round-face guys.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
Our inspiration
is the battle tank.
So I start working on my gun arm
and immediately change the idea
from it being a flamethrower arm
to being a grenade-launcher arm.
Boom!
I go back to molding
my hand pieces.
Fuck!
And the mold cracked.
Whenever you have a crack
in the mold,
one thing's gonna happen
for sure-- it's gonna break.
Cracked along the fingers.
The fingers curled up.
The piece just fell all apart,
and it's too late in the day
to scrap the whole thing
and start over again.
So I've decided to risk it
and just finish the molds
the way that they are.
To piece it back together again,
it looks like Frankenstein,
'cause it's all these pieces
just jammed together
with bubble gum and good luck.
I just keep on looking
at the clock, going...
Mm.
I'm being forced
to re-sculpt the face
in a very short amount of time.
Is this square enough?
And then also,
is it just a good makeup?
You know, more importantly,
is it gonna move
on his face well?
This sculpt
I'm just not thrilled with,
but this is the best I can do
in this amount of time.
- That's really coming together.
- No, it's not.
- It's falling apart...
- Oh.
Is the problem.
Try some epoxy.
- Some what?
- Epoxy.
Thank you.
I managed to salvage the molds,
so I poured some polyfoam
into them
to give them more stability.
I also need to keep
the molds hollow
for the actor's hands.
So I saran-wrap my arm...
And then insert my arm
into the molds
while the polyfoam is curing.
I'm absolutely slow.
Rod's really behind.
I'm just trying to make sure
our superheroes get done.
So I have to do
as much as I can,
but it's just a lot
of weight to carry
when you know
you're already behind.
I don't care
what this looks like,
it just needs to be done
by the end of the day.
That's time, everybody!
Because of this re-sculpt,
Jason and I didn't get to do
many other things
that needed to take place.
I don't like waiting
till the last minute,
but we have no choice.
Okay.
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab
and then one hour left
on last looks.
Jason has a silicone appliance
that he has to apply now.
I have my prosthetic.
But we really need
to get two neck pieces
and two headpieces
run in polyfoam.
All of this is using up
our very limited amount of time
to actually do applications.
See that flamethrower
back there?
- Yeah.
- That's you.
These are your headpieces.
This is what gives you,
uh, your superpowers.
This is ripping everywhere.
I put a shellac coating over
my cowl when I ran the foam,
but I didn't let
the shellac dry,
and it caused my foam to burn.
If you burn foam,
it's not stretchy anymore,
and it will tear very easily.
Just...
And that's what's happening.
It's a hot mess.
We are gonna be using silicone
for this project.
I've never worked with silicone,
but I want to try to get
that transparency that's just
a little different than foam.
It's a little heavier,
so I'm a little worried
about applying it.
How much longer on that, Alana?
Done. I'm just
waiting for it to dry.
Okay, don't worry
about that right now.
Go ahead and get started
on Jenny.
Alana's job is to apply
the bald caps,
and it's just taking forever.
Yo, Alana, it doesn't
have to be pretty.
It just has to be functional.
The silicone
was not the right color
for his skin,
so I have to airbrush
the whole thing a new color.
So you kind of lose the effect
that silicone would give you
to begin with,
which is the translucency
that it has.
- Laura.
- Yes, sir?
- It's just not working.
- What isn't?
This whole thing.
This is coming
out of the bald cap.
This is tearing up.
I'm thinking about taking
this fucking thing off.
Tommy is having some issues.
The cowl ripped.
The edges were bad.
It's just a spiral
of bad coincidences.
Just stick to the plan.
All this can be covered
with hair,
- and we'll hide it.
- All right.
Just keep going.
All right.
The whole time that
we're doing the application,
I'm worried that
I don't have enough stuff.
Everybody else
has way more prosthetics
or at least bigger prosthetics.
Got the beauty makeup to do,
also a really cool hairstyle.
So I'm hoping
that's gonna be enough.
Roy, we got 30 minutes left.
We got less
than 30 minutes left.
♪
- And that's time, everyone!
- Awesome.
- That's it.
Time.
All right, everybody, let's go.
I'm definitely feeling
a little nervous.
I'm a little worried
about the jaw.
It's a little heavy.
There's a big chin.
Big lips.
And, uh, I haven't glued it
down yet.
So I have to do that
during last looks.
Coming up...
Anything can happen
when you walk out onstage.
Everything about it
screams comic book to me.
She just looks like
she has dirty makeup on.
It's last looks. I have
one hour to complete my makeup.
I'm not happy about
how far behind Rod and I are.
I still have to airbrush
the whole thing
and lay down his eyebrows,
lay down some hair work
around his forehead.
But anything can happen
when you walk out onstage.
- Do you see his chin, Derek?
- I'll get it.
- Okay.
- Open your mouth.
I have to finish
gluing down the jaw,
and it's not staying.
The jaw seems
a little to heavy.
Are you about done on painting?
Almost done. I'm just about
to get those flames on her,
but I don't know
how to do that.
Alana's job is to apply
the flames on her arms.
She starts panicking
a little bit.
I'm so worried
about this not working out.
- You think it will work?
- Stop worrying.
I tell you what to do
and you do it-- that's it.
Take tape, wrap around it,
pull the gloves up.
- She's done.
- You look like a superhero.
Five minutes, everybody!
Five minutes!
- Excuse me.
- Yeah, get the flamethrower.
Excuse me, coming through.
And that's time, everyone.
Brushes down.
- Brushes down.
- All right.
I'm not sure how it's gonna go.
We did our best.
We both know that
this is not our strength.
It's not something
that I'm really proud of.
Oh, my God!
Welcome
to the Face Off reveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
Say hello to your judges--
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick...
- Hello.
- Hi.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill...
- Evening, guys.
- Hey.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page...
Hello.
- Hey.
- Hello.
And joining our panel
this week...
He's an actor,
writer, and director
with a huge fan following
for films like Clerks, Dogma,
and most recently, Red State.
He also runs a podcast empire
at smodcast.com.
Please give a warm welcome
to Kevin Smith.
Whoo!
Hi.
This is phenomenal, man.
I literally feel like
I'm on the deck
of a star destroyer.
Kevin Smith is an amazing
writer/director/
comic-book enthusiast.
I love Kevin Smith.
I got into filmmaking
because of Kevin Smith.
He made me believe
that I could do it myself.
Well, thank you so much
for being here.
Thanks for having me, man.
I'm ready to judge.
- That's what I'm here for.
- Fantastic.
Well, everyone knows that
you are a huge comic-book fan.
You've even written
for Daredevil, Batman.
In your opinion,
what does it take
to make a great superhero?
You got to kill
their parents early on.
- Really?
- Oh, hands down.
Orphans, that's what makes
a great superhero.
This week your spotlight
challenge was to create
a superhero and sidekick
that would use the vehicles
you chose.
So let's see
what you came up with.
Our models walk out onstage,
and I love the contrast
between the two,
and I am hoping
that the judges realize
that the contrast
was deliberate.
It fits the genre
of what we were going for
the best we could,
so I'm not sure
how this is gonna go.
Overall, the look of everything
and the cohesion
that the characters have
with the background,
with the motorcycle--
we're both feeling
pretty good about it.
I can't keep my eyes
off of Britney.
I think she's popping.
I think she's so confident.
And Jenny is just
this cute little imp
and just, like,
scurrying along behind her,
and it just looks fabulous.
Judges, why don't you
take a closer look.
I go right for the nails.
What does that say about me?
Well, see the inside
of your hands.
See, to me, that's
kind of interesting.
This is the edge
of the bald cap.
His muscles are getting so big
that he's busting out
of his skin.
That sculpture
does not say that to me.
I'm just hoping that ve
can see that I listened to her.
I changed everything.
It may not be enough.
I mentioned to Rod
that all of his sculptures
were looking very similar.
He's changed it a little bit,
but it still
looks like the same guy.
I sense trouble.
I could be the one going home.
We want to know what you think
of tonight's transformations.
I mentioned to Rod
that all of his sculptures
were looking very similar.
I see ve talking
to the other judges
about the face that I did.
He's changed it a little bit,
but it still looks like
the same guy.
And that is nerve-racking.
Now, this is
kind of interesting.
Can you open your mouth?
I hate mouth inside of mouth.
I just don't know what this is.
I mean, it's undefined.
Looks like he's into scars.
Well, it's supposed
to be a scar, yes.
Oh, my God.
Can I touch this?
Tilt your head down
so we can take a look
at how this all integrates
in what's going on up here.
Looks like there
might have been some horns
supposed to be here.
How does it feel to wear?
- All right.
- That's important.
You don't want to be on set
with somebody that's like,
"get it off!"
Move your hand.
This is the character
I most identified with.
Kevin, you're a super fan.
What do you think?
This is stuff I've dreamed
about since I was a kid.
Back when I was a youngster,
I wanted to do special effects
and makeup.
You guys
did a great, great job.
The judges would like to speak
with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Laura and Tommy,
please step up.
Start us off
telling us the backstory.
Arthur Flynn,
AKA Kid Dynamite--
he's a special ops
demolition expert,
and he notices
his love is captured,
and he's like,
"I'm gonna break her out."
So he's lighting
all this dynamite,
and it blows off his hand
and my goggles.
And his face gets torn to crap,
but he rescues Thorn,
and they both
are on the run now.
Laura, I see one
of the only makeups
with elements
of existing superheroes.
It feels like
a mutant superhero.
I think that the work
that you did as a team
is extremely polarized.
In plain English,
I like that...
And I hate that.
Tommy, your guy looks
like a football player
that got put
through a meat grinder.
Laura has got
a complete makeup job there.
Your attention to detail,
with her nails, her fingers,
everything is still on her.
She's all intact,
and she's beautiful.
Boy, what a bunch
of hard-asses.
They both are very evocative.
This is very Geiger-esque
on this side.
This over here,
Toxic Avenger-esque.
I think that's cool
because it calls to mind
something immediately.
But I love this.
This is fun for me.
- Please step back.
- Thank you.
Jason and Rod,
please step forward.
Now, tell me
what makes these guys
as cool as that car back there?
Um, these headpieces
are what gives them superpowers.
We immediately thought,
just looking at that the car,
that that's a rich person's car,
for sure.
And they would have a driver and
that would be a good disguise
to go with during the day.
Yesterday when
I did the walk-through,
I had a really long talk
with you,
- not once, but twice...
- Yes.
About not doing the same guy.
Let me just say this-- it still
looks like the same guy.
Mm-hmm.
He's got a fat head
like all the other guys did.
Mm-hmm.
And you did not change
the mouth.
It still has
a turned-down mouth.
I'm disappointed that you didn't
think out of your little box
with your fat head.
Now, as far as you go,
explain to me
what those pieces
are supposed to be.
That's supposed to be,
like, when he gets pumped up
from the superpowers,
his skin is splitting
and cracking.
It doesn't really
read like that.
It just looks like weird patches
of some kind of growth
he has going on.
And as far as you using silicone
on his face,
you've destroyed it
by painting it too dark.
Your concept--
muscles expanding
and skin tearing--
you didn't do a good job
conveying that.
You put a coat over it,
and we can't see it.
Do you mind
taking your coat off?
The guy's got
an incredible physique.
Don't put him in a coat.
It's gonna automatically
feel superhero.
The devices that you created
as props are bothersome to me,
because it's a cool idea,
but there's no level
to the detail.
It's just a flat thing.
I don't know why
you picked floppy foam.
It's not even sitting
on their heads correctly.
Jason, Rod...
Step back.
Derek and Sarah.
Real quick--
explain the concepts.
When we saw the bike,
we thought Dick Tracy
meets Indiana Jones.
The detail
of the lower-jaw piece--
it doesn't work for me
when I see that his bottom lip
is somewhere
buried in the makeup.
As soon as you
bake in an expression,
you do not give your character
the opportunity to emote
beyond what we see here.
Sarah, for you,
it's kind of cool,
but I just don't see the work.
I like the insignia
that you guys came up with.
Shocking nobody else
has done that yet.
This feels most like
a superhero team to me.
Thank you.
The eye patch-- in your mind,
how does it stay on?
Glue.
Why would she
glue her eye patch on?
There's riveted plate
all over your vehicle.
Doesn't it make more sense to
have used the riveted-plate idea
that was so conspicuous?
Yeah, that's what you said.
Okay, guys,
explain to me--
it looks like this
should have been up higher.
Did it just slip?
- It's just slipping.
- Dang.
Sarah, I know yesterday
when I saw your sculpture,
which was this humongous thing
that was gonna be on her mouth--
I'm really glad
that you didn't do that,
but I think you might have gone
a little too far
in the other direction.
She just looks like
she has dirty makeup on.
And that's kind of unfortunate.
Derek, Sarah, please step back.
Thanks, guys.
Alana and Roy.
This-- I can't
take my eyes off of it.
I need to know the backstory,
'cause this reminds me
of me and my wife, man.
Tall, hot chick,
trolly-looking dude
sitting at her knee
trying to get some play.
This is Fire and Chaos.
Fire is a daughter of Satan,
and she's curious
about the human world,
so she comes to the surface,
and Chaos is sent along
to cause trouble.
The way you did the flames
is really cool.
This reminds me
of a comic book.
Please give us what each
of your contributions were.
I sculpted the face.
I cut out all the pieces
of accuform here.
I assisted Roy
in his creature suit.
And Roy did
a lot of work as well.
This is the only team
that represents
comic-book art to me.
And I don't even need to ask
how it matches the vehicle,
which is awesome.
I think the two characters meld
together really well as well.
- Thank you.
I know that you had sculpted
a whole different sculpt, right?
You were trying
to put the flames
into her head, into the makeup,
and you switched over to this.
I think that was probably
a really good choice.
I would love to see them driving
down the street together.
That would be hysterical.
Alana, Roy,
will you please step back?
Thank you, guys.
Thank you, ladies.
All right, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
Please head back
to the makeup room
while they make
their decisions.
All right, guys, why don't
we talk about the looks
you liked the most?
Let's start with Laura
and Tommy.
I think that one of the
strongest things about this team
is that Laura's concept
is very X-Men superhero to me.
Laura does succeed
in making sure she fills the--
She took
the comic-book thing literally.
- Yep.
- All right, let's do this.
I think that was brilliant.
The paint job
was really striking,
and I think she
has a great silhouette.
It's very superhero-looking.
The kid dynamite thing
was not nearly as strong.
The thick neck
kind of throws you off.
Laura's definitely superhero,
and for that reason
and that reason alone,
this team ends up
in the top looks.
All right, let's move on
to Alana and Roy.
Very colorful.
I mean, they were definitely
the most colorful duo out there.
The flames on the character
that she created
is immediately
recognizable to me
as an actual
comic-book character.
This week, that's
making me love this makeup.
Let's move on to the looks
you liked the least--
Jason and Rod's.
Jason and Rod just didn't feel
like as much effort was put in.
The idea was really clever,
the execution not so much.
The costume choices were
bizarre, to say the least.
There was nothing,
and particularly Jason--
this guy had such
a fantastic physique.
Yes.
He wanted him to be the muscle,
and we barely see the muscle.
It's like a little
peek-a-boo sport coat.
Let's talk about the fact
that he used silicone
and then painted
this guy's face so dark.
His face was, like, about five
shades darker than his body.
Rod, for me, is failing
this week once again.
I specifically said to him,
"you have to change
the anatomy of this character
because it's the same person
we've seen every single time."
All right, let's move on
to Derek and Sarah.
There's nothing happening
on the female character.
I didn't care
for the wee eye patch
that is wood grain
that has no means of attachment.
Yeah.
It would have looked badass--
one spike right through
the middle of it.
It tells a story,
where you're like,
"oh, my God, that's how
it's stuck into her head?"
I was looking
for anything that told me
there was a reason
it was glued on.
My issue wasn't with her
as much as with him.
He reads as, "hey, I came
from the depths of hell."
More monster-ish.
This makeup was
as muddy as it gets.
Yep.
Okay, judges, have you
made your decisions?
- Yes.
- I believe we have.
- Let's bring them back out.
- Yeah.
Okay, Glenn, tell us
about the top teams.
Our top teams tonight
are Gloria and Tommy.
The Dynamite character
was a bit of a mess,
but Thorn was
a really cool superhero
and helped hold it through.
Alana and Roy...
Your makeups both successfully
evoked the comic-book feel
we were looking for this week.
All right, so which team
came out on top?
Our top team tonight is...
All right, so which team
came out on top?
Our top team tonight is...
Alana and Roy.
You guys did a lot
of work this week,
and you provided us with
two very complete characters,
not to mention it tied in
really nicely with the car,
which was a huge part
of the challenge.
Well done.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you, guys.
Roy and Alana, great job.
But we can only have one winner.
So, Glenn...
Our winner tonight is...
Alana.
Your character really
felt like she had stepped out
of the pages of a comic book--
Congratulations.
Thank you so much.
This is the best makeup
I've ever done, ever.
And I know how much
Roy contributed to this as well.
But I could hear
the hallelujah chorus.
I'm like, "Lord, take me now."
Alana, congratulations.
You and Roy can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you.
Laura, Tommy,
you are also safe this week.
You can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you.
- Bye, Mr. Smith.
Uh, Mr. Smith
is my father, sir, so...
Unfortunately, that means
the rest of you
are on the bottom this week.
One of you will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
All right, so, Glenn,
tell us about the bottom looks.
Jason and Rod--
Poor sculpting, painting,
prop design, decision making.
Not a whole lot
was working for you.
Sarah and Derek--
We liked the overall concept,
but we just weren't sure
how you spent all of your time.
It felt like
so much was missing.
So who's going home tonight?
The person going
home tonight is...
Jason.
Your sculpture
just didn't represent
your concept at all.
The painting wasn't realistic.
All right, thank you
for the opportunity.
Jason, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
The rest of you are safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
You know what, man?
Forget these fools right here.
Come work for me, man.
We got some light makeup work
that we can do some stuff on
over at Smodco, if you want to.
Excellent.
Jason, it has been great
having you here with us.
If you'll please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you, guys.
- Thank you.
- See you Monday, dude.
- Bring doughnuts!
- Jelly?
Yes!
- All right.
- Look at me-- of course jelly.
I like that kid.
It's me.
Aw, I'm sorry.
I'm disappointed
with the makeup that I just did,
and if I could do it again,
I'd do things differently.
It sucks to go home,
but if anybody
was gonna send me home,
at least it was Kevin Smith.
The fact that I made it
this far is cool.
So I'm gonna just keep on
doing what I'm doing.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net