Previously on Face Off...
In a monster-sized twist,
the eliminated contestants
return for a shot at redemption.
And Nicole fought her way
back into the competition.
Oh, my God.
In the spotlight challenge,
Laura's makeup
took her to the top.
And Rod was sent home.
Now only six artists remain.
Tonight they will
reinvent characters
from a legendary artist.
Your challenge this week
is based on a true classic.
Awesome!
And get judged
by a titan of Tinsel Town.
Oh, my God!
This is the biggest person
we've ever had on Face Off.
Dude, I'm just
not a happy camper.
This will be the one
that sends me home.
I have a lot to prove because
I got pulled back from the dead.
I'm just, like,
totally in turmoil.
I feel like such an idiot.
Your paint application
is a morbid failure.
Something about this
makes me smile.
In the end, only one
will win the opportunity
to be a guest lecturer
at Makeup Forever's academies
in New York and Paris.
A new 2012 Toyota Prius V
and $100,000.
And for the first time ever,
America, your voice
will be heard
in selecting the winner.
Only one will win Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
I wake up in the morning
and I just feel horrible.
I'm bummed to go into this day
without having Rod around.
Morning!
Girl.
What's up?
Alana's really sad.
Her best friend Rod is gone.
I'm concerned about her.
It just tore me up, you know?
Yeah.
I think that without Rod,
she's really confused
on how she's gonna do this
and it's all up to her now.
Come on, get up.
Let's go!
I don't wanna get up yet.
Get up, sleepyhead!
Let's go to work!
I'm just feeling
a little sour apples.
I miss my friend.
We are on
the Universal back lot.
Which is so awesome,
I've never been here before.
Oh, cool!
We come walking
around the corner
and there's snow on the ground.
Okay, so what is this place?
I'm freaking out
with excitement because
this is where
movie magic happens.
There's these two cars.
There's these crazy houses
with snow all over them.
And there's McKenzie.
Welcome to the set of Whoville,
on the Universal
Studios backlit.
- Awesome!
- Oh, my gosh.
This is one
of the many elaborate sets
used in the film,
How The Grinch Stole Christmas.
So for generations
the rhythmic words
and imaginative characters
of Dr. Seuss have been adapted
into numerous TV shows,
musicals and films.
Including The Cat In The Hat
and The Lorax.
So in honor
of its 50th anniversary,
your challenge this week
is based on a true classic.
Dr. Seuss's Sleep Book.
- That's cool.
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
- Yeah.
- I'm excited.
Dr. Seuss's Sleep Book
is about how they go to sleep.
It's just a really
good bedtime story.
Dr. Seuss had a knack
for making creatures
that have an almost
human-like quality to them.
With that in mind,
your spotlight challenge
is to select a character
from the Sleep Book
and use it to inspire
an original human-hybrid makeup
that captures
the essence of Dr. Seuss.
- Awesome.
- I love Dr. Seuss.
I can't think
of any other artist
that has such
a definitive style.
So right now
I would like to introduce
a very special guest
who definitely knows
a thing or two about
making a classic character.
He's an academy award-winning
producer for A Beautiful Mind,
has been nominated
for Apollo 13,
Frost/Nixon and Splash,
which he also co-wrote.
In total, he has produced
over 100 films.
Wow.
Please welcome
Mr. Brian Grazer.
Yay! Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my God!
Brian Grazer.
He's won an Oscar.
Wow. This is probably
the biggest person
we've ever had
in Face Off history.
Hi.
Thank you so much
for being here.
Thanks for having me.
You have made
so many great films,
including Dr. Seuss's
The Cat In The Hat,
The Grinch Who Stole Christmas.
So tell us, how were you
able to make it so successful?
To take Dr. Seuss's
imaginative characters
from the page and then
translate it to a screen?
Well, you want to feel
the reality and the truth
of the actor.
And so to do that the makeup
has to feel seamless and real
so that you're not distracted
by makeup that feels
in any way artificial.
Brian gives us
some great advice,
'cause as a producer
he has to look at all makeup's
and pretty much every aspect
of the films that he works on.
So he's somebody
at you want to listen to.
Okay, so what
you guys don't know
is that Brian is not
just a guest here today,
he's actually
going to be joining us
on the reveal stage to take
a look at your final creations.
Oh, wow.
All right, so displayed
behind me are the names
of eight characters
from Dr. Seuss's Sleep Book.
Each of you will get
to select one from which
to base your designs on.
Nicole, you get to pick first.
I really just like the sound
of Bumble-Tub.
So I grabbed Bumble-Tub.
Ian and I always go,
"Oof! Oof!"
- There you go.
- So Oof!
I don't know
what Alana's thinking.
She picks the only one
up there that has
nothing recognizable about it.
'Cause that's something
that her and her boyfriend say,
that's not a good enough reason
to pick a character for makeup.
Chippendale Mupp.
Foona-Lagoona Baboona.
The Hinkle-Horn Honker.
I think it just
sounds kind of fun.
I don't know
what it's gonna be.
Last but not least.
Snorter McPhail's
still on the board
and that's the one I pick.
So, cool, I'm excited to see
what this character looks like.
All right, guys, it is time
to get started on your designs
so grab a sketchpad
and get started.
I will see you all soon.
The challenge is to not only
create a Seuss character,
but it has to be
a human-hybrid character.
So the first thing obviously
is I need to figure out
what my character looks like.
I find out
the Hinkle-Horn Honkers
are these little yellow guys
with crazy hair, in beds,
and they are horn players.
I really like that they've
got long noses, big smiles,
and I can do some
really fun hair work.
I'm looking through the book
and Snorter McPhail
is a conductor
of snores that make music.
He has long ears,
so my idea is to do a hairstyle
with the hair long
like the ears.
And the nose, I'm gonna
make kind of like the Who nose
but more human-looking.
But still have that
pointy upward look to it.
My character is Bumble-Tub.
He sits in this little crate
and he floats down the river
with his sleep crew.
So there's Sleepy.
I'm sketching curly-Q's
on his head.
And then I want them to be big.
I wanna have this big belly,
these crazy fingers,
and lots of curly stuff.
I'm not really sure
how I'm gonna do this,
but it looks cool on paper.
I'm flipping through the book
and I'm flipping, I'm flipping.
I finally find my character.
And it looks like
a cotton ball puff monster.
There's really no detail at all.
It doesn't look like any animal.
Everyone else has characters
that resemble a dog or a dragon
or a chimp.
And I got this
cotton ball monster.
I got the
Foona-Lagoona-Baboona.
This is the picture and
I'm basically just thinking,
like, chimp that's
swinging from tree to tree.
I decided to go with
my character-- more human,
more realistic ape.
'Cause a human-hybrid
with Dr. Seuss
could be, like, what
the Grinch looks like.
Or it can be more human
than the Grinch.
So that's where
my concept's going.
Oh, your character looks cool.
Mine has a giant tail.
My character
is the Chippendale Mupp
and he'll bite his tail
right before he goes to sleep
and then about eight
or nine hours later,
he'll wake up again
and go, "ow!"
It's either gonna look cartoony
or really, really weird.
Everybody's doing amazing stuff
so it's gonna be hard.
It's anybody's game, I think.
We get back to the lab
and choose our models.
Immediately start sculpting.
I'm trying to get the nose
to look more human
and make it look real.
Oh, God.
- How would you do this bitch?
- Uh...
I'm miserable.
I have no feeling of inspiration
from this particular character.
I don't want
to do a big fur suit.
I just don't want
to say anything
and then the judges
not like it, you know?
I know, I just
want your advice.
I'm not gonna
be saying it--
'Cause really I'm just so lost.
You're really good
at this stuff.
I'm lost.
I think Alana
is worried about going home.
I'm thinking about doing,
like, a chubby girl.
Big head with this tail
on the top.
You could do that.
It doesn't seem like she has
a clue what she's gonna do.
Thank you.
I mean, I-- honestly,
I mean-- I don't know.
- Hi.
- What?
- Hello?
- Huh?
- Hey.
Since Nicole's been back
we've really started connecting.
She's a really cool chick.
I'm just glad I'm getting
to know her better.
- This is fun.
- Mm-hm.
I like this one.
I'm taking what
Brian Grazer said
and I'm using my model
and I'm going with the forms
of his face.
And I'm sculpting that out.
It's really looking
like something
that would happen naturally.
If he was turning into
a Seuss character.
You having fun, Laura?
My concept for
the Chippendale Mupp
human-hybrid...
it's a mix
of interesting genres.
And I thought, oh!
Dr. Moreau. Dr. Seuss.
That might be cool.
A little realistic
Dr. Moreau route
while still keeping
to the Dr. Seuss world.
Can I ask you what
you're doing for your costume?
- I am doing--
- Are you making him furry?
This.
Yeah.
Yours is more like
a pajamas, huh?
He is kind of but I don't know
if I want him in pajamas.
Pajamas would be cute.
'Cause this is a whole
sleepy, bedtime book.
Good idea.
Good. You're right.
You know?
- Hey, Roy.
- I'm just not a happy camper.
I'm trying to make sure
it doesn't look like the Grinch
but I can't really remember
what the Grinch
looks like either.
And that's looking
more and more like the Grinch.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Hold on, I'm trying
to figure it out.
This will be the one
that sends me home
because it has a big,
Grinchy grin on it.
I see everybody
knowing what direction
they want to take,
getting inspired.
How's it coming?
I'm just, like,
totally in turmoil right now.
I just wanna cry my eyes out.
I feel like such an idiot.
I don't know how
to make this work.
I just want to do
a great makeup and it's, like,
this huge chicken
with a mask on.
That's, like,
the number one thing.
- Alana, Alana--
- I, like, never want to do now.
I'm going home.
Like, I'm just so freakin'
defeated right now.
Coming up...
I'm gonna
paint it mustardy yellow
and then hints of brown.
But we're back
into that fun fur zone,
which is unfortunate.
Please welcome
Oscar-winning producer,
Brian Grazer.
I don't feel
the Seussian heartbeat.
Something about this
makes me smile.
Today is the first day
of our Dr. Seuss challenge.
And I'm a mess right now.
I just want
to do a great makeup--
- But here's-- listen.
- And it's, like, this huge...
- Okay.
- ...chicken.
Take a deep breath.
Use what you like to do,
which is use
the person's face, right?
Use that.
I'm still feeling
like I'm in trouble,
but I don't feel alone.
Give me a Sarah hug.
- That is too cool.
- Why, thank you.
It's looking more and more
like the Grinch.
I gotta change it.
I don't think it looks
anything like the Grinch.
Especially the eyes
and everything.
The most important part
is the face.
So hearing Nicole say that
gives me a lot of encouragement.
What you making with the wire?
- I wanna make his wand.
- Ah.
Kind of all swirly
like Dr. Seuss.
I'm gonna do some fabrication
'cause I want to get my makeup
detailed as much as possible.
I want to do a huge belly.
So it can be,
like, a human belly
but in the shape
of a Dr. Seuss character.
Five minutes.
By the end of the day,
I'm actually
in pretty good shape.
'Cause I've got
my face sculpted
and I actually have my body
halfway sculpted.
So tomorrow I'll just
be making the mold.
All right, that's it.
Let's go home.
I really have
so much work to do tomorrow.
So I really need to keep
my eyes on the prize here
and stay focused.
Good luck.
It's day two,
I've got ten hours.
In this challenge I have
to be top or, better yet, win.
And I cannot be bottom.
If I'm bottom,
I might as well leave.
I'm definitely going
for a more realistic sculpt.
So I find pictures of primates.
I'm gonna try to combine it
with the nose of a lion
and do the mouth
of an older person.
So this creature's
just a hodgepodge
of many different elements.
- Need help with that?
- Yeah.
Come on, then.
Great.
So this torso belly
is a really big piece.
I mean, I've got 250 pounds
of wet clay on it.
Got a lot of clay.
This is a gigantic mold.
This thing is gonna
be a nightmare.
We need, like,
a little mold gnome.
All right, give me your gnome.
It's time to mold.
I'm still not sure
how to color the hair.
The character
in the book is yellow,
but I see that a lot
of people are going for yellow.
So I definitely
want my character
to look different
than anybody else's.
- Hello, everybody.
- Hi, guys.
I have Ve with me.
We're gonna come
do a little walkthrough.
So I see Ve and I'm, like,
"I really don't want
to let you down.
Please say that I'm going
in the right direction."
Oh, my gosh, Ve.
Are you okay?
What's going on?
Look at that.
Oh, my gosh.
What am I gonna do?
It's called an Offt.
So I'm gonna do
a yellowy flesh tone.
Mm-hm.
And I really
want it to be a girl.
But I'm so lost here.
This is very masculine.
And I know she's supposed
to be, like, a little fluffy
but I wouldn't
put too many chins.
If you're going
for a little girl,
this is not gonna work for you.
Okay.
Is there a reason why
you wanna go with silicone
as opposed to foam?
I want it to have
that human flesh look to it.
'Cause it's supposed
to be a human-hybrid.
It's kind of heavy.
That's what
I'm worried about though.
So that's why I'm asking
for a little advice here.
Which way would you go?
Would you go foam or silicone?
I would go back
to foam personally.
- I dig your wig.
- I know. I love that.
That is really cool.
- So instead of the ears--
- Mm-hm.
I want to incorporate
the hairstyle.
Oh, look at the hair,
that's--
So it's more of a human-hybrid
kind of a thing.
- That's a cute idea.
- Smart.
What's his wardrobe?
All this is gonna be fur and
I'm gonna paint it
mustardy-yellow
and then hints of brown.
But we're back
into that fun fur zone
which is kind of unfortunate.
Fun fur is cheap-looking,
costume-y fur material
that doesn't look
professional enough.
I know Glenn does not
like fun fur
and I'm worried about it,
but my guy's
gonna be in fun fur.
So I have the
Hinkle-Horn Honker
and he's yellows
and greens with plum.
Everybody has yellow creatures
this week.
- I know.
- Yes.
It's gonna
be pretty interesting.
I'm hoping his hair
is the yellow-est part of him.
And the rest is gonna be
a little more flesh-esque.
Okay.
So Derek, he had
the Snorter McPhail.
I do like the idea of the hair,
then using it as the ears.
I love that.
Using that as ears.
- That, to me is--
- Yeah.
Adding in that Dr. Seuss
quality with a human aspect.
- Yeah, it will be great.
- So let's move on to Sarah's then.
I didn't really think
a lot of the sculpture.
Right.
I think the sculpture
was kind of weak.
We'll have to see
how that one comes together.
Exactly.
So let's move on to Alana.
I'm concerned it's not
gonna be a sweet little girl,
if that's what she's going for.
Right.
And plus she's got
the big ball for a suit again.
So that's kind of
a worry for me.
- Yeah.
- I don't know.
Sarah and Alana are
kind of my concerns right now.
The two that
you're concerned about?
- I can't wait for tomorrow.
- Me neither.
All right, gang,
we're heading out.
- It's looking good.
- Bye, everybody.
- Bye.
- Good luck.
Thank you.
Ve's not down with my character
and I'm just freaking out.
So I have to re-sculpt the face.
The cowl's not finished yet.
So I need to get it together
and keep moving
or else I'm gonna go home.
At this point I've pretty much
got everything done
that I needed to get done.
I wish I could listen
to music or something.
I don't know what to do,
I'm just bored.
I decide that
I'm going to fabricate a horn.
I take some armature wire
and foam tube
and wrap it around
this armature wire.
Spray paint everything.
I'm enjoying
what it looks like.
Hey, Roy.
I'm now left with
hardly any time at all
before the end of the day,
and my mold is not popped.
I'm getting really nervous.
Heat is what's gonna
cure this mold faster.
So I'm throwing
garbage bags over it.
Bringing two hair dryers up
to it and I'm trying to create
this heat bubble.
Time's running out
and if this mold is not cast
for tomorrow's application,
I'm not gonna
have anything here.
It's gonna be a nightmare.
Hey, Roy.
I don't know
if I can crack this.
I'm now left with
hardly any time at all
before the end of the day
and my md is not popped.
That there needs
to dry some more.
I'm totally in turmoil.
I'm having such a hard time
coming up with a concept.
But now I'm not even
gonna have a cowl
and that's the whole thing
that even inspired me
even a little bit
on this makeup.
I got all the hair
laid up where I want it.
The swirls are
turning out really well.
- Looks cool.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- I super-respect Derek.
I think he's awesome.
So for him to come over and
be, like, "dude," was awesome.
It, like, felt really good.
Originally I was gonna
make, like, a fur hood
to put overtop of the cowl.
But I'm running out of time.
I've opted to just
lay the hair by hand.
We have six minutes.
Time is running out
and my mold is not popped.
If this is gonna get done,
it needs to get done right now.
Do it carefully.
Carefully. Very carefully.
- He's coming.
- There we go.
So we all start going to town,
picking the clay
out of this mold.
Just slip it right out.
Get those little guys or you
won't have your little bumps.
Let's take it outside
and we'll clean it out there.
Oh, I could cry.
I love you guys so much.
A minute, 17.
All right.
This side's done.
Thank you.
- That's time, everybody.
- Thank you so much, dude.
Oh, man, what a day.
It's application day.
We have four hours to apply
and then one hour of last looks
at the stage.
Application day is really
the make or break day
for any of these makeup's.
'Cause I've heard
the judges say 1,000 times,
"you can save a bad prosthetic
with a good makeup.
You can also destroy a good
prosthetic with a bad makeup."
I'm ecstatic.
My foam came out amazing.
At this point it's all
a matter of time management
and to do all of the details.
Hee-hee-hee.
Good morning.
That's your costume.
You're a conductor
of a snoring band.
Oh, cool.
- I got a big noggin, huh?
- You got a big ol' noggin.
Lay your head back.
Immediately I start applying
the prosthetic on the model.
I'm taking my time.
It's not a big piece.
Trying to get
the edges really clean.
I definitely think I have
a shot at winning this one.
I think I have
a strong concept.
But I'm also kind of worried.
Did I do too little?
How does that feel, mama?
I get my pieces and my edges
are, like, thick wedges.
And on top of this,
I still don't even know
how or what I'm painting here.
I can't use
the same paint techniques
I've been using.
I need to challenge myself
and do something new.
I'm a fighter.
I'm not rolling over
and dying in this competition,
I need to keep pushing.
I don't like
this poofy right here.
With that fun fur on I'm, like,
"this is so bright yellow."
You're gonna look like
a frickin' chicken.
I'm really, like,
not liking this color.
Oh, lord.
You're fluffy today.
The gloves are taken care of.
The feet are taken care of.
I just need to work on
the cowl and the face.
So having all this time
to just focus on blending
and airbrushing
and detail work...
I'm excited.
I love this.
Everything is going
pretty smooth for me
here in applications.
For some reason
I just had this idea
to put some purple
in with the pink.
I thought that along
with the yellow pajama suit
would pull everything together.
One foot at a time, I guess.
I'm gonna have you
put your head forward.
I'm gonna put
the wig on real quick
and see what it looks like.
I feel like I'm in
a pretty good place.
I'm happy with what
I'm coming up with.
I think he's looking cool.
This one piece
is not gonna work.
It's way too tight.
Turn for me.
If I have to I'll cut it off
at the zipper at last looks.
Make it like
a Grinch Christmas suit.
I decided to go with human hair
and I'm liking the way
this is turning out.
30 seconds.
That's time! Time!
Now that everything's done
I'm looking around and thinking,
"oh, wow, there's
a lot of color."
I'm wishing I had put color
somewhere else on him
rather than just the hair.
So this could either
go really good or really bad.
Coming up...
I have a giant chicken
I have to make
not look like a chicken.
You're freaking me out.
I don't feel
a Seussian heartbeat
living inside of this.
That's just tragic.
This makeup could
be sending me home.
My model's sitting
in his suit and
I get his face on and
he's starting to fall asleep.
And it's kind of hilarious.
He's in this fat suit and he's
got this little greeny face,
it's happy, and he's sleeping.
And he's just like...
♪ away and he
is living Bumble-Tub right now.
♪ he wakes up.
You're killing me.
So we get the last looks,
we have an hour left
to apply everything else
that's needed.
This last hour
is really important to this
because I have a giant chicken
I have to make
not look like a chicken.
I'm still slightly
unsure about my paintjob.
I'm wondering if I should
still pop in some of that color.
God, that's creepy as hell.
The edges of my prosthetic
around the mouth are lifting.
I am pretty worried.
It is tough getting those edges
to look flawless.
If it's not blended out,
you're gonna see it.
I'm gonna keep painting you
until the last second.
Come on over here, girl.
Guys, that's time!
That's it.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
Say hello to your judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
- Evening.
Three time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
- Hi, everybody.
- Hi, ve.
Creature and concept designer,
Neville Page.
Hello.
And please welcome back
our very special
guest judge this week,
Oscar and Emmy-winning producer,
Brian Grazer.
Whoo!
Thank you.
Thanks for having me.
All right, guys, so this week
your spotlight challenge
was to select a character
from The Sleep Book
and use it to inspire an
original human-hybrid makeup
that captures the essence
of Dr. Seuss.
Let's see what
you came up with.
The hair is just very,
like, standout-ish and fun
and over-the-top,
very Seuss-like.
And I'm very happy.
He is able to show emotion
through the prosthetic,
which is exactly
what Brian asked for.
So I think I pulled
that part of it off very well.
I'm liking
how the makeup looks.
The judges I'm sure got a good
first impression from far away.
I'm just a little
worried about closer looks.
Overall I'm very happy
with the makeup.
Whether it looks like
a Dr. Seuss character or not
is the thing
that's up for question.
This is a nightmare.
My dream is over.
This is the worst makeup
I've ever done in my whole life.
I think he's cute
and I like him.
My makeup is probably
not on top,
but I'm hoping that it's safe.
I'd really like
to not be on the bottom.
Judges, why don't
you take a closer look?
This is cool, the way
that he did the brows.
- Yeah.
- That's a nice touch.
I love the hair.
As you can see,
I'm interested in hair.
- So was I, at one point.
- Yeah.
From where I'm at, looks like
everything's holding up, so...
Yeah, it's pretty
nerve-wracking still.
Gesticulate and let's
just see the movement.
Open your mouth
as much as you can.
Oh, wow. Great.
A little planet of the apes.
You're freaking me out.
See this shape is working
really well for me.
I looked at it from far away,
I really hated the shape.
- Yeah.
- But now close up it works.
And it really looks Seussian
in profile.
- See the edges?
- Yeah.
Really rough.
Not even close.
It seems like they like it
and then they see Glenn
touch the edge of her mouth.
It doesn't really look good.
I'm really worried that this
makeup could be sending me home.
Join the conversation
on Twitter.
Use #FaceOff to tell us
what you think
about tonight's designs.
- These edges are really rough.
- Yeah.
I see Glenn touch
the edge of her mouth.
I'm really worried this makeup
could be sending me home.
The ears are
a little alien for me.
Now is this sculpted at all?
Oh, no. That's just all paint.
The texture
comes from the paint.
I think it's cool.
This is actually the tail
up on the head.
She's covered it up.
Maybe she didn't like the way
it came out, I don't know.
Yeah, that makes two of us.
This a weird transition
right above the eye.
It's very strange.
It feels a little bit
like Beetlejuice to me.
So Brian, how do you
feel they did tonight?
I know how difficult it is,
given that I've lived
in a few Seuss movies myself.
And I thought you guys
did a great job.
- Thank you.
All right, the judges
would now like to speak
with each of you,
to learn more about your work.
Roy. You're up first.
Begin by telling us
your basic concept
for this character.
This is a hybrid
of the Foona-Lagoona-Baboona
and a human.
So what I did is I tried
to capture the essence
in the face
of the Seuss character.
And then I decided
to go with human hair
instead of the wild Seuss hair.
Once again you've
certainly taken on
an incredibly ambitious endeavor
in the amount of work.
This week I think
it was the right decision.
I'm really impressed
with the amount of work.
- Thank you.
- This makes me smile.
- Don't know what it is.
- It's 'cause he's smiling.
Could be.
I really do like him.
Thank you.
From a producer's
point of view,
there's a lot
to work with here.
I thought it was very Seussian.
I think you did a good job.
- Thank you very much.
- Roy, please step back.
Nicole.
So tell us about your concept.
My guy was the Bumble-Tub
and he had little curly-Q's
on his head in the drawing
and he had hair
coming from his cheeks.
So I just wanted
to take some of that
and just kind of bump it up
a little bit.
Feels like he automatically
plugs in to this world.
You took the hair down
into kind of these sideburns.
Yeah.
That is great.
Probably the most Seussian
of all of the characters
that I'm looking at.
The hair is very groovy.
I like the hands.
Thank you.
Did you bring airbrush colors
down to the fun fur as well?
- Yeah.
- I think it's great.
It's quick, it's sloppy,
but it works.
It looks like a Seuss character
and for once
I don't hate that there's
fun fur covering this guy.
Thank you so much.
Nicole, thank you very much.
You can step back.
Derek.
Derek, can you
explain the concept?
Uh, my character
is called Snorter McPhail.
And he is a conductor
of a band of snores in a cave.
There's something
that's out of balance.
It has to do with the size
of her face
and the size of the hair.
The paint is marring
an otherwise salient concept.
You sort of have this
very indiscriminately applied,
garish makeup
that's just tragic.
What happened to your wig?
It's, like, totally different
than it was yesterday.
And what's all this
mess down here? Good God.
Just trying to get
the hair, kind of-- continuation.
I think you kind of missed
the mark this week, honey.
Derek, thank you very much.
- Please step back.
- Thank you. Thanks.
Alana.
Let's start with
your basic concept.
I had a very, very hard time
with this makeup, I truly did.
I just wish I could reset.
It's refreshing
that you're that aware
of where you're at this week.
You can't get better if you
can't acknowledge your mistakes.
Which this most certainly is.
It is calamitous.
Your paint application this week
is a morbid failure.
Yesterday, honey,
you told me that your character
was supposed to be
a sweet, little girl, right?
There's no nice, big,
soft, round bald cheeks.
Like, big cherry cheeks.
No cute little turned-up nose.
It's like a pinched
little weird--
like a bad nose job.
And where's your
little freckles?
You did some other weird thing,
I don't know.
I looks like bad age-spots
all over his head.
I just wish I could
have the opportunity
to do something better.
Alana, thank you very much.
Will you please step back.
Thank you.
Good job.
And Laura.
Would you tell us about
your character, please?
My character was called
a Chippendale Mupp.
The picture looks like
a dragon-dog-lion thing.
So this is what I came up with.
Overall I like the look
of this character.
I do like the color palette.
I love the hair.
I think all that
works really well.
Thank you.
If you can turn sideways.
Just below his ear
there's some really great
fake sculpt going on
with your paint.
Definitely.
And that's pretty magnificent
that you can render that well
with an airbrush.
Thank you.
For me, I like
the dimensions of the body
and I like the color
of the body,
and I think it works very well
with your original idea.
- Congratulations, good work.
- Thank you.
Laura, thank you very much.
If you'd please step back.
Sarah, you're up next.
Would you tell us
about your creation
and who your character is?
I have the Hinkle-Horn Honker.
They play horns.
From far away the paint job
doesn't look all that fantastic.
I think there's probably
a lot of things
that you could have done
to really bump up the paint job.
And I also think you put
a little too much hair
on this guy.
We're thinking he looks
a little Beetlejuice-y.
- Oh.
- Um, yeah.
Well, for me, I probably--
if I were just to enter
onto the set,
I'd say maybe
we have to start over.
'Cause I don't feel
the Seussian heartbeat
living inside
of this particular identity.
I'm disappointed
that you didn't disrupt
the human form here.
Something as simple
as a bell-shaped stomach
or something.
Just anything other than
just a guy in pajamas,
because that
is what it feels like
and that's
a huge problem for me.
Sarah, thank you very much.
You can step back.
Thank you.
All right, everybody, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you would please head back
to the makeup room
while the make their decisions.
- Thank you.
All right, guys,
let's start with the looks
you liked the most.
Why don't we begin with Laura.
This one stands out
in stark contrast
against the work
of the competitors.
And she executed it so well
that I've gotta give her
massive credit for it.
I think there's
a lot of ability
in this particular creation.
Let's move on to Nicole.
I liked what she did
probably the best.
And that hairdo
was so fabulous.
I'm really proud
of the fight from her
since she's come back.
- Oh, yeah.
- It's a different Nicole.
- That's amazing.
- Yeah, it is.
All right, guys,
let's move on to Roy.
I really did
like this one a lot
because it so manipulated
the actor's eyes
underneath the rubber.
It didn't just
feel like an actor
was looking through
a rubber mask.
Even the stomach,
it's a little too big
and a little too lopsided.
- I'm not sure it's Seuss.
- It doesn't even bother me.
I'm not sure it's human,
I'm not sure that it did
any of the things they
were supposed to do this week.
But I still like it.
All right let's move on
to the looks
you liked the least.
Why don't we start with Derek.
He wasn't thinking
about the big picture.
She has a tiny little face.
And he encapsulated her
with this giant hairdo.
This show is about makeup
and that muddy paintjob
just won't fly tonight,
it's just not good enough.
All right, let's
move on to Alana.
Oh boy, Alana
kind of blew it today.
If that were presented
to me by the director,
it'd be a very bad day for me.
Because I just didn't think
it was within the world at all
of anything that I would want
in a Seuss movie.
Let's move on to Sarah.
I just thought it
was kind of a wipeout.
I think she didn't work
very hard at the costume
and getting us past that.
I just didn't feel like
there was much hope at all.
The mouth is a cool shape,
but then you have to address
where that goes.
It's just these mounds
sitting out here.
Not good.
Judges, have you
made your decisions?
- Yup.
- Yes, we have.
Let's bring them back out.
All right, Glenn, why don't you
tell us about the top looks.
Roy, this is
a really fun character.
Once again impressed with how
much you were able to get done
in the time
that you were given.
Laura.
You had a really
nice color palette
and you added some great
structure into your makeup
with your airbrushing.
And Nicole, you got
a lot right this week.
We really liked
the character's hair.
The sculpture, and loved
that you brought your paintjob
down into the fur.
So Glenn, who is the winner
of this week's challenge?
The winner is...
So Glenn, who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner is...
- Nicole.
- Yay!
- Oh, my God.
- Ooh, girl.
Congratulations.
We thought that
you did the best job
embracing both
your model's humanity
and the quintessential
Dr. Seuss aesthetic.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you so much.
What an amazing feeling.
I've come back
and now I'm doing something
that the judges are loving.
Nicole, congratulations.
You can head back
to the makeup room.
Laura, Roy, you are
also safe this week.
Please head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you.
Good luck, guys.
Unfortunately that means
the rest of you
are on the bottom this week
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, please tell us
about the bottom looks.
Sarah, we liked some of
the aspects of your character,
but it ultimately felt
a little bit more Beetlejuice
than it did Dr. Seuss.
Derek, we thought
your silhouette and profile
were really, really strong.
But you made
some critical errors
in your sculpt and paintjob.
And Alana, there were glimpses
of what it was
that you had hoped to do
with your character,
but a lot of things did not
work out well for you this week.
So then who
is going home tonight?
The person
leaving tonight is...
Alana.
Your inability
to settle on a concept
was blindingly obvious tonight.
Alana, I'm sorry but
you have been eliminated.
Derek, Sarah, you guys
are safe this week.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room.
Alana, honey, please
keep in touch with me.
Absolutely.
I just can't wait to see
where you're gonna be in a year.
Hearing this from Ve Neill
is the highlight of my life.
I feel like a million bucks
right now.
Thank you all so much,
this has been the best stress
I've ever been under
in my whole life.
Alana, it has been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- Of course. Thank you.
- Thank you. Good luck.
Thank you.
This has been
an amazing experience.
- It's me.
- Oh, there she is.
- Oh, my God.
- Are you okay?
Dude, I knew it.
I just knew the Offt
would get me offed, you know?
I know that my family
and especially my dad
is gonna be so proud of me
and I'm so excited for him
to see the work
that I have done here.
Face Off has given me the
courage to believe in myself.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net