We are live from Los
Angeles on Halloween.
SyFy's biggest
night of the year.
Tonight for the first time in
"Face Off" history, your votes
will crown our champion.
It's a night filled with
exclusive behind-the-scenes
footage and
never-before-seen moments.
Plus, a sneak peek at what's
in store for next season.
The live season finale of
"Face Off" starts now!
- 11 weeks ago on the biggest season
of "Face Off"-- - I'm freaking out.
This is stunning.
The challenges were
bigger and bolder.
Took my breath away.
The competition was fierce.
My mold just starts cracking.
Fuck.
It's a disaster.
There is a lot of blood.
I'm bleeding like a maniac.
You are incredibly ambitious and
the huge risk really paid off.
I don't know what to say.
I love it.
- The design is vey exquisite.
- And now just three remain-- Derek--
I definitely want to win this.
Laura.
I will try to knock
it out of the park.
Nicole.
I just want to win this.
Really bad.
Really, really bad.
But only one will win.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Good evening, everybody,
and happy Halloween.
I'm McKenzie Westmore.
Welcome to SyFy's biggest night of the year
and the first ever live "Face Off" season finale.
Oh, yeah.
Last night, you witnessed an
incredible stunt routine
featuring witches and demons
created by our three finalists.
Then we asked you to
determine the winner.
You rocked.
Well over a million votes.
Tonight, a brand new "Face Off"
champion will be crowned.
Plus, the cast and judges will
be answering your questions
throughout the evening.
Joining us tonight is our expert
panel of judges-- owner of
Optic Nerve Makeup Effects
Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
Creature and concept
designer Neville Page.
Production designer and
director Patrick Tatopoulos.
Thank you so much for
being here tonight.
Thanks for joining us.
As you can see, we are missing a
familiar face on our panel here.
Our three-time Oscar-winning makeup
artist Ve Neill, she is currently on set
for The Hunger Games sequel
"Catching Fire" but she sent a
message to our finalists which
we'll show you later in the show.
Now... let's say hi to the
cast for the season.
Hey, guys.
I have some questions for you.
Before we do that let's
bring out our finalists.
First up, from Florida,
we have Laura.
You look beautiful!
Next up from Miami,
Florida, we have Derek.
And finally from Sacramento,
California, we have Nicole.
All right.
So there is a huge grand prize
package on the line here tonight
for one of these three
very talented artists.
The opportunity to become a guest
lecturer at Makeup Forever's
academies at New York and Paris,
the 2012 Toyota Prius V, and
$100,000.
It's great to see
you guys again.
Nice to see you as
regular human beings.
We're like on a stage here.
I heard that you have all been
up to some amazing things,
really working hard
since we wrapped up.
Jason, I hear you
have a new gig.
What's going on?
I do.
I work at "Saturday Night Live."
I have been assisting
in the shop.
It's been awesome.
It was a nice transition to go
from this crazy show to another
crazy show.
Just the wealth of
knowledge there.
They have so much experience.
It's awesome to work there.
I'm sure this was a great training
ground to head over there.
Same turn around.
Two days and the show.
That's fantastic.
I love "SNL".
Tommy, what's
going on with you?
"Face off" hasn't ended for me.
I hit the ground running, packed
up the car in Ohio and me and my
girlfriend took the long drive
to California, moved out here.
Welcome to LA.
Thank you.
Just to pursue my career as a makeup
artist, special effects artist.
As soon as I landed I was
welcomed by the "Face Off"
family from the previous cast.
Here we go!
I love that picture!
They have been helping me out.
They have been showing me how
to handle the new life I have
and how to be more professional.
I live with Gage from season
1 and Greg from season 2.
- It's like some Face Off's fart house
there. - It's like that every week.
We all watch the episodes together
and take care of each other.
We're like a family.
Very cool.
I couldn't have done
it without them.
That's awesome.
Rod.
Yeah?
My heart went out to you through
the season with your wrist.
How are you doing?
The wrist is much better.
I have to thank the viewers
that have written in and asked.
It's much, much better.
I had great physical
therapy on it.
It's stronger.
Now I can sculpt and do
everything I need to do.
Thank God.
CC, I hear you have a
new business venture.
Tell us about it.
I got a great opportunity to
start my own makeup brush line.
It's been really amazing.
You can see there.
Check them out and
find them online.
Go, CC!
Congratulations.
You'll hook me up
with some, right?
Of course!
It's great to hear how
well you're doing.
You all did amazing makeups
and creations this season.
What we didn't always get to see
is what you thought of each
other's makeups.
Let's take a look.
- The winner of this challenge is--
- The first spotlight challenge
and we're doing "Star Wars."
All of us start freaking out.
Rod and Roy's was unlike
any other makeup.
Really, really cool.
Awesome!
I have never seen anything
like that before.
The sheer concept
is unbelievable.
Thank you.
I'm extremely impressed.
Oh!
We have to do it.
I love her.
I knew you were
going to kill it.
I'm in love with Sarah's.
I want to rock the
sea urchin dress.
It's perfect.
Oh, God.
They love my ooze trick.
I'm happy I did it.
That is great.
Awesome!
I'm looking at Tommy
and Derek's makeup.
They nailed it.
What they incorporated, if you
look at the detail work, it
is phenomenal.
One of the strongest collaborations
I have seen on the show.
Thanks.
I'm pretty thrilled
with this thing.
Laura, I look at her sculpt
and it's incredible.
I'm happy with it.
She's going with a longer chin
and it's really, really creepy.
The tubing around the head so it
bleeds from the eyes, it's a
sick, solid design.
Can you stick your tongue
out of the mouth hole?
Ooh!
Welcome to the junkward.
I like this one.
Nicole, you suck.
That's amazing.
She had a really elegant
cyborg princess thing.
It's the coolest thing
I have ever done.
You could put her in front
of a camera right now.
Your final spotlight challenge.
We have to do good
witch and demon.
This is a toughy tonight, guys.
We like them all.
It's a difficult decision.
I'm glad we don't have
to make it tonight.
Okay.
Well, you guys have been sending
us great questions about this
season's makeups and challenges.
We're going to answer some of
them throughout tonight's show.
If you have a question for us,
post it on Twitter now using
♪ FaceOff.
Let's get started.
The first question
is for Sarah.
What was your favorite
challenge this season?
I loved the pirate.
But I think my favorite challenge
was probably the kid challenge.
It was really fun to
work with the kids.
They have such creativity and
haven't learned to hold back yet.
It's inspiring to
work with them.
Kind of like working with a
client-- that's a lot younger.
A 7-year-old client.
Yes.
It was fun.
That was my favorite, too.
I loved that with the kids.
Derek, what was your favorite?
Definitely the dragon challenge
was one of my favorites.
The dragon one hit me at home.
Just because I'm a tattoo artist I
wanted to incorporate a tattoo
design in one of my makeups.
With Tommy, we made it happen.
I loved how it came out.
That one show cased your
talents as a tattoo artist.
It was beautifully done.
I appreciate it.
Nicole, what was yours?
Definitely the cyborg.
That's up my aisle.
There she is.
It's dark, dangerous
but still beautiful.
That's my aesthetic.
Can you make me that for
Halloween this year?
I would love it.
That would be awesome.
Okay.
Let's go to the next
question from Maddie R.
Alana.
Whose creation our of all the
challenges was your favorite?
My favorite hast to be Rod's from
the pirate challenge.
He did a fabulous seahorse.
It had so much detail and the
application was absolutely flawless.
It was two characters in one.
I was blown away.
Speaking of Rod, you were very
close through the show and
you were upset when
he was eliminated.
Do you keep in touch?
Every day.
I love you, Rod.
I ask myself every morning,
what would Rod do.
You wake up with that
thought to start the day.
Now all of us,
what would Rod do?
Eric, whose makeup did you
really like this season?
There was a lot of them.
They were all awesome.
- But it's not just because of
my brother-- - Sure, sure.
Uh-huh, right.
But the cyborg
creation was awesome.
The design he made was so
cool-looking from the drawing to
the makeups.
It just looked sweet.
I definitely want to wear
that if I get a chance to.
Brotherly love.
I love it.
Laura, what about you?
I really liked Roy's watchman
from the "Dishonored" video game.
It looked like a videogame character.
I play so many RPGs and
video games myself.
It looks like it was
straight out of one.
He made the articulated arm.
- Well done.
- Totally agree.
Roy, you made such an
impression and everybody was
sorry to see you go.
Many questions came in for you.
We have one from
Zach Hill @dudeinabox for Roy.
What kind of background led you to
being so awesome at fabrication?
First of all, I don't
think I'm that awesome.
But it started when I was a kid
and I would take things apart to
see how they worked.
That led to trial and error.
That taught me not to be afraid
to fail and learn from mistakes.
That's the biggest thing.
You did amazing work and you
are the king of fabrication.
Thank you.
All right.
For those of you at home who would
like to see more exclusive
footage from the show including
Roy's incredible creations, be
sure to check out the SyFy synch
app and keep an eye on it.
More bonus content will be unlocked
there throughout the night.
Now let's switch gears a little
bit and get to your questions
for our judges.
Glenn, we'll start with you.
The first question
comes from Linda S.
What movie makeup inspired you
to get into this industry?
That's a really
difficult question.
I have been asked
that many times.
There are so many films that
were so important to me.
First are the films like Dracula
which I watched at a young age.
But the I have to say honestly that the
cinebite makeups in "Hellraiser."
I had such an impression that I really
galvanized my decision to make this my carreer.
I'm shocked, to be honest with you.
Not Mary poppins?
Not Mary poppins.
I'm shocked.
Neville?
You would be surprised.
It doesn't show up in the work I
do but "The Exorcist" was a film
my mom took my mom and my sister
and I to when I was 9 years old.
What is wrong with your parents?
I know.
It made such an impact.
It horrified me but it presented
what you can do to an audience
with powerful makeup.
I wanted to know
how it was done.
Dick Smith who did the makeup
for the movie came out with a
monster maker kit.
I was lucky to
get one of those.
Used up the whole
kit in one weekend.
At that point I guess you
could say I was-- possessed.
I have to say I'm not shocked.
This explains a lot to me now.
Really?
Totally get you now.
Glad I could help.
Patrick, this is for you
from Alexis Taylor.
How does taking a risk stack up
to playing it safe in elimination and can a
creative concept help save you?
Playing safe for me is
not giving all of it.
If you're safe, you're
not giving it all.
That's a problem.
Especially on the final.
You have to give
everything you have.
You have to go beyond that.
The final is about winning, but
even if you don't win you want
to be remembered for
something special.
You don't want to
be bland, boring.
Take the chances and
go all the way.
That's the way to go.
Couldn't agree more.
Boring is bad.
Don't like boring.
Later on in the show we will
reveal which artist will see
their "Face Off" dream
become a reality.
When we come back, you will see
how Laura landed a place in the
final three and surprising
unseen moments with our judges.
This is the live season
finale of "Face Off."
Welcome back to SyFy's biggest
night of the year and
the first ever live season
finale of "Face Off."
Later on, we will reveal the
results of your vote and crown
this season's "Face Off"
champion.
Now, remember, if you have
questions you would like to have
answered on tonight's show, send
them to us using hash tag,
♪FaceOff.
So with that, Laura,
I have a question for you.
Is it hard to fall asleep at
night or do you keep tweaking your
designs instead of
counting sheep?
It was never hard
to fall asleep.
We would be very, very tired
from our busy day of work.
But, yes.
I would continuously tweak my
designs throughout the three
days of the challenge.
You never know what's going to
make or break your character.
It could be the last-minute decision
that takes it over the top.
So true.
Let's take a look at the highlights
of your journey this season.
Laura.
Oh, my gosh!
My name is Laura.
I'm a self-taught special
effects makeup artist.
I can't believe we
got "Star Wars."
I'm such a nerd.
I like seeing my
art come to life.
This is probably the
cleanest makeup I have seen.
Excellent job, ladies.
Thank you.
My art creates a story.
Tell us about the top look.
Laura and Sarah.
Laura.
Laura and Tommy.
I have only been safe twice.
The rest of the time I have
been in the top looks.
But I haven't won a challenge.
Winner is Derek.
Sarah.
Alana.
The only way I can get my head in
the game is to block out emotion.
Looks like you're
really going for it.
Trying!
I'm not going to say
"next time" anymore.
I can just be myself
and have fun.
I know I can do this.
Our winner tonight is Laura.
You got it!
What?
No.
Laura.
- Congratulations
- Thank you!
Very impressive.
My heart is soaring.
I can't help but think how
proud my husband would be.
Without him I wouldn't have had the
confidence to try out for this.
Couldn't be more proud.
"Face Off" has been inspiring.
If I win, I can do anything.
Don't cry.
Congratulations on being the
only artist this season to not
have a bottom look.
Well done.
All right.
So, Glenn, what was it about
Laura's work this season for you
that helped land her a
spot in the final three?
I think it's three
things really.
She starts off with truly
stellar conceptual design.
She follows through on the
design with excellent
decision-making in the lab.
She sticks to the concept
and plays it out.
That allows her to create these
really well-made prosthetics.
When she applies them
it's beautiful edge work.
The edges are blend blended
seamlessly, beautiful paint job
and color.
Everything comes
together in the end.
Perfect.
Thank you!
Nice work, Laura.
We love our amazing judges
but there are times we have
wondered if Glenn and Neville
are the only two people in the
room who have any idea as to
what they are talking about.
I'm disappointed in what
you have done this week.
You have this indiscriminately
applied makeup.
It's calamitous.
It's ecorche-ish.
The bald cap gives you a primary,
secondary and tertiary level.
So cromagnan-like in a way.
The external mastoids
are discordant.
It's a dissertation of love
that was quite palpable.
♪
- What?
- *
The iconography.
There is no connection.
The anti-diluvian technology.
- What?
- The anti-diluvian technology.
- *
Sexual dimorphism, etcetera.
It's very efficacious,
subcutaneous and scintillating.
Seafaring ambivalence.
I'm glad you talk and not me.
Wow.
Big words.
I'm glad I'm not the only
one that doesn't know.
Ve doesn't know either.
Thank God.
Up next, we'll show you
hilarious behind-the-scenes
footage plus how Derek and Nicole
earned their spots in the
final three.
This is the live season finale
of Face Off.
Welcome back to the first ever
live season finale of "Face Off."
We are well on our way towards
crowning a new "Face Off"
champion.
Now syfy.com recently held a
transformation of the week
contest for our viewers to submit
their own makeup creations.
We have the winner right here in
our audience tonight-- Brittany
Mitchell.
Brittany, congratulations
on your winning design!
Really nice work.
Let's get back to some
of the questions here.
Derek, here's another question
from one of our viewers at home.
This is from
McKenzie, nice name.
Did you or your brother start
special effects first, and why?
We definitely started at
the same time, I think.
Just growing up, definitely my
dad influenced us with his
stories of makeup that he's
done-- well, costumes he made
growing up and all that.
Just him painting us as
zombies one year, all that.
Who's who?
I'm on the right.
I think the left.
Pretty sure I'm on the right.
Yeah.
Creepy.
I love it.
That's so great.
Let's look at how you
impressed our judges.
Derek.
Are you related?
My name's Derek.
I'm a tattoo artist but
my passion is makeup.
Me and my brother have never
competed against each other.
Whoever gets it,
we'll be proud.
I think it will be me.
That's awesome.
The winner this
evening is Derek.
Who's leaving us tonight?
Eric.
I'm going home.
The win last night
was bittersweet.
Eric had to go home.
We pushed each other.
The mouth on the
left is fantastic.
It's slipping.
Dang.
I want to win this but it's
going to push me to win it for
my brother.
The winner is-- Derek.
He's a very good visual artist.
I'm feeling great.
My brother would be proud.
This is truly stunning.
I could see it in
one of my films.
I want my wife to see this.
Gives me inspiration.
I miss you.
I miss you, too.
There's only three spots left.
I want one.
The second person going
to the finale is Derek.
Thank you.
Week after week he
comes out so strong.
I can't believe I
made it this far.
You will each get to choose two
former competitors to join your team.
My brother.
Yeah!
My brother could help me win.
This is my last chance to impress
the judges and impress America.
Beautiful work.
Nice work, Derek.
All right, so Neville, what do
you feel earned him a spot in
the finale?
Derek's ability to conceive
on paper gives him a leg up.
It gives him a road he's created
that he can navigate with great
efficacy to the bitter end.
Plus, he's a good designer.
You really have the skills to
design because you have a great
sense of form, of color.
And he's under the radar.
You know, he plays it cool and I
think that's one of-- when you
combine all that you've gotten out
of boobfish is what you've got.
Thank God we got out of that.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Nice work, Derek.
Even though all these guys worked
long hours and were under
a lot of pressure, they still
managed to have a lot of fun
this season.
I think they don't want
you to make any noise.
Nothing loud or
anything like that.
This must be what's
left of the bunny ear.
There is something about
that color I like.
My first think--
my first think?
I didn't know that spray
paint melts styrofoam.
Yes, it does.
Awesome.
You were calling it a periscope
and it's a telescope.
My apologies.
Use a microscope.
Can you help me here or what?
No.
Is your hand bleeding again?
Is this blood?
Why am I always bleeding?
I'm going to slip
and kill myself.
Alana.
I curse like a sailor.
Let me stop myself.
I can't fucking curse anymore.
Time out.
That doesn't fucking count.
I need more booty.
Very shiny chest.
Not a big one.
That's crappy.
My chest?
Plastic boobs.
I'm sorry.
Didn't mean to be fresh.
So much for child friendly.
This is a tickle monster.
I can't talk about this one.
When you're tickling me.
Huh?
What?
Medic.
You're a bad influence, Neville.
You can see we have
a lot of fun here.
Well, we have more exclusive
moments coming your way right
after this break, including a
look at the biggest twist in
"Face Off" history.
Right here on the live
season finale of "Face Off."
Welcome back to the live
We are getting closer and closer
to crowning our new champion.
Now this season featured
our biggest twist ever.
It was one that dramatically
changed the course of the whole
competition.
Let's take a look.
This has never happened
in "Face Off" history.
Today's challenge could potentially
change someone's life.
There is always some M
Night Shamylan twist here.
You guys won't be
competing today.
They will.
Oh, my gosh!
Everyone is back.
The winner will rejoin the cast
and earn another chance at
winning our grand prize.
Ready for a shot at redemption?
Yes!
This would be a tremendous
opportunity for anyone to have a
second chance.
I'm not sure how I feel
about that at this point.
I'm definitely wanting my
brother to win, come back and
join the competition.
The winner is-- Nicole.
Oh, my God!
I'm back.
Thank you.
You get to rejoin the
cast of "Face Off."
Oh, my God.
My mom is going to
be proud of me.
Oh, this is insane!
Nicole, you quickly
became a fan favorite.
We received many comments, a lot
saying how people were inspired
by your story of how you
deal with fibromyalgia.
How was it to cope with that, to
get through the season with that?
It was insane.
The amount of people-- in the
beginning I didn't want to bring
it up.
I didn't want to talk about the
fact that I had fibromyalgia.
I'm really glad that I did.
The amount of people that wrote
me messages saying I have
inspired them to follow their
dreams and other people with
fibromyalgia and everyone's
just been so great.
You know, I think I have helped
a lot of people put that
strength back into it.
I really get that strength from
my mom because my mom also has
fibromyalgia.
Growing up, I never knew there
was anything wrong with her.
She lived a normal life and we did
everything the same as anybody.
So I definitely get that
from her, from my mama.
Oh.
I cope with the pain with focusing
on something I'm passionate about.
Makeup is my passion.
It's my whole life.
It's my dream.
When I'm doing makeup it takes me
to a whole nother place and I
forget about the pain and
do something that I love.
Well, you are definitely
an inspiration.
Thank you for
sharing your story.
As you know, it takes more than
winning just one challenge to
land a spot in the finale.
Let's see what got you here.
Nicole!
Oh, my gosh.
My love for special effects started
with my love for Halloween.
I will be the next "Face Off"
champion.
Your time starts now.
Part of the challenge is to put a
piece of myself into the makeup.
I'm making a warrior and he
just rips a dude's heart out.
I like the ideas.
But it's the paint work that
really makes it go flat.
The person going home
tonight is Nicole.
I don't think I got to
show what I can do yet.
What would I give for
a second chance?
Everything.
Nicole!
Oh, my God.
You get to rejoin the
cast of "Face Off."
I'm so thankful for
making it here.
Mom!
I said, mom, I'm going
to win for you.
Everything I do here I want
it to be the best work.
In the beginning I was doing stuff
I thought you wanted to see.
Now I'm doing what I
would like to see.
The winner is Nicole.
Yay!
She's spectacular.
It's a different Nicole.
This is awesome.
Nicole.
I was eliminated and I
just won my second one.
She's fighting back since she
got her second opportunity.
She's got the hunger.
One more chance.
You've got this.
I have one last chance to
bring everything I've got.
To win would be the greatest
accomplishment of my life and
that's what I will do.
Great work, Nicole.
So, Patrick, you were the one to
actually bring Nicole back into
the competition.
Oh, yeah.
What do you feel about her work
earned her a spot in the finale?
Yes, this is a great story.
I saw the work of
Nicole early on.
I noticed she had a very bold
design sense, great application
work as well.
When I came back I was
shocked she was eliminated.
Because the job she
did was unbelievable.
Very quick, bold, strong.
And since then she's
been amazing.
I think something happened.
I think that switch was made.
She found something deep inside her
that made her so much stronger.
Sometimes it's a great opportunity
in life to have this situation.
Since then I have
been a big, big fan.
She's certainly never boring.
Thank you so much.
Coming up, more never before seen
moments from the show and a
special message from Ve Neill.
Plus we'll reveal who you have
chosen as this season's winner
of "Face Off."
First an exclusive look at the
shocking season of "Total
Blackout" airing Tuesdays at
10 right here on SyFy.
We'll be rigth back.
Welcome back to the live
season finale of "Face Off."
We are just minutes away from
naming our new champion and we
have a sneak peek
at the next season.
But first, Alana.
Hey, girl.
You definitely were
a fan favorite.
And you certainly had
a way with words.
Let's take a look at some
of our favorite Alana-isms.
The world is more interesting
through my eyes.
Alana has a way
of saying things.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
My brain is all over the place.
All over the shop.
I still coudln't tell you
some of the things Alana says.
Here we go.
Keep my eyes on the prize.
I'm shaking like a leaf.
Bingeo-bango.
I'm borderline having a
seizure, borderline.
I'm sorry.
I don't speak other
side of the room.
I'm going to give it a hundred
and thousand ten percent.
130,000%.
50/50 teamwork.
Sell me out.
Let's go.
Wham, bam, thank you, ma'am, hioyo,
here we go, Face Off, the best.
Come on.
Cut it out.
You'll forgive me.
Alana, where do you come
up with this stuff?
I guess I have been blessed
with a beautiful mind.
All right.
Well, let's talk about some of
our other memorable moments.
We were very lucky to have
some of the biggest names in
Hollywood join us as our
guest judge of the season.
Let's take a look.
I want to introduce you
to your guest judge.
Leila Ali, Kevin
Smith, Brian Grazer.
I'm ready to judge
and eliminate.
I looked at his crotch.
That's the last thing
I want to look at.
Eric, Derek.
Nice to see you.
Welcome.
It's Sean Astin.
How long have you
guys been brothers?
Wow.
Brian freaking Grazier.
You're cute, he's cute.
This is probably the biggest person
we've ever had on the Face Off history.
Speaking of God.
You need to phone
home, my friend.
I love Kevin Smith.
I feel like I'm on the
deck of a star destroyer.
I'm sorry.
Are we not allowed to talk?
This is weird.
Shh!
What are you doing?
It's awesome having
producers, judges, guests.
The hamster wheel.
I love that hyper sexualized
monstrosity of it all.
That's who hires us.
I love the hair.
As you can see, I'm
interested in hair.
So was I.
To have them give insight on our
makeups is an opportunity for us.
See you Monday.
Bring doughnuts.
Jelly?
Look at me.
Of course jelly.
We did have great guest judges,
but we are lucky enough
to have our own industry
titans right here.
The fans are asking what you
gentlemen are up to now.
Glenn, let's start with you.
Building and designing the
effects for CSI New York,
"Hunger Games 2" with Ve and
another project called
Necroscope which is a series
of books with Brian Lumley.
Very cool.
Patrick? What about you?
Just finished the new "300"
movie, designing a new beast
for "Beauty & The Beast," the
European production and casting for
my next job starting next year.
Very cool.
Neville?
Finished working with JJ Abrams on the
most recent "Star Trek."
Been working with the creator of
"Spartacus" on his new piece of
science fiction and have been
working with Brian Grazer in
blacklight and a lot
of development.
The last thing that's kind of
interesting is I'm developing a
creature design book that's being
published by Design Studio Press.
Amazing.
Great to hear what
you guys are up to.
We haven't crowned the winner
for the season yet and we are
already talking about the
next season of "Face Off."
That's right.
It's already in the works.
Premiering in January it will
feature the biggest, most
extreme challenges yet.
Here is an exclusive
sneak peek.
This January, the
search begins again.
Face Off is back for our
biggest season ever.
14 talented makeup artists will
take the ult mall plunge in a
competition unlike any other.
That's just crazy.
They will face
breathtaking challenges.
Wow!
That's freaking cold!
Unbelievable deadlines.
Two minutes!
I can't do this.
Take it off.
Just take it off.
I'm sorry.
It's a disaster.
And the most extreme
competition in "Face Off"
history.
I'm really blown away.
Along the way they will come face
to face with industry titans.
You guys really pulled it off.
Great silhouette, great
first impression.
Who will be the next great
name in movie magic?
Find out in the all new
season of "Face Off."
I can't believe we already
got through another season.
When we get back, the moment
we have all been waiting for.
We'll reveal our new champion on
the live season finale of "Face
Off."
Welcome back to our live
finale where we are about to
announce the new "Face Off"
champion.
I have the results right here.
But first I mentioned earlier
that Ve wasn't able to be here
tonight because she's on set for
"The Hunger Games" sequel,
"Catching Fire."
She sent a special message.
Hi, guys.
I'm sorry I can't be here, but
I'm so excited to see who
America has chosen
as our winner.
Laura, Nicole, Derek. You have done an
amazing job this season and may the odds be
ever in your favor.
With that, it's time to find out
who America has chosen
as the Face Off champion.
Laura, Derek, Nicole.
Please, step forward.
Last night America saw
each of you create an
incredible witch and
damon character.
And then watched as they battled
out in a spectacular stunt routine.
Laura, you have consistenly
impressed the judged with your
sculpts and impecable detail work.
Derek, your vision for design
helped you create some
outstanding characters and elevated
you all the way to the top three.
Nicole, you struggled early on
the competition,
But fought your way back with a clear
focus and relentless determination.
All right, America has voted
and I have the results right here.
The winner of Face Off is...
Nicole!
It's real!
How does it feel?
Say hello to your family.
Congratulations.
Thank you everyone for
watching the live season
finale of Face Off.
Happy Halloween!
www.tvsubtitles.net