Previously, on Face Off...
The artists teamed up
to create original superheroes
and sidekicks
inspired by exotic vehicles.
[Laughter] Oh, yeah!
Alana's flame-inspired makeup
landed her on top.
I like this so much.
And Jason was eliminated.
Now seven artists remain.
Tonight...
One of the most anticipated
games of the year...
- Dishonored.
- Oh, boy.
I've got
to make these arms work.
[Groans]
[Grunts] This is a distraction.
And I don't want
to use it as an excuse.
I could not disagree
with you more.
It's like nothing you've done
before, so congratulations.
His head is badass.
It looks malformed.
I'm more than likely
going home.
In the end, only one
will win the opportunity
to be a guest lecturer at
Make Up For Ever's academies
in New York and Paris,
a new 2012 Toyota Prius V,
and $100,000.
And for the first time ever,
America,
your voice will be heard
in selecting the winner.
Only one will win Face Off.
[Dramatic music]
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
[Edgy pop music]
♪ ♪
Honestly, I didn't see Jason
going home last night.
I thought that it would be Rod
that was going last night.
I really did.
I believe that if Rod intends
on staying here,
he's got to change a lot
of things.
Otherwise, he'll be
the next one gone.
I like you guys,
but if somebody's got to go,
better you than me.
Good morning, guys.
We walk in and we see...
Seven beautiful models,
in these fantastic dresses,
standing there.
As some of you may
or may not know,
to survive in Hollywood,
special effects makeup artists
need to be able to do it all.
That means more than just creating
horrible monsters and cool aliens.
But sometimes stepping
into the beauty side of things.
[Laughs] Oh, here we go again. Every
foundation so far is so not my thing.
So your foundation challenge
this week
is to create
an avant-garde beauty makeup
that compliments the outrageous
outfits we have on these models.
Oh, crap.
Every time I've ever done
beauty makeup,
it ends up looking
like a cheap hooker.
I would like you to meet
our special guest this week.
She has an incredibly
varied portfolio,
having worked with stars
like Twilight's Ashley Greene
and the cast of Mad Men.
She's also worked
with Florence + The Machine
on their recent video Spectrum.
Please give a warm welcome
to the head makeup artist
for Make Up For Ever,
Lijha Stewart.
Whoo, girl.
I know Lijha Stewart's work,
and I have great respect
for her.
So Lijha, what are you
gonna be looking for
in the final makeups today?
Well, I really want you guys
to focus on doing makeup
for a runway.
A great avant-garde makeup
needs to be bigger,
and your placement needs
to be perfect and impactful.
Okay. So your names
have been drawn at random.
Roy, you get first pick.
I'm looking at dresses
and there's one that stands out.
And it looks very organic
and mechanical at the same time.
Laura, you're next.
I know exactly
who I'm going for.
Gorgeous redhead beauty.
Rod, you get to pick.
I hope this works out.
[Laughs]
- Tommy.
- A pleasure.
Sarah.
Alana.
Derek, you're next.
All right, the winner
of this challenge
will receive immunity
and cannot be eliminated from
this week's spotlight challenge.
Make Up For Ever has stocked
the lab
with everything
you could possibly need.
You have two hours
to complete this challenge.
Time starts now.
[Overlapping chatter]
I want
to make this very theatrical,
so you can never go wrong
with a good, deep smoky eye.
Ooh, here we go.
I grabbed duo,
I grabbed eye shadow,
and I'm gonna try
to incorporate
that glitter motif from her
dress into overall look.
I'm already sweating.
This is not my field.
This is for me.
[Guffaws]
[Laughs] Keep on
making her look worse.
And I'm wiping it off
and she's wiping it off.
It's just one of those things
you just go, "I'm trying."
I don't know how
to apologize more.
The dress is made
out of surgical masks.
So I start with the color
of the dress on the eyes,
and white eyeliner.
Open your eye for me.
The dress I selected has
this piece on the chest,
and it also has a piece
on the head
that has the same kind
of swirls.
So my idea is to take and carry
that up through the face
and over the eyes.
I have this concept to make my
model's skin snakeskin-texture.
If I pulled this off,
it would be so impressive.
But I'm just failing miserably.
My concept is to use that
patterning in her dress
and bring it straight up
to her face. Beautiful.
Ten minutes left to go.
Time's up, everybody.
- I'm so sorry.
- Brushes down.
I can't look at either one
of you in the face.
Rod, Rod, Rod.
Oh, boy, Rod.
What happened?
Well, lots
of good things happened.
- She's really nice.
- Okay.
We removed the makeup
several times and started again.
So what do you think?
You know, Rod,
that's what I would call
a hot mess.
Yes, I would agree.
[Laughter]
I saw this,
and I saw mechanical and fluid.
And I knew that I could take it
up onto the face,
just making
that continuous flowing pattern.
I love that.
It's perfectly placed
on her bone structure.
Thank you.
I like you're use
of aqua cream.
I love it.
And this is great.
It's my favorite color.
I think it's cool
how you tied in the necklace
with the lips and the lashes.
Close up,
it's missing small details.
Right.
I do think from stage
this would be really impactful,
because you've altered
the shape of the face.
I love the line work
on this dress.
I just wanted to work with the
different contours of her face.
I actually love your design,
like, overall.
But I wish
you would have played more
with the blue in her shoes.
A couple tweaks could've made
a big difference.
Thank you.
So Lijha,
you are the expert here.
How do you think they did?
I think you guys
all did very well.
Roy, I enjoyed the texture
that you brought in,
the color placement.
- You did a great job with that.
- Thank you, thank you.
And, Derek, I also
really enjoyed your makeup.
You used so many products
so uniquely.
Just grabbed them, mixed them
and went with it.
And I was really impressed
by that.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
All right, Lijha, who is
the winner of today's challenge?
The winner of
this foundation challenge is...
Roy.
[Applause] Thank you.
I feel more in shock
than anything.
I'm really glad
I have immunity now.
So at least I know
that I can't go home.
Well, great job today, guys.
I will see you all tomorrow
for your next challenge.
All: - Bye.
- Later.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
We walk into this bar,
and it is absolutely beautiful.
There's all this copper
and steel.
This could be steampunk.
Welcome to the Edison,
a world-class lounge known for
its authentic steampunk style.
Many of today's
most iconic makeups
are based on novels,
comic books
and... even video games.
Take a look at one of the most
anticipated games of the year...
Dishonored.
Dishonored is an immersive,
first-person action game
set in a steampunk Metropolis
where industry
and the supernatural collide.
The game is hyper stylized,
which is probably most evident
in the exaggerated
physical proportions
of its character classes.
[Contestants murmur]
This week's
spotlight challenge is
to create an original
and over-the-top version
of one of the game's characters
whose features have become
outrageously exaggerated
or distorted.
The game features many
classes of characters.
You will have four
to choose from.
The city watch.
They're a specialized guard unit
with sharp features.
The aristocrats.
They're very thin
and elongated.
The thugs.
With intimidating features
such as oversized,
broad shoulders.
And then we have the weepers.
They're very gaunt,
but their
most distinguishing feature is
that the plague actually makes
them bleed from the eyes.
All right, we have chosen
your names at random.
Tommy, you're up first.
I picked the thug,
that brute of the underworld.
Oh, this will be great.
Rod, you're next.
And Roy.
Now that you each have
your characters,
take some time here
to work on your designs.
Just so you know,
Glenn is gonna be stopping by
in the lab
to help you with your concepts.
Oh, boy.
I will see you soon.
- Thanks, girl.
- Bye.
Thank God I have immunity,
'cause... if you don't do
steampunk well,
Glenn is going to murder you.
I'm really not 100% sure
what I'm gonna do.
I just kind of
start drawing out long faces.
My concept is an aristocrat
who is going into his study,
when a hand grenade goes off,
and a display case shatters
and gets blown into his face.
My character is a cleric,
a holy priest.
So he's more educated
and more wise
and, that way,
a little bit more old.
And the concept for my thug
is that he's this engineer
whose bolting himself
back together
as he's creating weapons
for the underworld.
But, at the same time,
he's got to pay the bills,
so he's thugging on the side.
We get back to the lab,
pick our models
and get right to work.
I'm doing a guy.
I don't want
to spend any more time drawing.
I go right in
and start sculpting.
I want to take the features
of the aristocrat
and make it into a weeper,
as if this once was
a high-class citizen
who now is on the lowest
of the bottom of the barrel.
I don't want to rush
into just another fast sculpt,
because, in the last challenge,
he made a big deal about
always doing the same thing.
It was really disappointing,
because I've worked so hard
to change things up.
I'm shaken,
because I'm just not sure
what the judges are looking for.
I know if I don't change it,
I'm in trouble.
Coming up...
I could not disagree
with you more.
This is the worst thing
I've done on the show.
[Groans] It's just a disaster.
It no longer feels
like a human feature.
I think I could be on bottom.
I'm really shaken
by the last challenge,
because he said,
"you didn't change anything.
You just squared up the nose
and the cheeks."
So I'm now trying
to piece this puzzle together.
All the sculpts that I've done
had fabricated ears,
and maybe that's
the connection.
So instead of sculpting ears,
I am going to be using
the actor's real ears.
I want the judges
to know I'm listening to them.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, how's it going?
Stopped by
to see what you're working on.
- How's it going?
- Hi.
Well, I have an aristocrat.
And I was seeing
all these male features
and having her
as someone more androgynous.
Work with bringing your
forehead back and up,
and the head back and out.
Figure out how
to get the game into that makeup
- and you'll be right on track.
- Okay.
I really want
to make my character look
like
an aristocrat-turned-weeper.
I could not disagree
with you more.
Starting off by
aligning yourself conceptually
with what two other people
are doing,
to me, is a little dangerous.
He, just straight up,
is just shooting me down.
You have a really cool
character class.
I would focus on that.
I totally respect
Glenn's opinion.
But I'm moving forward
in my own creative direction.
I'm gonna push myself,
and I'm gonna pull this off.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
I am a little paranoid
about what I've heard from Ve.
I just wanted
to get your opinion
on doing an elongated head.
Yeah.
I think this is a great idea.
I love where this is going.
And I'd like to see someone work
with a makeup
where the eyes of the character
are not right where the eyes
of the performer are.
Show me what's happening.
Looks like you've got
some muttonchops going on.
I was thinking about something
that would give him
a little bit more character.
Cool hair pieces
are great opportunities
to the aesthetic
into the makeup.
- Concentrate on that makeup.
- That's--
- Let us really see
awesome sculpting,
playing with the proportions,
getting those scars in there.
- That's my plan, sir.
- Look forward to it.
All right.
Thank you.
Trying to stay away
with the--
the kind of sculpt I did
the last challenge,
which had a big jaw.
I mean, I have a thug so.
- That was last challenge?
- Yeah.
- This is completely different.
- Right.
So this is a good idea,
giving him a heavy brow,
thickening his jaw.
- Can't wait to see it.
- Thank you.
This leper that's still trying
to heal people--
that's very, very cool.
I like where this is going.
The one question I have is,
how are the proportions going
to be exaggerated?
That being a huge part
of the challenge.
I've already exaggerated
her jaw at least--
oh, my gosh--
an inch or so.
I'm trying to extend her nose.
That's what you've done
in your sketch.
Make sure that what's
happening here happens there,
- 'cause this is a cool idea.
- Okay.
Although the challenge is
about this amazing game,
you should have human faces
and musculature laying
in front you all the time.
- Make those arms look real.
- Uh-huh.
Don't just throw it together
and go,
"oh, look, it's a proportion
that I've extended."
Make the anatomical decisions
correctly.
And that's a big thing you got
on me last week about.
Get some reference in front
of you while you're doing it.
It works wonders.
Okay, guys, I'd like you all
to come over here real quick.
I have one note for everyone.
I'm not seeing
the exaggerated proportions.
Make sure that you really alter
the proportions
of the characters.
Good luck.
[Machine whirs]
Glenn's like, "listen to me.
Pull out a reference book,
distort these characters."
Okay, well, I'll definitely
pull out a reference book.
On our tablet there's
references of different thugs.
There are also fun house
mirrors,
just to see different ways
a face can be distorted.
I have Derek right beside me,
and I'm looking at my sculpture.
[Groans]
And that's when it clicks.
I'm not going
over the top enough.
So I rip it all off
and start over.
This time I want to bring
some exaggerated features
down into the chin.
So I extend the jaw out
a little bit more.
Unfortunately, doing this
put me way behind schedule.
I finish my face sculpt,
so it's time to make the mold.
You make a mold
by putting a cement-like
substance onto your sculpture.
From there, you could pour in
silicone or foam,
which will eventually become
your prosthetic.
By the end of the day,
I have my face molded.
But tomorrow I still have
to finish my cowl
and work on my prop.
All right, that's it guys.
Time's up.
It is a lot of work.
I'll miss you, deformity.
And I just hope
I can pull this off.
So it's day two in the lab,
and we have ten hours today.
I've already got
my face piece sculpted,
and so I want
to get the mold made for that.
Okay, go ahead.
Tommy was very nice
and said he would let me
use his hands
for a base for me sculpt off of.
Actually I don't know how long
it takes
for this alginate to kick.
I've never used
this kind before.
Sarah's probably
about an hour behind me,
at this point in the game,
so figured I'd help her out.
I've got my work cut out
for me today.
Immediately, I go back
to sculpting the face,
because I know that needs
to get molded
so it can be ready for foam.
♪ Awesome ♪
Day two, I start making
control arm gloves
for these giant popeye arms
I want to give my character.
Halfway through sculpting
my hulk-style arm,
I'm thinking
"how am I gonna mold this?"
'Cause if I sculpt this side
of the arm and flip it over,
I'm gonna mess up
the other side.
So I just finish one side
of the arm.
And I decided
to mold that side first,
so when I flip it over
it doesn't get damaged.
That's a good idea.
I didn't even think of that.
One of the things
that I want to have fabricated
into my makeup
are shards of glass.
And I actually sculpt the detail
of how the skin would fold
into where the glass is.
Since I have immunity,
I really want
to do a silicone piece.
It's just one thing
that you really have
to have experience with,
and I've had a little bit.
Perfect.
I've actually just impressed
the hell out of myself.
I have gotten a face
and two side-molds done
in less than 14 hours.
So I'm thinking
I'm doing pretty good.
I plan to stick my hand
in the mold
and form the polyfoam
around it.
Then I have some major issues.
Fuck.
I might have fucked this up.
I don't get polyfoam down
into the fingers, I can feel it.
So I scrap it, pull it all out.
Fuck.
I did it stupid.
I put my hand in there
and then poured the foam in,
and I didn't get
the fingers all full.
Should of poured the foam in,
then--
Yeah, just stick your hand
in there.
I just went backwards.
Stupid oversight.
So I have to start over.
Fuck.
And now I've got holes
in the bottom of my mold.
I might as well have just taken
a bucket of latex
and thrown it all over the lab.
Oh, it's just a disaster.
I've wasted so much time.
If I can't get these molds
to work, I'm going home.
[Groans]
It's day two
of our Dishonored challenge.
I've got
to make these arms work.
Ultra mess!
And I've got holes
in the bottom of my mold.
It's just a disaster.
I don't know what went wrong,
but I finally patch them up.
And now I'm praying
that this polyfoam expands
everywhere that I need it
to go,
and that I can get
these giant popeye arms done.
[Machines whirring]
I get everything cast.
And it now comes time
to pop the main face
from the mold.
[Grunts]
And I can't get leverage.
And it really feels like I'm
gonna tear a tendon doing it.
This is a distraction,
and I don't want
to use it as an excuse.
So I'm trying to use my knee.
I'm trying to use
anything I can, just to pry.
And it's very, very frustrating.
And thankfully Alana asked,
"do you need help?" Yes.
[Grunts]
[Clicks] There we go.
- Thank you, my dear.
- You're welcome, lovely.
[Blow-dryer humming]
What are you gonna do?
Oh, that's cool.
I'm using a tubing device.
And I start heating it up
with a heat gun
and trying
to mold it around the face.
But it's just not working.
And then it hits me.
"Oh, I'm
just gonna simplify this."
Just take the tubing
and run it up the center
of the bald cap.
It just makes more sense.
- How's it work, Laura?
- Good, I think.
I've never rigged anything
like this.
If it works,
it's gonna be really cool.
If it doesn't,
it's gonna really suck.
How did the thumb turn out?
Ah! Fuck me!
It takes me longer than I'd
like, but I get the arms out.
And they're not great.
The seams around it
are pretty terrible.
So I have trim the crap
out of these hands.
Kind of a pain in the butt.
But, by the end of the day,
I get them to a point
where I'm reasonably happy.
I'm thinking
that when I paint it,
I can hide a lot of the flaws.
As the day gets closer
to the end,
I'm running out of time.
I don't get the hands done
the way I want to, with foam.
So I'm running them with latex
and leaving them
to dry overnight.
One minute, everyone!
Time!
For the first time before
an application, I'm set up,
I'm ready to go
for the next day.
And it feels great.
[Grunts] Boy.
I am.
This is the best piece
you've done here.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
I love it.
I have to say,
by the end of that second day,
I'm actually feeling confident
that this is gonna work out
for me.
How are things in Sarah land?
I don't know how the hands
are gonna turn out yet.
I don't have a prop,
and I'm not sure how the judges
are gonna react to that.
I'm worried for Sarah.
Her issue last week was
that she wasn't going big enough
and not doing enough.
I don't want
to see Sarah go home.
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab,
and one hour
for last looks at the stage.
I come into the shop,
look at my pieces,
and my edges
are just God-awful.
I thought I had all this time
and that I was ahead
of schedule,
and really,
I just backed myself up,
maybe another hour,
trying to fix this thing.
Come on over here.
These are
our video game characters.
I just want to rip the foam
but here you go.
- Yo. Deal.
- Cool.
I'm pretty sure
I'm gonna scrap the hands.
They're still kind of wet,
then they're gonna just get
all misshapen and look weird.
So if I'm only doing the head,
I really need
to make sure my edges
and everything look really good.
I want to change
my model's ethnicity.
I want to make his skin tone
as light as the foam plastic.
I'm also gonna line the hair.
I'm gonna lower it down.
Can you see at all
through there?
At this point,
I'm really concerned
with my actor's vision.
Oh, that's a tough one.
- Yeah.
- All right.
Now I start picking up
my foam latex,
trying my best
to make a vision area for him
and see how that fits on him,
and this is gonna take time.
Perhaps some more base coat
with the airbrush
and then we're done with that.
So I'm actually looking
really good, dude.
Can you see?
[Laughs] Can you see?
You can see?
That's the key.
We got 20 minutes.
[Exhales]
And be like, "okay."
At this point,
I'm thinking, "wow.
I finally
pulled this together."
And all I have to do
is throw a wig on this guy,
lay down some hair and finish up
some minor details.
And then it starts
all falling apart.
I start laying down this hair,
and it is just the worst hair
I've put on anything in my life.
I don't know who to fix it.
- Time, everyone!
- Fucking shit!
Brushes down!
I leaving for last looks,
and I just don't know
what I'm gonna do.
Coming up...
It's like nothing
you've done before.
Congratulations.
His head is badass.
I'm very disappointed.
Nothing seems exaggerated.
I'm more than likely
going home.
The last looks can be scary,
because some split-second
decision
can really just ruin everything
or make it all perfect.
I'm looking at my piece,
and it looks reminiscent
of my white rabbit.
I did not realize it until now.
I need to tone down this yellow
with blues and greens.
The seams on the arms
are looking like garbage.
Screw it,
I'll just tape 'em down
and hide 'em under the sleeves.
It's really important for me
to get his paint job right,
and it's not quite going
the way I want it to.
The coloring's a little off.
Wasn't gonna do-- oh!
By the end of last looks,
I can't figure out what
to focus on,
I'm so all over the place.
And my confidence
is dropping dramatically.
Guys, that's time!
I look at my model,
and I honestly believe that this
is the worst thing I've done.
I just need to keep my head up
and wear a smile
when I walk out onto that stage
even though I want
to cry right now.
Because I'm more than likely
going home.
[Suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Welcome
to the Face Off reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
First, say hello
to your judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
- Hey.
Three time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
- Evening guys.
- How you doing?
Creature and concept designer,
Neville Page.
- Hello everyone.
- Hi.
This week,
your spotlight challenge
was to choose
one of the characters
from the new video game
Dishonored,
and create
an over-the-top version
with outrageously exaggerated
or distorted features.
So... let's see
what you've come up with.
[Tense music]
♪ ♪
Aesthetically,
I don't like this piece.
And when I walks out,
I'm just horrified
of what the judges
are gonna say.
When my model comes out,
and she's standing there
with the backdrop,
I feel like she could be
a part of that world.
And I'm feeling good.
At this point, I don't know
if the judges are gonna get
what I created.
I'm feeling good
about what I did,
but that doesn't mean
the judges will.
I can definitely see this
character in the video game.
I tried
to keep the same features,
the same style, the clothing,
so I think I accomplished that.
He looks amazing on stage,
I love it.
I like the look of it,
except for the neck.
It's kind of thrining
the whole thing off for me.
Overall it looks good,
so I'm really happy with it.
I went pretty bold
with this challenge.
I fabricated more pieces
than anybody else.
I'm hoping that the judges
will recognize the effort.
I'm still not 100% happy
with the paint,
but, at this point,
I can't do anything more,
so we'll just see
what they have to say.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look?
Wow.
The judges walk up
and Glenn grabs the arms.
And he sees
that they're unfinished.
I'm just like, ugh!
Can you turn around
so we can see the back?
[Laughs]
The judges get poky
with the back of her head.
I'm worried
that I didn't do enough.
I don't have all the big
pieces everyone else does.
I don't have the fingers
I wanted to do.
I think I'm in huge trouble
this time.
What do you think
of tonight's designs?
Tell us on Twitter,
using #FaceOff.
There's nerves
whether you've done
a good piece or a bad piece.
And I really don't know
what they're gonna say.
What do we have here?
And I'm not so sure
about the pinhead,
because it takes it out
of being human.
I'm very nervous
when the judges are looking
at my makeup,
because there are things wrong
with it.
Oh, yeah.
Ooh, she's leaking.
- There we go.
- That's cool.
Can you stick your tongue out
of the mouth hole?
[Laughter]
Ooh! Okay.
He has some decent sculpting
going on.
He has gone super asymmetry.
I like the fact
that his nose has biceps.
- [Laughs]
- Fascinating.
All right, the judges
have scored your creations,
so... let's find out
what they thought.
Rod...
Tommy...
Sarah...
Derek...
You were the best
and worst looks of the week.
The rest of you are safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
All right, the judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Rod, please step up.
Could you start by telling us
about the concept?
He's an aristocrat.
He was going into his study
when one
of his display cases exploded
and hit him in the face.
Did you have a particular
reference in mind
when you were sculpting?
I went through
all the reference shots
from the game
and I just let that
influence me.
It was delightful
when I saw him,
because it's like nothing
you've done before.
Thank you.
Kind of reminded me of
my dad when he's upset with me.
He's just, "ugh!"
You know,
I really like the proportion.
But it just stops at the head
and becomes a bobble head.
So I assume the visibility
is through the nostrils,
- is that correct?
- Yes, it is.
All those things were handled
beautifully in this makeup.
You picked what was important
within the challenge this week,
and came up with something
very successful.
- Thank you.
- Rod, you can step back.
Thank you.
Tommy, you're up.
Hi, Tommy.
What's your concept here?
This is Tonka.
And he fabricates weapons
and stuff
for the local crime bosses.
What happened with the arms?
It looks like you got 'em
duct-taped on.
Well, I ran it in polyfoam,
and it was just really chunky,
and it was just not gonna
go down well, so I just...
I really feel that you kind of
missed the boat here.
The popeye arms--
I understand what you
were going for,
but nothing seems to have
been elevated or exaggerated,
in any way, in his face.
Your sculpting is poor.
The coloration is poor.
I'm very disappointed
in what you did this week.
I really don't see
very many elements of the game
or the other aspects
of the challenge.
I would love
to have seen something
with his jaw or his forehead.
His forehead
could have been massive
for the size of his face--
that would've been interesting.
Tommy, thank you.
If you'd please step back.
Thank you, guys.
Derek.
Let's start off
with your concept.
He's part of a gang of thugs.
The tattoos are signatures
of their look,
so people could tell
who they are.
His head is badass.
Thanks.
It's kind of
classic tough-look--
which you're going for a thug,
so you've achieved that.
It feels very cohesive,
it's got a nice palate,
and it really does fit
within this world.
Thank you.
I do love the fact
that his nose
is all smashed in like that.
My father was a boxer,
and I remember seeing guys
that looked like this guy, so.
[Laughs]
You know what else I want
to say is
you did an ethnicity swap,
which is kind of a trip.
We went, "oh, yeah. Cool."
I love the aesthetic of it.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
Derek, thank you very much.
You can step back.
Sarah, you're next.
Begin by explaining
your concept for us.
I have the aristocrat.
And so I decided
to enlarge the back of her head
and try
to angle out her features.
If feels like you're trying
to make the character fit
into the game.
However, there some striking
anatomical inaccuracies
in the sculpture.
You've lost the shape
of the human cranium in there,
and so now it doesn't look
disproportionate to me,
it looks malformed.
If her face was locked
into an expression
that said aristocrat--
sort of one eyebrow
higher than the other,
maybe one eye really big
compared to the other,
with the other squinting,
right?
I think that would have said
aristocratic.
You've got a monocle.
It would be perfect
to have that monocle
baked into her look.
I can think
of a half a dozen things
that would've made this
an amazing-looking aristocrat.
You could've elaborated
on the lips.
You could've done
some crazy thing with the hair.
I feel that you've lost
the vision on this one.
Sarah, thank you.
Will you please step back.
Thanks.
All right, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they make
their decisions.
All right, judges, why don't we
start with
the top looks of the night?
Let's begin with Rod.
What are your thoughts?
- I like it a lot.
- Yeah.
Because of the proportion.
It's not that creative
as a head sculpt,
but he added pores,
and he added wrinkles that seem
to make sense.
I think he made a lot
of smart decisions this week.
If he would have made the body
just a little bit bigger
it would have helped,
'cause I loved
the whole look of it.
All right let's move on
to Derek.
It fits the game perfectly.
He addressed all the elements
of that period,
as well as the fact
that he was supposed
to exaggerate
all those features.
So what do you think
about the arm?
I think the arm is way too big!
It could have been half as big
and still have been gigantic.
All right, let's move on to
the looks you liked the least.
- Let's start with Tommy.
- Oy vey.
I don't know what the hell
he was thinking about
this week.
He's not making smart choices.
Terrible job on anatomy that's
so abundantly available.
Just roll your sleeve up,
take a look.
It's hard not to look at
your arm while you're sculpting.
- Yeah.
- Actually, it's sort of
in the way, isn't it?
[Laughter]
And then duct-tape the whole
thing together, you know.
Let's move on to Sarah.
- I'm bummed out about Sarah.
- Yeah.
Disappointing
performance from Sarah.
I think one of the worst.
She wanted pointy features.
I get it.
She didn't have the sculptural
skills to make that happen.
She didn't round things off.
She didn't put any skin texture
over them.
No.
There's nothing
organic-feeling.
- Yeah.
- It does not feel Dishonored.
At all.
It certainly is not part
of this franchise.
All right, judges,
have you made
your decisions then?
Ve & Neville: - I think so.
- Yeah, we have.
Let's bring them back out.
[Suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Glenn, why don't you tell us
about the top looks?
Our top looks tonight are...
Derek.
We could tell a lot
about your character
before you even explained
your concept.
He immediately read
tough-guy thug.
And, Rod, you really made
great decisions
with your time management
this week.
It's very obvious
you've been listening.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
So who's the winner
of this challenge?
Tonight's winner is...
All right, Glenn,
who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner is...
Derek.
We felt that your makeup
was the best combination
of the game's aesthetic
and the exaggerated-proportions
element of this challenge.
Well done.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
I'm feeling great,
this is my second win.
Last time I won,
my brother went home,
so I didn't really get
to enjoy it.
But this time I'm definitely
enjoying it,
and I think my brother
would be proud.
- Derek, congratulations.
- Thank you.
You can head back
to the makeup room, please.
- See you guys.
- Thank you.
Rod, you are also safe.
Will you please head back
to the makeup room.
Unfortunately, that means
you guys are
on the bottom this week.
One of you will be eliminated.
Will you please step forward.
Glenn, why don't you tell us
about the bottom looks.
Tommy, you seem to have
really struggled this week.
I think you spent a ton of time
on those hands,
and it was very detrimental
to the rest of your makeup.
Sarah, you had some issues
with the structure
of your sculpture.
And it also seems that,
somewhere along the way,
you lost track of your vision.
So who's going home tonight?
The person leaving
tonight is...
Tommy.
We just couldn't look past
the fact that there was
no recognizable structure
to your sculpture.
We also felt the makeup
simply didn't meet the criteria
of this challenge.
It's been a hell of a ride.
I worked really hard
to get here,
and it's been a pleasure
to meet all three of you.
I hope to see you guys
again soon.
Sarah, you are safe.
If you would please head back
to the makeup room.
Tommy, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
I'm really glad that we got
a chance to meet you,
and I think that your passion
is very obvious.
All you need
to do is keep working on it.
Thank you.
Tommy, it's been great having
you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- Thank you, Tommy.
- See you, guys.
Good luck, Tommy.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
[Whimpers]
Mr. Pietch.
I pushed the limits of what
I thought I could do every time.
- It was fun.
- Yeah.
And, in that respect,
I have no regrets.
I've learned more
than I ever thought I would,
just experimenting
and trying out other techniques.
I feel like I could probably do
anything right now.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net