Previously on Face Off...
The artists teamed up
to make original
Chinese new-year dragons,
and their makeups
were put to the test
in an acrobatic dance.
Derek's unique vision
took him to the top.
But his twin brother Eric
fell short and was sent home.
Now nine artists remain.
Tonight they will dive
down the rabbit hole.
Yay!
I love Alice in Wonderland.
The virus
has infected Wonderland.
I got a plan.
It's gonna be something
nobody's ever seen before.
It just crumbles
into, like, four pieces.
I screwed up really bad.
And zombies take over
the reveal stage.
I love it.
Well done.
- That is the most distracting,
God-awful thing I've ever seen.
I'm definitely going home.
In the end,
only one will win
the opportunity
to be a guest lecturer at
Make Up For Ever's academies
in New York and Paris,
a new 2012 Toyota Prius V,
and $100,000.
And for the first time ever,
America,
your voice will be heard
in selecting the winner.
Only one will win Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪
I won last night.
It was bittersweet.
Derek had to go home.
Waking up this morning
was pretty sad
with my brother not here.
We pushed each other.
I want to win this for myself.
But it's gonna give me a push
to win it for my brother.
♪ Let's go, let's go,
let's go ♪
So we head downtown
this morning
for the next
foundation challenge.
Oh, no.
Is it something
like a battle royal
where nine walk in
and one walks out?
Welcome to one of
the most hard-core fighting gyms
in Los Angeles.
Before I tell you anything more,
I want to introduce you
to your guest judge this week.
She's a four time
world-championship
professional boxer,
who went undefeated
her entire career.
- Please welcome Laila Ali.
- Thank you.
Laila Ali--
She's a legend.
It's really cool to meet her.
So excited to be here.
Thank you.
We are excited to have you.
So, guys,
in films like Raging Bull
and Rocky and The Fighter,
makeup artists
have been called upon
to create
a realistic trauma makeup
for the big screen.
That is the basis
of your foundation challenge,
to make your models look like
they have just gone through
a nasty ten rounds in the ring.
So, Laila,
needless to say, you do know
what this stuff looks like.
A lot can happen in a fight.
You can get anything
from a busted lip
to a broken nose,
bruising, swelling,
a gash over your eye.
So there's a lot that can happen
over ten rounds.
Your models and makeup stations
have been randomly assigned.
The winner will receive immunity
and cannot be eliminated
in the spotlight challenge.
Remember, guys,
realism is everything today.
You have 90 minutes.
Get ready, contenders,
because your time starts now.
Ready to get all bloody
and disgusting today?
Yeah.
This is pretty easy.
I used to take martial arts,
and I feel like
I got a good shot
at taking
this foundation challenge.
And I think I'm gonna
go subtle and realistic
with the swollen-eye
prosthetic.
Ready to beat you up.
My plan is to build up a lot
of swelling around the face,
do a broken nose, busted lip,
and then some body bruising.
Just blend, blend, blend,
blend, blend.
I'm trying
to incorporate everything
that laila had to say--
punches, bruising,
to swelling--
without overdoing it.
I'm going with some blues
on my paint job.
And once I do that,
it just starts turning purple.
This ain't gonna be good.
Five minutes, guys.
I need to just kind of like,
smear across your face.
That's it.
Brushes down.
He got his eye pretty
messed up in this fight,
and his lip is cut,
and he's bleeding everywhere.
I like the way that the blood
is splattered over his body.
The only thing I will say
is that the color of the blood
looks like it's older.
When you just come out
of a fight,
it wouldn't be that thick
and that dark.
He's actually the winner
of the fight,
despite how he looks.
Swelled up his eye.
Both his ears got cut
in the fight.
You did a pretty good job
with the thickness of the blood,
it's kind of watery,
because in a fight
you're sweating.
It looks good.
Busted lip, broken nose,
a little bit of gashes.
I think you did a good job
with the swelling,
just the shape of it
around the eye
and then down the cheekbone.
The lip looks
very, very bloody.
He's taken a couple blows
to the face,
and we have a busted nose
and a split in the eyebrow
that's still fresh.
Being that he is beat up
pretty bad,
there would be more blood
on his body.
Got you.
All right, Laila,
so how did they do overall?
You know, I thought everyone
did a really great job.
It seems like they knew
in their mind
what their fighter
was going through,
and they went from there.
Who were your favorites?
Nicole,
your model looks like he just
came out of a bloody fight.
Very believable.
Jason, that eye was great,
the cuts were very realistic
for a boxing match.
Thank you.
All right, Laila, who is
the winner of this challenge?
The winner
of this challenge is...
Jason.
- Sweet.
- Yoo-hoo.
Even though
your model didn't have as much
as everybody else's,
what you did do, you nailed.
Jason, congratulations.
You have earned immunity
and cannot be eliminated in
this week's spotlight challenge.
That feels good.
This is the first time that I've
been on top, on any challenge.
- I'm stoked.
- Great job today, everyone.
I will see you tomorrow for
your next spotlight challenge.
Good job, everybody.
We're walking
around Descanso Gardens,
and it's absolutely beautiful.
We come through the woods,
come around this bend,
then, all of a sudden,
all of these colors pop out.
There's pink mushrooms
and oversized sunflowers,
and it looks amazing.
And McKenzie's standing
in this magical garden,
and I'm thinking, "oh, great.
We're gonna do munchkins
or fairies."
Welcome to
the beautiful Descanso Gardens.
This week your
spotlight challenge inspiration
comes from a very famous book.
Alice's Adventures
in Wonderland.
Yay!
I love Alice in Wonderland.
If I had a tail,
it'd be wagging.
This book has become
a phenomenon,
saturating pop culture and
spawning several feature films.
But it's also found its way
into places
that you really
would never expect,
like the Resident Evil
film franchise.
I love the franchise.
I've watched the movies
since I was a kid.
Finally a challenge
that I wanna tackle.
The Resident Evil films
take place in a world infected
by the T-virus,
which turns humans and animals
into zombies.
Today, that virus
has infected Wonderland.
- Yes.
- This is amazing.
Oh, my God.
Your spotlight challenge is
to create
a completely original take
on one of the iconic characters
from Alice's Adventures
in Wonderland
as a virus infected zombie.
Wow.
We have Alice,
the Hatter,
the Queen,
Cheshire Cat,
and White Rabbit.
Jason, go ahead
and pick your card.
I choose the Hatter.
Rabbit.
Ooh.
I'm taking the rabbit.
The Hatter.
The Queen.
Cheshire Cat.
Okay, now that you each have
your characters,
take some time here
to work on your designs,
and then head back to the lab,
pick your models
and get started.
It's really important
to have a good design
before you go into makeup,
because it's easier to execute.
I'm gonna be wanting her
to have the rabbit in her hands
and she's just gnawing away
on it.
Just really dark.
I'm gonna make Alice more
my style.
My idea is to have her
becoming a mutant zombie.
It's like her skin creates
a crown in her clothing.
I grew up in
a Mennonite community,
so I don't really know very much
about zombies.
I'm not really getting
any sketching done.
Nothing's really coming to me.
I'm thinking more
of, like, a thrasher zombie.
He has all these wristwatches
going arm
for each stage
of the infection.
All right.
That's it.
We get to the lab, and I
immediately started sculpting.
First step
to creating a prosthetic
is sculpting clay
on the cast of the model.
And for my cheshire cat,
part of his face is gonna be
missing a lot of the skin.
So it's only gonna have whiskers
on one side of his face,
and then the other side,
his teeth are gonna be exposed.
I'm gonna individually glue
teeth on the prosthetic.
My character, she ripped all
of her hair out.
She's tweaking out.
But just like everything I do,
there'll be some form
of sex appeal in this.
I'm lost on the concept
and frustrated
that I don't know what to make.
Just one concept
not completely going through
the way you want it to--
That's what's gonna send
somebody home.
Coming up...
My cowl falls
on the ground, ears first.
I want to cry.
- That is the most God-awful
thing I've ever seen.
The pressure is on.
I have to turn a Cheshire Cat
into a zombie.
I am having some trouble
sculpting.
I don't know what to make,
other than just a cat
with a big grin.
Think of, like, the original,
and then think about
just shredding up
the original version.
I talked
to Nicole a little bit,
and her suggestion
really helped.
So I decided that this cat
is not a happy kitty
that sits in your window
and looks outside all day long.
This is a dead, run over
roadkill cat.
I'm going to use this immunity
to try out some new things
and different techniques.
My makeup is gonna look cool
or it's gonna look terrible.
Regardless,
I'm gonna still be here.
So this is probably
one of the most complicated
makeups that I've done.
My concept is a skull piece
on the bottom,
and there's skin over it.
If I can pull it off,
it's gonna be something
that nobody's ever seen before.
By the end of today, I want to
have my face and chest sculpted.
With the chest piece,
you could see the rib cage
and the deterioration
of the skin.
My goal is to have this sculpt
out in the next two hours.
It's time to make the mold.
We do this
by covering the sculpture
with a cement-like product.
After that hardens,
it's time to remove the clay
on the inside,
and we either pour silicone
or foam latex into it
and have our final piece.
I have my face done.
I have my cowl roughed out.
I'm feeling really good
at this point.
- 19 seconds.
- Shit.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Time.
That's it.
There you go.
It's day two
of our "Alice in Zombieland"
challenge.
My cowl is on its way
to being finished,
and I'm feeling really good.
- You okay?
- Oh, shit.
Alana, what happened?
My cowl falls
on the ground, ears first.
What the fuck am I gonna do?
I want to cry.
I don't have time for this.
No use crying
over a spilled bunny, right?
I'm thinking,
wouldn't it be cool
if the mad hatter's
measuring tape
was some of his intestines,
and he was confused,
because he's a zombie,
that it's
his actual measuring tape?
So that's when it starts getting
a little gory.
Hey guys.
I'm here with Neville
to do a little walkthrough,
see how you're doing.
I'm really excited
to talk to Neville.
I'm really anxious for him
to see this
from the drawing stage
to where it's at right now.
So tell us about your concept
and what you're doing
with the queen.
The plan is to take it
and have, like, her skin
and her muscles
actually coming up
and creating the crown.
So the face is actually--
Yeah, the skin on it
is just, like, tearing away
and it goes up
and forms a crown.
- Cool idea.
- Yeah.
So you have the queen.
Tell us about your concept.
The queen is infected
with something
that speeds up her metabolism.
And she just needs fresh blood.
The more she gets,
the fatter she gets.
Such a great idea,
but it needs
to work visually as well.
So you want it
to be demonstrative visually.
- So you have Alice.
- I do.
You were the only person
to chose Alice.
I know.
She's gonna have, like,
her rib cage kind of showing
and then this bottle.
Can you explain a bit more
about the wound.
Has this bottle
been stabbed into her?
And somebody went--
It feels more
like the bottle is...
- Coming out.
- Exploding out, yeah.
- Pushing from the inside.
- Right.
Once he said that, it clicked.
I'm like, "oh, my God.
It's like a bullet."
So, you chose the hatter.
Tell us about your concept.
When he died,
he fell on the table,
and all of the dishes and cups
and teapots got into him.
So I'll be adding it
into the body.
All embedded into his body?
- Exactly.
- That's cool.
We're going totally
Resident Evil on this one.
Good.
I thought
if the white rabbit was
just thrown in this situation
and he's infected,
he's always worried about time.
He puts all these wristwatches
on his arm,
and each watch is a timer
to each stage of the infection.
I'm curious how you're gonna
go about painting these pieces.
We're gonna start
with a dark wash,
so I can get all
of these nice crevasses,
but the outer layer is a nice
clean base for me to brush over.
Just be careful.
You might end up
with so much texture
that, at a distance...
It's gonna be hard
to read much.
Okay.
Very cool.
So with the cheshire cat,
what are you doing conceptually
with it?
Head to toe costume.
So I'm actually making
a body suit right now.
- I'm gonna use some of this fur.
- Wow. - Wow.
Yeah, I realize
it's incredibly ambitious.
God, yeah.
The overall dominance
of your character
is gonna be in how you make
the fur zombie-like.
And maybe even some hair product
would be good.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Who do you think
is really standing out?
Rod.
I love the idea a lot.
Will he be able
to pull that off?
And Roy, conceptually,
head to toe, very cool idea.
- He's doing a lot.
- He is.
So with Sarah
and her cheshire cat?
I'm a little concerned
she is gonna be burdened
with this choice
of making this huge statement.
And I'm a little concerned
about Tommy's.
I think that it could get worse
in paint.
Mm.
Thank you very much.
We'll see how
this all turns out.
All right, everybody,
we're heading out.
Good luck tomorrow.
- Thank you.
- See you.
See you later.
Now I'm starting to do
a decapitated version
of the human head.
But it's a whole another makeup,
it really is.
It's not just a head prop,
it's a key feature here.
Since I have a cat costume,
and I don't want them to look
like a mascot or like a kitty,
I'm making some foam pieces
to put underneath the fur
to give it kind of
a lumpy, bumpy, creatur-y thing.
I want it to look really ratty,
have skin pieces on it
falling apart.
And then I decide
to use some gelatin.
Basically,
just making it a mess.
I'm back in the mold room.
And as I'm scraping out clay...
Oh.
The wrist literally shatters,
on it, into, like, four pieces.
It just crumbles.
I'm just like, "no."
I don't know if you
noticed this, but...
I'm pretty jealous.
I wish I had some sexy glasses.
Sadly, as one gets older,
they need glasses to see detail up close.
So I have these glasses and they're
really great glasses.
You can snap them together,
snap them apart.
And they're there,
they're not gonna fall.
Oh, I don't know, know, man.
Fuck, I don't know.
I'm freaking out.
I got 30 minutes left,
and I got this shattered mold,
and I'm just like, "no."
I really want this extra arm.
I feel like this
is gonna give me the leg up.
So I brush in two nice coats
of latex,
kind of slap one
on top the other,
and then duct-tape it all
together so the pieces hold.
I hope it dries overnight
and, you know, the next day,
come what may, man.
All right, that's got to work.
If it doesn't work, I'm fucked.
Everyone's doing
these amazing creatures.
Wow, that outfit came together.
All I got is a human zombie.
I got to amp it up a little bit.
I find some rope.
This is gonna be
a quick and easy way
to make some intestines.
You just look so disgusted.
You're like, "Ew."
All right, guys, that's time.
So by the end of the day,
I'm nervous about tomorrow.
I'm worried about my painting,
and getting all the pieces
applied on time and finished.
'Cause we only have
five hours altogether
to finish our piece,
and that's not that much time
for a whole character.
It's application day.
We have four hours in the lab
to do all of our application
with our models.
Then we have one hour
for last looks.
The first thing I do
is I look at my pieces.
And they all turned out
fantastic.
I came here
to fight and compete.
And I'm-- Damn it--
I'm gonna compete.
I just know I need
to save my rabbit zombie arm.
Got more work in here.
This is the first time
I've ever done a zombie.
I want my queen to be short,
so decide to go with Kevin,
who was shorter.
I hope you're ready
for the mad hatter.
I really do.
How does it feel?
- I mean, nose and everything?
- It feels good.
I'm not liking
my paint job right now,
because it seems a little flat.
So I need to put
some kind of detail for depth.
I'm hoping
that having my little extras
make this character
over the top
and awesome to look at.
Squeeze it.
Yes! It worked.
Oh, my God.
It's exactly
what I was thinking.
Like, just these boils--
just, like, infection,
just, you know?
Oh! Loving it!
I'm loving it.
It looks cool!
All right.
Let's start this makeup.
I'm feeling so nervous,
and I'm looking around me,
and I'm seeing that everybody
is basically done
applying their makeup.
And I'm-- I don't even
have the ears on my thing yet!
I'm just staring at this thing
and I'm just baffled
on how I'm gonna get this
to work.
At this point,
I cannot figure out a way
to get these ears to stay up.
I don't know how
I'm freaking out.
I'm-- I feel like an idiot.
I'm just like "how could I not
prepare for this to happen?"
I'm just like, "don't cry,
don't cry, don't cry."
Just calm down.
Don't panic.
Who do I go to but Roy,
because that's my mold cowboy.
Just turn it inside out.
The foam is what's giving it
so much weight,
so Roy helps me
pull the foam out
to get this ears to stay up.
Or we bend it that away.
- Yeah, that'll work.
- Okay.
I'd kiss you on the mouth,
but it's very inappropriate.
I can't thank you enough, dude.
Sorry, I wont torture you
that much longer.
I've got the face applied,
and now I'm pinning the skin
over the face,
and everything has
just come together on this.
Do me a favor
and open your mouth for me.
You're the prettiest ugliest
thing I've seen in a while.
I look up,
and I see Derek's makeup,
and I see how fantastic
he's doing.
It's pushing me to go harder.
I'm almost thinking,
"let's not use that."
I am nervous about the look
of the overall character,
because with so many
prosthetics,
it looks too realistic,
as if he's not wearing anything.
And I don't know
if that's gonna hurt or help me.
Look straight ahead.
Laying hair is not something
I normally do,
so with the immunity,
I'd like to just give it a shot
and see what I can do.
If this arm would have
came out like it would,
you'd be able
to slip it on like a glove.
That's how I designed it.
My zombie rabbit arm--
of course, it looks like crap.
I'm just wrapping it tight,
and I'm stuffing foam
in some of the bulgier areas.
You know,
old-school bush-league tactics,
but you know, when you're put up
against the wall,
what are you gonna do?
A rabbit, for me--
this is how I feel all the time.
I feel like I'm constantly
running out of time.
It really is ripping
her head back.
A real dead body
is pretty colorful.
There's a lot of blues,
there's a lot of purples,
there's a lot of green, yellow.
And I'm painting and it's not
looking like what I'm picturing.
Oh, please make me be able
to do the detail in time.
- What's the time?
- Five minutes.
Thank you.
- I'm excited.
- Is that yours?
Fits better?
I'm now freaking out.
That's time, everybody.
I've got a lot of work
for the last hour.
I have to do all these veins
that I haven't touched yet,
because I'm not sure what color
to put on them.
There's just a lot of things
that aren't clicking
in this paint job,
and I'm really concerned.
Coming up...
Welcome
to the Face Off reveal stage.
I'm feeling like I could be
one of the bottom looks.
A bit of a mess.
I'm just mesmerized
by the look of this makeup.
We have one hour of last looks,
and we got to get everything
done as fast as we can.
Oh, my God. All right.
I'm just gonna start painting.
My airbrush is broken.
Plan "B" is
to just paint by hand,
which is gonna take
so much more time.
All right guys,
that's ten minutes.
We got ten minutes.
My paint it getting darker
and darker.
I made a lot
of wrong color choices.
Fuck!
And that's time, everyone.
Brushes down.
Everybody's look so good,
and I'm a little worried
at this point.
Everything went wrong,
and I ran out of time.
♪
Welcome to
the Face Off reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
First let's say hello
to your judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
- Hey.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
Hi guys.
Creature and concept designer,
Neville Page.
Hello.
And joining our panel
this week,
writer, producer, and director,
with films like Event Horizon,
Death Race,
Alien Vs. Predator,
and, most recently,
The Three Musketeers.
He's also written and produced
all the Resident Evil films.
The newest addition
to the franchise,
Resident Evil, Retribution,
which he also directed,
comes out this Friday.
Please welcome
Paul WS Anderson.
It's really cool
to have Paul WS Anderson here
to judge our zombie makeups.
I'm hoping that when he looks
at my piece,
he sees
that Resident Evil quality.
Paul, thank you so much
for joining us.
It's my pleasure to be here
with so many talented people.
Okay, guys.
So your spotlight challenge this
week was an original take
on one
of the classic characters
from Alice's Adventures
in Wonderland, as a zombie.
Let's see what you come up with.
♪
I still don't think I've got
a chance at the top.
I think my cat's too generic.
I feel good at this point, but
I've been feeling good all day.
It's just a nice feeling
to know that I'm safe.
Under the lights on the stage,
it's looking
really, really, really dark,
and I'm noticing a bunch
of flaws.
I think I put
too much blood on him.
I'm worried that maybe they're
not gonna see all the details
as well as I hoped.
I see my creature come out,
and it looks
like a hillbilly rabbit.
I should have taken a step back
and looked at it as one piece,
but I was so into it,
I got blinded.
Everybody else's looks
so much more developed.
I'm feeling like I could be
one of the bottom looks.
I'm feeling really good
about this makeup.
It's probably one
of the best ones that I've done
since I've been here.
I'm really, really pleased
with it.
It's definitely different from
what other people have created.
I'm thinking,
"that's not too bad."
My makeup walks out,
and I am thrilled.
If I go home, I will go home
with my head held up high.
Well, judges, why don't you
take a closer look?
Wow, this is colorful.
Ah, thank you.
- Nice brain.
- Thank you.
Mouth open and close?
Mm-mm.
- It doesn't open at all?
- Mm-mm.
Okay, thanks.
Tilt your head
all the way back, please.
I like the top half of it.
And from the bottom down,
I screwed up really bad.
That's gonna put me
at the bottom.
We want to know what you think
of tonight's transformations.
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
I know it's bad.
I'm just hoping
that my concept,
at this point,
is gonna save me.
Shoulder pad?
- It's creeping me out.
- Yeah.
I know.
I still love it.
I'm really confident
that I'm at least safe.
Open and close your moth.
Can you turn profile for us?
Don't pull on those ears.
Those things are put together
with latex, a lick,
and a promise.
Paul, what were your thoughts?
How do you think they did?
There was a lot of creativity
that went into it.
And to see how many great ideas
there are here,
I was really impressed.
Thank you.
All right, well, the judges
have scored your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Sarah, Jason, and Alana...
You are safe.
Thank you so much, guys.
Please head back
to the makeup room.
So that means the rest of you
were the best
and the worst looks of the week.
The judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Tommy, you're up first.
Tommy, give us a background
on the ideas
you were working with here.
Well, my concept was
the infection is running
through his body.
He can see that different stages
are happening
at different times,
so he puts
all these wristwatches on.
While those watches
are still ticking,
he's running through the city,
and he's taking out zombies.
And what we have here is
finally the last watch ran out,
and he quite literally
ran out of time.
It seems like there's some
cool ideas in there.
I can't see them.
I don't know what's happening,
because you've just kind of got
that loathsome device
known as fun, fur, and gore.
I love all the concepts
behind your creation.
And, I've got to say,
I love the top 15% of it,
which is the head.
I just wish the rest
of your creation kind of matched
what you've done
with the-- with the head.
His left eye
is such a big feature,
but there's not enough gloss
to make it stand out.
It's a bit of a mess.
What the heck is he wearing,
and why?
That is the most distracting,
God-awful crap I've ever seen.
Um, well, in the storybook,
he has got, like,
that tweed jacket.
- Dude, that is not tweed.
- Oh.
That is a bloody flannel shirt.
Tommy, thank you.
You can step back.
Laura.
So, Laura,
tell us about your
thought process behind this.
He's a zombie but he still has
that memory of being a hatter,
so he uses his intestine
as a measuring stick
to measure the hats.
Nice.
One of the things I love about
him is there's a real unity.
The color pallet
is all very unified,
which, I think,
is very, very strong.
I think
he's a wonderful creation.
- Thank you.
- I love it.
I love the fact
that it's sympathetic,
and it's locked in this echo
of the human emotions,
and it makes it
more frightening.
Well done.
Yes. Thank you.
Laura, please step back.
Roy.
Tell us about the inspiration
behind this character
you've created.
Uh, the inspiration
is that this is the queen,
and she's been infected
with the virus,
and so she's starting to mutate.
And her skin is making her
into the queen,
so she's forming the crown
out of her skin,
and all of her clothing
is starting to just rip away
and pull and bend and twist
into-- into her wardrobe.
I'm just mesmerized
by the look of this makeup
that you did.
- Really beautifully done.
- Thank you very much.
If I was making a movie,
I'd be delighted
to see a design like this.
But also, I'd be expecting
a team of like six or seven
people to execute it.
I think it's quite remarkable.
Roy, the fact
that you've created the design
on the top of the head
that is so regal and elegant
is my absolute favorite thing
about this makeup.
Well done.
Roy, thank you very much.
You can step back.
Thank you.
Nicole, you're up.
Give us a brief description
of the concept.
I wanted to play off
the eat me, drink me.
I wanted this vial
to be the infection,
and then she's
now eating the rabbit.
I like the ideas,
but it's the paintwork
that really makes it go flat.
She just disappears.
I don't know
what would have possessed you
to make her face all dark.
Even if your veins went south,
you could have painted
the veins on by hand.
I applaud the ambition
of the pulsing boils,
but that stuff is really
difficult to get right.
You know, maybe just
a bit too ambitious
for the time that you had.
Nicole, thank you.
Will you please step back?
Derek.
I got to tell you,
when he first walked out,
I thought he made
a pink cat, own criminy."
And then I got up close.
And it's pretty cool.
I mean, the asymmetry is great.
The whiskers on one side,
the teeth on the other.
He's morphed, he's gross,
he's very colorful--
I got to give it--
but the cheshire cat was purple,
so there you go.
I'm not sure what it is,
but there's something about that
shirt color that I really like.
The mouth on the left side
is fantastic.
I love this design.
It encapsulates the world
of mutation in Resident Evil.
I love how asymmetrical
the whole design is,
which I think is really fresh.
Cool, thank you.
Appreciate it.
Derek, thank you so much.
Will you please step back?
Rod, please step forward.
Rod, give us the backstory
to your character here.
The virus
that she's infected with
has hyper-accelerated
her metabolism.
Because of that, her skin goes
from full-sized to shriveled
and back and forth.
And that's what all the texture
has come from.
I'm having a hard time
finding the driving forces
propelling this design.
I don't really understand
the color choice
that you made
by giving her this skin color.
It's not really rotten
and it's not really dead,
and it's just kind of
an odd color choice.
And I think, for me, you just
kind of missed the mark on it.
What I don't find at all
is a zombie infected
with the virus.
You've missed the point
of the whole challenge.
Rod, thank you very much.
- Thank you, thank you.
- Please step back.
Okay, well, the judges have
heard what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they make their decisions.
All right guys,
so let's start with the looks
that you like the most.
Why don't we start with Roy.
I really dug that makeup.
You know, with the right
lighting and a little gloss,
that thing could be
amazing-looking just as it is.
It really captured
what I think is great
about Resident Evil,
which is the kind of
mutation aspect of it.
Okay, let's move on
to Laura's makeup.
There are no gaps between
the coloring of her makeup,
the wardrobe choices,
even the concept.
Very, very solid
all the way through.
Very well executed.
All right, let's move on
to Derek.
It was really, really good.
I loved the mask.
I loved the asymmetry of it.
When we got up close to it,
you really could see the detail
a lot better.
All right,
so why don't we move on
to the looks
that you liked the least.
Let's start with Tommy.
It looks like even
that one big bulging eye
just sort of got lost
in the makeup.
I was disappointed
with the design.
It felt very thrown-together.
All right,
let's move on to Nicole.
I can't believe that she would
just paint the face
charcoal gray.
The boils
that looked like brains,
you know, it just looked
like bad brains.
Yeah.
All right, let's move on
to Rod.
This bums me out so much.
For me that makeup looked like
a very bizarre old-age makeup.
It has nothing
to do with Alice in Wonderland.
And then it has nothing
to do with zombies.
- Right.
- Like drinking blood.
That's more kind of vampiric.
Okay, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- I think so.
- We have.
Yes.
Let's bring them back out.
♪
all right, Glenn, why don't you
tell us about the top looks?
This week our top looks are...
Roy...
We loved
your hyper-stylized queen,
and we thought
that you accomplished
an absolutely amazing amount of
work in the time that you had.
Thank you.
Laura...
You made some really interesting
sculptural choices,
and you really managed
to create
this feeling of sympathy
with your character.
Derek...
Your design really captured
the spirit of this challenge.
And your asymmetrical approach
to your design
left a big impression on us.
Paul, why don't you do
the honors tonight,
and tell us who the winner
of this challenge is?
The winner is...
Paul, why don't you do
the honors tonight,
and tell us who the winner
of this challenge is?
The winner is...
Roy.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
This is the best moment
I've had on the show,
because this is me individually
with a win, finally.
Roy, congratulations.
You can head back
to the makeup room.
Laura and Derek,
you are also safe.
Please head back
to the makeup room.
Unfortunately, that means
the three of you were
on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Nicole, Tommy, Rod...
If you'd please step
to the center.
Glenn, why don't you tell us
about the bottom looks?
Tommy, I think you might
have had some good ideas,
but it's just impossible
to see any of them.
Nicole, there is
just too many things
that went wrong
for you tonight,
in particular, your paint job.
Rod, it didn't read as a zombie,
and we were just confused.
All right, Glenn,
who's going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Nicole.
Ultimately, we felt
that there were so many ways
that you could have saved
your makeup.
The rest of you are safe
this week,
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Nicole, we can tell
that you have a great passion
for your craft.
Just keep plugging away,
you'll get there.
I will.
Thank you.
Nicole, it's been really great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room,
and pack up your kit.
Thank you guys.
Hi.
- Me.
- No.
A lot of people go through life
and never find what they love
to do,
and I'm a lucky person
that's found that.
Makeup is my soul.
It's what I live for.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net