Previously, on Face Off...
12 talented makeup artists
arrived in Los Angeles,
and for their first challenge
created original
Star Wars aliens.
I'm geeking out.
Rod's stellar creature
makeup took him to the top,
and Joe was
the first contestant to go home.
Now 11 artists remain.
Tonight, they'll take
to the high seas...
Oh, my God, I knew it!
I knew it was pirates!
Where the stakes are higher than ever.
This is a Face Off first.
You need to learn
to mold faster.
I don't know if I can do this.
Oh, shit.
The cowl is stuck.
Oh, God, this is trouble.
This is gonna look stupid.
This may put me in the bottom.
And on stage, they will lay
everything on the line.
Fuck.
I really, really, really
wanna win this challenge.
It took my breath away.
The thing's wretched.
It doesn't work at all.
I'm thinking,
"this is terrifying."
In the end, only one
will win the opportunity
to be a guest lecturer
at Makeup For Ever's academies
in New York and Paris,
a new 2012 Toyota Prius V,
and $100,000.
And for the first time ever,
America,
your voice will be heard
in selecting the winner.
Only one will win Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
What's going on with the arm?
Uh, I overworked it.
I went to the doctor
and it turned out all
the tendons from all my fingers
are inflamed and crossed over.
During the first challenge,
then I noticed something
terribly wrong with my wrist.
Do you feel like you can do
the next challenge okay?
It's gonna get worse.
The pain's gonna get worse.
So what do you do?
It's one of those choices--
either quit,
or just grin and bear it.
I'm not quitting.
Uh, guys!
There's something down here
in the kitchen!
My eye catches a chest that
I had not seen there before.
"Good morning, artists.
I'm sending you on
a little trip today.
Before you head out,
open the box and pick one.
Make sure to bring it along.
You're gonna need it.
See you there,
McKenzie."
Oh, wow.
- Do it, do it.
- Do it? Do it?
All of us take a key.
And we're all trying
to match 'em up to one another.
And maybe
it's a team challenge.
Let's get ready.
Let's go.
- Yep.
- Okay.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
We're all really excited,
and we have no idea
what's coming next.
I've never been on a train,
so...
It's pretty bad-ass
and it's fun.
I'm ready
for whatever's coming.
I'm bingo, bango,
ready to go-go.
We get off the train,
and we are in San Diego.
Ooh, look at the front
of that ship.
We're walking along this pier,
and I notice
this magnificent vessel.
Hi, guys.
Welcome to San Diego.
This is the HMS Surprise.
It's been used
in major Hollywood films
like Master And Commander
The Far Side Of The World,
also The Pirates
Of The Caribbean films.
This week's spotlight challenge
is to create an original
pirate character
who has become one
with the seas.
Oh, my God, I knew it!
I knew it was pirates!
So excited because
I love pirates so much.
I've wanted to do
a crazy pirate for so long.
This is also going to be
your first individual challenge.
A little scary.
Onboard are all kinds
of treasure chests.
Inside each one is
a different inspiration
for your makeups.
Now did you all
bring your keys?
Each one of your keys
opens one of the chests.
When I call your name,
I want you to head up
onto the ship
and claim the scroll inside.
Nicole, you're up first.
Yeah, buddy!
"Ship in a bottle."
This is scaring me,
because how am I supposed to put
a heavy ship in a bottle
on my makeup?
Jason.
Cool.
Oh.
Derek.
Before I send you back to L.A.
to start your work,
I'm sure you've noticed
there's one extra chest here.
- You wanna know what's inside?
- Yeah.
Yes.
Oh, wow.
This is a Face Off first.
The winner of this spotlight
challenge
will receive a pirate's booty
of their own.
$5,000.
Oh, that's awesome.
There's a money prize,
which is incredibly exciting,
and terrifying,
and I immediately think
all right,
the pressure is incredibly on.
I want you to get
inspired with this challenge,
so why don't you take some time
to just hang out, sketch?
And when you're done,
I want you to head back to L.A.,
pick your models,
and get started.
Good luck, everybody.
I do love pirates.
So this is a pretty
fantastic day for me.
I have kelp.
I came up with this whole idea
for this ship captain
whose ship has sank and
he's walking the ocean floor.
I really, really, really
wanna win this challenge.
I got crabs.
I wanna take all the high points
in my model's face
and accent them
with crab shells,
make them look
like they're hard.
I'm hoping I have enough time
to do all this stuff.
I have a dagger.
So I start thinking
about my pirate
being an expert with daggers,
and she keeps them in her body.
So her daggers are
in her ribcage in the front,
and then also in her ribs
in the back.
Just doing this challenge
is great,
but having that extra $5,000--
that's extra incentive.
We all arrive back at the lab,
and now it's time
for us to choose our models.
In my head, I'm picturing
the old captain with a beard.
But I'm the last one
to pick my life cast
and I'm stuck with a girl.
So I have to do a gender swap.
It's gonna be a hard one
for me.
Immediately, I need
to start sculpting his face,
and I think, man,
that would be cute
to have a shell
on the guy's head
and his face as a creature
so we can still
incorporate the eyes
and have that creature
just coming out of the shell.
I wanna put hair in here.
You're making him look
so angry.
Yeah.
Derek and I wanna sit next
to each other just to have fun.
I love hanging out
with my brother.
He's like one
of my best friends.
I got barnacles.
I'm not a great sketcher,
so I jot down notes
of textures, textures,
and the design
of what it is that I wanna do.
I definitely
wanna challenge myself
and change it up
as much as I can.
Pirate is becoming one
with the sea.
So I wanted to have a seahorse
that's being born through him
into the sea.
I'm gonna have
to really be good
with my time management
and planning.
So I'm concerned.
My concept is
this pirate is lazy,
not doing what he's supposed
to be doing,
so the captain fused
this spyglass
to his face permanently.
So that's pretty much
all he's able to do
is look out in the ocean.
When I see jewels,
I'm kinda like okay,
I could do whatever
I would like with this.
What are you doing?
Doing a pirate
that's infested with octopus.
My concept is a greedy,
jewel thief pirate.
He's got the treasure,
but the octopus
got him as well.
If I won the extra five grand,
I'd probably throw most of it
onto my student loans.
That's my biggest burden
right now.
It's what holds me back.
The thing I keep going back to
is on the sidewalk outside
there are all these cracks.
And I'm thinking
about the sea urchin
just kind popping out
of this ball thing.
So I decide I'm gonna do
a chest piece of cracking,
so we'll see where it goes.
I'm gonna do this part
a different color
from that part.
Yeah, ah, yeah.
So this looks hard
and that looks soft.
This is a lot of work.
It's the most work I've
ever taken on in my life,
single-handedly,
and I'm terrified.
I'm not too sure
what's going on with CC.
She seems lost.
Like she can't solidify
a concept.
I'm looking around the lab,
I'm seeing amazing things,
a lot of fabrication.
I'm still trying to figure out
a neat design.
How much time we got left?
2 hours, 51 minutes.
I'm a little nerve-wracked
at this point.
I'm trying to get
a game plan together.
I have to really pull
some tricks out of the bag
because I don't wanna
be going home.
Coming up...
I don't know if I can do this.
My mold is stuck.
This is trouble.
Tonight, for the first time,
we have a very big prize
on the line.
Great silhouette,
fantastic job.
You were a little
directionless here.
I'm worried
I'm going home tonight.
I'm trying to come up
with an original pirate.
Barnacles are tough
because I don't know
a whole bunch about them.
It's not a crab or a shell--
something that is
a little more common.
So I'm starting to rough out
my sculpture
while trying to incorporate
the basic shape of the barnacle.
Ah! Damn it!
I'm trying to be careful
when I'm trying to use the tools
the way I normally use them,
and they're attacking me.
Where can I get a band-aid?
I'm bleeding like a maniac.
I just don't wanna
take anymore time for bleeding.
Thank you.
I'm just like, why?
Why now?
It's gonna affect my sculpture
and my mold-making.
All right everybody, time's up.
Let's go home.
So, it's day two, and I pick up
where I left off yesterday.
The winner of this challenge
will win $5,000.
That just raised the stakes
for everybody.
Everybody wants to win
that booty.
Once my sculpture is finished,
it's time to make the mold.
You do this by putting
a cement-like substance
on top of the sculpture.
Once it hardens,
you clean out the clay
and it fill it with foam
or silicone.
The foam or silicone eventually
becomes the prosthetic.
I chose to do the one piece
because I want to focus on
the detail that I wanna put
into the face.
And this mold is all I have.
I have to get it done right
the first time.
This is actually gonna be
a belt buckle
or a centerpiece
for my character.
He is a jewel thief,
and I'm tying the barnacles
in there
in the fact that
when he does these bad deeds
the barnacles start to grow
out of his skin.
So those are actually gonna be
in my face piece.
Hey, everybody!
- Hey.
- Hi, guys.
I have the amazing Ve
here with us today
to see how you're doing.
Of course it's gonna be Ve
because she's done
all the pirate movies.
You know,
Pirates Of The Caribbean.
She did amazing stuff with
each one of those characters.
Hi, CC.
How are you?
My inspiration was barnacles.
But he's all about his money
and finding jewels.
So right now,
I'm making him a belt piece
that's gonna have some
of the pieces on there that--
Wow. I was beginning to think
your inspiration was jewels.
Right, yeah.
Uh, hearing Ve say
that she thinks I have jewels
is a little nerve-wracking
because I feel like
I have to kinda change
my concept up again.
I'm going for like maybe
a steampunk type of look to it.
So he's got all the wiring going
in through his skin.
If you're doing steampunk,
you better do it right,
'cause Glenn'll really be
down your throat if you don't.
- Okay.
- Oh, yeah.
Here's my concept is, uh--
She actually carries her daggers
with her all the time
and has 'em in her ribcage
and in her back.
- Wow. She's bad-ass.
- Yeah.
Can't wait to see it.
- Hey, Nicole.
- Hello.
- How are you?
- Good, how are you?
My inspiration piece
is a ship in a bottle.
I'm thinking the captain
of a ship.
Then his ship blow up,
and now he's like been impaled
with pieces of wood
from the ship.
Are you doing a male
or a female?
'Cause this is a female body.
It's a female body, but--
You're making a female
into a male.
Okay, I think the transition
is gonna be a detriment
to your makeup
as opposed to something
that's gonna make it better.
Now I'm thinking,
should I change everything?
This may put me in the bottom
for trying to change a gender.
- Hi.
- How are you?
When Ve walks in, I think
everyone is pretty nervous.
You know,
the last time I saw her
I was on stage
and it wasn't such a good time.
- Holy smoke, that's cool!
- Wow.
- Thank you!
- Wow!
- I'm calling you for Halloween.
So, she has this chest piece
that's gonna go down here.
Oh, that's really bitchin'.
And then the face piece goes
here and back into her hairline.
She's gonna be
slightly grotesque
within this beautiful costume,
isn't she?
Awesome.
Anything standing out to you?
Um, I liked Roy's
with the daggers.
I liked the idea that
they're stuck in the ribcage
and all that.
That was a really cool idea.
Sarah and the amazing costume.
Which isn't makeup, but
it's still an amazing costume.
So I think that might be
really cool
when it's all put together.
Nicole,
who had "ship in a bottle."
Yeah, and she's doing
the female as a male.
How did you feel about that?
If she's a real tiny woman,
I think it could be a detriment
to the whole picture.
Just have to scale it all down.
All right, well, we'll see
how it turns out tomorrow.
- Yeah, can't wait.
- Thank you.
Okay, everybody,
we're heading out.
Good luck tomorrow.
Good luck, everybody.
What do you think I should lay
this up with? Just some shim?
I'm trying to do
a face and a cowl,
which is basically
a hood for a makeup.
Never applied more than five
prosthetics in my life,
so, this is a lot of work.
I'm running around the shop,
asking everybody
I know for advice,
because I'm the youngest person
in this competition.
Do you think I could start
the other half of this mold?
Oh, yeah, a long time ago.
I want my character to have
a coral skin structure,
and hands
turning into tentacles.
It's definitely gonna be a lot
of stuff I want to get done.
Ve said that she didn't like
that I was turning
a girl into a guy.
I was feeling really good,
I was really liking my concept,
and now I'm just
really concerned.
It's like, maybe I did
the wrong thing.
I'm at a loss right now.
I don't really know
what I'm gonna do.
I just wanna do a scary pirate.
Like, a dude, like, a--
You know?
So, the sea urchin has
this yellow gooey stuff in it,
and I want to have yellow gooey
stuff on my sea urchin.
So, my plan is to work out
with my model
squeezing the syringe
and letting it all ooze out.
If something gets stuck,
or it's the wrong consistency,
then it might splatter
on the judges,
and that terrifies me.
I have a lot
of work to finish up.
I need to get this cowl molded,
and I don't even
have my claw finished yet.
I'm running around the shop,
shaking like a leaf.
I'm like, "I don't know
if I can do this".
Alana, there's one hour left.
I just need
to get my beauty coat
onto my other half of my cowl.
All I want to do
is cry right now,
because this is
gonna be a disaster.
You need to learn
to mold faster.
Oh, shit.
My molds are set.
I have to clean them out.
It seems impossible
with one hand.
My mold is stuck
to the positive of the head.
I grab a hammer, 'cause I know
I have to break the edge.
Time is ticking,
I'm going at this
as smoothly and as fast
as I can make myself go.
Ouch.
And the cowl
is just not giving.
It's feeling like,
oh, God, this is trouble.
The cowl is stuck
to the positive of the head.
Okay...
You just want to do
all these things calmly.
If you get frazzled,
you will crack a mold,
and break it, and be without.
Thank God the positive releases
out of the negative,
and I start cleaning clay.
What am I looking for?
Um...
Uh, I don't know what to do!
Everyone is really
stepping it up.
A lot of people
are fabricating stuff.
I've never fabricated
anything before,
but I'm thinking a mast
from the ship going through him.
I'm just gonna do everything
I can to figure it out.
This is gonna look stupid.
This is gonna, like...
If it's in somebody,
it's, like, wobbly. You know?
My problem
for the rest of the day
is trying to figure out how
this fabrication is gonna work.
I'm trying to get
my cowl finished
before the end of the day.
And time is just ticking
and running out.
I'm shaking like a leaf
at this point.
I'm like, I don't know if I'm
gonna be able
to do this in time.
Last mold of the day, we're
gonna pull it and clean it.
Are there any
wooden tools out here?
I'm trying to get
my cowl cleaned out,
and nothing
is going as planned.
I have a hole in my mold.
Awesome.
This could go one of two ways.
And I just don't want it
to go that other way.
Oh, fuck!
You wanna go help Alana?
Needs to get her shit molded,
and she's got 20 minutes left.
- She outside?
- Yeah.
We're trying to clean
Alana's mold.
Alana's having some trouble
getting a mold finished up.
If I was in the same position,
I'd want someone to help me,
so, I'm gonna go help 'em.
This sucks.
We gotta get you
making faster molds, missy.
I know, dude, I really
thought that I was like,
hauling ass on my mold,
and then I looked up,
and it's like,
oh, okay, time's almost over.
I have angels all around,
and they are helping me.
All right, guys. I think
I gotta close my core up.
I'm just like,
looking up to the sky,
just thanking God
for all these amazing people.
Okay, guys, it's time!
Let's go.
At the end of the day,
I'm amazed that I have a cowl
and a chest piece done.
So, I am concerned.
How am I going to get
these pieces well-applied?
With one hand, and this.
Today is application day,
and we have four hours
in the shop
to apply our makeup,
start pre-painting,
working on our costume,
and then have an hour
for last looks.
I really want
to win that $5,000.
It would really
help out back home.
Me and the girlfriend
are struggling.
So, that money's
pretty important to me.
I'm feeling pretty nervous,
just because there's
a lot to do in four hours.
And there's never
enough time in the day.
Glad this me out okay.
Shoot, models are coming in.
- I'm Jason.
- James.
Nice to meet you, James.
I just want to see if it fits.
Immediately,
I put on the headpiece.
I'm on a timeline here.
Gotta just start
busting stuff out.
Looks good, looks good,
looks good.
Let's see if this will fit you.
I have quite a bit to do.
I need to lay down my bald cap
and then get
my face appliance on my model,
blend the edges off,
and then start to paint it.
I learned that sea urchins
eat kelp beds.
That's why your skirt
is kind of kelpy,
and the sea urchins are coming
through and eating you,
turning you into
this sea witch character.
It would be amazing to win this,
and to get this money.
I would probably take my
boyfriend out for a nice dinner.
He might deserve that.
You, my dear, look awesome.
I'm in a comfortable place.
I get the face on,
I get the chest on,
just like I planned to do,
and I go to put on the wig...
And it doesn't fit.
It doesn't fit at all.
I had hot glued all these
different plants into the hair,
and so it's all
tied and glued together,
and there's no untying it
and making it work.
Bring your hand down with me.
Crap.
So, I make the decision
to put a bald cap on this guy.
It would fix my problem.
Yeah, that'll be nice.
I'll just have to
lift the appliance.
It definitely takes
a giant chunk out of my day.
Fuck!
I just know naturally, I'm
a very scatterbrained person.
Who the fuck
would leave that on?
And I know I need
to slow down a little bit.
Someone left
the soldering iron on.
Thank you.
Because the more time
I spend with Mr. Medic,
the more time I take away
from my application.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
As I start painting my model,
the paint is starting
to dry really fast.
Starting to crack a lot.
I see his skin coming through,
so I know, like,
the only way to really cover it
and to get an even tone
is to darken his skin tone.
- A lot-- lotta work.
- And your chin back.
Application day
is a nightmare for me.
I lost a lot of time
realigning that wig.
At first I was thinking
I might win the $5,000,
and now I'm thinking
I'll be lucky to be safe.
We have four minutes left.
Yeah, buddy.
I rip my crab claw
out of the mold,
and it still
has flashing around it.
I don't have time to trim this.
I gotta worry about it
at last looks.
I have to finish my makeup,
get my model in her costume,
and trim this whole thing,
and make it work.
Guys, that's time.
I have a lot of work
to do in this last hour.
I gotta boogie, I gotta roll.
I'm borderline having a seizure
at how nervous I am.
Coming up...
We have a very
big prize on the line.
You can't help but think it's
a kick-ass-looking character.
Honestly, you were a little
directionless here.
It was just wretched.
It took my breath away.
I can almost smell $5,000.
We have an hour for last looks.
I'm just hoping
mine stands out,
because everybody's doing
really big pieces.
I have so much
to do at last looks.
I don't have much
prosthetic-laying experience,
and it's showing.
Ah, this is pulling
too much, okay.
It really is tough to
finish a piece with one hand.
That's one minute!
Put your hands out for me.
I have a finished product,
I don't know how the judges
are gonna feel about it,
but I'm very proud.
Time!
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
First, say hello
to your judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
Argh, mateys!
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
Hello, everyone.
- Hi.
This week,
your spotlight challenge
was to create
an original pirate
who has become
one with the sea.
And tonight,
for the first time,
we have a very
big prize on the line.
A pirate's booty of $5,000.
So, let's see what
you've all come up with.
First up is Rod.
At this point,
I'm looking at the silhouette,
and the shape is looking good.
My pirate walks out onstage,
and I think he's awesome.
He's pulling off
the whole character.
It looks great, I love it.
I think that I have
a really good chance
of being in the top looks
on this one.
I mean, I can almost
smell $5,000.
I feel like
my character is striking.
It carries the emotions
that I put into it.
I've never fabricated anything,
and I'm worried
about the mast right now,
just 'cause
the thing's bending.
This could possibly
put me in the bottom.
I do feel confident, I feel
proud of what I've accomplished.
Now whether or not the judges
will like it or not, you know,
is another story.
I'm pretty proud of my makeup.
I mean, there's
a couple of things
I would've maybe rather
have done different,
but it's pretty
cool-looking.
I'm feeling
pretty good about it,
but there's some
really strong pieces,
so... we'll see what happens.
I think he looks pretty gross.
He had his finger
in his belly button.
He looks nasty. He looks
like I wanted him to look.
She looks amazing.
She is a crab girl,
and she is one fierce bitch.
I question maybe
one or two of the things,
but 90% of it I'm happy with.
Judges, why don't you
take a closer look?
See that bottom of the nose,
and the lips sloughing off?
Oh, oh. I thought
that was actually lips.
Yeah, no,
this is the lips up there.
- This is all pretty cool.
- Yeah.
This idea.
It's a shame
it's not more of it.
Yeah.
Looks like the mast
has gone a bit flaccid.
My mast totally bent
really bad.
I'm just thinking,
"I'm going home tonight."
We want to know what you think
of tonight's transformations.
Tell us on Twitter,
using the #FaceOff.
Looks like the mast
has gone a bit flaccid.
My mast totally, like, bent.
She needs a little Vi-arr-gra.
I'm really concerned
about going home tonight.
First thing that comes to mind
is the barnacles should
at least look like barnacles.
I don't see "barnacle"
in it anywhere.
What do we have coming through
the forehead there?
That's the sea urchin things
coming out.
Oh, God.
- Oh!
- Nice.
They loved
my little ooze trick,
so I'm really happy I did that.
The texture on the face
is lacking detail.
The inspiration was jewels.
And there they are.
You were gesticulating and
doing some cool stuff in here.
So, you're doing this?
Uh-huh.
Thanks.
The judges have scored
your creations.
Let's find out
what they thought.
Tommy.
Nicole.
Rod.
Derek.
And Alana.
You are all safe.
Oh!
Please head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you guys.
So, the rest of you
were the best
and the worst of the week.
The judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Eric, you're up.
Your inspiration is the...
- The spyglass looking out.
- Right?
It seems to me like you missed
a chance to do something
different and fun
with that whole scenario,
- Yeah.
- and you didn't do it.
That being said,
I do like that side of his face
- with all that detail with it...
- Thank you.
Like, being fused in there.
Honestly, the thing
sticking out of his face
is just wretched.
I wish you would've
seen that and changed course.
Looks like
a small chimney stack.
Little bricks.
And I really didn't
like the eyeball.
It turned it, really,
into a cartoony effect.
I was kind of worried
about that happening,
but I like the paint job
that I did on it.
I was trying
to go for a steampunk
kind of aspect with the...
Told you to stay
away from that.
Eric, you can step back.
Fuck.
Roy, you're up next.
So, tell us a little bit
about what was the inspiration.
Scarlett was a captain who was
both beautiful
and deadly with a knife.
And after she spurned
the affections of Davy Jones,
he condemned her to the reef.
Great, well,
you know, the silhouette
when she first came out was
one of the more profound ones.
You can't help but think it's
a kick-ass-looking character
when you've got knives
in the back.
M'kay, thank you.
I think the greatest success
that you've achieved
in this makeup
is the fact that it's
very hard to figure out how
to integrate a dagger without
doing lame-ass knife hands.
You know, something like that.
You go, "what do I do
with this knife?"
Just a really cool image.
Not at all what
I would have gone for,
which is what makes me respect
and appreciate it even more.
Thank you very much.
I love all your
little clever things
making the sea urchins
out of the feathers up there.
What a clever idea.
You did a great job, Roy.
Roy, thank you very much.
CC.
CC, could you start
by explaining
the concept behind your makeup?
My guy has been
cursed by a sea witch
for all of his evildoing.
I feel like you were
a little directionless here.
And I see that reflected
in the makeup, unfortunately.
I want to find out
why you chose
to alter his skin tone so much.
Initially, I was going
with more of a lighter paint,
but it started to do
some cracking on me,
so I just decided to go
with something a lot darker.
I don't think this was very
successful for you today, CC.
The growths on his face
don't feel like barnacles.
And you've made it
so symmetrical,
it feels more like
a face flute.
That's not a good thing.
CC, thank you very much.
Sarah, you're next.
Tell us a little bit
about the concept.
She's a pirate wench.
The boat capsized,
and then these urchins
have infested her
and are starting to come out.
There's this wonderful
rhythm of-- of form.
It keeps it dynamic,
and keeps your eye interested.
Thank you very much.
My favorite thing
about this is this haunted look
that comes from the color
palette that you chose.
- Really, really cool color.
- Thank you.
- Really cool breakup.
When we were
in the lab yesterday,
it took my breath away.
And I thought, oh, my God,
if the makeup
is as good as this costume,
it's gonna be amazing,
and you did not disappoint.
- Thank you very much.
- Sarah, thank you so much.
Jason, you're up.
Well, Jason,
can you please explain to me
what jewels has to do
with your pirate.
He was going for the treasure,
but not without
getting attacked by octopus.
I'm kind of disappointed.
You could've done
so many other things.
You just didn't
embrace the jewel thing.
It doesn't look like
there's a huge amount
of character design
within that facial sculpture
to warrant having gone
through all of that effort.
We've spent all of this time
creating a full-facial
prosthetic,
and a chest and belly,
which accomplish,
for me, almost nothing.
I could've spent a little bit
more time sculpting the octopus,
but I really wanted to stay away
from being too terrifying.
I wanted to make
a believable character.
I think that may be
right where you fell down.
And that's
in the conceptual stage.
Jason, thank you very much.
Thank you.
Laura.
Could you begin by telling us
about the concept
of your makeup?
The item I was given
was a shell.
And I decided that I would have
the model's face coming out
as the creature,
and the head be the shell.
It's got a really nice feel
head to toe.
It feels to me like you've
endeavored to tackle
a lot of different elements
you addressed head to toe,
which-- that's awesome.
I thought it was
a great silhouette.
The fact that you were able
to get that much definition
in this headdress piece
is really quite good.
- Fantastic job.
- Thank you.
I do like the coloring,
I like the way you painted it,
and I think you did
a successful makeup.
Thank you very much.
You can step back.
Okay, guys, the judges have
heard what you have to say.
Please head back
to the makeup room
while they make
their final decision.
All right, guys, so let's
start with the top looks.
Why don't we begin with Laura's
shell-inspired pirate?
I love her form,
I love her attention to detail.
Everything else I'm looking at,
we have human facial form
popping through
whatever they did underneath it.
Yeah, she tried
just a little bit harder
to do something different,
and that was a really
huge challenge, I mean, wow.
All right,
then let's move on to Sarah.
I love the profile
of that makeup,
all of her choices
were really well-done,
right down to the little goo
when we walked up,
that was so cool.
It exudes confidence to me
that she was able to do
all that work,
and still manage to remember
to put one little
gag in there...
- Yeah.
- To push it over the top.
All right,
let's move on to Roy.
He addressed
a large part of the challenge.
Very simple,
very straightforward,
and then spent
the rest of his time
figuring out how to put those
daggers in in a way that works.
It was a beautiful color,
good execution. Impressive.
Why don't we talk
about some of the looks
you liked the least this week?
Why don't we start with Jason?
Jason's approach
was totally lackluster.
The whole thing was really bad.
And jewels.
- Where were the jewels?
- In his hand.
This is BS,
this handful of jewels.
All right, let's move on to CC.
Everything she did she made
bad choices, unfortunately,
and I don't even
know where to start.
Sculpturally, huge problems.
Application-wise,
huge problems.
Coloring, huge problems.
All right,
let's move on to Eric.
It might as well have been
a paper towel roll
glued to his eyeball.
Could not have been worse.
It came out too far.
- Yes.
- The eyeball looks fake.
He liked the paint job
on the eyeball, so he put it on.
- Ah, I heard that. Uh...
- Yeah.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- Yup.
- I believe so.
Okay,
let's bring them back out.
Glenn, why don't you tell us
about the top looks?
Laura, your character
had really interesting colors,
and you did a great job
embracing the challenge.
Sarah, your character
had an incredible silhouette.
The makeup and the wardrobe
was fantastic.
And, Roy, you did something
very unexpected.
The daggers were incorporated
in a really cerebral way.
All right, then, Glenn,
who is the winner
of this challenge
and the $5,000 prize?
The winner
of this challenge is...
All right, then, Glenn,
who is the winner of this
challenge and the $5,000 prize?
The winner
of this challenge is...
Sarah.
Thank you.
It was just awesome.
The spines that were
bursting from the skin,
the paint job--
Very, very complete character.
Well done.
It feels incredibly amazing
to have my work recognized.
Plus I'm taking home $5,000.
Well done, Sarah.
Congratulations
on your $5,000 win.
Thank you very much.
You can head back
to the makeup room.
Laura and Roy,
you are also safe this week.
Please head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Unfortunately,
that means the rest of you
were our bottom looks
this week.
One of you
is going to be eliminated.
If you please step forward.
All right, Glenn,
why don't you tell us
- about the bottom looks?
- Eric...
You had the opportunity
to do something
really cool with this concept.
And instead, we ended up
with a lame attempt
at a steampunk pirate.
CC, your lack
of a solid concept
really compromised
your final product.
And, Jason,
the jewels seemed like they
weren't really much of
a consideration in your makeup.
It was a dispassionate job.
So, who is going home tonight?
The person
going home tonight is...
CC.
Your sculpt didn't read
as barnacles.
That was the big problem.
In the end,
we just think that you need
to work on your skill set
and your design work.
CC, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
The rest of you
are safe this week.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room.
Sorry.
I want to say
that what I see out of you
is the passionate
makeup artist.
Don't give up.
It's just the beginning.
CC, it's been great
having you here with us.
Will you please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you, guys.
- Thank you, CC. Good luck.
- Good luck.
So, I'm going home.
No.
I think the hardest part
about leaving now
is I would love to show
more of my skills.
The future, I feel like,
for me, is bright.
I'm moving forward,
I'm gonna continue to push,
and show that I can
do amazing art.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net