- Previously on
"RuPaul's Drag Race"...
You'll be competing
in the drag-apella movie,
- Previously on
"RuPaul's Drag Race"...
"Bitch Perfect."
- Previously on
"RuPaul's Drag Race"...
all: ♪ Now sissy that walk ♪
- Previously on
"RuPaul's Drag Race"...
- Chi Chi DeVayne,
- Previously on
"RuPaul's Drag Race"...
condragulations, you are the
winner of this week's challenge.
- Previously on
"RuPaul's Drag Race"...
- Dax ExclamationPoint,
- Previously on
"RuPaul's Drag Race"...
Laila McQueen,
- Previously on
"RuPaul's Drag Race"...
neither one of you survived
that lip sync.
- Previously on
"RuPaul's Drag Race"...
[dramatic music]
- Previously on
"RuPaul's Drag Race"...
Sashay away.
- Previously on
"RuPaul's Drag Race"...
[laid-back music]
♪
- Oh, my God.
- Oh!
[laid-back music]
- I did not
even see that coming.
[laid-back music]
- Gag of the century.
- You never know
what's gonna happen,
[laid-back music]
and when you on the stage,
bitch,
you better own it.
[laid-back music]
This is a wakeup call
for all of us.
[laid-back music]
If you ain't stepping
that pussy up,
[laid-back music]
your ass is going home.
- So who do you guys think
that RuPaul called?
[laid-back music]
- I had to eliminate
two queens today.
[laid-back music]
How soon can you get here?
- One queen who needs
to be redeemed
more than any queen
on the "Drag Race"
- One queen who needs
to be redeemed
is Victoria "Pork Chop" Parker.
- One queen who needs
to be redeemed
- Question is
when Shangela returns,
- One queen who needs
to be redeemed
what are we gonna do?
- One queen who needs
to be redeemed
[laughter]
- One queen who needs
to be redeemed
I think we should all agree that
whoever the girl that comes in,
- One queen who needs
to be redeemed
we just ignore her
and treat her like poo.
- One queen who needs
to be redeemed
- Damn.
- One queen who needs
to be redeemed
We have another bitch
coming into the competition?
- One queen who needs
to be redeemed
[dramatic tones]
- One queen who needs
to be redeemed
Girl,
this is some bullshit.
- One queen who needs
to be redeemed
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- The winner
of "RuPaul's Drag Race"
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
receives
a one-year supply
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
of Anastasia
Beverly Hills cosmetics
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
and a cash prize of $100,000.
With extra-special guest judges
"Empire's" Tasha Smith
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
and the legendary
Faith Evans!
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- ♪ May the best woman,
best woman win ♪
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
[tires screeching]
[upbeat music]
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- Work.
[laughter]
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- It's a brand-new day!
We've survived.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
[siren wails]
- Ooh, girl.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
She done already
done had herses.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
To be America's
next drag superstar,
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
you don't need to be humble.
- Agreed.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- But if you trip or stumble,
well, honey, that's just
the way that cookie crumbles.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
[chuckles dramatically]
[laughter]
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
[door squeaking]
- Hello, hello, hello.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Wow!
- This is the outfit.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- Why, thank you.
It is
a Klein Epstein & Parker suit.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
They're made to measure.
- [laughs]
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- Now, ladies,
when the Supreme Court
legalized same sex marriage,
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
they moved this country
boldly forward.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
But when it comes
to their sense of style,
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
the justices are,
like, so 18th century.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- Yeah.
- Oh, Pit Crew!
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- Whoo!
- Oh!
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- Now for today's
mini challenge,
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
I want you to drag up
these basic black robes.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
Think Judge Judy Couture.
We'll take a 30-minute recess,
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
and then, the Supreme Court
Fashion Show will be in session.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
Go!
- Ah!
[laughter]
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
[upbeat music]
- Think this looks like
absolute garbage, and I love it.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- Ladies!
Time's up.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
Category is,
Supreme Court Realness.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
[gavel pounding]
First up,
Bob The Drag Queen.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
She received
her law degree online
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
from the Tyler Perry "I Can
Learn Law All By Myself" school.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
Supreme Court Justice
Naomi Smalls
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
from the law firm
of Evangelista and Fangs.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
She almost got disbarred
for excessive mouth pops.
- [pops]
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
That was only one.
- [popping]
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- [laughs]
Justice Derrick Barry.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
She was inspired to study law
after sneaking into a matinee
of "Legally Blonde."
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
Oh!
- Oh, and then my wig come off.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- All rise
for Supreme Court Justice
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
Cynthia Lee Fontaine,
AKA Cuckoo Freedom.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- [laughs]
- She made herstory
with her landmark verdict
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
for legalizing sex.
[record scratches]
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
Really, Judge?
- [laughs]
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- I think it was funny.
- [laughs]
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- Supreme Court Justice
Acid Betty.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
She believes
in every citizen's right
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
to go fisting.
[record scratches]
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
Uh, it said--
I'm sorry, it's go fishing.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
[laughter]
Supreme Court Justice
Robbie Turner.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
If Justice Turner
had her way,
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
she'd outlaw ex-boyfriend
Donald Trump.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- [laughs]
- All rise
for Supreme Court Justice
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
Kim Chi.
She got her start at the law
firm of Ching Chang & Chong.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
I did not write these.
[laughter]
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
Do not send me letters.
Supreme Court Justice
Thorgy Thor.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
She made herstory
legalizing the right
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
to stop traffic
and tap-dance.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
[car horn honks]
[laughter]
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
All rise
for Supreme Court Justice
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
Chi Chi DeVayne.
She made herstory
with her landmark verdict
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
legalizing ass clapping.
- Wha!
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
[laughter]
- Yes, Your Honor, yes.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
If justice is blind,
that bitch is missing out.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
[laughter]
The winner is...
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
[drum roll]
Naomi Smalls.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- Nice!
- Ooh!
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- And I'll be posting
all of these supreme looks
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
at logotv.com.
Ladies, last week,
several eliminations
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
left a void
that I've decided to fill
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
with the one and only...
[dramatic music]
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
- Bitches, I'm back!
[all screaming]
- Naysha Lopez.
- Bitches, I'm back!
- Oh, my God,
it's Naysha!
- Bitches, I'm back!
She's back on the competition.
- Naysha should have walked in
with her luggage
- Bitches, I'm back!
and just kept on walking.
Bye, girl.
- Bitches, I'm back!
- Naysha, you're getting
a second chance.
- Bitches, I'm back!
So don't fuck it up.
- Okay.
- Bitches, I'm back!
- Now, for this week's
maxi challenge,
- Bitches, I'm back!
you'll be overacting
in a pilot for my new TV series,
- Bitches, I'm back!
"RuCo's Empire."
#DragEmpire
- Bitches, I'm back!
- Whoo!
- [laughs]
- Bitches, I'm back!
- That's right,
RuRu kitty girls.
- Bitches, I'm back!
It's cookie time.
- Whoo!
- [laughs]
- Bitches, I'm back!
- Naomi Smalls,
you won the mini challenge.
- Bitches, I'm back!
So you're a team captain.
And Naysha Lopez,
as a welcome back gift,
- Bitches, I'm back!
you're team captain too.
- I'm not trying to fuck
my second chance,
- Bitches, I'm back!
so let's do this.
- Naomi, you get first pick.
- Bitches, I'm back!
- I choose Robbie Turner.
- All right.
- Bitches, I'm back!
- [laughs]
- Naysha.
- Bitches, I'm back!
- Derrick Barry.
- Yay!
- Bitches, I'm back!
- Bob The Drag Queen.
- Whoo!
- Bitches, I'm back!
- Thorgy.
- Yes!
- Bitches, I'm back!
- Awesome.
- Whoo!
- Bitches, I'm back!
- Chi Chi.
- Whoo.
- Bitches, I'm back!
- Kim Chi.
- Yeah!
- Bitches, I'm back!
- Well, that leaves Acid Betty
and "Santee Alley" Fontaine.
- Bitches, I'm back!
[suspenseful tones]
- I'm gonna go
with "Santee Alley."
- Bitches, I'm back!
- Which means Acid Betty,
you are on Naysha's team.
- Bitches, I'm back!
- Oh, fuck.
Just kidding.
[laughter]
- Bitches, I'm back!
- Gentlemen,
start your engines.
- Bitches, I'm back!
And may
the smartest cookie win.
- Bitches, I'm back!
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
"Ginger Snap,
classic militant activist."
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
She's intense, so you want
to take that role?
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
- Uh...
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
- Derrick's playing
this militant lesbian.
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
Really?
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
- "Chocolate Chip Cookie,
the over-the-top super diva.
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
She's got major attitude
and blingy style."
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
- I will feel comfortable
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
with Chocolate Chip Cookie,
personally.
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
- There's a lot of words
in this.
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
Did you look at the script?
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
- That's right,
Chocolate Chip Cookie's back!
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
- I did not understand at all
what you said.
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
- [high pitched]
And this gonna be my chance
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
to win back Rucious for good!
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
- Why are you talking up here
like that?
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
- Think the other team
should be worried
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
because they have a lot of girls
that are just like...
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
not black.
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
- Coming up...
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
together: Action.
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
- I'm here to get what's mine.
- Bitch!
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
You couldn't even make bail.
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
- I'm a strong gay woman!
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
- Okay.
- [laughs]
- Boom!
[grunting]
- [laughs]
- "You double-crossing bitches."
- For today's challenge,
- [laughs]
we have to perform in scenes
inspired by the show, "Empire."
- [laughs]
It's got drama.
It's got Cookie.
- [laughs]
I mean,
this is a dream come true.
- [laughs]
- "Maybe it was a lil'
somethin'-somethin' extra
- [laughs]
I put in the drink."
[laughs]
- [laughs]
- I've never seen "Empire," but
Cookie sounds like a handful.
- [laughs]
And Bob is a fuckin' handful,
so it's just a match
made in heaven.
- [laughs]
- One thing I would say,
make it, like a
"Or maybe..."
- [laughs]
- Let's do it again.
- 'Cause it got lost.
- [laughs]
- Robbie,
she's a trained actress
- [laughs]
and she's giving us
all these tips.
- [laughs]
- Like, this whole thing,
and then be like,
- [laughs]
"Stand back, bitches!"
[laughter]
- [laughs]
- We're definitely
gonna win this challenge.
- [laughs]
- "What you want?
Oh, hello, Rucious's doctor."
- [laughs]
It's Rucious's doctor.
- This is one stale-ass
Chocolate Chip Cookie.
- [laughs]
Just an observation
that I'm just making,
- [laughs]
Thorgy and Kim Chi switch.
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
- This is gonna be so good.
I really want to do this.
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
"Oh, you better think again,
RuRu kitty.
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
That's right;
Chocolate Chip Cookie is back."
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
- "Did I hear my name?"
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
- It sounded
like Bob was doing...
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
- Of course.
- Yeah.
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
We're gonna be up
against each other.
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
What part did you pick, Bob?
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
- Chocolate Chip Cookie.
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
- Of course
both myself and Bob
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
are playing
Chocolate Chip Cookie parts,
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
and we're gonna be compared.
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
- Rivalry!
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
- Thorgy's hilarious,
but I'm like,
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
"I am not worried about that."
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
"Well, where the hell
is Rucious? Rucious!"
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
- There's a fire under my ass.
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
And I really, really fucking
want to win the challenge.
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
[upbeat music]
♪
- All right.
Team Naysha.
[upbeat music]
- It's time to shoot the scene,
and everyone's feeling
a little nervous.
[upbeat music]
- Welcome to our beautiful set,
furnished by our friends
at Rrivre Works.
[upbeat music]
And say hello to my co-director.
Grammy award-winning
First Lady of hip-hop,
[upbeat music]
Faith Evans is here.
- Hey.
- Hi, ladies.
[upbeat music]
- What's up?
Mm-hmm.
- All right, places,
people, places.
Mm-hmm.
It takes a village, people.
- Jesus, be my savior.
Mm-hmm.
- Here we go, and...
together: Action.
Mm-hmm.
- I'm here to get what's mine.
- No, you're not.
[in deep voice] Yes, she is.
Mm-hmm.
Who are you?
[in deep voice]
Stop interrupting me.
Mm-hmm.
- [chuckles]
- You all need to chill.
Mm-hmm.
The big RuCo White party
is coming up.
Mm-hmm.
- And cut.
Kim Chi,
I need to see more of this.
- And cut.
I need to see this.
- We smack a lot
when we ratchet.
- And cut.
[smacking lips] Girl.
- Mm-hmm.
- And cut.
- [no sound]
Like this.
[clicks tongue]
- And cut.
[all clicking tongues]
- Um...yeah.
Let's try that again.
- Listen, Ho Ho!
[smacks teeth]
- Um...yeah.
- [laughs]
- Chocolate Chip Cookie's
supposed to be in jail!
- Um...yeah.
[clicks tongue]
[laughter]
- Um...yeah.
- That was much better.
And action.
- Um...yeah.
- I'm gonna make you a star.
- Bitch, you couldn't
even make bail.
- Um...yeah.
- Ooh...
- [laughs]
- Um...yeah.
- But I can whoop yo ass.
[both grunting]
- Um...yeah.
[all gasp]
- laughter]
- Um...yeah.
- Nobody wants a bitch who
gets kicked off to come back,
- Um...yeah.
so I was glad to beat
the shit out of her
- Um...yeah.
with this dirty broom.
[laughter]
- Um...yeah.
- The White party is the time
for me to tell the whole world,
- Um...yeah.
it's okay to be gay.
- Cut.
- Um...yeah.
Derrick, I'm losing you
in that moment.
- Um...yeah.
I know--you're not sort of
connecting with anyone.
- Um...yeah.
Just make sure
that you command the room.
- Um...yeah.
- Okay.
The White Party is the time
for me to tell the whole world,
- Um...yeah.
that it's okay--
[cries]
- Um...yeah.
It's okay to be gay.
- What the hell
is Derrick doing?
She's lost in an afro.
- What the hell
is Derrick doing?
She's not funny.
- What the hell
is Derrick doing?
Come on, Britney.
Step it up.
- What the hell
is Derrick doing?
- Team Naomi.
My co-director,
Faith Evans is here.
- Team Naomi.
- Hi, ladies.
- This Notorious B.I.G.'s wife.
- Team Naomi.
- I got my drag name
from Biggie Smalls,
- Team Naomi.
so I'm fucking freaking out.
- Now, she has lived this life,
- Team Naomi.
so if you have
any questions for her
- Team Naomi.
in terms of character
or inspiration...
- Team Naomi.
- What's the best hand
to slap a hoe with,
- Team Naomi.
like, the left or the right?
- Well, I'm left-handed.
[laughter]
- Team Naomi.
- All right, so places,
people, places.
- Team Naomi.
- Action.
- Now where the hell is Rucious?
Rucious!
- Team Naomi.
- Rucious probably smelled you
and went runnin'.
- Team Naomi.
- Well, then why
did I waste my time
- Team Naomi.
puttin' on this.
[cheers and laughter]
- Team Naomi.
Why you all gaggin'?
I bring it to you every episode.
- Team Naomi.
- [laughing]
- Cut.
- Team Naomi.
- You say this is
an over-acting challenge,
- Team Naomi.
I'm like,
[puffs].
- Team Naomi.
You ain't gotta tell me twice.
- Action.
- Team Naomi.
- ♪ Yo, yo, yo,
hallelu, hallelu ♪
- Team Naomi.
♪ My name's Shortbread,
that's my girl, Macaroon ♪
- Team Naomi.
- [laughing]
- And that's why they need
a strong woman on this company.
- Team Naomi.
- Cut.
Miss Cynthia Lee, you just
left out the word "gay,"
- Team Naomi.
when you said this company needs
a strong, gay woman.
- Team Naomi.
Yes, because that's--
that's the joke.
- Team Naomi.
Okay, let's try that again.
- This company need
a gay, strong woman.
Okay, let's try that again.
- Wait, cut.
The line is,
"A strong, gay woman."
Okay, let's try that again.
- I'm a strong, gay woman!
- Cynthia's Ginger Snap
is hilarious
Okay, let's try that again.
for all the wrong reasons.
I don't even know if she knows
what she's saying.
Okay, let's try that again.
- [whistles]
- All right.
Let's move on.
Okay, let's try that again.
- That and how to shoplift.
Empty your pockets,
please, ma'am.
Okay, let's try that again.
Fuck, line.
- Robbie, differentiate
those voices,
Okay, let's try that again.
so that we know
it's two different people.
Okay, let's try that again.
- Do want it, like,
satanic or something?
Okay, let's try that again.
- [clears throat]
- Just make them different.
- Okay.
Okay, let's try that again.
- That and how to shoplift.
[stammering]
Please, sir, empty your--
Okay, let's try that again.
[high pitched] Please ma'am,
will you empty your pocketbook?
Okay, let's try that again.
Ah!
- Robbie is really
screwing it up.
Okay, let's try that again.
You're the one
I was most confident in.
Okay, let's try that again.
- We're gonna have
to work with what we have.
Okay, let's try that again.
- We could end up losing this
because of Robbie's mistakes.
Okay, let's try that again.
- Coming up...
- The girls are gonna do
a runway in roller skates.
- Coming up...
- I've never skated before.
- Really?
- Coming up...
This is a mess
I can't wait to see.
- Coming up...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa whoa.
- Whoa, whoa.
- Coming up...
- [shrieks]
- [laughs]
[upbeat music]
[all screaming happily]
- [laughs]
- For the first time
in drag herstory,
- [laughs]
the girls are gonna do
a runway in roller skates.
- [laughs]
♪
- So anybody nervous
about skating?
- [laughs]
- I've never skated before.
- Really?
- [laughs]
- Ever.
So since I can't skate,
I have this idea,
- [laughs]
like, maybe I can, like,
turn into a car
- [laughs]
to, like, mask it.
- Do you have, like,
wheels for your arms and stuff?
- [laughs]
- Oh, I have to make
my wheels, so.
- [laughs]
- You have to make wheels.
- Yeah.
- [laughs]
- So he plans on falling
and what,
- [laughs]
crawling across the stage
like a Transformer?
- [laughs]
This is a mess
I can't wait to see.
- [laughs]
- How you feelin', Robbie?
- I feel...actually...
better.
- How you feelin', Robbie?
Girl, I'm the disco rockin' diva
of the roller rink.
- How you feelin', Robbie?
And my hope is that
my runway look redeems me
- How you feelin', Robbie?
from that horrible performance
in the acting challenge.
- How you feelin', Robbie?
I'm actually wearing my mom's
vintage sunglasses,
- How you feelin', Robbie?
which I'm really excited about.
- My parents
were straight-up hippies.
- How you feelin', Robbie?
- I would love,
love to meet your parents.
- How you feelin', Robbie?
- My mom, uh, passed away
when I was 19.
- How you feelin', Robbie?
- What happened?
- She had cancer.
- How you feelin', Robbie?
I was in college,
like, having a blast,
- How you feelin', Robbie?
and, like, I would always call
and be like,
- How you feelin', Robbie?
"How's everything?"
It was always fine.
- How you feelin', Robbie?
But it wasn't.
And I finally got a call
from my dad being like,
- How you feelin', Robbie?
"You know, you should probably
really come home."
- How you feelin', Robbie?
When I went home, I mean,
she was not the--
- How you feelin', Robbie?
She was not a person.
She...
- How you feelin', Robbie?
She wasn't there.
I wish they were just a little
bit more honest with me,
- How you feelin', Robbie?
'cause when I got home,
she died that day.
- How you feelin', Robbie?
- Oh, my God.
- She was a skeleton
in a hospital bed.
- How you feelin', Robbie?
I didn't really get a good-bye.
And I kinda feel like
that was taken from me.
- How you feelin', Robbie?
And I'm very angry about it,
but I don't know
where to put that anger.
- How you feelin', Robbie?
It comes out of love for my dad,
he's like,
- How you feelin', Robbie?
"I just don't want to, like,
interrupt your life and ruin--
- How you feelin', Robbie?
Like, I want better things
for you."
- How you feelin', Robbie?
And I'm like, I get that...
- "My parents wanted
to protect me."
- How you feelin', Robbie?
- But things like that, like...
I didn't get to say
good-bye to her.
- How you feelin', Robbie?
She didn't want
to make my dad and my sister
- How you feelin', Robbie?
feel, like, terrible,
but...
- How you feelin', Robbie?
How come they didn't, like,
tell me to come home?
- How you feelin', Robbie?
I will never forget that day.
I guess that's why
I talk about things so much.
I will never forget that day.
- Just get it over with.
That's a great idea.
I will never forget that day.
Keep doing that.
[upbeat music]
I will never forget that day.
["Cover Girl" by RuPaul plays]
♪
I will never forget that day.
- [laughs]
♪
I will never forget that day.
- ♪ Cover girl ♪
- Yeah!
I will never forget that day.
- ♪ Put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe ♪
[laughter]
I will never forget that day.
♪ Let your whole body talk ♪
And what?
I will never forget that day.
- [laughs]
- Yeah!
I will never forget that day.
- Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
I will never forget that day.
Michelle Visage, thanks for
helping me build my empire.
I will never forget that day.
How was prison?
- [laughs]
I will never forget that day.
- Fashion superstar
Carson Kressley,
I will never forget that day.
what's your favorite cookie?
- I like those Samoans.
- It's a Samoa.
I will never forget that day.
- Oh, is it a Samoa?
- Samoan is the person.
I will never forget that day.
[laughter]
- From the hit shows,
"Empire" and "Power,"
I will never forget that day.
my acting class pal,
Tasha Smith is here.
I will never forget that day.
- Hey, baby!
Hey!
I will never forget that day.
- And the legendary Faith Evans.
- Hey, Ru.
I will never forget that day.
- Were you mesmerized
by my girls?
I will never forget that day.
- Oh, my, was I.
- [laughs]
I will never forget that day.
- This week,
we challenged our queens
I will never forget that day.
to act up a storm
in "RuCo's Empire."
I will never forget that day.
Tonight, for the first time
in drag race firstory,
I will never forget that day.
category is
Roller Girl Realness.
I will never forget that day.
Gentlemen,
start your roller skates.
I will never forget that day.
And may the best woman win!
["The Realness"
by RuPaul plays]
I will never forget that day.
- ♪ The realness ♪
- Naysha Lopez.
I will never forget that day.
- Oh, my gosh,
you're giving us Tamar Braxton.
I will never forget that day.
- And Adrienne Bailon.
- Mm-hmm.
I will never forget that day.
- I'm giving you "Xanadu"
realness, boo.
I will never forget that day.
Next thing you know,
I fall.
I will never forget that day.
Oh, my God, if they show me
falling as my runway,
I will never forget that day.
I'm gonna be furious.
- That booty is cute, boo.
I will never forget that day.
- Booty wonderland.
- Bootilicious.
I will never forget that day.
- Thorgy Thor.
- She's giving very
"Three's Company."
I will never forget that day.
- Come and knock on her door.
- [laughs]
I will never forget that day.
- I'm super comfortable
in these roller skates.
I will never forget that day.
This is one of
the first looks I ever did,
I will never forget that day.
like, this is classic Thorgy.
- Hey, good-lookin'.
I will never forget that day.
Be back to pick you up later.
- Call me on the party line.
I will never forget that day.
Is this a three-way?
- Derrick Barry.
Very Skaty Perry.
I will never forget that day.
- [laughs]
- I love my outfit.
I will never forget that day.
I feel like I'm giving them
pop Princess Peach.
I will never forget that day.
It's different from anything
that I've worn before.
I will never forget that day.
- Oh!
- That's a bubble butt
if I ever seen one.
I will never forget that day.
Kim Chi.
- Toucan!
I will never forget that day.
- Look at the size
of that cockatoo.
I will never forget that day.
- The entire ensemble is
inspired by John Galliano.
I will never forget that day.
It's a contrast between nude
and all the colors
that are in a parrot.
I will never forget that day.
- Yes, honey,
you better sissy that macaw.
I will never forget that day.
Acid Betty.
"Beyond Thunderdome."
I will never forget that day.
- Punk unicorn realness.
I am a bitch on wheels
times ten.
I will never forget that day.
I'm reliving my childhood
in the '80s, honey.
I will never forget that day.
Don't turn your back on me.
- Mad Maxi Pad.
I will never forget that day.
- Naomi Smalls.
- Classic beauty.
I will never forget that day.
- She is like a flamingo.
- Yes.
I will never forget that day.
- I'm wearing
a pretty in pink bedroom scene.
I will never forget that day.
My outfit
is so not roller girl,
I will never forget that day.
but I'm pulling it off.
- Michelle, what's the hardest
part of roller skating?
I will never forget that day.
- Mm.
- Telling your mother
that you're gay.
I will never forget that day.
[laughter]
See you later, roller skater.
I will never forget that day.
Bob The Drag Queen.
Not to be confused with
Bob The High School Counselor.
I will never forget that day.
- I didn't have enough time to
finish this Transformer outfit,
I will never forget that day.
so I do my backup plan.
I'm like "Tron,"
robot-inspired character.
I will never forget that day.
- She's a ro--oh, yes girl.
- Uh-oh. Be careful.
I will never forget that day.
- And I'm just like,
try to move
I will never forget that day.
offstage without
breaking a limb.
I will never forget that day.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa whoa.
- Whoa, whoa.
I will never forget that day.
- [shrieks]
- Nice save.
I will never forget that day.
She's like a rumba!
- Don't go too fast now.
Don't go too fast.
I will never forget that day.
- [shrieks]
- Oh, work it!
I will never forget that day.
[laughter and applause]
- Cynthia Lee Fontaine.
I will never forget that day.
- She's a little bit country.
- It's Barbara Mandrell
on wheels.
I will never forget that day.
- I love my runway look.
It's like Farrah Fawcett
I will never forget that day.
meets with Olivia Newton John
in Texas.
I will never forget that day.
I feel like the goddesses
of roller blades.
I will never forget that day.
- If she falls,
there will be a hoe down.
I will never forget that day.
- There will be.
- [laughs]
I will never forget that day.
- Chi Chi DeVayne
from Louisiana.
I will never forget that day.
Yeah, this had
a roller street part.
I will never forget that day.
- Yes!
- She got tricks.
I will never forget that day.
- I'm a disco queen, honey.
Funky, tight roller girl.
This is me.
I will never forget that day.
- She's got that hair
snatched back in a afro puff.
I will never forget that day.
- Ooh, a little
backwards skating.
I will never forget that day.
- Yeah, back rolls.
- [laughs]
I will never forget that day.
- Up next, Robbie Turner.
Oh, lord!
- All right!
I will never forget that day.
- Uh-oh!
- I am roller girl realness
personified.
I will never forget that day.
It's got my initials on my ass
and a little star booty.
I will never forget that day.
And I'm wearing
my Aunt Diana's hair.
I will never forget that day.
I scalped her in, like, 1975.
- It's like a rhinestone
roller girl.
I will never forget that day.
- Yes.
- Mmm.
I will never forget that day.
- Coming up...
- Taraji is going to die.
I will never forget that day.
Lee Daniels is going to die.
- Yes!
[laughs]
I will never forget that day.
- [laughs]
- Welcome, ladies.
I'm really, really impressed.
- [laughs]
[laughter and shouting]
Now it's time
to view your scenes.
- [laughs]
First up, Team Naysha.
[dramatic percussive music]
- [laughs]
- Y'all here today
because yo daddy,
Rucious Charles,
- Y'all here today
the head
of the Rooker Rackers Empire,
- Y'all here today
has a message for all of y'all.
[clicks tongue]
- Y'all here today
- Hey, cookie girls.
[coughing]
- Y'all here today
Aw, damn.
I'm dying.
- Y'all here today
And I gotta figure out
which one of you bitches
- Y'all here today
gon' get my empire.
Will it be my beautiful
Halle Berry wannabe girlfriend,
- Y'all here today
Vanilla Wafer?
[coughs]
- Y'all here today
My brilliant daughter
with multiple degrees
- Y'all here today
and multiple personalities,
Macaroon?
- Y'all here today
My overly sensitive daughter,
who thinks
she's sittin' on a secret,
- Y'all here today
Ginger Snap?
My hood rat baby girl,
- Y'all here today
Shortbread?
Or will it all go
to my sassy ex-wife,
- Y'all here today
Chocolate Chip Cookie?
[coughs violently]
- Y'all here today
- What?
[clicks tongue]
- Y'all here today
But Chocolate Chip Cookie's
supposed to be in jail!
- Y'all here today
[clicks tongue]
- Ooh!
- Y'all here today
You better think again,
RuRu kitty.
- Y'all here today
That's right.
Chocolate Chip Cookie's back!
- Y'all here today
Get off of me.
And I'm here
to take what's mine.
- Y'all here today
Now get this orange shit
off my body.
- Y'all here today
- Ex-squeeze me?
I'm in charge of this company.
- [screams]
- Y'all here today
Oh, bougie bitch,
please!
- Y'all here today
I should be running this empire.
Who asked you?
- Y'all here today
[in deep voice]
I did?
- Y'all here today
[normal voice]
No, I didn't!
- Y'all here today
- Oh, cray-cray.
I got this.
- Y'all here today
♪ Rock-a-ta-ta
ta-ta-ta-ta-ta ♪
- Y'all here today
♪ Rock-a-ta-ta
ta-ta-ta-ta-ta ♪
- Y'all here today
♪ I'ma rap ♪
- My baby's got talent.
- Y'all here today
[grunts]
[RuPaul and Michelle laugh]
- Y'all here today
And that's for not visiting me
in prison, bitch.
- Y'all here today
- Stop!
It's time I get something
off my chest.
- Y'all here today
♪ This is my day
I was born this way ♪
- Y'all here today
♪ And my biggest secret is ♪
♪ I I'm proud to be ♪
- Y'all here today
all: Gay.
We know.
- Y'all here today
- But damn, my little baby's
got a voice.
- Y'all here today
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna make you a star.
- Y'all here today
- Bitch,
you couldn't even post bail.
- Y'all here today
[clicks tongue]
- No...
- Y'all here today
but I can whoop yo ass
with this!
- Y'all here today
- [gasps]
[both grunting]
[gasping]
- Y'all here today
[grunting and groaning]
[dramatic music]
- Y'all here today
This is harder on me
than it is for you guys.
- Y'all here today
No, it's not!
[shouting]
- Y'all here today
- Y'all need to chill!
The big White Record party's
comin' up,
- Y'all here today
and we need to show Rucious
that we are a family.
- Y'all here today
[clicks tongue]
[phone ringing]
- Y'all here today
- Oh, it's Rucious's doctor.
What?
Rucious is dead!
- Y'all here today
[all gasp]
Oh, Rucious wants me
to give him head.
- Y'all here today
[laughs]
Be right there.
- Y'all here today
I will see each
and every one of you bitches
- Y'all here today
at the White party.
♪
[laughter]
- Y'all here today
- Cookie Monster!
[applause]
- Y'all here today
- Next up, Team Naomi.
[dramatic percussive music]
- Y'all here today
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
we're gonna act like a family.
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
- [creepy laughter]
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
I know y'all ain't starting
this white-ass party without me.
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
And why it gotta be white,
you know?
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
[laughs]
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
Uh, where's Rucious?
Rucious!
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
- Rucious probably smelled you
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
and went runnin'.
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
- Oh, well, then
why did I waste my time.
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
putting on this?
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
Oh, there's more.
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
This!
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
Why'd I waste my time
doin' that, bitch?
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
- 'Cause you the crazy ass hoe.
[chuckles]
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
- Where'd you learn
to talk like that?
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
- I learned it from you, bitch.
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
- That's about the only thing
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
you taught us.
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
- Yeah, that,
and how to shoplift.
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
Empty your pockets,
please, ma'am.
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
[high pitched]
I didn't do it!
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
Mama told me to!
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
- Well, well.
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
This is nice,
but let's have a drink.
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
- [stammering and shrieking]
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
In this house,
before we drink,
we say grace.
In this house,
before we drink,
Now can I get
a "Amen, hallelu"?
In this house,
before we drink,
- ♪ Yo, yo, yo,
hallelu, hallelu ♪
In this house,
before we drink,
♪ My name's Shortbread,
that's my girl, Macaroon ♪
In this house,
before we drink,
♪ Eat these cookie now ♪
In this house,
before we drink,
♪ Whatcha want do ♪
In this house,
before we drink,
♪ And drink this milk, bitch ♪
In this house,
before we drink,
♪ You know you want to ♪
In this house,
before we drink,
- All right,
I knew you had it, baby!
In this house,
before we drink,
- Yes!
- I knew you had it.
In this house,
before we drink,
- Stop oppressing me!
In this house,
before we drink,
♪ I am sickening ♪
In this house,
before we drink,
♪ I am gorgeous ♪
In this house,
before we drink,
I'm a strong, gay woman!
In this house,
before we drink,
all: Bitch, we're all gay.
In this house,
before we drink,
- I'm not gay.
In this house,
before we drink,
[in a deep voice]
Yes, you are.
In this house,
before we drink,
[normal voice] That one time
in college doesn't count.
In this house,
before we drink,
- My baby.
In this house,
before we drink,
[grunts]
- Jeez!
In this house,
before we drink,
- Girl, you better step
your medications up.
In this house,
before we drink,
- Wow, you really all are crazy.
In this house,
before we drink,
That's why I'm secretly
plotting to go work
In this house,
before we drink,
for our rival company,
In this house,
before we drink,
Lady Bunny Death Hoe Records.
In this house,
before we drink,
[all gasp]
In this house,
before we drink,
- You fake-ass,
In this house,
before we drink,
Dominique Deveraux wannabe!
In this house,
before we drink,
[screams]
- Oh, my God.
In this house,
before we drink,
- Take it, bitch.
Expensive vodka.
In this house,
before we drink,
- Stand back, bitches.
In this house,
before we drink,
- Bring it, bitch.
In this house,
before we drink,
[stammering and shouting]
[phone ringing]
In this house,
before we drink,
You lucky
my pre-paid phone ringin'.
In this house,
before we drink,
I woulda whooped
your little skinny ass.
In this house,
before we drink,
Who dis?
In this house,
before we drink,
It's Rucious' doctor, y'all.
In this house,
before we drink,
Hello, Rucious's doctor.
In this house,
before we drink,
What, what?
In this house,
before we drink,
Rucious is...
In this house,
before we drink,
severely deadly illnesses
is...contagious?
In this house,
before we drink,
[all screams]
In this house,
before we drink,
- Oh!
In this house,
before we drink,
- Is because I'm gay?
In this house,
before we drink,
Isn't it?
In this house,
before we drink,
- Peace.
- Oh...
I guess whatever Rucious had,
it really was sickening.
- Oh...
[laughs]
Or maybe it was a lil'
extra somethin-somethin
- Oh...
I put in the cocktails.
[maniacal laugh]
- Oh...
Oh, you thirsty, bitch?
[laughs]
- Oh...
Whoo!
I'ma take this motherfucker.
Gimme the shoe, bitch.
- Oh...
[laughs]
Oh!
Look at all this money.
- Oh...
He ain't got
no motherfucking backup.
- Oh...
Is the train still runnin'?
[laughter]
- Oh...
[cheers and applause]
- Wow.
- Oh...
Well, there you have it,
ladies.
- Oh...
And all based on actual events.
- [laughs]
- Oh...
- Ladies, this week
you acted in teams.
- Oh...
but tonight,
you'll be judged individually.
- Oh...
Coming up...
- I don't know what you were
saying, but I didn't care.
Coming up...
- I think you were very
convincing as a schizo.
Coming up...
- Show me that you do have soul.
- [laughs]
Coming up...
- Ladies,
when I call your names,
- [laughs]
please roll forward.
Naomi Smalls.
- [laughs]
Kim Chi.
Naysha Lopez.
- [laughs]
Chi Chi DeVayne.
Ladies, you are safe.
- [laughs]
You may leave the stage.
[upbeat music]
- [laughs]
The rest of you
represent the high rollers
- [laughs]
and the low rollers
of the week.
- [laughs]
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
- [laughs]
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- Your roller girl look--
You're giving me '70s.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
You had the big blonde 'fro.
Not the most wildly inventive.
- Okay.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- Now I'm gonna go
to your performance,
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
which was so good.
Your delivery, your choreography
was meticulously done.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- Yes!
[laughs]
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- I'm so proud of you.
Great job.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- Next up, Derrick Barry.
- I like this whole, like,
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
Jeremy Scott for Katy Perry
kind of thing.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- You are doing a great job
with trying
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
to give us something
other than Brittney.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
But I feel like
you're coming out
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
and these clothes
are wearing you.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- With your performance,
the personality of the character
didn't really connect.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
It was too laid back.
- I'd love to see you show me
that you do have soul.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
So what you need to get to work
on is giving us your soul.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
[chuckles]
- Thank you very much.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
Next up, Acid Betty.
- Your performance,
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
I felt like you gave me
the "Sybil" multiple personality
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
with a little bit
of Carol Burnett goin' on.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- I think you were very
convincing as a schizo.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- This look tonight,
it's getting kinda predictable.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
I'd love to see something
way different.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- Another challenge, Michelle.
- I fucking love challenges.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- Be you but don't be you.
Give us less but more.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
[laughter]
- All right, next up,
Bob The Drag Queen.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- I love this look.
You did this Glamazon girl
from "Tron."
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- Tin Man, I have to say,
needs some lubricant.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- [laughs]
- Now let's get
to the performance.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
Everything about it
was on point.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
That adlibs were
really, really good.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- Taraji is going to die.
Lee Daniels is going to die.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- Next up,
Cynthia Lee Fontaine.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- Cynthia.
You have a great body with
a shirt that's like a formal
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
with a formal necklace
and formal earrings,
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
then you have, like, Hooters
shorts that don't fit at all.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
It's so discombobulated.
- The "Empire" scene, I don't
know what you were saying,
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
but I didn't care.
- There were some nuances
that were missed.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
What did you think,
watching yourself in the scene?
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- I love it.
- [laughs]
- It was really good.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
It was really good.
[laughter]
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- Thank you very much.
All right, next,
Robbie Turner.
- Thank you very much.
- I do love the jumpsuit.
But what's bothering me
is all the silver accoutrements
- Thank you very much.
and then a gold necklace.
I would lose the necklace.
- Thank you very much.
- Um, when we were workin'
on that scene,
- Thank you very much.
Ru was directing you
to kinda get into
the two different voices.
- Thank you very much.
I don't think
you stuck with that.
- Thank you very much.
- It was kinda like I
didn't have a moment to, like,
- Thank you very much.
break
and think of your notes
- Thank you very much.
before we moved on
to another note
- Thank you very much.
and also remember where
the blocking for the camera was
- Thank you very much.
because I can't see very far.
When we originally read it,
I was Vanilla Wafer.
- Thank you very much.
And it--we did change it.
- Did that hurt you, you think?
- Thank you very much.
- I think it did hurt me,
and I didn't speak up
- Thank you very much.
even though I was feeling it,
and so for the betterment
of the team, I was like--
- Thank you very much.
- You can't allow yourself
to be a victim
- Thank you very much.
and use the excuse of,
"I was being nice."
- Thank you very much.
It's a competition.
- Well, thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
- Thank you very much.
While you untuck backstage,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
- Thank you very much.
[car engine starting]
All right, now just
between us squirrel friends,
- Thank you very much.
what do you think?
Thorgy Thor.
- Thank you very much.
- Her Chocolate Chip Cookie
killed it.
- Thank you very much.
- It's safe to say that,
uh, her Chocolate Chip Cookie
- Thank you very much.
was baked in a lovin' oven.
together: Mm-hmm.
- Thank you very much.
- It brings all the boys
to the yard.
- Thank you very much.
- Yeah!
[laughs]
- Thank you very much.
- That's the milkshake.
- Oh.
- [laughs]
- Thank you very much.
- Derrick Barry.
She goes from Britney Spears
to Katy Perry.
- Thank you very much.
I'm still waiting
to find Derrick Barry.
- Thank you very much.
- I thought the runway
was really cute.
- Thank you very much.
- But in the scene,
Ginger Snap got lost to me.
- Thank you very much.
- I've seen her perform
as Britney Spears.
- Thank you very much.
She puts her whole self into it,
and that's what she
needed to do in this challenge.
- Thank you very much.
Acid Betty.
- I think she did look
like a roller warrior,
- Thank you very much.
but I could probably
do without the Mohawk.
- Thank you very much.
- In this role,
she looks like
- Thank you very much.
she's one french fry short
of a Happy Meal straight away.
- Thank you very much.
- Bob The Drag Queen.
- It's not easy to improv,
- Thank you very much.
but also stay focused
on the scene.
- Thank you very much.
I am feelin' her swag.
- She has charisma and it allows
her to sell absolutely anything.
- Thank you very much.
- This Tron jumpsuit
is so basic,
- Thank you very much.
and I found myself goin',
"Oh, my God, I love it so much."
- Thank you very much.
[laughter]
This is great.
- Thank you very much.
- Cynthia Lee Fontaine.
- Bless her cotton socks
with that runway outfit.
- Thank you very much.
- Oh! Oh!
- They were Fruit of the Loom.
- Thank you very much.
- I just felt like she didn't
commit to the role that she had,
- Thank you very much.
as sweet as she is,
but what's sweet
got to do with it?
- Thank you very much.
- All right, Ike Turner.
Yes.
- Thank you very much.
Robbie Turner.
- You had given
a lot of direction,
- Thank you very much.
but Robbie
did not really get it.
- Thank you very much.
- But I love that jumpsuit.
I would wear the hell
out of that jumpsuit.
- Thank you very much.
I love it.
- Silence!
I've made my decision.
- Thank you very much.
Bring back my roller girls.
- [laughs]
- Thank you very much.
- Welcome back, ladies.
- [laughs]
I've made some decisions.
Thorgy Thor.
- [laughs]
You're safe.
Bob The Drag Queen.
- [laughs]
Condragulations, you're the
winner of this week's challenge.
- [laughs]
- Whoo!
- Thank you!
- [laughs]
- You've one $3,500
of innovative eyewear
- [laughs]
from Bradley Kenneth.
- Wow!
- [laughs]
Ah!
Now all the other girls
can see what I can do.
- [laughs]
I feel like everyone knows
I'm a girl to beat.
- [laughs]
- Acid Betty.
You're safe.
- Thank you, Mama.
- [laughs]
- Cynthia Lee Fontaine,
your Ginger Snap was loca,
- [laughs]
but the judges were not crazy
about your roller girl.
- [laughs]
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
- [laughs]
[dramatic percussive tones]
Robbie Turner,
- [laughs]
your Macaroon
was not coconut-y enough.
- [laughs]
Derrick Barry,
your Ginger Snap
did not snap, crackle, or pop.
- [laughs]
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
but you are up for
elimination.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
Derrick Barry,
you are safe, but...
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
you better work, bitch.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
- [chuckles]
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
- Cynthia Lee,
Robbie,
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
now it's your choice.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
Do you want to lip sync
in heels or wheels?
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
- Heels.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
- Wheels.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
- Ooh.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
- Two queens stand before me.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
Prior to tonight,
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
you are asked to prepare
a lip sync performance
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
of "Mesmerized"
by Faith Evans.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
Ladies,
this is your last chance
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
to impress me
and save yourself
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
from elimination.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
[dramatic music]
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
The time has come...
[thunder rumbles]
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
For you to lip sync...
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
for your life.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
[echoes]
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
- I deserve to be here.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
I'm not going.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
- Good luck
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
and don't fuck it up.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
["Mesmerized"
by Faith Evans plays]
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
- ♪ You ever heard
about that thing? ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ I mean that real thing? ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ You don't know ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ What you do to me,
do to me ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ Let me tell you ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ How ya make me feel ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ My heart is on fire since
you put that thang on me ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ Oh-oh ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ You put that thang on me,
baby ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
- I'm the star right now.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
Everybody is mesmerized
about my cuckoo and my dance.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
- ♪ You got so caught up ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ Baby, I'm spellbound ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ I'm floating on cloud nine ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ I can't even sleep ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ Boy, you got me weak ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ My heart is on fire since
you put that thang on me ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
- Am I the first girl
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
that's ever broken a light
on the runway?
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
I'm gonna say yes.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ You don't know ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ What you do to me,
do to me ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ Let me tell you ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ How ya make me feel ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ I can't even sleep ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ Boy, you got me weak ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ My heart is on fire since
you put that thang on me ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
♪ Oh-oh ♪
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
[all scream]
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
- [shouting]
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
[applause]
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
- Ladies,
I've made my decision.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
Robbie Turner...
shantay, you stay.
[clapping]
Robbie Turner...
- Thank you.
- Cynthia Lee Fontaine,
Robbie Turner...
Puerto Rico, Austin,
Santee Alley,
and now the world.
Robbie Turner...
Keep spreading your cuckoo.
Now, sashay away.
Robbie Turner...
- I love you.
Thank you.
Robbie Turner...
[applause]
- Whoo!
Robbie Turner...
- Thank you.
- Love you.
Robbie Turner...
- See you soon, mis amores!
I feel sad,
but, at the same time,
I don't have any regrets.
I feel sad,
but, at the same time,
I would like
to encourage everybody,
I feel sad,
but, at the same time,
don't stop believing.
I feel sad,
but, at the same time,
Even if you are the only one
that believes in yourself.
I feel sad,
but, at the same time,
[speaks Spanish]
I feel sad,
but, at the same time,
This is Cynthia Lee Fontaine,
#MisAmoresCuckoo.
I feel sad,
but, at the same time,
- Condragulations,
my queens.
Now remember,
if you can't love yourself,
- Condragulations,
my queens.
how in the hell you gonna love
somebody else?
- Condragulations,
my queens.
Can I get a Amen up here?
- Condragulations,
my queens.
all: Amen!
- Condragulations,
my queens.
- All right,
now let the music play.
- Condragulations,
my queens.
- ♪ Dance for life ♪
- Condragulations,
my queens.
♪ Die tomorrow,
live tonight ♪
- Condragulations,
my queens.
♪ Die tomorrow,
live tonight ♪
- Condragulations,
my queens.
♪ Die tomorrow,
live tonight ♪
- Condragulations,
my queens.