- Previously on
"RuPaul's Drag Race"...
You'll be competing
in the drag-apella movie,
"Bitch Perfect."
all:  Now sissy that walk
- Chi Chi DeVayne,
condragulations, you are the
winner of this week's challenge.
- Dax ExclamationPoint,
Laila McQueen,
neither one of you survived
that lip sync.
[dramatic music]
Sashay away.
[laid-back music]
- Oh, my God.
- Oh!
- I did not
even see that coming.
- Gag of the century.
- You never know
what's gonna happen,
and when you on the stage,
bitch,
you better own it.
This is a wakeup call
for all of us.
If you ain't stepping
that pussy up,
your ass is going home.
- So who do you guys think
that RuPaul called?
- I had to eliminate
two queens today.
How soon can you get here?
- One queen who needs
to be redeemed
more than any queen
on the "Drag Race"
is Victoria "Pork Chop" Parker.
- Question is
when Shangela returns,
what are we gonna do?
[laughter]
I think we should all agree that
whoever the girl that comes in,
we just ignore her
and treat her like poo.
- Damn.
We have another bitch
coming into the competition?
[dramatic tones]
Girl,
this is some bullshit.
-  RuPaul's Drag Race
- The winner
of "RuPaul's Drag Race"
receives
a one-year supply
of Anastasia
Beverly Hills cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100,000.
With extra-special guest judges
"Empire's" Tasha Smith
and the legendary
Faith Evans!
-  RuPaul's Drag Race
-  May the best woman,
best woman win
[tires screeching]
[upbeat music]
- Work.
[laughter]
- It's a brand-new day!
We've survived.
[siren wails]
- Ooh, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
To be America's
next drag superstar,
you don't need to be humble.
- Agreed.
- But if you trip or stumble,
well, honey, that's just
the way that cookie crumbles.
[chuckles dramatically]
[laughter]
[door squeaking]
- Hello, hello, hello.
[cheers and applause]
- Wow!
- This is the outfit.
- Why, thank you.
It is
a Klein Epstein & Parker suit.
They're made to measure.
- [laughs]
- Now, ladies,
when the Supreme Court
legalized same sex marriage,
they moved this country
boldly forward.
But when it comes
to their sense of style,
the justices are,
like, so 18th century.
- Yeah.
- Oh, Pit Crew!
- Whoo!
- Oh!
- Now for today's
mini challenge,
I want you to drag up
these basic black robes.
Think Judge Judy Couture.
We'll take a 30-minute recess,
and then, the Supreme Court
Fashion Show will be in session.
Go!
- Ah!
[laughter]
[upbeat music]
- Think this looks like
absolute garbage, and I love it.
- Ladies!
Time's up.
Category is,
Supreme Court Realness.
[gavel pounding]
First up,
Bob The Drag Queen.
She received
her law degree online
from the Tyler Perry "I Can
Learn Law All By Myself" school.
Supreme Court Justice
Naomi Smalls
from the law firm
of Evangelista and Fangs.
She almost got disbarred
for excessive mouth pops.
- [pops]
That was only one.
- [popping]
- [laughs]
Justice Derrick Barry.
She was inspired to study law
after sneaking into a matinee
of "Legally Blonde."
Oh!
- Oh, and then my wig come off.
- All rise
for Supreme Court Justice
Cynthia Lee Fontaine,
AKA Cuckoo Freedom.
- [laughs]
- She made herstory
with her landmark verdict
for legalizing sex.
[record scratches]
Really, Judge?
- [laughs]
- I think it was funny.
- Supreme Court Justice
Acid Betty.
She believes
in every citizen's right
to go fisting.
[record scratches]
Uh, it said--
I'm sorry, it's go fishing.
[laughter]
Supreme Court Justice
Robbie Turner.
If Justice Turner
had her way,
she'd outlaw ex-boyfriend
Donald Trump.
- [laughs]
- All rise
for Supreme Court Justice
Kim Chi.
She got her start at the law
firm of Ching Chang & Chong.
I did not write these.
[laughter]
Do not send me letters.
Supreme Court Justice
Thorgy Thor.
She made herstory
legalizing the right
to stop traffic
and tap-dance.
[car horn honks]
[laughter]
All rise
for Supreme Court Justice
Chi Chi DeVayne.
She made herstory
with her landmark verdict
legalizing ass clapping.
- Wha!
[laughter]
- Yes, Your Honor, yes.
If justice is blind,
that bitch is missing out.
[laughter]
The winner is...
[drum roll]
Naomi Smalls.
- Nice!
- Ooh!
- And I'll be posting
all of these supreme looks
at logotv.com.
Ladies, last week,
several eliminations
left a void
that I've decided to fill
with the one and only...
[dramatic music]
- Bitches, I'm back!
[all screaming]
- Naysha Lopez.
- Oh, my God,
it's Naysha!
She's back on the competition.
- Naysha should have walked in
with her luggage
and just kept on walking.
Bye, girl.
- Naysha, you're getting
a second chance.
So don't fuck it up.
- Okay.
- Now, for this week's
maxi challenge,
you'll be overacting
in a pilot for my new TV series,
"RuCo's Empire."
#DragEmpire
- Whoo!
- [laughs]
- That's right,
RuRu kitty girls.
It's cookie time.
- Whoo!
- [laughs]
- Naomi Smalls,
you won the mini challenge.
So you're a team captain.
And Naysha Lopez,
as a welcome back gift,
you're team captain too.
- I'm not trying to fuck
my second chance,
so let's do this.
- Naomi, you get first pick.
- I choose Robbie Turner.
- All right.
- [laughs]
- Naysha.
- Derrick Barry.
- Yay!
- Bob The Drag Queen.
- Whoo!
- Thorgy.
- Yes!
- Awesome.
- Whoo!
- Chi Chi.
- Whoo.
- Kim Chi.
- Yeah!
- Well, that leaves Acid Betty
and "Santee Alley" Fontaine.
[suspenseful tones]
- I'm gonna go
with "Santee Alley."
- Which means Acid Betty,
you are on Naysha's team.
- Oh, fuck.
Just kidding.
[laughter]
- Gentlemen,
start your engines.
And may
the smartest cookie win.
- Okay, so let's go through
all of them real quick.
"Ginger Snap,
classic militant activist."
She's intense, so you want
to take that role?
- Uh...
- Derrick's playing
this militant lesbian.
Really?
- "Chocolate Chip Cookie,
the over-the-top super diva.
She's got major attitude
and blingy style."
- I will feel comfortable
with Chocolate Chip Cookie,
personally.
- There's a lot of words
in this.
Did you look at the script?
- That's right,
Chocolate Chip Cookie's back!
- I did not understand at all
what you said.
- [high pitched]
And this gonna be my chance
to win back Rucious for good!
- Why are you talking up here
like that?
- Think the other team
should be worried
because they have a lot of girls
that are just like...
not black.
- Coming up...
together: Action.
- I'm here to get what's mine.
- Bitch!
You couldn't even make bail.
- I'm a strong gay woman!
- Okay.
- [laughs]
- Boom!
[grunting]
- "You double-crossing bitches."
- For today's challenge,
we have to perform in scenes
inspired by the show, "Empire."
It's got drama.
It's got Cookie.
I mean,
this is a dream come true.
- "Maybe it was a lil'
somethin'-somethin' extra
I put in the drink."
[laughs]
- I've never seen "Empire," but
Cookie sounds like a handful.
And Bob is a fuckin' handful,
so it's just a match
made in heaven.
- One thing I would say,
make it, like a
"Or maybe..."
- Let's do it again.
- 'Cause it got lost.
- Robbie,
she's a trained actress
and she's giving us
all these tips.
- Like, this whole thing,
and then be like,
"Stand back, bitches!"
[laughter]
- We're definitely
gonna win this challenge.
- "What you want?
Oh, hello, Rucious's doctor."
It's Rucious's doctor.
- This is one stale-ass
Chocolate Chip Cookie.
Just an observation
that I'm just making,
Thorgy and Kim Chi switch.
- I would love to.
- Yeah, super diva.
- This is gonna be so good.
I really want to do this.
"Oh, you better think again,
RuRu kitty.
That's right;
Chocolate Chip Cookie is back."
- "Did I hear my name?"
- It sounded
like Bob was doing...
- Of course.
- Yeah.
We're gonna be up
against each other.
What part did you pick, Bob?
- Chocolate Chip Cookie.
- Of course
both myself and Bob
are playing
Chocolate Chip Cookie parts,
and we're gonna be compared.
- Rivalry!
- Thorgy's hilarious,
but I'm like,
"I am not worried about that."
"Well, where the hell
is Rucious? Rucious!"
- There's a fire under my ass.
And I really, really fucking
want to win the challenge.
[upbeat music]
- All right.
Team Naysha.
- It's time to shoot the scene,
and everyone's feeling
a little nervous.
- Welcome to our beautiful set,
furnished by our friends
at Rrivre Works.
And say hello to my co-director.
Grammy award-winning
First Lady of hip-hop,
Faith Evans is here.
- Hey.
- Hi, ladies.
- What's up?
Mm-hmm.
- All right, places,
people, places.
It takes a village, people.
- Jesus, be my savior.
- Here we go, and...
together: Action.
- I'm here to get what's mine.
- No, you're not.
[in deep voice] Yes, she is.
Who are you?
[in deep voice]
Stop interrupting me.
- [chuckles]
- You all need to chill.
The big RuCo White party
is coming up.
- And cut.
Kim Chi,
I need to see more of this.
I need to see this.
- We smack a lot
when we ratchet.
[smacking lips] Girl.
- Mm-hmm.
- [no sound]
Like this.
[clicks tongue]
[all clicking tongues]
- Um...yeah.
Let's try that again.
- Listen, Ho Ho!
[smacks teeth]
- [laughs]
- Chocolate Chip Cookie's
supposed to be in jail!
[clicks tongue]
[laughter]
- That was much better.
And action.
- I'm gonna make you a star.
- Bitch, you couldn't
even make bail.
- Ooh...
- [laughs]
- But I can whoop yo ass.
[both grunting]
[all gasp]
- laughter]
- Nobody wants a bitch who
gets kicked off to come back,
so I was glad to beat
the shit out of her
with this dirty broom.
[laughter]
- The White party is the time
for me to tell the whole world,
it's okay to be gay.
- Cut.
Derrick, I'm losing you
in that moment.
I know--you're not sort of
connecting with anyone.
Just make sure
that you command the room.
- Okay.
The White Party is the time
for me to tell the whole world,
that it's okay--
[cries]
It's okay to be gay.
- What the hell
is Derrick doing?
She's lost in an afro.
She's not funny.
Come on, Britney.
Step it up.
- Team Naomi.
My co-director,
Faith Evans is here.
- Hi, ladies.
- This Notorious B.I.G.'s wife.
- I got my drag name
from Biggie Smalls,
so I'm fucking freaking out.
- Now, she has lived this life,
so if you have
any questions for her
in terms of character
or inspiration...
- What's the best hand
to slap a hoe with,
like, the left or the right?
- Well, I'm left-handed.
[laughter]
- All right, so places,
people, places.
- Action.
- Now where the hell is Rucious?
Rucious!
- Rucious probably smelled you
and went runnin'.
- Well, then why
did I waste my time
puttin' on this.
[cheers and laughter]
Why you all gaggin'?
I bring it to you every episode.
- [laughing]
- Cut.
- You say this is
an over-acting challenge,
I'm like,
[puffs].
You ain't gotta tell me twice.
- Action.
-  Yo, yo, yo,
hallelu, hallelu
My name's Shortbread,
that's my girl, Macaroon
- [laughing]
- And that's why they need
a strong woman on this company.
- Cut.
Miss Cynthia Lee, you just
left out the word "gay,"
when you said this company needs
a strong, gay woman.
Yes, because that's--
that's the joke.
Okay, let's try that again.
- This company need
a gay, strong woman.
- Wait, cut.
The line is,
"A strong, gay woman."
- I'm a strong, gay woman!
- Cynthia's Ginger Snap
is hilarious
for all the wrong reasons.
I don't even know if she knows
what she's saying.
- [whistles]
- All right.
Let's move on.
- That and how to shoplift.
Empty your pockets,
please, ma'am.
Fuck, line.
- Robbie, differentiate
those voices,
so that we know
it's two different people.
- Do want it, like,
satanic or something?
- [clears throat]
- Just make them different.
- Okay.
- That and how to shoplift.
[stammering]
Please, sir, empty your--
[high pitched] Please ma'am,
will you empty your pocketbook?
Ah!
- Robbie is really
screwing it up.
You're the one
I was most confident in.
- We're gonna have
to work with what we have.
- We could end up losing this
because of Robbie's mistakes.
- Coming up...
- The girls are gonna do
a runway in roller skates.
- I've never skated before.
- Really?
This is a mess
I can't wait to see.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa whoa.
- Whoa, whoa.
- [shrieks]
- [laughs]
[upbeat music]
[all screaming happily]
- For the first time
in drag herstory,
the girls are gonna do
a runway in roller skates.
- So anybody nervous
about skating?
- I've never skated before.
- Really?
- Ever.
So since I can't skate,
I have this idea,
like, maybe I can, like,
turn into a car
to, like, mask it.
- Do you have, like,
wheels for your arms and stuff?
- Oh, I have to make
my wheels, so.
- You have to make wheels.
- Yeah.
- So he plans on falling
and what,
crawling across the stage
like a Transformer?
This is a mess
I can't wait to see.
- How you feelin', Robbie?
- I feel...actually...
better.
Girl, I'm the disco rockin' diva
of the roller rink.
And my hope is that
my runway look redeems me
from that horrible performance
in the acting challenge.
I'm actually wearing my mom's
vintage sunglasses,
which I'm really excited about.
- My parents
were straight-up hippies.
- I would love,
love to meet your parents.
- My mom, uh, passed away
when I was 19.
- What happened?
- She had cancer.
I was in college,
like, having a blast,
and, like, I would always call
and be like,
"How's everything?"
It was always fine.
But it wasn't.
And I finally got a call
from my dad being like,
"You know, you should probably
really come home."
When I went home, I mean,
she was not the--
She was not a person.
She...
She wasn't there.
I wish they were just a little
bit more honest with me,
'cause when I got home,
she died that day.
- Oh, my God.
- She was a skeleton
in a hospital bed.
I didn't really get a good-bye.
And I kinda feel like
that was taken from me.
And I'm very angry about it,
but I don't know
where to put that anger.
It comes out of love for my dad,
he's like,
"I just don't want to, like,
interrupt your life and ruin--
Like, I want better things
for you."
And I'm like, I get that...
- "My parents wanted
to protect me."
- But things like that, like...
I didn't get to say
good-bye to her.
She didn't want
to make my dad and my sister
feel, like, terrible,
but...
How come they didn't, like,
tell me to come home?
I will never forget that day.
I guess that's why
I talk about things so much.
- Just get it over with.
That's a great idea.
Keep doing that.
[upbeat music]
["Cover Girl" by RuPaul plays]
- [laughs]
-  Cover girl
- Yeah!
-  Put the bass in your walk
Head to toe
[laughter]
Let your whole body talk
And what?
- [laughs]
- Yeah!
- Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
Michelle Visage, thanks for
helping me build my empire.
How was prison?
- [laughs]
- Fashion superstar
Carson Kressley,
what's your favorite cookie?
- I like those Samoans.
- It's a Samoa.
- Oh, is it a Samoa?
- Samoan is the person.
[laughter]
- From the hit shows,
"Empire" and "Power,"
my acting class pal,
Tasha Smith is here.
- Hey, baby!
Hey!
- And the legendary Faith Evans.
- Hey, Ru.
- Were you mesmerized
by my girls?
- Oh, my, was I.
- [laughs]
- This week,
we challenged our queens
to act up a storm
in "RuCo's Empire."
Tonight, for the first time
in drag race firstory,
category is
Roller Girl Realness.
Gentlemen,
start your roller skates.
And may the best woman win!
["The Realness"
by RuPaul plays]
-  The realness
- Naysha Lopez.
- Oh, my gosh,
you're giving us Tamar Braxton.
- And Adrienne Bailon.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm giving you "Xanadu"
realness, boo.
Next thing you know,
I fall.
Oh, my God, if they show me
falling as my runway,
I'm gonna be furious.
- That booty is cute, boo.
- Booty wonderland.
- Bootilicious.
- Thorgy Thor.
- She's giving very
"Three's Company."
- Come and knock on her door.
- [laughs]
- I'm super comfortable
in these roller skates.
This is one of
the first looks I ever did,
like, this is classic Thorgy.
- Hey, good-lookin'.
Be back to pick you up later.
- Call me on the party line.
Is this a three-way?
- Derrick Barry.
Very Skaty Perry.
- [laughs]
- I love my outfit.
I feel like I'm giving them
pop Princess Peach.
It's different from anything
that I've worn before.
- Oh!
- That's a bubble butt
if I ever seen one.
Kim Chi.
- Toucan!
- Look at the size
of that cockatoo.
- The entire ensemble is
inspired by John Galliano.
It's a contrast between nude
and all the colors
that are in a parrot.
- Yes, honey,
you better sissy that macaw.
Acid Betty.
"Beyond Thunderdome."
- Punk unicorn realness.
I am a bitch on wheels
times ten.
I'm reliving my childhood
in the '80s, honey.
Don't turn your back on me.
- Mad Maxi Pad.
- Naomi Smalls.
- Classic beauty.
- She is like a flamingo.
- Yes.
- I'm wearing
a pretty in pink bedroom scene.
My outfit
is so not roller girl,
but I'm pulling it off.
- Michelle, what's the hardest
part of roller skating?
- Mm.
- Telling your mother
that you're gay.
[laughter]
See you later, roller skater.
Bob The Drag Queen.
Not to be confused with
Bob The High School Counselor.
- I didn't have enough time to
finish this Transformer outfit,
so I do my backup plan.
I'm like "Tron,"
robot-inspired character.
- She's a ro--oh, yes girl.
- Uh-oh. Be careful.
- And I'm just like,
try to move
offstage without
breaking a limb.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa whoa.
- Whoa, whoa.
- [shrieks]
- Nice save.
She's like a rumba!
- Don't go too fast now.
Don't go too fast.
- [shrieks]
- Oh, work it!
[laughter and applause]
- Cynthia Lee Fontaine.
- She's a little bit country.
- It's Barbara Mandrell
on wheels.
- I love my runway look.
It's like Farrah Fawcett
meets with Olivia Newton John
in Texas.
I feel like the goddesses
of roller blades.
- If she falls,
there will be a hoe down.
- There will be.
- [laughs]
- Chi Chi DeVayne
from Louisiana.
Yeah, this had
a roller street part.
- Yes!
- She got tricks.
- I'm a disco queen, honey.
Funky, tight roller girl.
This is me.
- She's got that hair
snatched back in a afro puff.
- Ooh, a little
backwards skating.
- Yeah, back rolls.
- [laughs]
- Up next, Robbie Turner.
Oh, lord!
- All right!
- Uh-oh!
- I am roller girl realness
personified.
It's got my initials on my ass
and a little star booty.
And I'm wearing
my Aunt Diana's hair.
I scalped her in, like, 1975.
- It's like a rhinestone
roller girl.
- Yes.
- Mmm.
- Coming up...
- Taraji is going to die.
Lee Daniels is going to die.
- Yes!
[laughs]
- [laughs]
- Welcome, ladies.
I'm really, really impressed.
[laughter and shouting]
Now it's time
to view your scenes.
First up, Team Naysha.
[dramatic percussive music]
- Y'all here today
because yo daddy,
Rucious Charles,
the head
of the Rooker Rackers Empire,
has a message for all of y'all.
[clicks tongue]
- Hey, cookie girls.
[coughing]
Aw, damn.
I'm dying.
And I gotta figure out
which one of you bitches
gon' get my empire.
Will it be my beautiful
Halle Berry wannabe girlfriend,
Vanilla Wafer?
[coughs]
My brilliant daughter
with multiple degrees
and multiple personalities,
Macaroon?
My overly sensitive daughter,
who thinks
she's sittin' on a secret,
Ginger Snap?
My hood rat baby girl,
Shortbread?
Or will it all go
to my sassy ex-wife,
Chocolate Chip Cookie?
[coughs violently]
- What?
[clicks tongue]
But Chocolate Chip Cookie's
supposed to be in jail!
[clicks tongue]
- Ooh!
You better think again,
RuRu kitty.
That's right.
Chocolate Chip Cookie's back!
Get off of me.
And I'm here
to take what's mine.
Now get this orange shit
off my body.
- Ex-squeeze me?
I'm in charge of this company.
- [screams]
Oh, bougie bitch,
please!
I should be running this empire.
Who asked you?
[in deep voice]
I did?
[normal voice]
No, I didn't!
- Oh, cray-cray.
I got this.
Rock-a-ta-ta
ta-ta-ta-ta-ta
I'ma rap
- My baby's got talent.
[grunts]
[RuPaul and Michelle laugh]
And that's for not visiting me
in prison, bitch.
- Stop!
It's time I get something
off my chest.
This is my day
I was born this way
And my biggest secret is
I I'm proud to be
all: Gay.
We know.
- But damn, my little baby's
got a voice.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna make you a star.
- Bitch,
you couldn't even post bail.
[clicks tongue]
- No...
but I can whoop yo ass
with this!
- [gasps]
[both grunting]
[gasping]
[grunting and groaning]
[dramatic music]
This is harder on me
than it is for you guys.
No, it's not!
[shouting]
- Y'all need to chill!
The big White Record party's
comin' up,
and we need to show Rucious
that we are a family.
[clicks tongue]
[phone ringing]
- Oh, it's Rucious's doctor.
What?
Rucious is dead!
[all gasp]
Oh, Rucious wants me
to give him head.
[laughs]
Be right there.
I will see each
and every one of you bitches
at the White party.
[laughter]
- Cookie Monster!
[applause]
- Next up, Team Naomi.
[dramatic percussive music]
- Girls, at this
damn White party,
we're gonna act like a family.
- [creepy laughter]
I know y'all ain't starting
this white-ass party without me.
And why it gotta be white,
you know?
[laughs]
Uh, where's Rucious?
Rucious!
- Rucious probably smelled you
and went runnin'.
- Oh, well, then
why did I waste my time.
putting on this?
Oh, there's more.
This!
Why'd I waste my time
doin' that, bitch?
- 'Cause you the crazy ass hoe.
[chuckles]
- Where'd you learn
to talk like that?
- I learned it from you, bitch.
- That's about the only thing
you taught us.
- Yeah, that,
and how to shoplift.
Empty your pockets,
please, ma'am.
[high pitched]
I didn't do it!
Mama told me to!
- Well, well.
This is nice,
but let's have a drink.
- [stammering and shrieking]
In this house,
before we drink,
we say grace.
Now can I get
a "Amen, hallelu"?
-  Yo, yo, yo,
hallelu, hallelu
My name's Shortbread,
that's my girl, Macaroon
Eat these cookie now
Whatcha want do
And drink this milk, bitch
You know you want to
- All right,
I knew you had it, baby!
- Yes!
- I knew you had it.
- Stop oppressing me!
I am sickening
I am gorgeous
I'm a strong, gay woman!
all: Bitch, we're all gay.
- I'm not gay.
[in a deep voice]
Yes, you are.
[normal voice] That one time
in college doesn't count.
- My baby.
[grunts]
- Jeez!
- Girl, you better step
your medications up.
- Wow, you really all are crazy.
That's why I'm secretly
plotting to go work
for our rival company,
Lady Bunny Death Hoe Records.
[all gasp]
- You fake-ass,
Dominique Deveraux wannabe!
[screams]
- Oh, my God.
- Take it, bitch.
Expensive vodka.
- Stand back, bitches.
- Bring it, bitch.
[stammering and shouting]
[phone ringing]
You lucky
my pre-paid phone ringin'.
I woulda whooped
your little skinny ass.
Who dis?
It's Rucious' doctor, y'all.
Hello, Rucious's doctor.
What, what?
Rucious is...
severely deadly illnesses
is...contagious?
[all screams]
- Oh!
- Is because I'm gay?
Isn't it?
- Peace.
- Oh...
I guess whatever Rucious had,
it really was sickening.
[laughs]
Or maybe it was a lil'
extra somethin-somethin
I put in the cocktails.
[maniacal laugh]
Oh, you thirsty, bitch?
[laughs]
Whoo!
I'ma take this motherfucker.
Gimme the shoe, bitch.
[laughs]
Oh!
Look at all this money.
He ain't got
no motherfucking backup.
Is the train still runnin'?
[laughter]
[cheers and applause]
- Wow.
Well, there you have it,
ladies.
And all based on actual events.
- [laughs]
- Ladies, this week
you acted in teams.
but tonight,
you'll be judged individually.
Coming up...
- I don't know what you were
saying, but I didn't care.
- I think you were very
convincing as a schizo.
- Show me that you do have soul.
- [laughs]
- Ladies,
when I call your names,
please roll forward.
Naomi Smalls.
Kim Chi.
Naysha Lopez.
Chi Chi DeVayne.
Ladies, you are safe.
You may leave the stage.
[upbeat music]
The rest of you
represent the high rollers
and the low rollers
of the week.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
Starting with Thorgy Thor.
- Your roller girl look--
You're giving me '70s.
You had the big blonde 'fro.
Not the most wildly inventive.
- Okay.
- Now I'm gonna go
to your performance,
which was so good.
Your delivery, your choreography
was meticulously done.
- Yes!
[laughs]
- I'm so proud of you.
Great job.
- Next up, Derrick Barry.
- I like this whole, like,
Jeremy Scott for Katy Perry
kind of thing.
- You are doing a great job
with trying
to give us something
other than Brittney.
But I feel like
you're coming out
and these clothes
are wearing you.
- With your performance,
the personality of the character
didn't really connect.
It was too laid back.
- I'd love to see you show me
that you do have soul.
So what you need to get to work
on is giving us your soul.
[chuckles]
- Thank you very much.
Next up, Acid Betty.
- Your performance,
I felt like you gave me
the "Sybil" multiple personality
with a little bit
of Carol Burnett goin' on.
- I think you were very
convincing as a schizo.
- This look tonight,
it's getting kinda predictable.
I'd love to see something
way different.
- Another challenge, Michelle.
- I fucking love challenges.
- Be you but don't be you.
Give us less but more.
[laughter]
- All right, next up,
Bob The Drag Queen.
- I love this look.
You did this Glamazon girl
from "Tron."
- Tin Man, I have to say,
needs some lubricant.
- [laughs]
- Now let's get
to the performance.
Everything about it
was on point.
That adlibs were
really, really good.
- Taraji is going to die.
Lee Daniels is going to die.
- Next up,
Cynthia Lee Fontaine.
- Cynthia.
You have a great body with
a shirt that's like a formal
with a formal necklace
and formal earrings,
then you have, like, Hooters
shorts that don't fit at all.
It's so discombobulated.
- The "Empire" scene, I don't
know what you were saying,
but I didn't care.
- There were some nuances
that were missed.
What did you think,
watching yourself in the scene?
- I love it.
- [laughs]
- It was really good.
It was really good.
[laughter]
- Thank you very much.
All right, next,
Robbie Turner.
- I do love the jumpsuit.
But what's bothering me
is all the silver accoutrements
and then a gold necklace.
I would lose the necklace.
- Um, when we were workin'
on that scene,
Ru was directing you
to kinda get into
the two different voices.
I don't think
you stuck with that.
- It was kinda like I
didn't have a moment to, like,
break
and think of your notes
before we moved on
to another note
and also remember where
the blocking for the camera was
because I can't see very far.
When we originally read it,
I was Vanilla Wafer.
And it--we did change it.
- Did that hurt you, you think?
- I think it did hurt me,
and I didn't speak up
even though I was feeling it,
and so for the betterment
of the team, I was like--
- You can't allow yourself
to be a victim
and use the excuse of,
"I was being nice."
It's a competition.
- Well, thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
While you untuck backstage,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
[car engine starting]
All right, now just
between us squirrel friends,
what do you think?
Thorgy Thor.
- Her Chocolate Chip Cookie
killed it.
- It's safe to say that,
uh, her Chocolate Chip Cookie
was baked in a lovin' oven.
together: Mm-hmm.
- It brings all the boys
to the yard.
- Yeah!
[laughs]
- That's the milkshake.
- Oh.
- [laughs]
- Derrick Barry.
She goes from Britney Spears
to Katy Perry.
I'm still waiting
to find Derrick Barry.
- I thought the runway
was really cute.
- But in the scene,
Ginger Snap got lost to me.
- I've seen her perform
as Britney Spears.
She puts her whole self into it,
and that's what she
needed to do in this challenge.
Acid Betty.
- I think she did look
like a roller warrior,
but I could probably
do without the Mohawk.
- In this role,
she looks like
she's one french fry short
of a Happy Meal straight away.
- Bob The Drag Queen.
- It's not easy to improv,
but also stay focused
on the scene.
I am feelin' her swag.
- She has charisma and it allows
her to sell absolutely anything.
- This Tron jumpsuit
is so basic,
and I found myself goin',
"Oh, my God, I love it so much."
[laughter]
This is great.
- Cynthia Lee Fontaine.
- Bless her cotton socks
with that runway outfit.
- Oh! Oh!
- They were Fruit of the Loom.
- I just felt like she didn't
commit to the role that she had,
as sweet as she is,
but what's sweet
got to do with it?
- All right, Ike Turner.
Yes.
Robbie Turner.
- You had given
a lot of direction,
but Robbie
did not really get it.
- But I love that jumpsuit.
I would wear the hell
out of that jumpsuit.
I love it.
- Silence!
I've made my decision.
Bring back my roller girls.
- [laughs]
- Welcome back, ladies.
I've made some decisions.
Thorgy Thor.
You're safe.
Bob The Drag Queen.
Condragulations, you're the
winner of this week's challenge.
- Whoo!
- Thank you!
- You've one $3,500
of innovative eyewear
from Bradley Kenneth.
- Wow!
Ah!
Now all the other girls
can see what I can do.
I feel like everyone knows
I'm a girl to beat.
- Acid Betty.
You're safe.
- Thank you, Mama.
- Cynthia Lee Fontaine,
your Ginger Snap was loca,
but the judges were not crazy
about your roller girl.
I'm sorry, my dear, but you are
up for elimination.
[dramatic percussive tones]
Robbie Turner,
your Macaroon
was not coconut-y enough.
Derrick Barry,
your Ginger Snap
did not snap, crackle, or pop.
Robbie Turner, I'm sorry,
my dear,
but you are up for
elimination.
Derrick Barry,
you are safe, but...
you better work, bitch.
- [chuckles]
- Cynthia Lee,
Robbie,
now it's your choice.
Do you want to lip sync
in heels or wheels?
- Heels.
- Wheels.
- Ooh.
- Two queens stand before me.
Prior to tonight,
you are asked to prepare
a lip sync performance
of "Mesmerized"
by Faith Evans.
Ladies,
this is your last chance
to impress me
and save yourself
from elimination.
[dramatic music]
The time has come...
[thunder rumbles]
For you to lip sync...
for your life.
[echoes]
- I deserve to be here.
I'm not going.
- Good luck
and don't fuck it up.
["Mesmerized"
by Faith Evans plays]
-  You ever heard
about that thing?
I mean that real thing?
You don't know
What you do to me,
do to me
Let me tell you
How ya make me feel
My heart is on fire since
you put that thang on me
Oh-oh
You put that thang on me,
baby
- I'm the star right now.
Everybody is mesmerized
about my cuckoo and my dance.
-  You got so caught up
Baby, I'm spellbound
I'm floating on cloud nine
I can't even sleep
Boy, you got me weak
My heart is on fire since
you put that thang on me
- Am I the first girl
that's ever broken a light
on the runway?
I'm gonna say yes.
You don't know
What you do to me,
do to me
Let me tell you
How ya make me feel
I can't even sleep
Boy, you got me weak
My heart is on fire since
you put that thang on me
Oh-oh
[all scream]
- [shouting]
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
[applause]
- Ladies,
I've made my decision.
Robbie Turner...
shantay, you stay.
[clapping]
- Thank you.
- Cynthia Lee Fontaine,
Puerto Rico, Austin,
Santee Alley,
and now the world.
Keep spreading your cuckoo.
Now, sashay away.
- I love you.
Thank you.
[applause]
- Whoo!
- Thank you.
- Love you.
- See you soon, mis amores!
I feel sad,
but, at the same time,
I don't have any regrets.
I would like
to encourage everybody,
don't stop believing.
Even if you are the only one
that believes in yourself.
[speaks Spanish]
This is Cynthia Lee Fontaine,
#MisAmoresCuckoo.
- Condragulations,
my queens.
Now remember,
if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna love
somebody else?
Can I get a Amen up here?
all: Amen!
- All right,
now let the music play.
-  Dance for life
Die tomorrow,
live tonight