Previously
on RuPaul's Drag Race...
For the first time
inDrag Race herstory,
we're kicking off the season
with six lip syncs
for your lives.
Bitch, excuse me?
Kandy Muse, LaLa Ri,
Symone, Gottmik,
Olivia Lux, Tina Burner,
shantay you stay.
Aah!
Joey Jay, Denali,
Tamisha Iman, Utica, Rosé,
Kahmora Hall, and Elliott,
that means you're
getting the porkchop.
Here we all are
in the porkchop lounge,
who famously went home first.
Is that what's gonna happen
to all of us?
Attention, Queens.
You all have a chance
to return to the competition.
But first, you must give one
of your fellow queens the chop.
Let the voting begin.
Wait, for real-real?
How do... what?
This is fucked.
This is...
crazy.
We all have a chance to stay,
but we have to vote
one of the girls in the room
out the competition.
That becomes overwhelming.
What are we going to do?
I don't wanna vote anyone off.
I don't know any of you yet.
We literally just met.
None of us saw
each other's lip syncs.
I don't know how to pick.
I mean, the only thing
we know about each other
is our first impression.
We have to vote someone off.
This is a competition.
This is what we signed up for.
All right, bitches,
shit about to go down.
Each individual girl
has to walk up to the box,
select the lipstick with
one of the girls' names on it,
and drop it in the box.
If we're going off
of first impressions,
I don't know you, sis,
but where's the look?
I don't see wow factor.
I hate to be the shallow bitch,
but I'm just not a fan
of chicken feathers.
Kahmora and myself, we're
both in ostrich feathers,
and she's in
the lower-quality feathers.
So sorry, girl, gotta go.
Eenie-meenie-minie-mo,
Utica, you gotta go.
It sucks to have to vote.
I don't wanna crush
somebody's dream,
and I definitely do not
want my dream to be crushed.
I'm scared that
I could be voted out.
Attention, queens
in the porkchop loading dock.
The votes are in!
We have a tie...
Between Elliott with 2 Ts
and Utica.
Let the tie-breaker
voting round begin.
Oh, no.
We have to do a tie-breaker.
This time, we can only vote
between Utica and Elliott.
I'm trying to fight
for this crown,
and I feel like my dream
is slowly fading away.
As each queen goes up
and chooses again,
my heart just drops
lower and lower
as the queens pick theirs.
I'm just dreading the worst.
The votes are in!
The queen that's getting
the first chop is...
Elliott with 2 Ts.
All righty, then.
Pblblblbl.
It's been a lovely 15 minutes
with all of you.
I'm disappointed
that it ended like this,
because I got sent home
for something
that I didn't have any say in
or any power over,
and that sucks.
And I feel like
I've let my fiancé down,
and I'm 100% heartbroken.
Oh, my God.
Unfortunately, we had
to vote somebody out,
and it was Elliott.
And while that's sad,
it's also a joyous occasion,
because the less people here,
the closer I am to the crown.
The winner ofRuPaul's Drag Race
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics
and a cash prize of $100,000.
With extra-special
guest judge Jamal Sims.
♪ RuPaul's Drag Race ♪
♪ May the best woman ♪
♪ Best woman win ♪
Aah!
Come on, winner's circle!
- All right!
- Okay?
It's a new day.
Last week was crazy.
The twists and turns.
I still don't even know
what's going on.
But I'm just happy to be here.
You guys, this is our,
like, first, kind of, day.
- Day. It's official.
- It's official.
After all that craziness,
bitch, well...
Hello, winner's circle.
- Hello!
- Hey!
Hello, winners.
There's high expectations
now for us,
now that we won this lip sync.
Yeah. Tea.
I wonder if we're gonna
get to meet the other girls.
We already sent them home.
That's it.
And if they're saved,
we went through that
on our first day,
- that's shady.
- I know, and if they're back,
they're gonna have
a vengeance, mama.
If for whatever reason
they happen to come back,
it's us against them,
because it's top six,
the winner's circle, and
they can't take that from us.
- That's it.
- I wanna see some bitches fight.
You gotta go.
I'm ready for you to fight,
bitch.
Not me!
Okay, all from Brooklyn.
Bitches already think
I'm causing trouble,
and I'm just here
to be a good girl.
- You are causing trouble, Kandy!
- Oh, girl.
Kandy, you walk in the room
and cause trouble.
You Captain Trouble, honey.
In New York, Kandy is known
to be like cunty and bitchy,
and, like, trying
to literally cause drama.
It's just not my tea, sis.
We'll see. We shall see, ladies.
Ooh, girl.
She done already
done had herses.
Woman's calling us.
My queens, con-drag-ulations.
I wanna thank you
for a job well done.
But now is the time to guard
your charisma, uniqueness,
nerve, and talent
from the fickle finger of fate.
I don't think I know
those words.
What the hell
does that shit mean?
Hello, hello, hello!
You better come on in this suit.
Racers, welcome
to RuPaul's Drag Race.
How do you like
the season so far?
Crazy.
Well, this week,
you can all take a deep breath
and just relax.
Oh, who am I kidding?
That's never gonna happen.
Now, before we get
to know you officially,
I wanna introduce you
to a fabulous queen
who'll be joining you
in the competition.
Uh-uh.
That's right,
someone I don't think
got a fair chance last week.
And I think she'll fit in
with this group just right.
Hello!
- Oh!
Guess who's back
in the house? Yeah.
This little angel twink
walks in.
I have no idea who it is,
but I'm gagged.
Elliott with 2 Ts.
I thought I sent you home.
We told you this season
would be full of surprises.
What the hell?
Why do you get to come back
into the competition
if you weren't one of the girls
that won their lip sync
during the first week?
What the fuck?
I sent that bitch packing.
What's going on?
Why is she back?
And what did she do
to get back here?
You smell that? It's distrust.
Hey, Elliott.
Hello.
You went through it last week,
but you are back
to prove once again
that losing is the new winning.
#DragRace.
Now, I want you all
to really hear this.
No queen is a loser
on RuPaul's Drag Race.
Victoria "Porkchop" Parker
was the very first queen
to ever be eliminated
on RuPaul's Drag Race
13 years ago.
And today,
she is a living legend.
Just ask anyone
at the Golden Corral.
Now, Shangela and Vanjie
were the first eliminated
from their seasons,
only to return and reach new
heights of international fame.
That's the tea.
Racers, you signed up
for a competition.
Queens will be eliminated.
But the moral
of this fairy tale is simple.
No matter what happens here,
out there, or online,
don't let anyone
make you feel like a loser.
Amen.
You know why?
Because you're a winner, baby.
Aah!
So let's get started.
All right.
Time to test
your fashion skills.
For your first mini-challenge,
you need to stomp the runway
in two devastating looks.
First, a ladylike daytime look,
and second,
a vampy nighttime look
that says, "I'm a whore."
Can you pull that off?
Every day.
Okay, Glamazons,
I'll see you on the runway.
Let's go.
Oh, yeah!
You bitch! You're a linebacker.
Our first mini-challenge
is a sickening runway show.
My soul has completely
returned to my body.
I'm ready to compete.
Girl, I get to
pull out my looks.
I get to model. Let's do it!
Cue the music, let's go!
Oh! Oh, my God, I'm living
my mirror fantasy!
I've always dreamt
about getting ready
in these werkroom mirrors.
It's making me so excited.
I totally feel like the real
competition is about to start.
Start your engines, bitch.
Ooh, the melanin girls
on this side.
- Oh, yes!
- Hello!
Brown girl power.
So how y'all feeling
about having a new bitch
in the competition?
The new girl?
I'm a little baffled,
because I liked the top six
from the beginning.
I thought it was
a cute moment, too,
but we should have known.
Bitch, what are you here to do?
Are you spying on us?
Bitch, RuPaul's set the bar.
She thinks she's slick.
But I already caught on
to her game.
Tina, how you feeling,
because you sent
Miss Elliott home, correct?
Well, we obviously know that
you can send somebody home,
and here they are.
All right.
- You never know!
- You never know.
I do not trust Elliott.
Elliott the spy, honey.
Well, keep your friends close,
keep your enemies closer.
Guess who I painted next to?
Elliott.
Isn't it so crazy to think,
like, you're a Ru girl?
- Ru girl, right, bitch?
- You're a Ru girl!
Kandy Muse, you've been
saying you're a Ru girl
for the last six years,
so I don't wanna hear it.
People called me
an adjacent Ru girl before this,
but that's because
a lot of my drag family
has been on Drag Racebefore.
Aja's my drag mother
and Dahlia's my drag sister,
so I walk into things
thinking I'm already famous.
So I may not be a Ru girl
before this,
but I'm gonna walk in there
like I am a Ru girl.
You gonna think I'm a Ru girl.
But I have a question.
It's something that I've noticed
a lot in the past seasons.
When girls come in
and they instantly say,
"Oh, my mom was on this season,"
whatever, this season,
they usually go home early.
- Oh?
Do you think
that's gonna affect you?
- No.
- No?
First of all, bitch,
who is talking to you?
Second of all, girl,
I don't even know you.
You done just walked
into the werkroom, okay?
Because, like, Vanjie came in
and was, like,
"I'm Alexis Mateo's daughter,"
went home.
Dahlia, "I'm Aja's daughter,"
Like, it's weird.
It's interesting to me.
You better break the mold, sis.
Elliott walks in here
first time de-dragging
just snapping like that,
like, I think she is here
to serve possible bitch.
"Aren't you worried that
your sister went home first
and you could go home first?"
You might wanna come down
with that, Elliott with 2 Ts.
There ain't no girl I would
just, like, come for her
if I don't know her.
Ooh.
Uh-huh.
I know it, because
he was getting to you.
- I felt it.
- Mm-hmm.
Girl, you just walked in here.
I don't know if
Miss Elliott with 2 Ts
wants to prove to the other
girls that she's a big, bad wolf
because she just
walked into this competition,
but I'm gonna do
what I'm gonna do,
and that's focus on me.
Because the pressure's
definitely on,
because my sister Dahlia
went home first on Season 12,
and I don't wanna
repeat history.
So, no, ma'am.
Coming up...
Category is Nighttime
Is The Right Time.
The bitch has arrived
at the party, honey.
Bitch!
I know you did not just trip.
What in the hell?
Category is Daytime Drama, Mama.
Fashion!
First up, Gottmik.
She's your weather girl,
and has she got news for you.
My daytime look
represents my drag style,
because it's
a fitted latex number,
oversized shoulders,
structured hair,
but with a girlie twist.
O-M-G, we match, we're rainbros.
It's cutesy, and I feel
like a little princess
in the middle of the day.
I'm normally intense
with my looks,
and I usually paint my face
clown white.
So, hello, showing them
range already.
A 100% chance of gorgeous.
I'm gonna say everything
like Don Adams.
Would you believe
100% chance of gorgeous?
Kandy Muse. Rock me, Mama-deus.
Mama-deus? Mama-deus?
I am excited to walk the runway,
because this is what I do.
Baby, I've been modeling in
the fucking streets of New York
my entire life.
Bitch, I might pretend
I'm walking down
a fashion show in Paris.
I'm just like...
even though I'm in the hood.
But it's fine,
it's cool, I love it.
This looks isn't necessarily
a classic Kandy look,
but I'm trying
to show the judges
that a big girl
can be fashion-forward.
So I'm gonna give you couture.
The Red Queen.
Off with her head!
Do-re-mi, LaLa Ri.
Ooh, the braid of it all.
She's part of the braidy bunch.
Okay.
Miss LaLa Ri is giving you
very Southern belle tease.
I'm in the field
with a glass of lemonade.
You know, she got her braids
cocked to the side,
and she swish it back
for the boys to see.
You know, hey, how you doing?
I'm walking down the runway,
living my best life,
and then boom, bitch,
I trip over all
this extra-ass fabric.
I'm like, bitch!
I know you did not just trip
on these good people's runway.
But don't fall, ho.
Do not fall. And I did not fall.
She going back
to the secret garden.
- Okay.
- Put the petal to the metal.
Olivia Lux.
She looks at life
through lilac-colored glasses.
I prefer Rose Nylund glasses.
This daytime drag
is flirty fashion.
She's walking down Fifth
Avenue without a care in the world,
and she has
her weekend bag in hand.
Everything she needs
for the weekend.
You know, you can tell
a lot about a queen
by the size of her purse.
When I walk,
the ponytail's going, like...
I'm living
this lavender fantasy.
Olivia Lux.
She has no Lux left to give.
Ladies and gentlemen, Symone.
The circus is in town,
and she's the big top.
Well, that makes one of us.
There's gotta be at least one.
My look,
inspired by the nineties,
with player's club hair.
My shoulders out,
a little peek-a-boo,
and then you turn around
and boom,
there's a cape
in the back, honey.
A little bit of old meets new,
which is very Symone.
Giving you everything.
Symone Pointer,
the last Pointer Sister.
Tina Burner.
She got my kettle boiling.
In my daytime look,
I'm living
my Carrie Bradshaw fantasy
in, like, a tutu,
but, like, fitted Dior top.
I got a big-ass bow.
People are gonna bow down,
honey.
Bow, bow.
Is that spelled the same?
Oh, my God, it is!
Bow down to my bow.
I gotta get me a Burner phone.
I do, yeah.
Tina Burner phone.
Elliott with 2 Ts.
I wonder if she got
that raspberry beret
at a second-hand store?
I do know she came in
through the out door.
Getting to do two runway looks
is so exciting,
because I get to show
why I was given
a second chance to be here.
And girl, I'm so ready.
And fancy was her name.
Category is Nighttime
Is The Right Time.
I told you twice the first time.
First up, Gottmik.
Now, is it me, or does she
look a little pasty?
This look, oh,
she's gonna steal your soul.
She is a spooky-ductress,
and, girl, my titty's out.
Ever since I got my top surgery,
I love having my chest out,
let me tell you that.
I am living for it,
and I never want
this feeling to go away.
Must get moose and squirrel.
Natasha.
Kandy Muse.
What in the hell?
This look definitely represents
a little more Kandy Muse,
because I love latex,
I love being sexy,
I love showing body,
I love showing curves.
It's just everything, bitch.
I'm everything.
She gets her kicks on Route 666.
The hole.
Is that for a tail, you think?
Not today, Satan.
Do-re-mi for LaLa Ri.
Salt-n-Peplum.
Yes.
Baby, that look,
I'm not over-over-the-top
drag girl.
But whatever I give you,
I'm going to sell it.
They say give you whore,
I'm gonna give you whore.
Ass out, titties out, pleather.
Not leather, 'cause
a bitch can't afford it.
But, bitch, I'm still serving it
like it's leather, girl.
I live for this look.
Honey, be the chain
you wanna see in the world.
Olivia Lux.
Oh. This time
she packed her big bag.
I'm really excited
to flip the script
and be this mysterious
mistress of the night.
I don't normally do dark hair,
but something about
this rich chocolate brown
against that
glittering burgundy,
a night at the opera, perhaps.
Trend alert.
Teeny, tiny handbags.
Teeny, teeny, tiny.
She packed an overnight bag.
All she needs are her panties.
Tee-hee!
Symone. Yes, honey.
Ooh, is the bus still running?
The bitch has arrived
at the party, honey,
Let's go.
For evening, Symone is
giving you very Mother Goddess
combined with
the last people in the matrix
partying and dying, darling.
Get this side.
It's my good side.
Oh, every angle.
Ooh, it looks like she started
the walk of shame early.
See you next Symone day.
Tina Burner.
What's latex got to do with it?
All her exes live in latexes.
I'm letting the judges know
that I not only can be
a costume comedy queen,
but I can be a sexy seductress,
fun party girl.
My boots are up to my pussy,
and I am swinging my hair,
trying not to throw my neck out
because I'm old.
I'm serving you my red claws,
because she's gonna claw
the competition.
Tina Burner,
available only on vinyl.
Something wicked this way comes.
Elliott with 2 Ts.
Michelle's been good,
but I've been bad.
This look right here
is out of the box for Elliott.
It is dark and mysterious
and just sex.
This look is what you see
when you go to the
gentleman's club on a fetish night.
And don't get too close to her.
She might whip you, honey.
And, poof, there she goes.
Well, that's it. Show's over.
My car is here.
- Oh.
- Bye.
Is the bus still running?
Yeah, can I borrow
a little change?
Yeah, I gotcha.
Coming up...
I'm still gagged Miss Thing
came for me earlier.
I already feel like I'm
the red-headed stepsister.
That's strike one.
Bitch, strike two, you out.
Oh, here we go.
It's starting early.
Oh, my.
Oh, my God.
Jesus!
That was everything.
Oh, bitch, oh, oh, oh.
My feet hurt so bad.
We're back in the werkroom,
and I'm looking around the room,
and everyone brought it
for the fashion show, bitch.
I'm kind of gagged.
I feel real confident,
I feel real good.
Can't wait
for that maxi-challenge.
We gonna see what happens.
Get this hair up off me, Lord.
Take it off, take it off,
take it...
- Ahh, feel that.
- Oh, Lord.
That's better than sex, honey.
Can someone get my hair
outta my dress?
Thank you, dude.
Ooh. Ugh!
Bitch, it's like
a steamed hamhog.
What the hell is a "hamhog?"
I just wanna hose myself down.
Oh, she's on brand.
Hose, fire hose, firemen.
- Oh, come on!
- Tina Burner!
Oh, here we go, here we go.
It's starting early.
Girl, I'm still so gagged
Miss Thing came for me earlier.
Miss New Girl on the Block?
Miss 2 Ts over there.
Mother hen got comfortable
real fast, girl.
Real fast, and that's
the thing, though.
Like, I respect everyone,
I give everyone a fair chance.
But if you're trying
to come for me
and I'm on the other side
of the room
minding my damn business...
Child, the entire time
Elliott has been here with us,
all that has been
running through my head
is "spy, spy, spy."
Don't trust the bitch.
That's strike one.
Bitch, ain't no strike three.
Strike two, you out.
- You only get two strikes.
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, fashion icons.
- Oh!
- Ooh!
Are you decent?
I'll take that as a "no." Yeah.
Racers, are you ready
to rock my world?
- Yes.
For your first maxi-challenge,
you need to perform
a new show-stopping version
of my song Condragulations.
Oh!
Aah!
Which is featured
as part
of the Werq the World tour.
For tickets and information,
go to VossEvents.com.
Now, each of you
needs to try and outdo me
with your own original verse.
Try it. I dare you.
- Ooh!
- Aah!
Then, as a group,
you need to come up with
your own winning choreography.
Oh, shit.
Any dancers in the house?
Now remember, the lyrics,
the performance, and the look
all need to show the world
that you are number one.
Racers, start your engines,
and may the best drag queen win!
Let's put the pen to the paper.
Rap...
lyrics.
Has anyone
written lyrics before?
I mean, I consider myself
a lyricist.
I'm sure you do.
Well, you've been
in a boy band, so...
Yes, honey.
So the first thing we have to do
for this maxi-challenge
is we have to sit down and we
gotta write out these lyrics.
And then we go up to Sweden
to record the vocals.
Because if you know
your boy band herstory,
all the boy bands go to Sweden,
and that's where they keep you
and they lock you up until
you come back with some singles.
Do you wanna sing or do you
wanna be, like, a bitch track?
Or, like, rapping?
- I don't know.
- Are you a bitch track?
I mean, I can...
She's a bitch track.
I'm a bitch track, but, like...
She's a bitch album.
I actually write music.
- Do you really?
- Word.
I compose music, yeah.
So I play the piano,
but I also write music.
Oh, she is a musician.
I'm so excited.
Our first maxi-challenge,
and we're writing music,
something I'm good at!
Who's ready
to be the star student? Me!
Don't forget, like, we're gonna
be judged also on what we write.
And that's
gonna be eternal, bitch.
That's what I'm saying.
So you think
you're just gonna be cute,
but remember, these lyrics
are gonna chase you around
for the rest of your life.
And that's
so much more pressure.
Girl, we're gonna be jet-set.
It's gonna be gorg.
Well, I mean, we're
definitely all performers,
since we won
that first lip sync.
- Well...
Oh, my.
Coming off of losing
my first lip sync,
it's a lot of stress
and a lot of pressure.
I already feel like these girls
feel like they have some type
of advantage over me.
I'm the red-headed stepsister.
I need to do an incredible job,
because I cannot
be sent home again.
Coming up...
♪ Condragulations,
you're number one ♪
How about
"Congratulations to our spot
for the next ho to come out?"
You a dancer now?
Let's just get
the choreography done,
because we're on limited time.
Girl, this is some bullshit.
All right, bitch.
Back on the stage.
So now it is time to get
this choreography together.
We have to choreograph
this entire thing,
top to bottom,
from our own noggins.
Okay, so what do we do?
We're on. Who wants
to start this thing off?
So you start first?
We should do the things
we're gonna do together first.
So we should do, like,
the chorus first,
and then focus on
individual stuff after.
- Sure.
- I agree.
Okay. So then let's start.
Who's a dancer
who is good with the choreo?
Cricket, cricket.
Girl, nobody
wants to be in charge.
And there you have it.
These girls don't know
that this is what I do.
I'm a choreograph dancer.
But I don't want to take charge
when I literally just walked in.
So I'm trying to just sit back,
let these hos figure it out,
and I'll just do what I'm told.
What if we all just went off
like ♪ Condragulations ♪
♪ We're number one, one, one ♪
Should it be this,
or should it be like this?
That's too cheer-ish.
And then we could
do it together.
We could go together, like that.
That way, you can
bring the hand down,
and maybe we should
put the hand on the waist?
And one?
This is some bullshit.
Options, bitch.
Oh, I like the options,
but I also...
We should definitely get,
like, a choreo down,
then formation after.
This is like a pop song,
it's not like no one, two,
Supreme-like type thing.
Like, we need
to boo-boo kat-kat.
This is choreography.
This is the shit you can find
in a parking lot
on the south side of Atlanta,
and you don't wanna go through
south side of Atlanta, baby.
Trust me.
Girl, this is some bullshit.
So take it from the top.
Five, six...
♪ Condragulations,
you're number one ♪
This some... okay, sorry.
♪ Da ♪
- Touch, step, touch.
- Step, touch.
I think we're all doing
together, together, out.
Yeah, together, together, out.
Uh, uh, out. Okay.
No, your legs need to be...
Like, they need to go out.
So...
So it goes, uh, uh, out.
Oh, honey, we gonna have
to go over this 5,000 times.
I am nervous.
To say the least.
Hand should be on the hip.
Like, I don't wanna
win my lip sync
and then get
in front of the judges
and, like, oh,
you can't do a one-two?
So let's take it from the top
again, from the chorus.
And then we gotta move on,
you guys.
We got so much to do.
Right now, the girls are really
focusing on such minute details
that we can just
clean up later on.
Watch my hands.
One, two, three, ha.
That's what I was doing,
with the right... the same hand.
Okay, let's do that, then.
- Is that cool?
- Sure.
I think it looks better
if we do...
- I like opposite.
It's becoming a lot harder
to not just take the reins.
So take it from the top?
- Tina?
- Yes?
Bah-gock. So what
I think we should do
is how about, since
our leg's already out,
we just turn on it,
since our leg is already out.
- Ooh.
- From the snap, turn.
So much fun.
Da.
You a dancer now?
All of a sudden, hey, Juilliard.
After we do the "Tell you
all the prizes you have won,
congratulations," to our spot,
for the next ho to come out.
We're already halfway through,
and now you're speaking up?
We already think
you're the mole.
Let's just get
the choreography done,
because we have limited time.
Okay.
I don't trust you, girl.
Do you guys wanna just, like,
stay in this formation
and then just go up
and do our solos?
Let's get a beat in the ear.
♪ Gottmik
was born a girl, baby ♪
Uh!
Oh, my God.
I wrote "I'm born a girl,"
and I haven't talked
to this bitches about it.
So I did not know
that I was going to have
to have all these girls
hear about my gender situation
before I can even talk to them.
Uh, do you, like, know what
you're gonna do during the...
Ha-ha. Not really.
I'm just a deer in headlights
right now, basically.
I just can't even seem to talk,
which is very unlike me.
I don't know what's going
through their heads.
I shouldn't even
be focusing on that.
Like, who cares?
But we have to
perform this tomorrow.
What the fuck
are you gonna do, bitch?
I feel like it'll just be,
like, very like...
Like a Gottmik,
and then it's like....
And then,
like, something, like...
I look over at Gottmik,
and I feel like Gottmik is
really in his head, you know?
Something's going on.
I mean, there is
an internal struggle.
- Okay, so...
- I'm going here to back.
- Are you doing...
- I do this.
Are you doing a full circle?
I'm going all the way around,
yeah.
I can't take
any of these moves in.
I'm just having
a hard time focusing.
It's so weird
that I feel like this.
I didn't even know
that I had a lot of
gender dysphoria anymore.
So the fact that
it's throwing me
into this weird hole like this
is so gaggy.
All right, ladies, time is up.
Oh, Lord.
I do not get like this.
If this sends me home right now,
I will not be happy.
Coming up...
Elliott, what happened
after you left?
I wanna know, because we
nicknamed you Elliott the Spy.
So you really wanna know?
Wait, what?
Oh, my God.
Meow! Yeah!
Money, honey-honey.
Let's get up in this gig.
The first maxi-challenge
is here.
We have to perform it
in front of the judges.
Judgment day is upon us.
Who's excited
about tonight, honey?
- I'm excited!
- Yes!
I'm a little nervous,
but I'm excited.
Yeah, it's nerve-wracking,
because rehearsal yesterday
was a little rough.
I went to bed worried myself.
I ain't gonna lie about that.
But I said we're the winners,
you know what I mean?
We're here, it's like a pack.
I literally feel
like the world is on
my shoulders right now,
because I am the girl
that was brought back.
I feel like in the back
of everybody's head
I was the weakest link.
So I have to turn this shit out.
How are you feeling
about your solos?
I feel mine is the most
complex choreography.
Oh!
Oh, girl, please.
Mik, how are you feeling
about your performance?
A little better today.
I was, like, really
so stressed yesterday.
Like, you guys all dancing,
to, like, talking
about how I'm a girl,
and it was like fucked to me.
I feel like
I based all my lyrics
about my gender situation,
and I haven't even
talked to you guys
about me being
a transgender guy drag queen.
Like, I was just gagged.
Like, my gender dysphoria,
like, took over my soul,
which so isn't like me, too.
Because I usually
don't give a fuck.
I just couldn't even take in
any of the choreo at first,
because it was just like...
It was so intense.
Like, it was, like,
I can't breathe about it.
Like, thank you
for sharing that with us.
And you're, like... you're
changing the shape of drag.
Like, this is... this is big.
Thank God I feel
a little better today about it,
because that was a moment.
But... yeah.
Gottmik reveals
that she is a trans man.
It wasn't the right time
to talk about it in rehearsal,
but I can be there for her now.
I'm so thankful and happy
that she was able to confide
and find that sister in me,
and I really wanna make sure
that I'm supporting her
every step of the way.
May I ask, what are pronouns...
Like, out of drag,
I use he/him/his,
and then in drag, she/her/hers.
I'm the exact same way.
I feel like when people
are trying to overthink it
and they call me "he" in drag,
I'm like, bitch,
you're just clocking me
and making me feel,
like, so weird.
- Yeah.
- We're all guys here,
so if you're gonna call them
she, do not try it with me.
I feel like a weight has
been lifted off my shoulders.
Cards are on the table.
My normal,
slightly narcissistic,
confident Gottmik headspace
took back over.
Now I just need
to kill this performance.
- Miss Symone.
- Yes.
I know you were struggling
a little bit in the rehearsal.
I am struggling.
I am very nervous
about the group stuff,
and making sure
that, like, I'm on point
and I don't mess up
and make it, like...
I think that if you for
some reason happen to mess up,
go for it and give attitude.
Girl, it was on... I messed up,
yeah, but that was on purpose.
What do you know?
You don't know choreo.
The other girls are wrong,
darling, I'm right.
Okay?
Very that about it.
Yeah, story time.
Elliott, what happened
after you left?
The real tea, though, Elliott.
Like, what went on?
So you really wanna know?
I wanna know, because we
nicknamed you Elliott the Spy.
I feel like I'm speaking
for the group here.
- Y'all can back me up.
- No, you right.
- Yes, honey.
- That's true.
I thought you came outta nowhere
and you already got sent home.
It was a little weird.
Reveal yourself!
Here's kinda what went down.
So all the losing girls
were set in the porkchop
loading dock.
RuPaul says you guys have
to vote one of the losers out.
Wait, what?
And they voted you out?
We did a lipstick vote.
It was a tie.
Then they had to break the tie
with a re-vote.
Oh, shit.
And it was unanimous.
- Ooh.
- Oh, my God.
All right, bitch, hold on.
Press pause.
She got eliminated
by Tina Burner. Boom.
And then you let
other eliminated girls
eliminate you again, sis?
Bitch, you got eliminated
three times
at the beginning of the season
on the first episode?
Oh.
So they think
that you went home.
Oh, now you're back
in the house.
So you might wanna make
some room in the werkroom
for some more girls.
Oh, my God.
That is gagging.
The girl that I beat
is coming back,
along with the other girls
that were beat?
I am definitely, like,
they are about to come back
with all the fires of hell
behind them.
Now that the tea is spilled,
we can kinda be nice to Elliott.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, I'm happy
to be here with you guys.
I love you guys so much.
- Oh!
- Oh, we love you, too.
We're Season 13 sisters now,
you guys.
Like, you can't take
that shit away, honey.
But, like, did we all forget
that we're also walking
into elimination tonight?
- We're all over here kiki-ing.
- Ooh, the mood has changed.
Oh, yeah, the mood
has changed, honey.
- The mood has changed, honey.
- Kandy?
Yes, baby?
If you had to send
somebody home in this room...
- Uh-oh.
- Oh, bitch.
Like, if I had to, like,
choose a lipstick,
I'm gonna send home
the biggest competition.
Because I wanna win.
So I would send home
Tina Burner. Goodbye.
I'll remember that.
Honestly, I'm afraid of Mik
and her fierce fashion.
Tina, who would you send home?
I mean, I have to send home Mik.
Thank you.
You just... you're a threat,
so I gotta send Mik home.
- Symone.
- Yeah, I would definitely...
It would be Tina.
You are a threat for sure.
LaLa?
I would say Mik.
Olivia, who would you send home?
Oh, yeah, Olivia,
who would you send home?
Well, I've realized
that a lot of you
don't think of me as the biggest
threat or a threat at all.
- She's nothing to me.
- Oh, it's not personal.
- Drag.
Good to know.
I think I am a big threat,
but the other girls don't.
I'm not as well-known
as some of the other girls,
but I'm not letting it
get in the way.
I have to show them
that I'm here for a reason.
Everybody loves
a dark horse, honey.
What'd you call me?
Oh, my God. Olivia!
♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
And what?
Welcome to the main stage
of RuPaul's Drag Race.
Michelle Visage.
Aw, I bet you say that
to all the whores.
The hilarious Ross Mathews.
Now, Ross, have you
ever put out a single?
No, but I have put out
for singles.
Yeah!
And director/choreographer
Jamal Sims.
Now, this week, the girls
did their own choreography.
Is that correct?
I just came to watch
and read for filth.
This week
we challenged our queens
to write, record, and perform
a Season 13 re-do of my song,
Condragulations.
And tonight on the runway,
category is Lamé You Stay.
Ooh.
It should have been Mother,
Lamé I Sleep With Danger.
- Next season.
- Yeah.
Racers, start your engines,
and may the best drag queen win!
Coming up...
♪ Condragulations,
you're number one ♪
♪ Condragulations ♪
Ooh!
It's time
for the Season 13 debut
of Condragulations,
brought to you
by Werq the World.
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Gottmik was born
a girl, baby ♪
♪ Was told
that I can't do drag ♪
♪ Knew I had
something to prove ♪
♪ And you're gonna lose ♪
♪ Kandy Muse is on top,
she will sit on the prow ♪
♪ Bitches,
bow down to the queen ♪
♪ I'll get in my car,
come on, Ru, pass it down ♪
♪ New York City
gave birth to me ♪
♪ I'm ready to attack,
it's a massive attack ♪
♪ You had better beware
of thee ♪
♪ Sitting alone in the VIP ♪
♪ You could never
compare to me ♪
♪ Ha-ha-ha, bitch ♪
♪ Condragulations,
you're number one ♪
♪ I wanna thank you
for a job well done ♪
♪ Condragulations,
you're so much fun ♪
♪ Now lemme tell you
all the prizes you have won ♪
♪ Condragulations ♪
♪ LaLa Ri, this ain't no drag ♪
♪ Flew from the egg
to snatch the bag ♪
♪ These girls will know
I ain't no joke ♪
♪ Watch my runways
gag their throats ♪
♪ Dance, twirl,
make mama proud ♪
♪ The next Supreme
took the crown ♪
♪ Now let me tell you
what y'all should do ♪
♪ Make room for the queen
of 13, boo ♪
♪ They call me Liv ♪
♪ Sad love, it includes ♪
♪ The new queen,
ready to shine ♪
♪ You see me play on the keys ♪
♪ Jersey, too, don't you see ♪
♪ Lux is someone to beat ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Condragulations,
you're number one ♪
♪ I wanna thank you
for a job well done ♪
♪ Condragulations,
you're so much fun ♪
♪ Now lemme tell you
all the prizes you have won ♪
♪ Condragulations ♪
♪ Condragula-a-a-a-a-ations ♪
♪ The name's Symone
and I'm here for the throne ♪
♪ Deep vixen,
I'm Arkansas-grown ♪
♪ The ebony temptress is me ♪
♪ Legs up to my waist ♪
♪ Talent you can't replace ♪
♪ Tina Burner, on fire
like theHunger Games ♪
♪ Too hot to handle, gettin'
burned by these flames ♪
♪ Panhead monster
with a heart of gold ♪
♪ This joker's wild,
these queens better fold ♪
♪ Death drops, splits
may be some girls' choice ♪
♪ Stand up, act up,
time to use your voice ♪
♪ The truth hurts,
but I'll tell it to your face ♪
♪ And I'll smile real big,
waving from first place ♪
♪ My hair is snatched,
you're looking ratch ♪
♪ Compared to me,
there ain't no match ♪
♪ But there's one up
in the batch ♪
♪ When it comes to fish,
I'm the biggest catch ♪
♪ Underdog,
that's what it took ♪
♪ Changing the game,
rewrote the book ♪
♪ All you queens
better take a look ♪
♪ My name is Elliott,
what, you shook? ♪
♪ Condragulations,
you're number one ♪
♪ Is somebody smoking? ♪
♪ Oh, it's me ♪
♪ I wanna thank you
for a job well done ♪
♪ So gorg ♪
♪ Condragulations,
you're so much fun ♪
♪ So much fun ♪
♪ Now lemme tell you
all the prizes you have won ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Condragulations ♪
♪ Condragula-a-a-a-a-ations ♪
♪ La-la-lations ♪
♪ Condragulations ♪
Oh, my God, what did I win?
- Gimme, gimme, gimme!
- ♪ Condragula-a-a-a-a-ations ♪
♪ Condragulations ♪
Bring back my girls.
Category is Lamé You Stay.
Up first, Gottmik.
It's the creature
from the gold lamé.
And the queen of the runway.
My look
is inspired by sea dragons.
I have a full lamé headpiece
with pleated lamé crazy-stoned
artistry all around my face.
I look like a lamé alien.
It's everything.
You know, I think
I saw that at Gold Navy.
Kandy Muse.
Négligée, you stay.
Do I make you horny, baby?
Fembot realness,
in my purple nightgown,
my little furry titties.
I'm giving the judges
Kandy Muse to the T.
Baby, pretty, sexy.
Eat it up, bitch!
I like a good Nancy boot
and Daisy Duke, mm.
These boots
were made for slaying.
LaLa Ri.
Look, Ru, there's
gold in them thar hills!
With this look, I wanted to go
for a whole dark chocolate
wrapped in gold,
limited edition, Willie Wonka
Golden Ticket situation, girl.
Big hair, big garments.
It's giving you
Atlanta drag-drag, you know.
I hear she's in
the new Bond film:
Goldsphincter.
Olivia Lux.
I think it's Olivia De-Lux.
I am serving
a water lily goddess, honey.
You see that little lily
on my shoulder?
It is trickling down.
I mean, I am giving you
a walking, old Hollywood
portrait painting, honey.
She looks expensive.
I bet she saved up
and bought that on lamé-away.
Symone.
Ooh!
Mama said knock you out.
T-K-O-M-G.
I am giving you
walks the house down, darling.
I got a little cut
on my eyebrow, honey.
I'm giving it to you.
I definitely wanted this runway
to be a little bit more clever,
showing that there is a brain
behind the beauty, darling.
Y'all, does this mean she spits?
That's a wrap on Michelle.
Ding, ding!
Tina Burner.
Oh, I know her.
She's a friend of Dorothy's!
- Yes!
- Ax purse rusted!
I am bringing
a full Tin Man fashion fantasy.
Motorcycle jacket and these
high-waisted lamé mom pants.
I thought it was so important
to give them a different side
of Tina Burner.
♪ Bring back my girls ♪
I'm skipping down
that yellow brick road.
I'm feeling fierce.
Tina, bring me the ax!
Elliott with 2 Ts.
It's Elliott with tutus.
My lamé look
is giving you
rhinestone titty fantasy.
Big puff sleeve,
Tara Lipinski meets 1980s prom.
She is just ready
to do a triple axel,
steal your man,
and go out for drinks after.
I think she's giving you
the cold shoulder, Michelle.
I see it.
♪ Bring back my girls ♪
Coming up...
You are a drag queen.
It's 24-karat magic.
I want you to explain to me
the thought process
behind that look.
Welcome, ladies.
Now it's time for
the judges' critiques.
Starting with Gottmik.
That fashion show
was so well done.
Thank you.
The difference
between your day look,
which was like preschool fun,
and your night look, which
was like, you know, evil whore...
I mean that could
kinda look like Michelle.
You were so versatile.
And this look is already iconic.
It's trending.
Now, the performance, I will say
that in the beginning,
I did sense a little bit
of hesitation in the front.
I think you were so concerned
with your dance steps
and remembering
the choreography,
yeah, that you were
losing the performance.
You have a story to tell.
Your drag is fierce.
Make it work, because
you've got the goods.
Thank you.
All right, up next, Kandy Muse.
What's the tea, honey bee?
You look adorable.
I love this kind of
Austin Powers fembot moment.
Thank you.
In your fashion runway,
the nighttime look,
there was a hole in the back.
Was that meant for a tail?
Yeah, it was supposed to be,
like, a panel.
I don't know.
A glory hole, girl?
Well, I mean, it could be.
Now, I want you to explain to me
the thought process
behind that day look.
When I was thinking, like,
medieval, like,
mother of the hookers.
But she's, like,
the head hooker.
And, like, you know, like,
she gives it to the girls,
and she gets the girls in check.
In my head, it made sense.
Uh-huh.
The thing I'm obsessed with
about you
is that, like, I never know
what you're gonna do next
or say next.
Have you ever watched a TV show
and not known
what the hell was going on,
but you stay tuned
for episode two?
95% of the time.
I don't even know
what you said, but, yes.
That is something
that money can't buy,
and it's your best attribute.
Tonight in your performance,
when you messed up your choreo,
don't let it show in your cara.
Because the minute
that happened,
we saw you going,
like, full-on panic.
If you're in the front,
there's no mistakes
unless you let us know
that it's going bad,
you know what I mean?
Thank you, Kandy.
Do-re-mi LaLa Ri.
I did not love your day look,
just because I thought
the colors looked kind of drab.
I loved your night look, though.
I'd like to go to the club
with that girl.
I'd, of course, take
an Uber home about 10:45.
She could stay out.
This look here, you are
a motherfucking drag queen.
It's 24-karat magic.
And then in your performance,
what I loved
was your confidence.
When you did your solo,
I was like, I wonder
where she's from.
And then you said Atlanta,
I was like, yep,
she's from Atlanta.
What clubs in Atlanta
do you work at?
Well, I actually work
at Lips Atlanta.
I've worked at MSR.
Of course I worked at the
Marquette, the Sleazy Queasy.
The Marquette is still there?
Oh, yes, girl,
it's still around,
up and running and strong.
You know, I used to go there
right after the Civil War.
- It's true.
- Yeah.
There was some rough girls
up in there.
Ooh.
Up next, Olivia Lux.
Tonight, I love
this old Hollywood glamour,
and I love to see a queen
of color representing it.
And I loved all your looks.
I thought your daytime look
had a lot of whimsy,
so I thought, okay,
she's got some humor in there.
You in the performance
was a joy to watch.
The funny things that you did,
the little Mariah thing,
you just owned that stage,
and that gets me so excited.
And then you were smart,
because you wore this outfit
that had some fringe on it.
That always just
enhances all the moves,
and I saw somebody that
I could not take my eye off of.
Thank you, Olivia.
All right, Symone.
This tonight was
a different approach to lamé.
It's very smart.
I love the French braid.
Yeah, it works.
- Thank you.
- The whole thing works.
In the runway,
I lived for that day look.
The look was hot.
- Thank you.
- And the night look,
with the hair the way it was,
it was just right.
Thank you.
You're fierce,
you're filled with attitude,
but you're not afraid
to go for it and be who you are.
When you came out, you know
what I wrote down here?
- What?
- I drew a star.
Yeah.
In the performance,
just the way you walked
from that corner
to the center of the stage
was like a spotlight
turned on you.
Just right away, I was hooked.
You've got star quality.
You got it, kiddo.
Thank you so much.
Oh, my God, I can't...
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Up next, Tina Burner.
I thought your daytime look
was so fun.
And the nighttime look
was the perfect
naughty compliment to that.
Tonight, I'm really excited
you're not wearing red,
orange, and yellow.
You're paying homage
to Ru's favorite movie,
The Wizard of Oz.
The ax purse,
the heart under there,
it was all very smartly done.
You pay attention to detail.
Thank you.
Your lip sync was well written,
and you performed
the hell out of it.
Not only that, I was really
shocked with the rap.
You were in the pocket,
and I think that
you are actually amazing.
Thank you very much.
One thing to remember.
This is not a bar,
this is not a theater.
- Yeah.
- What this is... is TV,
so it's gonna be
a little bit different.
You can't turn as much,
and remember,
the cameras are your friends.
They're your lovers, darling.
I'm getting the poppers.
We're ready to go.
That's good advice, and that's
good advice for all the girls.
- Poppers?
- Poppers, yes.
Up next, Elliott with 2 Ts.
So your day look was very French
and very beautiful.
Your night look is what
I was in love with, however.
I thought it was fantastic.
Thank you.
I loved how you looked
in the performance.
The splits, that moment
was just, like, okay.
Oh, she's that girl.
When you guys were in the group,
it felt like
you were just waiting.
Like, I'm about to show,
like when a bull's in the pen
and he's about to come out.
And I was like,
I wonder what this one's
about to do, you know?
I've been thinking about
what it must feel like
to stand in your heels
this week.
Because
you could have been gone.
- Yeah.
- And so if I were you,
I would really have
something to prove this week,
and I think you proved it.
You deserve to be here.
Thank you, Elliott.
Thank you.
Thank you, ladies.
I think we've heard enough.
While you untuck
in the werkroom,
the judges and I
will deliberate.
All right, now, just between
us squirrel friends,
what do you think?
Starting with Gottmik.
Gottmik got style, got talent.
That look was
so mind-blowing tonight.
As soon as the performance
started and picked up,
she got her stuff together.
And I just wish
that she could just own that
from the beginning.
She's new to
the performance part of drag,
so we've gotta see
if Gottmik is a queen
that has that tool
in her tool belt as well.
Kandy Muse, from the Bra-zonx.
I love that she has this body
positivity and shows it off,
but I think the jury's still out
on the aesthetic.
Kandy gives me
around the way girl,
but a little rough
around the edges.
Okay, yes, I get it,
the aesthetic's not great.
And, like, I didn't understand
what she was saying
when she was rapping.
Ha!
But can I keep her? Please?
I love her!
From Atlanta, Georgia, LaLa Ri.
In the performance,
she had a control,
and she knew what she was doing,
and I bought every second of it.
LaLa Ri knows how to perform,
and she's ready to bring it.
I cannot wait
to see what LaLa Ri does.
She's exciting.
Olivia Lux.
Olivia reminds me
of the First Lady.
Faith Evans?
More on the Michelle Obama tip,
but still, you get the idea.
She gives me that.
And then the performance,
I have to say Beyoncé.
- Yeah.
- You know, she had the class,
and she showed up
and she showed out.
And she is so beautiful
and charming.
I see that smile,
and it's like, oh, her.
I love her.
Symone.
I know that Jamal said
that Kandy Muse is like
an around the way girl,
- but so's Symone.
- Yeah.
She came out
and she struck a pose,
and she tilted her head
to the side.
Like, I can't even do it
because my neck roll
won't let me do it.
But she just, like,
just stood and did that,
and I thought, this bitch
has got that energy,
that confidence.
Symone scared me
when I first saw her.
Just to be honest.
And then with her runway look,
that kind of just said
everything about her.
Like, I'm gonna fight all
the way to the finish, you know?
And that's the spirit
that I get from her.
Tina Burner.
I was a little concerned
when I kept seeing
those same orange/red/yellow.
I'm, like, having a flashback
to my eighth birthday party
at McDonald's, right?
And I was thinking, okay,
let's rein those colors in
a little bit.
And she did
right at the right time.
I thought that
was the smartest thing
she could have done this week.
I know her from New York City,
and I have to say,
Tina has been living up
to the Tina Burner hype.
I think that she's got things
that she's gonna have to...
- Adjust?
- Yeah.
I see Tina here to play.
I was pleasantly surprised
in her performance,
and I think that
she has what it takes
to go all the way, actually.
Elliott with 2 Ts.
She came out here
to prove something,
and I think that's
what I picked up on.
She was so excited,
she kind of
got out of the element.
We can see that she's got it.
We see that she can do it.
And if she just
relaxes into it...
I know
we've all heard that before.
You gotta want it.
It's gotta be tough
to be Elliott this week.
I think I must have ESPN,
because I was looking,
I was, like, there's
something going on with her.
And it was true.
But I could tell
that the talent's there.
I can tell that
she can serve a look.
I love Elliott with 2 Ts'
aesthetic,
because it's very Exposé,
the group Exposé,
for those of you who don't know.
But it's quirky, and I love
that aspect of her presentation.
E-S-P-N. Got it.
Silence! I've made my decision.
Bring back my girls.
Welcome back, ladies.
Based on your performances
in the fashion show
and on the main stage,
I've made some decisions.
Olivia Lux.
Symone.
Con-drag-ulations.
You are the top two queens
of the week.
Aah!
Darling, I am on top of the
motherfucking world, bitch.
I'm a real competitor in this.
And now the girls know it.
They don't see me
as a threat, right?
Thank you!
The rest of you...
are safe.
This week, there are
no bottoms, only tops.
Well, with the exception of
the judges' panel, of course.
You may step
to the back of the stage.
I thought I was lip syncing
against Kandy,
and I love Kandy,
so I just feel so relieved.
We're all staying,
and I cannot get to the back
of the stage fast enough.
Olivia Lux, Symone,
great job this week,
but there can only be
one number one.
Two queens stand before me.
Ladies, this is your last chance
to impress me
and win a cash tip of $5,000.
Oh, my God.
The time has come...
for you to lip sync...
for the win.
This is when you
leave it all on the stage.
I'm going to attack it
with everything that I have,
coiffed and updo and all.
Good luck, and don't fuck it up.
♪ I've always been the one
to say the first goodbye ♪
♪ Had to love and lose
a hundred million times ♪
♪ Had to get it wrong
to know just what I like ♪
- ♪ Now I'm fallin' ♪ -
♪ You say my name like
I have never heard before ♪
♪ I'm indecisive,
but this time I know for sure ♪
♪ I hope I'm not the only one
that feels it all ♪
♪ Are you fallin'? ♪
♪ Yeah, center of attention ♪
♪ You know you can get
whatever you want from me ♪
♪ Whenever you want it, baby ♪
♪ It's you in my reflection ♪
♪ Now I'm afraid of all
the things it could do to me ♪
♪ If I would've known it, baby ♪
♪ I would've stayed at home ♪
♪ 'Cause I was doin'
better alone ♪
♪ But when you said hello ♪
♪ I know that was
the end of it all ♪
♪ I should've stayed
at home... ♪
I definitely
wanna show the judges
everything that Symone is,
and this is my moment
to be, like, no, bitch,
this is my stage and this
is my "5,000 dollars."
♪ Oh, no,
I was doin' better alone ♪
♪ But when you said hello ♪
♪ I know that
was the end of it all ♪
♪ I should've stayed at home ♪
♪ 'Cause now there ain't
no letting you go ♪
♪ Am I falling in love ♪
♪ With the one
that could break my heart? ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
Child, I am delivering
straight to you
to your doorstep.
♪ Break my heart ♪
♪ Am I falling in love ♪
♪ With the one
that could break my heart? ♪
♪ I would've stayed at home ♪
♪ 'Cause I was doin'
better alone ♪
♪ But when you said hello ♪
♪ I know that
was the end of it all ♪
♪ I should've stayed at home ♪
♪ 'Cause now there ain't
no letting you go ♪
♪ Am I falling in love ♪
♪ With the one
that could break my heart? ♪
Word!
- Aah!
- Oh, my God!
Ladies, I've made my decision.
Symone.
You're a winner, baby.
Thank you!
Con-drag-ulations.
You've won $5,000.
I'm a winner, baby!
First main challenge,
and Miss Symone
has taken the bag.
I am feeling great.
Olivia Lux, you're safe
to slay another day.
Con-drag-ulations, queens.
More twists and turns
are just around the corner.
But this one thing
I know is true.
If you can't love yourself,
how in the hell
you gonna love somebody else?
Can I get an "amen" up in here?
- Amen!
All right!
Now let the music play.
♪ I'm a winner ♪
♪ I'm a winner, baby ♪
Next time
onRuPaul's Drag Race...
You'll be performing
the song Phenomenon.
♪ It's all over the world ♪
♪ The world ♪
♪ It's a phenomenon ♪
You look rich. I would rob you.
Ladies, remember,
heads will roll.
This is like
RuPaul's Drag Race Tornado.
Like, there's a cow flying by.
Like, here comes a fence.
Like, what next?
♪ I'm a winner ♪
♪ I'm a winner, baby ♪
♪ Losers, weepers ♪
♪ Finders, keepers ♪
♪ I'm a winner, baby ♪
♪ Losers, weepers ♪
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org