- Hey, kitty girl.
- Hello.
- Blessed weather
we're having today.
- Indeed.
Can you believe
it's already "All Stars 3?"
- Oh, blessed be.
- Do you think there will be
lots of twists and turns
and shocks and surprises
this season?
- Oh, bitch.
- And do you think
some of the eliminated queens
will get to Ru-turn
for their Ru-venge?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God, they're not
gonna know what hit 'em.
[both laugh]
[sirens]
- Chad, the Drag Race
Hall of Fame
really isn't what
I thought it was gonna be.
- Girl, you're telling me.
[both sigh]
- You look really nice
in red, though.
- Thanks, girl.
- It's your color.
- [RuPaul] The winner of
"RuPaul's Drag Race All Stars"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia Beverly Hills
cosmetics,
a coveted spot in
the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize
of $100,000.
With extra-special guest judge
Vanessa Hudgens.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race
- ♪ May the best woman
- ♪ Best woman win
- Oh, honey. Whoo.
That's how I roll.
That is such
a fucking waste.
That would've killed
if someone was here.
I'm Trixie Mattel,
and I am the crownless drag
superstar from Season 7.
I came here to eclipse
people with my talent,
but also with my hair.
There's nobody in here.
It's like a Morgan McMichaels
meet-and-greet.
I feel like in the real world
I've been a real all star,
but on "Drag Race"
I was not an all star.
Howdy, y'all.
- You went
for the comedy gold,
but all we got was bronze.
- I need to make amends
for the fact that I came in here
and just hit the cement
and got dragged out
like a dead body.
Twice.
It's not about falling.
It's about getting back up.
- I..
just farted.
- [laughs]
- Hey, kids, Zaddy's home.
- Slay me, my dairy queen.
- Ooh!
The Milk fans will remember
my outside of the carton--
See the joke there?
Outside of the carton
thinking.
- She's got
a real nose for fashion.
- Hello, hello, hello.
I'm thinking about
wearing facial hair.
- Hope you're packed.
- I don't regret
anything that I did
because it got me into
a Marc Jacobs ad campaign,
and it got me notoriety.
She was cover girl,
French Vogue.
I cannot believe you
fucking showed up here.
Don't touch me.
- Good to see you.
- I very much expected
to see Trixie here.
- Whoo!
- Like myself,
she really proved
that she was an all star
off the show,
but she sort of sucks
in comparison to me.
- Wake up, wake up, wake up!
This ain't no dream.
I'm back, the bayou queen.
- Did it just get swampy
in here?
I'm Chi Chi DeVayne,
and y'all girls
better get ready
'cause I'm ready.
I told you I stay ready.
My mama ready.
Who's into glamour?
Who doesn't like a old
smoked turkey neck back?
- You turned it
completely out.
- Tell me why
you're out here
in a bathing suit
with no corset and a belt.
- I don't have the expenses
to pay
for something like this.
- You don't need money,
girl.
That's never an excuse.
- Hey! [laughs]
- Hey, baby!
- I was the trash bag queen
that had a heart of gold.
I just wasn't
polished enough.
But this time I got
my mind together,
I got my drag together.
It's all together, girl.
Oh, oh, hat coming off.
- Is this trash?
- Trash bags.
- I thought garbage day
was Tuesday.
- Chi Chi's here,
and she wore garbage again,
And also trash bags.
- Uh-oh.
- That hat
is your inner saboteur,
and I want you to let it go.
- [laughs]
Whoo!
- Oh, shit.
- [hums] Ow.
I think I just broke
my ankle doing that.
- My name is Thorgy Thor.
I was on Season 8,
and I made top six,
or as some of my enemies
like to say, bottom seven.
I'm colorful, I'm fun,
and I'm the fashion clown.
Whoo! I love everyone.
- [laughs]
- Bob, please shut up.
[all laugh]
- An issue I dealt with
on Season 8
is that I'm constantly
distracted by everything,
but I think 50% of it
was just because
Bob never shuts up.
And since the show,
I've found ways to focus.
Ooh.
I think I'm going crazy.
Oh, there is one.
Sorry. That's gonna
drive me ♪ insane
Yes. Yes, yes, yes, yes!
- Oh, God.
- All Season 8,
Thorgy complained
that she didn't win
because it was The Bob Show.
Okay, girl,
ain't no Bob here.
Let's see what you got.
- Is this yours?
- Yes.
- Can I try this?
- That's what
you should have come in.
- Oh, can I have this?
[laughs]
- Miss Thorgy Thor,
made top four, you didn't.
[laughs]
- I look pretty good
for a dead bitch.
- She's alive!
- My name
is Morgan McMichaels.
I'm from Season 2,
and I'm here
to rock the shit
out of "All Stars Season 3,"
babe.
You can't kill evil
that easy.
- She's a punk dude.
- Rock 'n' roll, baby.
I wonder what everyone's
gonna look like out of drag.
I hope some of you are
attractive boys like me.
Go fix your hair,
fix your mug.
- I don't need
to fix my mug, bitch.
- Honey, you do need
to fix your mug.
On Season 2, I was very blunt
with my opinions,
and I still kind of
have that to this day.
You know me, sharp-tongued.
- Hi!
- How you doing?
- Hello, beautiful.
- Morgan being here is
definitely intimidating.
She's a workhorse.
She probably
is the only girl
that works seven days a week
in Hollywood at every club,
so she's definitely
gonna be one to beat.
- I feel like I'm thanking
a veteran for their service,
because we wouldn't be here
if you weren't here.
- I fought for my country.
Now, what is this look?
- It' s my denim
Pinocchio look.
I'm here to inspire
future challenges.
- One thing I'm not a big fan of
is diva-dom.
I think I'm gonna have to smack
that bitch down a little bit.
- Good cast so far.
Who's gonna fuck it up?
[bell rings]
- Ayo, sis.
- Oh, Lord.
- I have some
unfinished business.
- Trixie,
she stole your act.
- No, you have
to wait there.
- I fuck it up
every time.
My name is Aja,
and I'm here to fuck shit up.
I'm sorry, I am.
- Your makeup is very dark.
- She could walk out there
in a fucking diaper
and they're like, Valentina,
your smile is beautiful.
I just don't feel like
you should be
Miss Congeniality.
- Oh, my God, hi.
Walking into Season 9,
I was thinking
and I was gonna win,
I was the shit
and I was, like,
oh, yes, I got this.
And then the challenges
and the runways came along,
and I was, like,
I don't look that good.
I'm not doing that good.
I'm not feeling that good.
And then I went home.
- She got
her lips done, too.
- I had my lips, my cheeks,
my chin, my skin.
I had Botox in my forehead.
- You're a drag queen
who got more chin?
- Well, bitch, I didn't
have one to begin with.
I was having like the Alyssa
Edwards, like, Season 5 chin,
like, the nonexistent one.
I kind of felt like
the ugly duckling of Season 9,
but I think in a weird way
it really did benefit me
to get criticized by the world.
I mean, look at her.
I am HD ready.
There is no face tune here.
Bitch, they're
gonna be telling me
my smile is beautiful.
Watch.
[laughs]
- Hi, everyone.
It's me, BenDeLaCreme.
Again.
[all laugh]
My name is BenDeLaCreme,
and I placed fifth on Season 6.
I am wearing
a repurposed version
of the gown that I wore
where I was crowned
Season 6 Miss Congeniality.
I've just been
sleeping in it
and spooning
my Miss Congeniality sash
and weeping into my
Overstock gift certificate
for the last four years.
Aah!
BenDeLaCreme
is terminally delightful.
Excuse me, we originated
the language.
- Bitch stole your look.
- [laughs]
- BenDeLaCreme Visage.
- This time I'm here
to get that crown
that I didn't get
the first time,
but I'm also here to show
that you can win
with kindness and integrity
rather than be a bitch.
Oh, crap,
is this an intervention?
- How you doing?
- Good, how are you?
- I'm very good.
- Ben, you're still alive.
She sort of fell off the face
of the earth for a while.
I thought
she just grew a beard,
ran into the woods,
was sort of just terminally
delightful to the squirrels.
- How do you feel
being back?
- I was super nervous
to come back.
- Wait.
Why were you nervous?
- Because I was so fantastic
the first time,
it was, like,
how do I live up to that?
[all laugh]
- BenDeLaCreme's
a little recycled.
You know, we've seen it.
I mean,
the Miss Congeniality dress?
That shit
is out the door.
That was
how many seasons ago?
Like, don't worry about
trying to be that.
Try to get the crown.
- Uh-oh.
- Round two, bitches.
Ha-ha!
- Yes.
[applause]
- I'm Kennedy Davenport
from Season 7.
The dancing diva of Texas
is back, baby,
and I'm dancing my way
to the top.
[pop]
- Newark, LaGuardia,
Kennedy Davenport.
- Aah! Shut up.
- [laughs]
- I've been in this business
for 17 long years.
I don't think
the other girls are ready.
That is a fucking opinion.
You either take it
or you don't.
You know what?
I can be an adult
and say that I may have been
a little bitchy sometimes,
but since the season,
things have changed.
I've grown.
Where are my sisters at?
[cheering]
- Yes!
Kennedy Davenport.
Male bitch.
- Hey!
- We have developed kind of
a mother/daughter relationship.
I get compared to Kennedy
all the time.
- You better come through,
Whoville.
- Oh, my God, the look
is white noise of ugly.
In fact, it's very Chi Chi.
I think Kennedy
is Chi Chi from the future
coming back to tell her
she's not gonna win "All Stars."
Bitch,
they are the same person.
- What's going on,
everybody?
- I'm sorry, I am just staring
at my reflection.
- So many mirrors.
- I know.
- So vain.
- Don't get too blind,
honey. [laughs]
[doorbell rings]
- Well, halle-who
could this be?
- It looks like the box
got an upgrade and so did I.
Halleloo, I'm back, bitches.
Again. Hey!
I'm Shangela.
Baby,
I'm a double kind of ho.
I was on Season 2 and 3.
You know what they say:
third time's the charm.
Halleloo.
Halleloo, ladies.
He's so gay,
and he's so good.
They always say," LaQuifa,"
I say, "What?"
- You have
an irrepressible energy,
but can energy make up
for a lack of experience?
- I think the biggest
misconception about my drag
was that
I wasn't trying hard.
And I swear, girl, y'all,
I was trying my hardest,
but come to find out,
you actually
do need to know something
about makeup and hair
and costumes
in order to be a full,
well-rounded queen.
Oh.
What's up, bitches?
[cheering]
Halleloo to you.
- Oh, God.
If I fucking hear "halleloo"
one more damn time...
I cannot stand it.
She's a halle-lunatic.
- Season 2's in the house.
I was there, too, one day,
but I was there.
- Very briefly.
[all laugh]
- You are back again.
- Again.
- 47th time.
- 47th?
- Well, 47th.
Since Season 3, y'all know
I've stepped it into high gear
and became
a true professional.
I've worked in television.
I've worked in film.
I have been able to headline
my own show
on the Las Vegas strip.
I'm not baby Shangie
anymore.
Chad and Alaska,
baby, make room for me
in that Hall of Fame.
- There's our two Season 2s.
- Yeah.
- Let's do
some more Season 5 girls.
- Eew.
- I feel like
there hasn't been enough.
[siren]
- Yes!
- Whoo, girl.
- What the fuck is it?
- No, it can't be.
- She done
already done had hers.
- Well, come on, girl.
- Welcome, All Stars.
[cheering]
This season is all about
my comeback kids.
Prove you've got what it takes
to go all the way,
and the last thing
you'll hear me say
is welcome to
the Drag Race Hall of Fame.
Henny.
[cheers and applause]
- Whoo!
- Hello, hello, hello!
[cheering]
I see
all the hookers are here.
[all laugh]
My legendary children.
Now, since last we met,
your careers have taken you
across the country,
around the world,
and today you're back
where it all started.
This is your chance
to make a killer comeback,
to rewrite herstory,
and to earn
your rightful place
in the Drag Race
Hall of Fame.
Y'all ready?
- Yes!
- Oh, oh, oh, but wait.
Before the race
starts officially,
I have just one more queen
I'd like to introduce
into the competition.
- Shangela's right there.
- Lock the door.
- Are they seriously
doing this?
- [laughs]
- Say what?
- Whoo!
- It's somewhere.
Whatever.
What were you saying?
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- I have just one more queen
I'd like to introduce
into the competition.
- What?
- All hail America's
OG drag superstar,
all the way from Cameroon,
BeBe Zahara Benet.
[cheers and applause]
- Hello, my beauties.
My name
is BeBe Zahara Benet,
and you may not
recognize me,
but I am the very first
crowned queen
of "RuPaul's Drag Race."
♪ Face, face, face,
I give face, beauty face ♪
Cameroon!
- The winner of "RuPaul's
Drag Race" is BeBe.
- Cameroon is back.
- Hold up, hold up, hold up.
Didn't she already win?
- I know
what you're thinking.
She done already
done had hers.
- Exactly.
- But 2009
was a very different time.
BeBe had to deal
with that Season 1 filter.
Remember that?
The grand prize
was a measly $20,000.
Hell, the Internet hadn't
even been invented yet.
BeBe,
are you ready to inspire
a whole new generation
of "Drag Race" fans?
- Mother, another day,
another slay.
Who's first?
- Ooh.
- Oh.
- [laughs]
- I am completely
intimidated.
That's like
if Ru just was like,
I'm gonna throw my hat
in the ring.
I'm competing
this year, too.
- She's already
had the crown.
Why does she need
another one?
Grandma, sit down.
Let us other bitches
have a crown.
- Ladies, if BeBe
goes all the way,
she'll be the first queen
in "Drag Race" herstory
to snatch two crowns.
But who stays and who goes,
well, that's up to you.
"All Star" rules
are in full effect.
Each week the top two queens
will lip sync for their legacy.
The winner will receive
a $10,000 tip,
plus the power to eliminate
one of her fellow queens.
- Baby,
this is "All Stars 3."
The rules are rough.
You don't have the opportunity
to save yourself.
You rely on other people.
So there's no space
for mistake. None.
- Keep your friends close
and your enemies even closer.
Because when it comes
to "All Stars,"
it do get shady up in here,
am I right?
- Hello.
- Now let's take a moment
to get reacquainted.
Oh, pit crew.
- Oh!
- Hey!
- That's right, ladies,
the library is open,
because reading is what?
[All] Fundamental.
- I can't wait to see
how this turns out.
First up, Thorgy Thor,
come on down.
- Whoo!
- Wait. Do you know
where my wallet is?
- What?
- Chi Chi, didn't you take it
when you stole my spot
in the top five of Season 8?
- Ooh.
- Shangela is the most annoying
thing I've ever met in my life.
She's like a pull-up toy
that says Halleloo,
but the only thing
more annoying than Shangela
is Bob the Drag Queen.
- Oh.
- Just my opinion.
- By the way, Ru,
do you know me and Aja
used to work together
in Brooklyn?
- No, I didn't know that.
- Do you know
she's a straight-up witch?
She cast a spell
on the producers.
How else do you think
she ended up on "All Stars?"
- Oh!
- Miss Thorgy Thor.
Girl, what the fuck
you got on your head?
[all laugh]
- Christmas with the Kranks,
honey.
[all laugh]
- Big and milky,
girl, just like the drink,
you give me the shits.
[all laugh]
- Me, too.
- Aja, welcome
to the big leagues,
where Charlotte Russe
and Forever 21
won't cut it, little girl.
[all laugh]
- BenDeLaCreme,
where you been?
- Ooh.
- [laughs]
- Like, literally,
where you been?
- Oh, Seattle.
- [laughs]
- It's okay.
I'm gonna Sia this bitch.
[all laugh]
Kennedy Davenport,
the only queen
that doesn't have to turn
to look both ways
before crossing the street.
[all laugh]
- I hate you.
- Shangela. I always thought
her name was Angela,
and people were just
telling her to shut up.
[all laugh]
- Chi Chi DeVayne,
girl, with that mouth,
you could've put Black &amp; Decker
out of business, bitch,
'cause you a mouthful
of tools, honey.
[all laugh]
- Kennedy Davenport.
- Be gentle, sister.
- You seem a little offended
by our little jokes.
We weren't offended
by your parents' little joke.
- Aah
- Ooh!
- Thorgy Thor,
you know, I love clowns.
- Uh-huh.
- And I never met an unfunny one
till I heard you read it.
- Oh!
- The low-rent
Michelle Visage,
sister,
it's nice to see you here.
It's nice
to see you anywhere
considering you've been
unemployed since Season 6.
[all laugh]
Morgan McMichaels,
sister, I know
you love to perform
hard rock music,
and that's good because
that face is also a hard rock.
[all laugh]
- Aja.
- Oh.
- You're beautiful,
you're gorgeous,
you look like Seal.
[all laugh]
Wow, Milk, you put a lot
into this look.
What, 2%?
Shangela.
- Hey!
- What if this season
we put you in a box?
'Cause you're gonna
halle-lose.
[all laugh]
- BeBe Zahara Benet,
you look like
an overweight Naomi Campbell.
- Aah!
[all laugh]
- Morgan McMichaels, I would
take the A out of your name
and replace it with an O
because I'm pretty sure
we'd like you Mor-gone.
- [gasps]
- What?
- Trixie, you look like
a Lisa Frank serial killer.
- I will take that.
I'm from Wisconsin.
- It's an aesthetic.
- Oh, Lord.
- Well, I'm very excited
to read all of my sisters.
Oh, Thorgy,
I love this full outfit.
I usually only get to see
about this much
when you're handing out balloons
from that sewer grate.
[all laugh]
- Oh, my God.
- Shangela,
you have come so far.
Initially your makeup
was kind of busted
and your outfits
were a mess
and your personality
was super grating,
but look at how far
you've come now.
You are much older.
[all laugh]
Trixie, you know, a lot
of people clock your makeup,
but I totally get it.
You know, you're just painting
for the back of the room,
which makes sense because that's
where your audience collects
if you remember
to lock the door.
[all laugh]
- And, BeBe, I hear
that this is the year
that you might
get two crowns,
which is really not
a lot of dental work
as far as those early seasons
are concerned.
[all laugh]
- Thanks, Mother.
[clears throat]
Thorgy Thor.
Mother, she looks homeless.
You know, I'm not gonna read
Morgan McMichaels.
Life already has.
Everybody,
I'm the only African here,
but why it does look like
with Kennedy Davenport
you can sponsor her
for 30 cents a day?
[all laugh]
- Ooh, somebody burned out
a light.
It's shady in here.
- [laughs]
- The library
is closed officially.
- Thank you.
- The winner of today's
mini challenge is...
BenDeLaCreme.
[cheers and applause]
You've won
a $3,000 gift certificate
from l.a. Eyeworks.
- Oh.
- So Miss Congeniality
won the reading challenge.
Some of the queens
are underestimating
what I'm bringing
to this competition,
and I'm gonna
prove them wrong.
- And I will be posting more
of your reads at VH1.com.
All right. Ladies,
it's time to get ready
for your big comeback
to the main stage.
For this week's
maxi challenge,
you'll be headlining
an All Star Variety Show.
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
- Tomorrow, in front of
a live studio audience,
you need to show that
your charisma, uniqueness,
nerve and talent, is bigger,
fresher, and better than ever.
#AllStars3.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may the best
All Star win.
[cheers and applause]
- I need to get
the fuck outta drag.
- This was Pearl's spot,
and she skated by,
so I'm looking to inherit
that energy.
- [laughs]
Bitch, you got jokes.
- Guys, BeBe's back.
- Mother.
- Winner, winner
chicken dinner.
More great things
are happening for you.
- Do you think you have a good
chance of winning this season?
- Everybody's competition,
but I'm here
to really, really
get to share my gifts,
and also
to be able to learn
from the all other girls
I have not worked with,
because everybody
has something special.
That sounds like
an Oprah moment, but it's true.
- BeBe's never really
experienced a hardship
on "Drag Race."
She hasn't had a bad moment.
It's actually scary
to be her.
- If you have a good experience
on "Drag Race,"
it's like so terrifying
to come back.
- Oh, there's more to lose.
- Absolutely.
And I have to say
that I really thought
Valentina was gonna be here.
- Me, too.
- And I am disappointed,
because I am now like
the Miss Congeniality
who, like,
if I'm like a bitch,
that's gonna look terrible.
But if Valentina was here,
she's just like already
automatically the worst
about that.
- I like Ben.
I just think
she can come across
as trying to be congenial,
but I don't think that
that's actually who she is.
I think
she will be congenial
to get
exactly what she wants.
- Trixie, are you making
a porno for your talent?
- No, I'm gonna play violin
in a red clown wig.
It's kind of my thing.
- Very funny.
The first challenge
is very, very important
because in "All Stars,"
it's about impressing
your competition,
so you really have to come out
as a front runner right away.
- What are you doing
for talent?
- I'm drag dancing it out.
What are you doing?
- Come through.
- I've never done it
before, so...
- Very good.
- And what are you doing?
- Just one of my songs.
- She's also
performing a song.
- A lot of the queens are doing
basically the same thing,
lip syncing or dancing
or singing
one of their original songs.
As long as I do well
with the violin playing
and my strings don't explode,
I'm gonna win. Whoo!
- How do you feel about
the whole elimination setup?
- I like it.
- Do you?
- I'm just gonna
send the bitch home
that I think
is the strongest.
- Really?
- That's exactly
what I'm gonna do.
- That is terrifying.
- Well, the thing is,
I mean, why lie about it?
Like, you know, everybody
played Kumbaya last year,
and it was like, oh, here.
Tch, tch, tch, tch.
We are all friends,
we are all sisters,
but, like, at the end
of the day, $100,000.
My strategy
for sending girls home--
it isn't shady,
it is honest.
This is a game.
You have to play it
to win it,
and I love the girls,
but I want to win.
- I feel like it would be
like career suicide
to look
straight in the camera
and say, that person
is my biggest threat, go home.
- But you don't
just have to deal with,
like, what other people's
response is.
You have to deal with, like,
how you feel about how you won
or didn't win.
- But if you're honest,
then there's no fast one
being pulled.
If you're straight up
from the jump,
then there's no--
there's no mincing of words,
there's no mixup
in your communication.
- It's hard, though,
because it's like a room
full of fan favorites.
- With the exception of me.
- That's true.
- [laughs]
- But it is. I mean--
- No, like the T, yeah.
- Everybody in here
is a fan favorite,
except I'm not worried
about that.
- Morgan is talking about
she's gonna eliminate
the strongest queens
to knock out
the competition.
Sweetie,
that's a great strategy
that you should not
have said out loud
in front of
all these queens.
- Would you say that it's not
"RuPaul's Best Friend Race"?
- Well, LaShauwn said it,
I didn't.
- Coming up...
- Everybody
is getting along.
Oh, I love you,
kissy, kissy, kissy.
But we all know
how this works.
We ain't talking about that,
Miss Thang.
- Okay, God bless you, too.
- Be nice, bitch.
- Girl, bye.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Good morning.
- Zaddy's home.
- Today's maxi challenge
is a "RuPaul's Drag Race All
Stars" Variety Extravaganza.
[pop] My talent is not
tongue popping. Don't worry.
- How's everybody doing?
- How are you doing?
- Of course everybody
is getting along.
Everybody is Kumbaya,
everybody is Mother Teresa,
Gandhi.
Oh, I love you,
kissy, kissy, kissy.
But we all know
how this works.
It will be very interesting
to see if all of this
sisterly love stays.
- Well, I'm just hoping
that I am not in the bottom
because every season
I've been on,
I was in the bottom
on the first episode.
- But one person
has to go home today.
I mean, it's always scary
like the very first elimination.
- [gasps] I'm shook.
- It sucks, but somebody
gotta do it, bitch.
Tonight
is the first elimination,
and it's all up
to the girls.
Right now you just don't know
how it's gonna go.
There's no set guidelines.
And then what if
we set the guidelines
and somebody steps
outside of those guidelines?
It just...
it wrecks my nerves.
- I think that we as a group
have generally gotten along
really, really well so far,
but I think people's true colors
will start to show
the minute the top
and the bottom are announced.
I think the claws
are gonna come out tonight.
- I want the claws
to come out.
- Me, too.
I like the drama.
- I think it'll be so fun.
I love drama.
- I'm always intrigued
because the fans are, like,
oh, you're the nice one,
you're the bitchy one.
I'm, like, baby, you realize
that drag queens
encompass everything, right?
Like, yes, I'm a little more
viper-tongued.
- You're such a meanie,
but I don't think
you are at all.
- Morgan is one of the nicest
people I've ever met.
- I really, like,
love you, Morgan.
- Oh, thanks, babe.
I'm just me.
- Do you know what?
I actually think
"Drag Race"
is more stressful
than any drag experience
I've ever had in the real world.
I think I spent the whole time
the first time on "Drag Race"
saying "I'm not scared,"
even though I was.
- Last time
I got really in my head,
and when I didn't do as well
as I thought I was gonna do,
I thought it was, like,
a reflection of my worth.
And Milk saw me, like, before
the show aired after our season.
- Yeah, she was in a mood.
- I was shook.
When I was eliminated,
I was devastated.
I felt like the air was
being sucked out of my lungs.
But this time around
I'm here to prove
that I can get through
anything that's thrown at me
without getting rattled
by it.
- Who did you gag on coming
into this room, honey?
- Aja, because
she just left the season.
So it was like--
- Are you surprised
to see me?
- Yeah.
- I mean,
you were just so new.
Girl, you just
got off the boat, bitch.
Bitch, you fresh meat,
bitch, so...
- But she just got off
the "Drag Race" boat,
but she's been doing drag
for like six-and-a-half years.
- We're not talking
about that.
- Sister, I'm allowed to put
a little piece in there.
- Oh, girl, but we ain't talking
about that, Miss Thang.
- Okay, God bless you, too.
- Ooh.
- Let me stop, honey.
- Be nice, bitch.
- They're gonna start thinking
I'm mean, girl.
- You still mean, girl.
You're still mean.
- I know the girls
are gonna underestimate me,
and my advice to them
is underestimate me
'cause we'll see
who gets the last laugh.
I will. Ha-ha!
- Coming up
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- ♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Cover girl,
♪ Head to toe,
let your whole body talk ♪
♪ Cover girl
- Welcome to the main stage
of "RuPaul's
Drag Race All Stars."
Michelle Visage, do you have
stars in your eyes?
- Darling,
I only have eyes for you.
- Style superstar
Carson Kressley,
are you ready
for a really big "shoe?"
- Oh, yeah, I can probably
squeeze into a lady's 15
if it's a slingback.
- Funny man Ross Mathews.
Do you love a comeback?
- A comeback? That's two
of my favorite things.
- And the gorgeous
Vanessa Hudgens.
Are you excited to be here?
- Oh, I can't believe
I'm here, baby.
I'm so happy.
- This week, I challenged
my All Stars
to gag us with their charisma,
uniqueness, nerve, and talent
in an All Star Variety Show.
Gentlemen,
start your engines,
and may
the best All Star win.
First up, our Werqin' Girl,
Shangela.
- ♪ Sit back, everybody
- ♪ Everybody
- ♪ I've got a little story
to tell ♪
- ♪ Tell it, girl
- ♪ Y'all know me
♪ A little diva
that came in the mail ♪
♪ You saw her, boss
♪ The Nancy Drew of drag
♪ Even threw a drink
on a bitch ♪
♪ And now
I'm back in this party ♪
♪ To break it down
like this ♪
♪ Let's go
♪ Clock the hair
♪ Clock the mug
♪ Clock the nails,
clock my skirt ♪
♪ This is how
you steal the show ♪
♪ I'm a pro
♪ Pro
♪ Work
Oh, you thought that was it?
Catch the verse.
♪ Just wait,
gonna get me some ♪
♪ Telling me stop,
but I'm not done ♪
♪ Working my body
like zoom-zoom-bum ♪
♪ If you wanna start the party,
bring Shangela back ♪
♪ Looking for an all star?
That's me ♪
♪ Don't need a sugar daddy
'cause I'm what? Sickening ♪
♪ Started from the bottom,
now I'm so full grown ♪
♪ Heading for the crown
like "Game of Thrones" ♪
Uh, Ru, is the bus
still running?
[cheers and applause]
- Welcome our queen
BeBe Zahara Benet.
- [male chorus]
♪ I found my way back home
♪ Cameroon
♪ She is Cameroon
♪ They call her Cameroon
♪ Cameroon
[scat singing]
♪ Rhythm
♪ The beat
♪ Pulsing
♪ The heat
♪ Hush
♪ Can you hear it?
♪ Now bam, bam
♪ Bam
♪ Now bam
[singing in native language]
- BeBe is the Lion King--
off Broadway--
but she looks great.
She turned to me and went,
"Arrr."
And I went, "Aah!"
[cheers and applause]
- She's looking good
and feeling Thorgeous.
Thorgy Thor.
[plays classical music]
[cheering]
- ♪ Looking good,
feeling Thorgeous ♪
[cheers and applause]
- All the way from the BK,
Brooklyn's Aja.
- Ugh. I don't understand
why people leave their house
looking like that.
What the --
was you thinking?
Ooh. She looks even uglier
out of drag.
I just can't take you.
How unfortunate.
♪ Down to the pussycat,
cat-cat-cat ♪
♪ Come on, cat-cat,
down, down, down ♪
♪ Down to the pussycat,
cat-cat-cat ♪
cat-cat-cat-cat ♪
♪ Down to the pussycat,
♪ Bad cat-cat,
down, down, down ♪
♪ Double your pussy up-up
♪ If you're
feeling-feeling down ♪
♪ Double your pussy up-up
♪ Step your cookies up-up
♪ So you'll get one up
♪ One, two
♪ Three, four, five
♪ Six, seven, eight,
nine, ten ♪
- Aah!
- Ooh, face crack.
- Oh, my God.
- Paramedics. Paramedics,
make sure she's okay,
because I was not ready.
Not.
- Coming up...
- You raised the bar today.
- Head to toe perfection.
- I was like, oh!
It was so good.
[all laugh]
[RuPaul laughs bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Welcome back to "RuPaul's
All Star Variety Show."
Coming in for a landing,
Newark, LaGuardia,
Kennedy Davenport.
[dance music plays]
- Yeah!
- Oh!
Oh!
What?
- I love it!
[cheers and applause]
- The terminally delightful
BenDeLaCreme
[stripper music plays]
- [laughs]
[all laugh]
- I don't have
enough nipples.
I want more nipples.
Oh...
[cheering]
[cheers and applause]
- Prepare to be slain
by Miss Chi Chi DeVayne.
[dance music plays]
- A flat, beaten-up jazz shoe
and no padding.
[groans]
She knows better than that.
But maybe she doesn't.
[cheers and applause]
- We are mad
for Morgan McMichaels.
- ♪ Welcome
to the legendary party ♪
♪ You know you love
my sexy padded body ♪
♪ I got J-Lo's ass
♪ But I still got sass
♪ I don't mean to be vain
♪ But, really,
look at my ass ♪
♪ Well, honey,
let me teach you a lesson ♪
♪ Because I'm
the brand-new obsession ♪
♪ Season 2 is back,
girls are unaware ♪
♪ I'm from Chicago, bitch,
so you better beware ♪
♪ Just kill the T,
I'm a sight to see ♪
♪ Punch holes in the floor,
keep you begging for more ♪
♪ Why you mad, though?
Why you mad, though? ♪
- Why you looking at us?
Why you mad?
- ♪ One, two, come on, Ru
♪ Three, four,
crown this whore ♪
♪ Five, six,
look at those chicks ♪
♪ Don't you know
they've all got dicks? ♪
♪ Why you mad, though?
Why you mad, though? ♪
♪ It's one of those things
that you can't deny ♪
♪ Got the "Drag Race" crown
in my eye ♪
♪ Don't blink, bitch,
'cause I'm here to say ♪
♪ I'm gonna need you
to sashay away ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Up next, the musical stylings
of Trixie Mattel.
- ♪ Living's like a jigsaw
♪ And the farther in
you go ♪
♪ If you're missing pieces,
you never really know ♪
♪ When you're ticking
like a timepiece ♪
♪ On which you can rely
♪ Wonder why you wind it
♪ When you're running
out of time ♪
♪ Sometimes there's a danger
of choking on the parts ♪
♪ No one gave a warning
to the breaking of your heart ♪
♪ Pick up all the pieces
and go back to the start ♪
♪ Never lose it, only using
all your moving parts ♪
♪ All your moving parts
[cheers and applause]
- Last but not least,
she still does a body good.
Here's Milk.
- ♪ It--it--it--it--
♪ It's called fashion,
look it up ♪
♪ Milk
[echoing] ♪ Milk
[groans]
♪ Milk
- [laughs]
- ♪ Walking with fashion
♪ Touch the fashion
♪ Walking with fashion
♪ Walking with fashion...
- Y'all should insert crickets
right there.
- What?
♪ Touch the fashion,
change your life ♪
♪ Fashion, darling
[cheering]
♪ It's just fashion,
darling ♪
♪ But you can't touch it
♪ Touch the fashion,
change your life ♪
♪ Let me tell you
♪ Touch the fashion,
change your life ♪
- Girl, bye.
- ♪ Touch the fashion,
change your life ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Coming up...
- You got to amp it up
a little bit.
- Any self doubt,
knock it off.
- Anywhere we go from here
is gonna be a plus for me.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Welcome, All Stars.
Remember, to win your place
in the Drag Race Hall of Fame,
you have to be both sickening
and strategic.
Now, when I call your name,
please step forward.
Trixie Mattel.
BeBe Zahara Benet.
Milk.
Kennedy Davenport.
You are all...
safe.
[applause]
Please step
to the back of the stage.
Ladies, you represent
the tops and bottoms
of the week.
Now it's time
for the judges' critiques.
- First of all, I want
to say this to everybody.
My goal
is not to make anybody cry.
- But are you going to
make someone quit again?
[all laugh]
First up, Shangela.
- What a way
to start the show, Shangela.
I wrote down
the second you came out
a 10
because you are so good.
- You just commanded
that stage,
and, oh, my God, the speed
at which you hit that shablam,
I was like, oh!
It was so good.
- This is a bodysuit
and some thigh-high boots.
Anywhere we go from here
is gonna be a plus for me,
because there were
four bodysuits
that were embellished tonight
on this stage.
- Consider it burnt.
[all laugh]
- Up next, Thorgy Thor.
- Hi, guys.
- You look amazing.
I love this jumpsuit.
It's so chic and beautiful.
- It's very Halston, Liza.
It's gorgeous.
- And a Phyllis Diller wig.
- I had never heard "Sissy
That Walk" played on the violin.
- [laughs]
- That was incredible.
- It's absolutely amazing
to see you marry
classical music and drag.
- But at the same time,
you seemed a little bashful,
kind of like, well...
And I want to see you,
like, own it more.
Like, I want to see
your fierceness a little more
'cause I know
that you have it in you.
- All right. Thank you
for that challenge.
- Up next, Aja.
You look like a model.
- Did you stone
those tights?
- [laughs]
- I like the many reveals.
I thought it was beautiful,
and it was just
really good drag.
- Aja, I remember being
very frustrated in Season 9
because I felt like I wasn't
getting enough of you.
You raised the bar today,
and then
you jumped off of it.
- Aah!
- You really brought it.
I'm so into vogueing
right now,
so that gave me life,
and that jump,
it was just insane.
- This is what I was waiting for
all of Season 9.
- What's changed?
- I don't give a fuck
what anybody thinks about me.
This is me, and if somebody
has a problem with it,
then that's a you problem
and not a me problem.
- That's right.
You just jump on their ass.
[all laugh]
Thank you, Aja.
All right, next up,
BenDeLaCreme.
- Hi.
- You're so beautiful.
- I know, right?
[all laugh]
- You look stunning
head to toe.
The little fascinator, the
jewelry, the color you chose,
and then you give us comedy
when you did the Ukrainian
nesting dolls of bras
that kept coming.
I was waiting
for one of Gorbachev.
- I think
you're just the tits.
I do.
You know, there are
certain queens come up here
and you go, I cannot wait
to see what they do.
You're one of them.
- Thank you.
Tch, tch.
- Up next, Chi Chi DeVayne.
- Hey, y'all.
- You look beautiful.
Your face looks beautiful,
but all I kept doing
was looking at the shoes.
You have to have
some kind of a heel,
because it immediately
crunches you.
- I have to agree
with Michelle.
Those shoes were killing me.
I know you have to have
a certain kind of shoe
to do what you were doing.
- Yeah.
- But I've seen
you do acrobatics.
- In heels.
- Yeah, girl.
- And I could've just easily
just put on a six-inch heel
and still
worked something out.
It was just a bad decision.
- I was not in love
with the hair.
I felt like
it was getting in the way
of the performance a lot.
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- I think
for the performance,
you gotta amp it up
a little bit.
- It was almost like
down here
when the rest of the girls
were taking it up there.
And I know that
you have what it takes,
so I want you
to push it there.
- Up next,
Morgan McMichaels.
- Finally I get to get judged by
the notorious Michelle Visage.
- Notorious, yes, darling.
You look amazing.
Out of the four
spangled bodysuits,
yours is above and beyond
my favorite.
- I mean, the shoulder details,
all of the embellishment,
the colors, the iridescence.
Really well done.
- Thank you.
- But when
you were performing,
I felt like your nerves got
a little bit too good of you.
Because I found you
almost doing the entire thing
over to the girls.
- Um, I had never recorded
a track before,
so I was shitting it
a little.
- I get to see you
in Palm Springs all the time,
and nobody owns a room
like Morgan McMichaels.
It's like everybody
in the club disappears
and I see is you because
you're in charge of me.
- I charge for that.
[all laugh]
- So any self doubt,
knock it off,
because anything less than 100
is not good enough.
- You heard it here.
Don't take less than 100.
[all laugh]
Thank you, ladies.
Based on
the judges' critiques,
I've made some decisions.
Aja,
BenDeLaCreme...
You are the top two All Stars
of the week.
Con-drag-ulations.
You've each won airfare
and a five-night stay
at the Grand Resort Hotel
and Spa in Fort Lauderdale.
Clothing optional.
- Perfect.
[all laugh]
- Shangela,
Thorgy Thor...
You are safe.
That means Chi Chi DeVayne
and Morgan McMichaels,
you are in the bottom two.
- Oh, shit.
First episode,
in the bottom.
I've worked so hard
to be here on "All Stars,"
and I do not want to go home,
like, at all.
Like...
Oh, God.
- Aja and BenDeLaCreme,
each of you needs to decide
which of the bottom two
you will eliminate
if you win the lip sync.
So while you queens
deliberate in the workroom,
the judges and I will watch
Vanessa and Pork Chop
lip sync for their lives.
[all laugh]
You may leave the stage.
Coming up...
- I really wish you would
have gave Morgan--
- Yeah.
- Like 1,000%.
I'm about
to ruin somebody life.
- I know that you're capable
of stronger work
than you did tonight.
- Yeah.
- But sometimes you're done.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Whew.
Thank you.
- This is "All Stars."
The lip sync for your legacy
rules are in effect,
and we have to eliminate
one of these queens already,
and I don't think anyone's
really ready for it.
- Well, first,
congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
- Cheers, top two.
- It feels insane because
I never was even in the top.
In my season, like,
I never went past safe.
- You're only gonna get it once,
so enjoy it.
- Fuck off.
[laughs]
- You're in a horrible position
right now, you guys.
- I mean,
it's not great, right?
Like, this is the worst
double-edged sword.
It is really exciting
to win this challenge.
However,
I wanna judge fairly,
and playing fair
does not involve eliminations
that you think are just
gonna help you personally.
This sucks.
- You have to pick somebody.
- We have to because it's like
we'll never get anywhere
if we're just like
hugging each other.
Girl, I'm okay
with sending people home
because
it's a part of the gig.
We signed up for it.
- Just think of it
as like a business decision.
- So as this goes on,
are you guys gonna go on,
like, the performance that day,
the performance
on the show overall?
- It should be
a combination.
- I'd like to know
if we all have any system
or code in place
for how we would like
to make our decisions
from this night on.
Are we going off
the judges' critiques?
Like, they sort of came
to a little bit
of a consensus last season.
- Okay.
So Miss DeLa apparently
is suffering from
the short-term memory loss.
Did you see "All Stars 2?"
The whole group consensus thing
didn't work out.
Yes, we would all love
to be fair,
and I think
we should be fair.
I will respect
the choice you make,
and you should do
the same for me.
- Underlying, we agree with
the judges most of the time.
- Yes.
- No.
- I think everything
has to come into play.
We should look at
the whole picture.
- As of now,
the elimination strategy
is definitely
a free-for-all.
Who knows
what's gonna happen?
- Can we all agree
that if one of us
lets the other borrow their
gross rhinestone tank top,
that we won't save them?
- Aah!
[all laugh]
- I would like to take a moment
with Morgan and Chi Chi.
- If that's okay with y'all.
- Yeah, that's cool.
- Unless y'all wanna fight.
If y'all wanna fight,
we'll fight.
- All right.
- Hi, how are you?
- It is what it is.
- Yeah.
- Somebody gotta go home first,
you know what I mean?
When it all boils down to it,
I fucked up,
but I don't want you
to feel like I'm giving up.
I've always been a fighter.
I've fought my whole life.
I fought to get here.
- I do think you're
a super fierce competitor,
and I know
that you're capable
of stronger work
than you did tonight.
- Yeah.
- But sometimes you're done,
and that's okay,
you know what I mean?
Because you have a full career
ahead of you no matter what.
- I don't want to go home
because I feel like I still
have something to prove,
but I'm really not counting
on DeLa to have my back.
- I haven't been on "Drag Race"
since 2010.
I've wanted this
for so long
because I have
so much more to give
and so much more to show,
and now the chance
that I might be going home,
that's the kick in the tits.
- This is the T.
You're such a bitch.
Like, you could literally
point at someone
and make them feel like
they're gonna fucking die.
But I really wish you would
have gave Morgan, like, 1,000%.
- The reason why
I was reserved
was because it was something
that I had recorded
and done myself.
- I've seen Morgan perform
several times.
I've had Morgan
force-feed me vodka in a bar.
I know she can give me
so much more than that.
- Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
- ♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe
let your whole body talk ♪
♪ Cover girl
- Girl, I just want you to know
whatever decision you make,
I am not mad about it.
It is what it is.
- My fear is not really
sending anybody home
because I don't really have
a problem doing that.
- Yeah.
- It's more so, like,
making the right decision
and knowing, like,
who really fell
and who fell the hardest.
I have to think about this
really hard
because I'm about
to ruin somebody's life.
Do I go with the girl
who was nervous
and give her another chance,
or do I go with the girl
who didn't really bring it
and give her another chance?
This is gonna be
a tough decision.
I'm gonna go put on
something more see-through
so I can be a ho.
- How are you doing?
- Well, as good as expected,
I suppose.
- I want to talk to you
about something.
- Mm-hmm.
- You were saying that you
would be strategic about--
- Absolutely.
- About possibly
eliminating girls
that you saw
as big competition.
- Uh-huh.
- And it is hard for me
not to think about,
like, if you stay--
- Is that what I'm gonna do?
- Would you knock me out,
you know what I mean?
Like, that's obviously
on my mind.
I can't pretend
that's not there.
- We talk about, oh,
we're family, we're sisters.
That's fine.
We are those things.
- Yeah.
- But like straight-up
honesty,
I would send
the stronger girl home,
and that's just the truth.
I guess you have to look
at how you think.
If you want to go
with what the judges said,
I think that they picked on
her hair and her shoes
and the kind of
all-around appearance,
and they just picked on
my, you know,
lack of effervescence,
you know.
- Yeah.
- It's clear
that DeLa does not agree
with the way
I want to send people home.
She's, you know,
Miss Congeniality.
But if DeLa's making her
decision based on the critiques,
I was not the worst out of
the two of us, so we'll see.
- Vanessa,
you were fantastic,
but I do love a pork chop.
[sighs]
Vanessa...
shantay, you stay.
[applause]
Pork Chop, my dear,
I'm sorry,
but you are lunch.
- [Michelle laughs]
- Silence.
Bring back my All Stars.
And can I get
a side of gravy?
[all laugh]
- I'm feeling a lot of pressure
to set a precedent
for how this competition
is gonna be run.
I feel the responsibility
to the group
for kind of setting the tone
of this whole thing.
- I'm just
following my heart
and following
what the judges say.
That's how I'm gonna
make my decision.
Just because I want
to send somebody home
does not mean
I don't like you
and it means
I don't respect you.
It just means you did bad.
It's nothing personal,
it's just drag.
[RuPaul laughs, bell dings]
[RuPaul laughs]
- Welcome back, ladies.
Two top All Stars
stand before me.
Ladies, this is your chance
to impress me, win $10,000,
and earn the power
to give one
of the bottom queens the chop.
The time has come...
[thunder]
to lip sync...
[echoing]
for your legacy.
Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
- ♪ My anaconda don't,
my anaconda don't
♪ My anaconda don't want none
unless you got buns, hon ♪
- ♪ Boy toy named Troy
used to live in Detroit ♪
♪ Big, big, big money
♪ He was gettin'
some coins ♪
♪ Was in shootouts with the law,
but he live in a palace ♪
♪ Bought me Alexander McQueen,
he was keeping me stylish ♪
♪ Now that's real,
real, real ♪
♪ One in my purse, 'cause
I came dressed to kill ♪
♪ Who wanna go first?
♪ I had them
pushing daffodils ♪
♪ I'm on some dumb shit,
by the way, what he say ♪
♪ He can tell I ain't
missing no meals ♪
♪ Come through and check him
in my automobile ♪
♪ So I pulled up in the Jag,
and I hit him with the jab
♪ Like dun-duh-duh-dun-
dun-duh-duh-dun-dun ♪
- ♪ My anaconda don't,
my anaconda don't ♪
♪ My anaconda don't want none
unless you got buns, hon ♪
- ♪ Oh, my gosh...
- Aja's giving y'all
Nicki Minaj, blblblblbl,
and BenDeLa's giving you
more comedy version
of the "Anaconda."
- ♪ Look at her butt
- Baby,
it's anyone's game here.
- ♪ He love this fat ass,
ha-ha-ha ♪
♪ This one
is for my bitches ♪
♪ With a fat ass
in the -- club ♪
♪ I said, where my fat-ass
big bitches in the club? ♪
♪ The skinny bitches
in the club ♪
♪ Yeah
Ha-ha!
[gasps]
[trilling]
♪ Yeah
♪ I got a big fat ass
Hey!
[cheers and applause]
- All right.
Ladies,
I have made my decision.
BenDeLaCreme,
you're a winner, baby.
[applause]
- Thank you.
I'm the first winner.
I won
my first lip sync ever.
I feel incredible.
Like,
I'm on top of the world.
- And you've earned
a cash tip of $10,000.
- I'll take it.
- [laughs]
- Aja, you are safe.
- Thank you so much.
- Will the bottom two
please step forward?
BenDeLaCreme, with great power
comes great responsibility.
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
- I think you guys are both
super fierce queens,
but Chi Chi,
I know that you know
that you didn't bring your
strongest performance tonight.
Morgan, I think
that you took a risk
and you tried
something new tonight,
and I don't think that
it was a perfect payoff,
and you know that.
And when we as a group
talked about
why we might eliminate somebody
moving forward,
we talked about that we would
not want to make that decision,
pretty much unanimously,
based on knocking somebody
that we saw
as fierce competition
out of the way.
And you were very forthright
in saying
that that is something
that you would do,
and in the interest
of everyone moving forward,
I chose Morgan McMichaels.
- Morgan McMichaels.
- Yes.
- You are and will always be
an All Star.
- Thank you.
- Now sashay away.
- Thank you, guys.
[applause]
- I'm confused by DeLa.
I think she believes that
we're set on a group consensus
of how we're gonna actually
send the girls home,
but nope.
Baby, that's a completely
different TV show.
- Performing my own track,
I think,
was a little,
you know, risqué.
But I think that
it's a little contradictory
that DeLa sent me home,
because I wasn't the worst
out of the two.
But I'm grateful to be here.
Even though
I'm the first to go,
I'm still part of a legacy,
so I'm excited about that.
If I had to say anything--
[bell rings]
Oh, shit.
- Blessed be, kitty girl.
Don't be scared.
I got your back.
[evil laugh]
- I don't know
what that means.
Like, seriously though,
does anyone want
to tell a bitch? No?
- Next time on
"All Stars..."
You'll be performing
our very own VH1 Divas Live.
[cheering]
- Five, six--
Kennedy, where you at?
- I got lost.
- You can't let your backup
dancers upstage you.
- 'Cause I'm coming for you
back here, baby.
- Ooh.
- You didn't know the words,
and if you did,
then you missed them.
- Okay.
- I'm being set up to fail.
- Don't ever sleep
on Chi Chi DeVayne, boo.
- I was in character
the entire time.
It's stupid.
- [chuckles] Girl...