- [RuPaul] Previously
on All Stars...
Each week the winner
will eliminate
one of her fellow queens.
- How do you feel about
the whole elimination set up?
- I'm just gonna send
the bitch home
that I think is the strongest.
- [RuPaul] Welcome to "RuPaul's
All Star Variety Show".
Aja.
- You really brought it.
That jump, it was just insane.
- [RuPaul]
BenDeLaCreme.
- You look stunning,
head to toe,
and then you give us comedy.
- [RuPaul]
Morgan McMichaels.
- Any self doubt,
knock it off.
Because anything less than
a hundred is not good enough.
- [RuPaul]
Chi Chi DeVayne.
- All I kept doing was
looking at the shoe.
It was almost like down here,
when the rest of the girls
were taking it up there.
- BenDeLaCreme,
you're a winner, baby.
- Thank you.
- Which queen have you
chosen to get the chop?
- When we, as a group,
talked about why we might
eliminate somebody
moving forward,
we talked about that we would
not want to make that decision,
pretty much unanimously,
based on knocking somebody
that we saw as fierce
competition out of the way.
And that is something
that you would do,
so I chose Morgan McMichaels.
- I think DeLa believes that
we're set on a group consensus.
Baby, that's a completely
different TV show.
- Morgan McMichaels,
sashay away.
- Oh, my goodness.
- Bitch.
- Somebody really fierce,
Morgan McMichaels,
has sashayed away.
Next week it could be me.
It could be Shangela.
It's probably Chi Chi.
- "Keep rocking and
slay fabulous."
- Ben, how shitty
do you feel?
- Really shitty.
It's just like these
are impossible decisions.
The reality of what this
competition is gonna feel like
is really sinking in.
I don't want it to be up
to me who goes home.
This sucks.
- Ugh. Wake up, bitch.
You had to make a decision.
Nobody envied you,
but you made it, move forward.
- But you got $10,000, girl.
Halleloo.
- Congratulations.
- But it's like not winning.
It's like--it feels
really bad.
- Mama, girl, oh.
Ms. BenDeLa is giving
y'all you boo-hoo fish
over here at the mirror.
Girl, she sent Morgan home
because Morgan was saying,
"Oh, let's get rid of
the strong competition",
and BenDeLa's a
strong competitor.
That's the reason
she sent her home.
Miss DeLa is playing the game
just like the rest of us.
- Well, I just want you
to know that
you didn't make
the wrong decision,
and I'm just gonna try
to rock it out for you, baby.
- Spritz, spritz, bish.
- So here's to Morgan,
everybody.
- Here's to Morgan.
- So if you, Miss Thing,
had won that lip sync,
what is in your titty?
- I chose, uh, Chi Chi.
- Oh, there it is.
- It's uncomfortable because
Chi Chi's right there.
- It was really just based on
the judges giving her a harder,
like, critique for everything.
- Really?
Okay.
Well, trust me, don't--don't--
don't--don't--don't ever sleep
on Chi Chi DeVayne, boo, because
I got something for that ass.
- So Chi Chi, you're taking
Aja out next time?
- Let's get the fuck
out of this!
- I'm getting all
these body suits
and I'm gonna go burn them.
I'm thankful that I wasn't
in the bottom two
this first challenge,
and so my goal now
is to try to get
in that top two.
Live to fight another day.
- Yes, we do.
- I'm coming at this like
"Game of Thrones," okay?
I am the Daenerys Targaryen
of drag.
Shangela Stormborn.
Baby, I'm the mother of dragons,
I'm the breaker of chains.
I'm coming for the crown.
[chuckles]
Y'all, give me some powder
'cause I feel sweaty. Oh!
- [RuPaul] The winner of
"RuPaul's Drag Race All Stars"
receives a one-year supply
of Anastasia
Beverly Hills cosmetics,
a coveted spot in the
Drag Race Hall of Fame,
and a cash prize of $100,000.
With extra-special guest
judges Todrick Hall
and Vanessa Williams.
- ♪ RuPaul's Drag Race
- ♪ May the best woman
best woman, win ♪
- We survived.
- Ahh!
- We made it!
- We did it!
- Good mernt'ing!
It is a new day, honey, yes.
Ha-ha!
- After last week,
I just think, bitch, the competition
has really turned, um--
- Everybody came to play.
The variety show was,
I thought, amazing.
- Yeah.
- I had no idea who was
gonna be in the bottom.
- I thought about it
and actually there were
other people that didn't
show as much talent.
- Do you have any opinions,
if you want to share them?
- Milk.
- Oh, she done shook
the table, honey.
[laughs]
- I just felt like it really
wasn't much talent there
besides that it was
your original song.
- Oh, God.
My performance was killer,
and the original song
is gonna become a bigger hit
than "Supermodel."
I thought I had a wonderful
mix of talents in there.
- Milk, your talent
can't be Velcro.
- I would've loved to come on
and skate for all y'all,
but ice is hard to come by.
[sirens]
- Whoa!
- She done already
done had herses.
- Hey, All Stars.
- Hi!
- Hey!
- My first name ain't Baby,
so call me Miss Ross
and get a new attitude
'cause a she-ro lies in you.
Y'all come back now, you hear?
[laughing]
- Oh, my God.
- Hello, hello, hello, ladies.
- Hi!
- All Stars, I have
some exciting news.
- Oh!
- For one night only, we're
bringing back some classic TV
as we throw our
very own "VH1 Divas Live".
[cheering]
- And this year, get this,
it's a salute to Mama Ru.
[cheering]
- I mean, it's really
just an honor
to be nominated by yourself.
[laughing]
- You'll be performing
some of my greatest hits
in a lip sync extravaganza.
- Whoo!
- Each of you will portray
a different iconic diva.
So, Milk,
you'll be Celine Dion.
- Yes!
- Kennedy,
you'll be Janet Jackson.
- Oh!
- Come on, Janet.
- Aja, you'll be
Amy Winehouse.
- Yes!
- Chi Chi, you'll be
Miss Patti LaBelle.
- Ooh!
- Trixie, you'll
be Dolly Parton.
- Oh!
- Stretch, what a stretch.
- Shangela, you'll be
the elusive chanteuse--
- Oh, yes.
- Mariah Carey.
- Darling.
Darling.
[laughs]
- Thorgy, you shall
be Stevie Nicks.
- Yes!
- Thorgy.
- Come on, Witchy Woman.
- BenDeLaCreme,
you'll be Dame Julie Andrews.
- Oh, yes.
- And last but not least BeBe,
you shall be
Miss Diana Ross.
- All right, Mother.
- #AllStars3.
Ladies, in a moment,
you'll be rehearsing
with the ridiculously
talented Todrick Hall.
[cheering]
- And tomorrow on
the main stage, we'll be joined
by one of my all time
favorite divas...
Vanessa Williams.
[cheering]
- Oh, my God.
- All right, Mother,
all right.
- And for this week's runway,
the category is Ru-demption.
We're giving you
a chance to do over
your most infamous Drag Race
fashion fails.
- Oh.
- I've got a lot of those.
- Uh-huh.
- Gentlemen, start your engines,
and may the best All Star win.
- Thank you, Ru!
- Love you, Mother.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to "VH1 Divas Live".
- There's different levels of
lip sync artistry in the room.
Some people are
professional lip syncers.
- ♪ I don't care
if people stare ♪
- Some people can actually
do their character better.
So it's hard to say
what's really gonna happen.
- All of these sections really
give us a huge chance to shine.
- Yeah.
- Like the cards aren't stacked
by what we have been given.
- Well, I feel like
everybody's diva
is a representative of
a little bit of them.
- Stevie Nicks could not be
more perfect for me,
however, when have you ever
seen Stevie Nicks do something
where some gay is in
the front row of her show
going like, "Work, Stevie.
You better fucking work!"
No. That's not Stevie.
I'm lucky that
I have less lyrics,
however, I think mine
was less funny.
It's really not fair.
There is no way,
because I'm Stevie,
I'm ever gonna win this.
And I come right after you,
and you literally are
set up to just win.
- Oh, no.
- Just face it, girl.
- Mine--let me tell you--no.
- All right.
- Let me tell you though.
- If you're gonna
argue that, you're crazy.
- I could take Amy Winehouse--
- Oh, I know.
- Dolly, and
make them all funny.
- I'm trying not to be like
a conspiracy theorist
because that's what
I was in Season 8.
It's just hard because I feel
like I'm being set up to fail.
- I love my part.
- Okay.
- When it comes to impersonating
Celine, I am feeling good.
These other girls will have
a tough act to follow.
- What are you wearing?
- I'm wearing her Met Gala
outfit from this past year,
which is like a
silver leotard
with like a Versace dress
over top of it.
- Do you think everybody's
gonna recognize that?
Like I don't know how
iconic that was
because I didn't pay attention.
- I--I can't think of
anything she wears
except that backward suit.
- The reason I want to choose
the Met Gala thing was
because this year her
fashion star is on the rise.
- Girl, nobody knows what
Celine wore to the Met Gala.
That's such a weird choice.
A really weird choice.
- I did this one event where
I performed Celine in front of--
- Oh, you've done Celine before?
- Yeah. In front of the guy
that was the event planner
for her wedding.
And so as soon as he saw
me perform it, he was like,
"Oh, my God, that
is the best Celine."
- Well, good luck, because
I think Ariana Grande
does the best Celine, but
you can be a close second.
Ahh!
Honey, the big and Milky,
she is mighty confident, Mama,
because the friend of a friend
of a friend who was a friend
of a friend of a friend
of Celine's had told her
it was lovely, girl.
Oh, she's about to throw the
diamond into the ocean, honey.
She's about to give it to y'all.
Well, all right.
- Coming up...
- Five, six, Kennedy,
where you at?
- I got lost.
- Shangela is pissing me off,
pissing Todrick off,
practically
pissing off everyone.
- Ah!
Okay.
[RuPaul laughing]
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Hi!
- Our maxi challenge this week
is to perform in our very own
version of "VH1's Divas Live".
It's time to rehearse
with Todrick Hall.
I hope the other girls
are ready, 'cause I am.
- How y'all doing?
- Good.
- We about to bring it with the
diva's--oh, Lord, here we go.
[laughter]
- She's already
in full character.
- Bitch, excuse me?
Are you ready?
- I'm sorry, darling.
I'm a method actress, okay?
I'm giving y'all
very Meryl Streep
in this moment.
- This is the "Divas" episode,
and you guys are gonna be
impersonating some of the
most iconic,
legendary performers
of all time,
so we definitely want
to represent them well.
Are you guys ready?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Well, we're gonna
start with Kennedy,
and everybody else
please have a seat.
Okay. You're gonna go
five, four, three,
you just bend
your leg, two, walk.
Five, four, three, two.
- Do I step my leg back out?
- Yeah, let me see it.
Five, six, seven, eight.
And five, four, three...
- Kennedy Davenport is known
for being a fierce queen
that can dance the house down,
but right now
the house is still up.
No chance of it
even shattering.
Don't need insurance because
it's not gonna come down.
And da, da, three, four,
and five.
Okay.
Are you gonna be able
to get that?
- I'll get it.
You have to understand
I am a dancer,
but I freestyle everything.
I don't choreograph anything, so
it's just tough on me right now.
- Can we move on?
- Yeah.
- Let's go slow.
Five, six, seven, eight.
And one, two, three, four--
- I'm lost.
- Kennedy, where you at?
- I got lost.
- Is this gonna be
too complicated?
- I mean, I can get it, but
I'm having trouble right now.
- Are you telling me
you're giving up already?
- Well, don't ask me--
I'm gonna give you my honest--
give you my honest answer.
- I just wanted--I--I want
you to say "Yes, I can get it."
- I can get it.
- Okay.
- Right now it's
not registering.
- Okay.
Tomorrow, no matter what,
you can't let your back-up
dancers upstage you.
- 'Cause I'm coming
for you back here, baby.
- Ooh!
- We'll be ready.
Okay, Thorgy Thor.
- I want to win
a challenge
'cause I never won one
on Season 8.
Fuck you, Bob.
- I am not gonna give you
that much choreography.
We're gonna collaborate.
So I want to know
if there are any things
that you specifically want to do
or that you had in mind to do?
- Sure.
♪ Tell me one thing, do you
like where you're going ♪
♪ I said who do you think
you are? ♪
- Okay.
Um, who is Stevie Nicks
to you?
- Stevie Nicks is one of
my biggest inspirational divas
throughout my entire life.
I love her.
The stereotype is
that she's this witch,
but she actually
is not a witch.
She's just an eccentric Gemini.
- Girl, if you're gonna bring
it, you have to bring it.
With the rumor that Stevie's
a witch, you can do so much.
Like, bitch, I would've came
out with a pot, a broom.
I would've came out like,
with a--with a wand,
like whoo! Whoo!
- So I think we
should incorporate
some of the stuff that
you're naturally doing
and make it choreography.
So when it gets
to the chorus, can you,
like, lean this way
a little bit?
- She's not a very, like,
active, acrobatic, you know.
- Person, yeah.
I just wanna see--
- She's just so strong.
There's usually a wind machine
underneath her or something.
- Yeah. We gave our
wind machine to Beyonce,
so we're not gonna
have that today.
- Oops.
- But we will pretend that
the wind machine is here.
Thorgy is such a Stevie Nicks
purist that he kept saying,
"Stevie Nicks doesn't
really do this.
She doesn't really dance."
And I think that's great to
know your character so well,
but what can you do to make
a drag version of Stevie Nicks?
- She's at a microphone
and she's--
it's all internal and like...
- Yeah.
But I think that it's a kind
of a touchy situation,
because I don't want you
to get lost in the shuffle.
- Stevie Nicks is difficult
to do because
next to divas like Diana Ross
and Patti LaBelle
and Janet Jackson,
she is not like, work,
you know what I mean?
It just doesn't feel fair.
Because it's gonna seem a
little too subdued, right?
- What, you mean, like levels?
What are you doing--
- When I'm spinning
like, I don't--
It's incredibly important
to stand out amongst
all these girls because
we're all so talented,
but how do you stand out
performing as Stevie Nicks?
That's my problem.
- All right. Let's bring up
Ms. Mariah Carey.
- She is on another level today.
Oh, my God.
Shangela doing her whole
Mariah fantasy...
Girl, she's pissing me off,
she's pissing Todrick off,
practically
pissing off everyone.
- Ah!
Okay.
Jealousy is a killer
in this industry, Mama.
- Let's play the music--
- Okay.
- --and hear what
Mariah's gonna do.
- Is it in my ear?
Hold on, baby.
- Oh, Lord.
- Ew.
I cannot--I cannot with this.
- Oh, my God, the girls
are so hateful this season.
Why they so hateful?
[laughs]
- Okay, I'm ready.
- The girls are shading me.
They're like, oh, she really
thinks she is the diva.
And some are joking,
but some are serious.
- You're gonna cover her up
with the fans.
- Okay.
- So everybody take a fan.
- Oh!
- Whoo!
- Sister.
Oh, girl, the big and
Milky, honey, oh, girl.
She's throwing shade and
then she plays it off
that she's just trying to be
loose and fun with the girls.
She's not being loose and fun.
Honey, she thinks she's better
than everyone in this room.
- And then she's
gonna walk forward.
I'm not gonna be here
to hold your hand.
- I'm sorry.
I saw the hand.
- You might have to walk
on your own.
- I'm sorry.
I saw the hand.
- Shangela, step down from your
high horse and just chill.
- All right. Ms. Ross?
- Yes.
- It's your time, darling.
- Thank you.
- I don't want to pressure you,
but you do know that Diana Ross
is RuPaul's, like,
diva of all time?
This is a very Bianca Del Rio/
Judge Judy situation--
- I know.
- --but to the umpteenth power.
You understand that?
- Yeah.
- And if you don't
fully embody Diana Ross,
he's gonna for sure know.
- Okay, Todrick, just keep
adding that pressure on.
No, no, no.
I really--I feel--I'm excited.
I'm excited that I get
to play the real diva.
- Just show me
what you would do.
Just take the stage, own it.
- BeBe does nothing.
Nothing.
Just walks out as Diana Ross,
but that's what BeBe does.
It's who BeBe is.
Okay. Okay.
- Diana is known to steal
the party, steal the show,
and this show
was far from stolen.
- That's great.
I love it.
So we're gonna do
you, BenDeLaCreme.
This is the thing,
the juxtaposition of you
rapping this as Julie Andrews
is what makes this funny,
so it has to be
a mixture of swag
and then some
pixie dust, okay?
Like, dun da da,
body like boom.
- Like that kind of thing?
- But with a little bit
more swag juice in it, okay?
- Okay.
- So you're gonna take
three steps, one--
- One, two, three.
- One, two, three, and four,
and you're gonna touch
your vagina with
one hand at a time.
- On four.
- Yeah.
Can I see you all do that?
Three and four.
And you gotta make
sure you go three and four.
Two, three--
- Okay, sorry.
- DeLa, there's a
lot of footwork going on
that is not the footwork
that we need.
I'm very, very worried.
Can she handle it?
I don't damn know.
I know you're coming off of
a good win, but I can't express
to you enough that it has to,
has to, has to be, like,
swag, it has to be the lyrics,
it has to be still in character.
- I totally hear that.
- If you slip up
one step, you're fucked.
- Yeah.
Todrick stares straight into
your soul
with those crazy,
honey-colored eyes,
and finds whatever you're
most insecure about,
and is like, don't do it.
He is terrifying.
- Okay. Chi Chi DeVayne.
And we're also gonna
have Dolly Parton
and Celine Dion in this part.
- Okay.
Todrick is randomly
choosing divas
to be part of other
divas' solo numbers,
and I noticed that
he wasn't choosing me.
- And BeBe should be in this.
- So I was like, this is
my chance to stand out.
- Shangela should be in this,
and Kennedy should be in it.
- Todrick?
- Yes.
- I haven't been
part of anything.
I feel like I'm the only one
who hasn't done anything.
- Come.
- I will seize the day in order
to kick everyone's ass and win.
- Thank you.
I--I love that.
Sure.
- I can tell that Thorgy really
wants to try and do more,
but I'm thinking she should
be focusing more on making
her character bigger,
not necessarily
in being in so
many people's numbers.
- One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, and pose.
Okay.
We can move on to the next girl.
Can I have Trixie?
- Thanks for including me.
- Honestly, I think
the competition
sometimes becomes
too much for Thorgy,
because she really compares
herself to other people,
and then she starts
to pick apart herself.
- Mamacita is in her head.
Good luck, sis.
- [RuPaul] Coming up...
- Watching yourself,
you see things
about yourself that you
may not have realized.
- Yeah, girl.
I didn't know I had
a resting bitch face.
- What?
- [laughs]
- You're gonna get
two good double blinks.
[laughs]
[RuPaul laughing]
- Whoo!
- We are here. Oh!
- Come on, divas.
- Good morning, everybody.
- This week's runway
is Ru-demption, where we get
to remake our worst fashion
faux pas,
and this is gonna be
really interesting
because a lot of these
girls have had some
real ugly fashions,
including myself.
Shangela.
- Yes, baby.
- How you feeling, boo?
- You know what?
I'm less concerned
about the divas thing.
- Uh-huh.
- And more concerned about
the Ru-demption look,
because not only is this a look
that I failed at last time,
but also, Vanessa Williams was
the judge on the episode I got--
- Gag!
- Yeah.
When--of the fail
that I'm doing today.
- So, if you fuck up,
she's gonna--
- Twice in front
of Ms. Vanessa.
- She's gonna see it.
- I was actually a little
disappointed at first
because your number
and Kennedy's number
and Ben's number and
Chi Chi's number--
- Everybody's number?
- --all are, like, super high
energy numbers, and I love--
- Do you think my number
is high energy?
- Girl, you're doing
Amy Winehouse.
You have dancers,
you have two backup dancers.
I live for backup dancers.
- You know, we did
a similar challenge
like this on my season.
We did Glamazonian Airways,
which was a lip sync challenge,
and I did fine then and
wasn't scared,
but there was also like twice
the number of people here,
so I think that
was part of it.
- Well, was the dancing
as intense?
- God, no.
- This dance is--
- Bananas.
- I mean, I wasn't here
for All Stars 2,
but I feel like this dance
seems to me like
the most intense dance that
has been on this competition.
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah.
- I feel like
the Herstory of the World,
they were like truly
lip syncing.
This is like choreography.
- Yeah.
- Do you think they're
gonna be looking
for a full transformation
into the diva?
- Absolutely.
- I think yes.
I think they're looking
for likeness big time.
- Really?
- Absolutely.
Do you remember last season
when they clocked Katya's wig
for not being perfectly
Diana's iconic hair?
- Yeah.
- He went home that episode.
- Trixie, how do you
think you came off
on your season, because--
- I came off as
pretty talentless.
- I disagree.
- I think it's pretty fair.
I never won any challenges,
and I went home twice.
- Shangela, how do you think you
were perceived on your season?
- It was mixed.
I mean, honestly, I would meet
people and they would be like,
"Oh, my God, I love you,
and during your season
"my boyfriend hated you,
but it's so nice to meet you
in person because now
we both love you."
And I'm like, "thank you."
- I get the same thing.
It's like being thrown in a room
with people that you don't know.
- Mm-hmm.
- Somebody's gonna
get on your nerves.
- Yes.
- And then on top of that,
I'm very vocal about my feelings
and how I feel about
a lot of things.
- Yeah.
But I take you different because
I know you and I know, like,
that's a southern way of drag.
Like, the girls get you
together in the room.
Kennedy and I go way back, and
she is straight up not edited,
not filtered, not watered down,
and those lips are
gonna be pressed together
and the eyes are
gonna be clocked,
and you're gonna get
two good double blinks.
I think that also watching
yourself--
- Yeah.
- --you see things
about yourself
that you may not have realized.
- Yeah, girl.
I didn't know I had
a resting bitch face.
- You didn't know?
- No, I did not.
- She didn't know.
Y'all, she didn't know.
- And I was like, bitch,
I was not even looking like--
like that at that time,
but I guess I was.
- Kennedy's just like
a grumpy old man.
She's like a grandpa, like
a grandpa who, you know,
can't hear well,
and is just kind of angry,
but is just your grandpa.
It's your grandpa in a wig.
- How do you guys think
I came off on my season?
- I thought you came off
like quirky, friendly, fun.
- That's exactly who I am.
- I did think you were,
like, jealous of Bob.
- I was the first person to say
he is the funniest person alive.
- You were always like,
"It's the Bob show."
- It's the Bob Show.
- You know what I mean?
Yeah.
- Every second.
There was just no room
for anybody else
because his personality
was so big.
That's what I was so, like,
eye roll about, you know?
- Yeah.
- With that said,
I hope he dies.
I probably was competitive
with Bob in my mind only,
which is what Bob
kept telling me, like,
"Girl, why you
comparing yourself to me?
Like, I'm not trying
to come for you."
I'm like, "I know,
but I'm just as good as you."
I was just so, like,
always in my head.
This is my thing.
It's who I am.
- You was like one of
my top picks.
I was like, damn,
I mean, she is so good.
- Thank you.
- But I also felt that you
just was like so defeated.
- Like within my own self?
- Yes.
- I feel like I'm much more
talented and much better
than people give me credit for,
and I'm always talked over.
- Why do you feel like
people over talk you?
I want to make sure I'm
not doing that to you
because I would hate
to make you feel like--
- Girl, tell her ass
to shut up, you're talking.
- I--I just don't--
- Please do that
to Kennedy
because she over talks
everybody.
- No, I over talk you.
- What?
- I over talk you.
- You should be
the last one to talk.
Shangela, you talk
so goddamn much.
- I do.
- [RuPaul] Coming up...
- ♪ Divas VH1
- ♪ VH1
- It was like
the wonderful
and quizzical blend of
confusion and confidence.
[laughing]
[RuPaul laughing]
- ♪ Cover girl,
put the bass in your walk ♪
♪ Cover girl, put the bass
in your walk ♪
♪ Head to toe, let
your whole body talk ♪
♪ Cover girl
- Welcome to the main stage of
"RuPaul's Drag Race All Stars".
When it comes to divas,
she wrote the book.
Michelle Visage.
- What? Oh, this?
[laughs]
- Go on.
- I really wish I could read.
[laughing]
- Style superstar,
Carson Kressley.
Are you ready for some
All Star Enter-taint-ment?
- Oh, yeah. I thought I
recognized that smell, Ru.
[laughs]
And the incredible Todrick Hall.
Did my divas wipe you out?
- Oh, girl, I can go all night.
- Ooh, okay.
And the forever soul of VH1,
my queen, Vanessa Williams.
Now, what made you come back?
- I can't get enough
of divaliciousness.
[laughs]
- This week we challenged our
All Stars to serve
diva performances in
a lip sync extravaganza,
and on the catwalk,
category
is Ru-demption Runway,
a chance for my girls to do
over past fashion fails.
Gentlemen, start your engine,
and may the best All Star win.
Michelle, I had no idea
they were honoring me.
- I mean, of course.
Who else would they be honoring?
- Okay, shut up.
Here they are.
- ♪ Divas, divas, divas
- RuPaul, I wrote
this for you.
- ♪ They're all coming back
for more ♪
♪ High high heels
on a hardwood floor ♪
♪ Peanut butter
- ♪ Must be jelly
'cause jam don't shake ♪
- ♪ Peanut butter
- ♪ Must be jelly
'cause jam don't shake ♪
- ♪ Peanut peanut
peanut peanut ♪
♪ Peanut peanut
♪ Butter
- Cannot be jam because
the jelly shakes.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Janet Jackson.
- This is about Ru's charisma,
uniqueness, nerve, and
talent, and it's gigantic.
Five, four, three, two.
♪ Charisma, uniqueness
♪ Nerve and talent
♪ Trust and he'll find you
The rebel within you ♪
♪ Let your body tell
the truth ♪
♪ Trust and he'll find you
The rebel within you ♪
♪ Let your body tell
the truth ♪
♪ Uh, uh, uh, uh
Don't you try it, bitch.
Please welcome Amy Winehouse.
- ♪ Oh
♪ Yeah, girl, work
that high and tight ♪
♪ Sophisticated, classy,
day and night ♪
♪ Relax, don't trip
now lay it right ♪
♪ You know you
wear it well ♪
♪ We get looking
so so chic ♪
♪ Break us through, man,
and let me sneak ♪
♪ Afro repping Mozambique
♪ You know you
wear it well ♪
♪ French tip, lip stick
♪ Bring it on
♪ Value show suits,
yo, oh, oh oh ♪
♪ Work it for me,
W-w-work it for me ♪
♪ Yeah, you wear it,
you wear it ♪
♪ You wear it well
Ru, I bet it all on black.
- Why it gotta be black?
- Ladies and gentlemen,
Patti LaBelle.
[RuPaul laughing]
- ♪ Hey, there girl,
walk away ♪
♪ I lose my inhibitions
when you spin ♪
♪ I don't care
if people stare ♪
♪ I brought my booty
and I'm trying to fit in ♪
♪ Don't be jealous of my boogiey,
jealous of my boogiey ♪
♪ You can say that you were not
but I always see you looking ♪
♪ Don't be jealous of my boogiey,
jealous of my boogiey ♪
♪ You can say that
you were not ♪
♪ But I always
see you looking ♪
Ladies and gentlemen,
Dolly Parton.
- Well, howdy, Ru.
It takes a lot of money to look
that cheap, and I should know.
♪ Give me one shot
♪ One shot of adrenaline
♪ Whoo
And to the ones I love, know
that y'all are the reason why.
I dare to live my life,
dare to liberate my mind.
♪ You're running
through my veins ♪
♪ Make me come alive
♪ One, two, three
♪ Give me one shot,
one shot of adrenaline ♪
♪ Adrenaline
♪ Give me one shot,
one shot of adrenaline ♪
♪ Adrenaline
♪ Give me one shot,
one shot ♪
♪ Of adrenaline
Whoo!
Can I get it to go, Ru?
Ladies and gentlemen,
Mariah Carey.
- Oh, God.
- Happy New Year, everybody.
[laughs]
- You made this song number one.
Can I get more of me?
I guess we're going over here.
[singing]
Nope.
Someone's getting fired.
Let's let the audience
sing along.
You sound good.
Cut the track.
RuPaul, I think you know
to get it right
sometimes a diva has
to do things on her own.
♪ I love you
Ta-da.
Still got it.
[laughing]
Ladies and gentlemen,
Stevie Nicks.
♪ Who're you waiting for?
Another savior ♪
♪ Always looking but you
never find, never find ♪
♪ Tell me one thing, do you
like where you're going? ♪
♪ Running all of your lies
♪ I say ooh
♪ Who do you think you are?
♪ I'll tell you
the truth now ♪
♪ All born naked and
the rest is drag ♪
♪ Spin with me
♪ La la la la la
♪ La la la la
la la ♪
♪ All born naked and
the rest is drag ♪
I'm a little dizzy, Ru.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Julie Andrews.
- Hello, Ru,
it's Julie Andrews.
Whenever there's
something I can't face,
I sing with a simple tune.
[laughing]
- ♪ Guess who's back
in the house? ♪
♪ Heels click-clacking about
♪ Fine fresh feminine,
style to eleven and ♪
♪ Divine, so heavenly,
gentlemen sweating ♪
♪ It's time to cross
the board, no doubt ♪
♪ Body like wow, pussy
match to end this drought ♪
♪ Titties so plentiful,
fishy cream Jezebel ♪
♪ Should be criminal
don't make sense ♪
♪ For a bitch
to be this endowed ♪
♪ I've been a bitch, yes,
I love that drama ♪
♪ Fishy, feminine
up and comer ♪
♪ From the Clintons
to the Obamas ♪
♪ I keep it tight now
they call me mother ♪
♪ Shady green bitch
I love that drama ♪
♪ Fishy, feminine
up and comer ♪
♪ From the Clintons
to the Obamas ♪
♪ I keep it tight now
they call me mother ♪
♪ Microphone drop
Good day.
Please welcome Diana Ross.
- Here we go again.
Chapter two,
turn another page.
You know the world
don't have to end
as long as the DJ's
record spins.
[laughs]
♪ This is the main event
Are you ready? ♪
♪ This type of music
gets me to the floor ♪
♪ Faster and faster
exhilarating ♪
♪ Just let the music
make you lose control ♪
♪ This is the main event
I love you, Ru.
I love you.
I mean it.
If you need me, text me.
[laughing]
- ♪ You say that
we inspire ♪
- We inspire!
♪ But when all is
said and done ♪
- Said and done!
♪ You're the brightest,
tallest star of them all ♪
♪ On Divas VH1
- ♪ VH1
- I'll always love you, Ru.
- Whoo!
- [RuPaul] Coming up...
- You are a superstar.
- I love this look.
- You didn't do much.
- Ooh, is that a read?
[RuPaul laughing]
♪ Sexy sexy drag queen
- [RuPaul] Serving
Ru-demption Runway, Milk.
Crazy, sexy, cool, Season 6,
and here's the remix.
- [Carson] Apparently
it's skim Milk.
- [RuPaul] Yes.
- [Milk] With the original,
the judges wanted
to see glamorous Milk,
and so I want to shove it
in the judges' face,
what they thought
I could never do.
- [RuPaul] I think she's pinning
all of her hopes
on this outfit.
Aja.
Fairy tale princess disaster,
Season 9, and this is the remix.
- [Michelle] Ahh.
- [RuPaul] You're beautiful.
- [Aja] This look is probably
where I felt the ugliest
and the lowest on Season 9,
and that's when the Aja
transformation truly began.
- [RuPaul]
Finally some disaster relief.
Thank you, FEMA.
Chi Chi DeVayne.
Neon realness, Season 8.
- [Carson]
It's a Janet Jackson Pollack.
[laughing]
- [Chi Chi] I got so many
harsh critiques about
not wearing pads or boobs,
so I got to show Michelle that
I can suck my waist in
and wear big boobs
and do all that too.
- [RuPaul]
Why it gotta be black light?
I love it.
- [RuPaul] Trixie Mattel.
The ugliest dress ever,
Season 7, and this is the remix.
- Whatever happened
to Baby Jane?
That looks like one of hers.
- [Trixie] I know
I'm nailing it because
Vanessa Williams is like...
I don't even know if she knows
that I'm redoing an ugly dress.
So she probably thinks
I'm supposed to be gorgeous,
and she's like "sure,
you're really painting with
all the colors of the wind."
- [RuPaul] You know, this outfit
reminds me I have pots
in the sink
I need to scrub.
Kennedy.
Death becomes her, Season 7.
Oh, honey, rigor mortis
done set in.
- Yes.
- Ooh.
- What?
Uh-oh, oh!
- [Carson] You know, she's
always so hot and cold with me.
- [Vanessa] She is!
- [Kennedy] So it's the
same story from Season 7,
a night after hooking.
Tre threw me in the fire,
but in the process,
I was crystallized.
- [Carson] You know, if you
can't beat them--
- [Michelle] Stone them.
- [Carson] Stone them.
[laughs]
- [RuPaul] Thorgy Thor.
Neon queen realness, Season 8.
- [Vanessa] All of a sudden
I'm craving a salad.
[laughs]
- [Thorgy] I live for
what I wore,
but I feel like that
was the child,
and this is like the mother.
- [Carson] I've heard of hammer
toe, but never hammer head.
- Yes.
[laughing]
- [RuPaul] Reclaiming my lime.
Reclaiming my lime.
BenDeLaCreme.
Dripping in jewels, Season 6.
Oh, my God,
it's Jewelry Andrews.
[laughing]
- [BenDeLaCreme] I feel
stunning in this outfit.
Anybody who says that
I am not currently
dripping in jewels is
just a flat-out liar.
- [Vanessa] Does the rug match
the beaded curtain?
- [Carson] That's what you
call vajazzled.
- Yes!
- [RuPaul] BeBe Zahara Benet.
Season 1 entrance look.
- [Todrick] Ooh!
- [Michelle] I love a power
bottom suit.
- Yes.
- [BeBe] Season 1 I was giving
you very secretary, honey.
But now, she actually owns
the company.
Very Wilhelmina Slater,
very that.
- [RuPaul] She serves at
the President's pleather.
[laughing]
- Oh, my God.
Shangela.
Christmas eleganza, Season 3.
Wow.
- Fantastic.
- [Shangela] First of all,
Ms. Vanessa ain't aged
or moved since Season 3.
Numero dos, to see the smile,
is just total validation
for this moment.
- [Carson] We're gonna get you
out of there, Shangela, hold on.
[laughs]
- [RuPaul]
Shangela, if you can hear me,
there's only 30 more seconds of
oxygen left in there.
- Good luck!
- [RuPaul] Coming up...
- She could have worked
a little harder.
- It's a tiny bit basic.
- You didn't know the words.
If you did,
then you missed them.
[RuPaul laughing]
- Welcome, ladies.
Based on your performance
in the lip sync extravaganza,
and your Ru-demption
Runway look,
I've made some decisions.
Now, when I call your name,
please step forward.
Shangela, BenDeLaCreme,
BeBe Zahara Benet.
You are the top three this week.
- All right.
- Chi Chi DeVayne,
Thorgy Thor,
Kennedy Davenport.
You are the bottom
three of the week.
Aja, Milk, Trixie Mattel,
you are safe.
Please step to
the back of the stage.
- Now it's time for
the Judges' critiques,
starting with Kennedy.
- I liked the runway look.
I loved the covered face,
and then this look, the makeup,
the contact lenses, the white
lip, I think it's really fun.
- But I'm afraid
with your performance,
you didn't know the words.
And if you did,
then you missed them.
And I didn't get any
Janet Jackson,
I got all Kennedy.
- I wasn't getting it in
the moves, I wasn't getting it
in the makeup, I wasn't
getting it in the wig.
- I do know Sean Cheeseman
who did the original "Control"
and "Rhythm Nation," 'cause
he left me to do Janet, so--
[laughing]
- Janet is a very specific kind
of move, very kind of staccato.
You could've worked
a little harder
in terms of making
it really crisp.
- With that being said,
I gave you
the most difficult choreography
out of everybody that was here,
and that should
be accounted for.
- Up next, Chi Chi DeVayne.
- When I first saw
you come out,
I knew instantly that
you were Patti LaBelle.
- Chi Chi, I was sold
on your Patti.
You got the flicks,
which is very Patti.
- And tonight on the runway
you have your neon challenge.
- Mm-hmm.
- Which for you and I, we--
- Yeah.
- Yes.
And you look
beautiful tonight.
I don't think you need
that coat though.
Yes, girl, look.
We get to see
your shape, beautiful.
- But it's a tiny bit basic.
Like, even with the hair,
the makeup,
like, it just needs
a little tweak.
- Can I just say, I just
loved you in "Eraser".
- Oh, wow.
- Oh, my God.
- Thank you.
- "Eraser", baby.
"Eraser".
- Next up, Shangela.
- I love this look.
The original look was
like Beyonce when she was
in Destiny's Child and sometimes
wore questionable outfits.
And then when she was Beyonce,
that's you right now.
You're slaying.
And I love that you
captured the Mariah
that we know and love,
which is a wonderful
and quizzical blend of
confusion and confidence.
[laughing]
- It's just so awesome to watch
you work from beginning to end.
From the moment you walked out
onto the stage yesterday,
you were in character.
Sometimes a little too
in character,
but I loved the fact that
you owned the role
and elevated the movements
that I gave you.
- This is a full circle moment,
because Vanessa judged
Shangela before.
- Yes, I did, and you've
come a long way
from when I saw you years ago.
You are a superstar.
- Thank you, Ms. Williams.
- Shangela, are you
a Mariah fan?
- I'm a huge Mariah fan,
and I hope when she meets me,
she won't know me.
[laughing]
- Up next, Thorgy Thor.
- Tonight on the runway,
I like this a lot
better than the one
on your season,
but it feels disjointed.
The wedge and the eyebrows
seem like one part,
and the dress feels
like a different part.
And then tonight
the challenge was to embody
and become these diva women.
- Okay.
- And I felt like I was looking
at Thorgy with a blonde wig on.
- Oh.
- Yeah. I got the same thing
that Michelle did.
I think it's about those
visual cues, and you gave us
that with the hat
and the costuming,
but the make-up
wasn't as Stevie.
It's a fine line to still
put yourself in it,
but also make somebody
that does know you
know who you're impersonating.
So that was a miss for me.
- I think Stevie Nicks was a
hard diva to do because it's--
- I'm trying to keep my mouth
shut because I don't--
I don't want
to make any excuses.
- Yeah, it's clearly not what--
- But it's not a gay--
it's not like a gay icon.
- Stevie Nicks is
definitely a gay icon.
- The words came out
of my mouth,
and I was like,
she is to me.
I thought I did a
really good job.
I'm a little surprised
I'm the bottom, to be honest.
- You are all All Stars.
Honestly, we have to pick up
on the slightest infraction
on the challenge,
do you know what I mean?
All right, thanks Thorgy.
Up next, BenDeLaCreme.
Jazz hot.
- I gave you probably the most
difficult challenge because
you had to be Julie Andrews, but
you also had to have swagger,
but then you also
had to know
every single one
of these lyrics.
And I think that you just
knocked it out of the park.
- How do you solve a problem
like "Call Me Mother,"
because I don't even
know the lyrics.
True story. It took me
five days to record that song.
- Really?
- To get the lyrics right?
- Yep.
- And it terms of the outfit,
you're a dream in pink.
Very artistic
in the 1930s, art deco.
- These are actually the
earrings that were given to us
for that challenge
in Season 6.
- I've been looking for those.
[laughing]
- Cameroon!
- Hello, Mother.
- BeBe Zahara Benet, have you
met the first lady of Cameroon?
- I have not met her,
but she's heard of me, honey.
[laughing]
- Baby, you were Diana Ross.
It was amazing to me.
And here's the key
that everybody
should look at for that.
You didn't do much
to embody Diana.
- There wasn't a lot to do.
There weren't a lot of lyrics,
but it was just
a couple of those gestures,
the wardrobe.
- And you even got
the hair bounce, girl.
- It was a real homerun.
- And then with this runway
look, I just love it.
This was like BeBe Priestly,
"Devil Wears Prada,"
the black version.
- Can we just say the black
version of "Devil Wears Prada"
is Wilhelmina Slater?
Hello? Thank you very much.
- Thank you, ladies.
Based on the judges critiques,
I've made some decisions.
Shangela, BenDeLaCreme,
condragulations,
you are the top two
All Stars of the week.
- Yes.
- You've each won a $1,000 gift
card from Sparkles Rhinestones,
and a $1,000 gift card
from Fierce Queen Heels.
BeBe Zahara Benet.
- Yes, Mother.
- Chi Chi DeVayne...
You are safe.
That means, Kennedy Davenport
and Thorgy Thor,
you are in the bottom two.
Shangela, BenDeLa,
each of you needs to decide
which of the bottom queens
you will eliminate
if you win the lip sync.
So while you and the queens
deliberate in the workroom,
the judges and I will play
a friendly game of strip poker.
Thank you, ladies.
You may leave the stage.
Coming up...
- My mind's not made up.
I want to know is Thorgy
going to be
a reliable strong ally for me.
If I throw you a bone,
I'm gonna expect a bone
thrown back to me later on.
[RuPaul laughing]
- Thorgy and Kennedy, one
of these bitches is going home,
but at this point I'm not
sure how this is gonna go down.
It seems like the girls
all have their own opinion
of how people
should get sent home,
so it's up to DeLa
and Shangela to decide.
- So how is everybody feeling?
- I'm just trying not to cry.
I'm like really holding it in.
Like, it really
doesn't feel good.
I'm like really trying--
- I would be crying right now.
- --to, like, get words out.
Just give me a second.
- Sorry, girl.
- I don't feel like it made
any sense to me, to be honest.
I'm nervous to go home.
I worked really hard
to get here.
- I want to chat with you
if that's okay.
- I'd love to chat with you.
- Should we go chat?
- Yes.
- Wish I could have a refill.
- Yeah, we all need a refill.
I told y'all, "Game of Thrones."
If I'm gonna take over
the Seven Kingdoms, honey,
I'm gonna have to
have some allies.
I want to know, is Thorgy
going to be
a reliable strong ally for me?
- Do I sit here and like beg?
- No.
- Is it even worth it?
- You know, I'm gonna
tell you the truth.
Yes, Kennedy is my friend.
I have known her for
a while, but also--
- I know.
It kind of like terrifies me.
- What I want to say is
that my mind's not made up.
- Okay.
- But she knows as well as I do,
this is a competition.
I respect you.
I know what kind
of a competitor you are,
and you know how I am.
- Yeah.
- If I throw you a bone,
I'm gonna expect
a bone thrown back
to me later on.
- I've been saying
since day one...
- That's how this game
is played, Mamacita.
- But it's a different game.
- Yeah.
- If you win and you save me
and you keep me, oh, my God,
I'm like--I want to--
I cannot leave.
I cannot go home.
I am not ready to go home.
- Thorgy. Pros:
she's here to play the game
and she is a fierce,
creative, talented queen.
Cons: it's no secret
that Thorgy sometimes
really gets in her head.
Is that gonna be a handicap
to her
moving forward in
this competition?
- I don't make excuses.
I'm very transparent.
This was a stumbling block, but
I have so much more to give.
I mean, that's my whole focus
of being here is
to let people see through
this and see my heart.
Not so much on stage, because
you can see my heart on stage.
- Right.
- But it's off stage that
I want you to see it.
- I see it, girl.
- Since Season 7,
I think mentally
I've grown to be a better me,
to be a more sickening
and ferocious me, honey.
So leaving is not an option.
So don't tell me nothing,
you know.
You make your decision based
on what you have seen,
but, I mean,
I don't want to go home.
- When I look at the full scope
of who's here, I can see
Kennedy in that final three,
but the biggest thing
working against Kennedy
is that,
yes, she had some
intense choreography,
but what I heard
from the judges
was she didn't fully
embody Janet
and she was a huge part
of this challenge.
- You seemed like you
really thought
you were gonna be in the top.
- I was in character
the entire time, and...
to be standing on
that stage and not--
not be commended for it...
- I think that's a lot
of emotion for safe.
- It's stupid.
- Girl, do you want Celine
to come over here
and sing you a song?
Girl.
- I was in eight of
the ten numbers,
and I did the goddamn thing.
When I know I did a really
great job, call me selfish,
but I want--
I want to hear it.
I was so excited
to get up there
and hear what they thought
of my performance,
and what they thought of
my Ru-demption look
because in Season 6 all
they wanted to see was glamour.
- I feel like you've been
giving a lot of glamour.
- I--I can assume that
that's what they think,
but I want them
to congratulate me.
- Milk's perception of
his performance
is obviously different
than the reality.
Her Ru-demption Runway
was something
that didn't really reflect
why we like Milk.
It was like a safe,
pretty choice.
Plus the Celine look
was not very Celine.
- Do you have an idea of like
why I should choose you
and Kennedy, you
know what I mean?
Because right now
I'm just like, I don't know.
- Here it is.
When you win this lip sync
and you save me,
I'll owe you one.
Can I ask you an
honest question?
- Yeah.
- Do you think I should be
in the bottom two?
- Uh, I--
- I actually thought
I did a great job.
- I was--I didn't see anybody,
you know what I mean?
- Yeah, yeah.
I just have so many thoughts
going through my head.
Like, when you're given
Diana Ross and, like,
every comment is like,
"It's Diana Ross, so..."
- Yeah.
- "You did less and
that was so much more."
I'm like, to me that means
you did nothing.
You just--it's Diana Ross.
I don't know, but that's why
in the rehearsal I was like,
use me more.
- I know that Thorgy feels
like she was focused
in the rehearsal process,
but she'd be like in the back,
like, frustrated because she
feels like she's being derailed.
It was like a weird subconscious
thing happening, I think.
- I'd like to say no matter
who you choose on that runway,
like, I love you,
but I can't predict
the way I'm gonna react.
I--I would not feel
right going home.
- I actually really love
what Thorgy has to offer
as a drag queen.
I think she's a total weirdo
in a way that I love,
but Thorgy gets upset
fairly easily.
I'm worried that she would
get in her own way eventually.
- So here's the tea.
You know we can talk real.
When I talk to Kennedy,
I want to make sure
that her heart is still
in this competition
because she's gotta be
in that top
or else I would've
just wasted a save.
If I win, why don't I have
your name in my hand?
- You know in your heart--
- Mm-hmm.
- --where my dedication was.
I put a lot into this.
- Yeah.
- And I--
- Oh, I saw you stoning
that wig for hours.
- I wouldn't have
did this Season 7.
That's why I feel like
I belong here,
because I have so much to give
and so much to present.
- Let me ask you this.
If given the opportunity, would
you send me to the house?
- There's certain boundaries
that you just do not cross.
$100,000 is not worth
losing a relationship.
It's just not.
And that's the type
of person that I am.
- There's a lot to think about.
Right now I'm feeling torn.
When you base decisions
just on your friendships,
then you make decisions that
you might end up regretting.
- I'll raise you 20.
- I'm in.
- I've got four queens.
[laughs]
- I hate this game.
These have always
brought me luck.
- I'll take them.
- Just your size.
- Silence.
Bring back my girls.
[laughing]
- This is not
an easy decision.
Each of these queens has
a lot more to offer,
but they both had
trouble delivering
what the judges
needed from them.
So I genuinely have no idea
what to do here.
- I made a decision, but am
I making the right choice?
Is this queen going to push
herself to be in the top,
and when she's there,
can I count on her?
[RuPaul laughing]
- Welcome back, ladies.
Two top All Stars
stand before me.
Prior to tonight,
you were asked to prepare
a lip sync performance of "Jump"
by the Pointer Sisters.
This your chance to impress me,
win $10,000,
and earn the power to give one
of the bottom queens the chop.
The time has come...
[thunder]
to lip sync for your legacy.
- Now BenDeLa, she's won
two challenges at this point.
She's a sneaky ho, okay?
She ain't taking my $10,000.
No, ma'am.
- Good luck,
and don't fuck it up.
[music plays]
- ♪ Your eyes
♪ Tell me
how you want me ♪
♪ I can feel it
in your heart beat ♪
♪ You're so excited I can
feel you getting hotter ♪
♪ Oh baby
♪ I'll take you down,
I'll take you down ♪
♪ Where no one's
ever gone before ♪
♪ And if you want more
♪ If you want more,
more, more ♪
♪ Then jump
- Yes!
- ♪ For my love
♪ Jump in
And feel my touch ♪
♪ Jump if you want to taste
my kisses in the night then ♪
♪ Jump, jump for my love
♪ You are the one,
you are the one ♪
♪ And heaven waits
here at my door ♪
♪ And if you want more
♪ If you want more,
more, more ♪
♪ Then jump
♪ For my love
♪ When you are next to me
♪ Oh, I come alive
♪ Your love burns inside
♪ Oh it feels so right
♪ Come to me
♪ If you want me tonight
♪ Jump
♪ Jump for my love
♪ Come on and jump for me
♪ Jump
♪ You know I need you
♪ Jump in
♪ Jump, jump for my love
[laughing]
- Yes!
- Ladies, I've made
my decision.
Shangela, you're
a winner, baby.
- Yay, thank you!
- You've earned a cash tip
of $10,000.
BenDeLaCreme, you are safe, and
you may join the other girls.
Will the bottom two girls
please step forward.
Shangela, with great power
comes great responsibility.
Which queen have you chosen
to get the chop?
- I know what it's like to
come back to this competition
and be sent home again
without getting the crown.
I know how that feels.
The person I've chosen
to send home...
is Thorgy.
- Oh, Jesus. Gross.
- Thorgy, you are, and will
always be, an All Star.
Now, sashay away.
- Gotcha.
I love you guys.
- Love you, too.
- I love you, Thorgy.
I really mean that.
I really do love you.
- Bye, guys.
Whoo!
I am not ready to leave
this competition at all.
I have so much to give.
In comparison to some of
the other girls here,
I think I deserve to stay
a lot more.
"Drag is fun," and then because
I'm gonna hate Shangela
for life, how about
"Suck it Shangella,"
and I'm gonna spell it with
two Ls because she hates that,
and then she can suck this,
'cause it's going that way.
Yeah, that's pretty disgusting.
Have a good time without me.
Bye.
It's gonna be boring TV.
[bell ringing]
I don't know what that means.
- Under his eye, kitty girl.
- Jesus Christmas.
- Today you've been
given a gift.
Well, it's actually
more like a Groupon.
- What the hell is going on?
Is this gonna explode?
Please don't explode.
- [RuPaul]
Next time on "All Stars"...
You'll be improving your
way through The Bitchelor.
[laughing]
- There's something different
about these girls,
but I can't quite figure out
what it is.
- I don't think I'm psychotic,
I just think I'm really
passionate about finding love.
- Yeah.
- While the leaves--
- And that's why I'm here.
- And you were constantly
overshadowed.
- If you're gonna be a bottom,
at least be a power bottom.
- Season 3 Shange,
you would've picked up
my cocktail and
threw it on that ho.
- Fuck my drag, right?
Every week is just
like turd city.
[laughs]