This is the search for the
next big name in movie magic.
Face off is back.
Casting for season two turned up
all kinds of incredible talent.
14 amazing artists rose to the top
and our here in los angeles
for the ultimate battle
of imagination and transformation.
This season, the challenges
are tougher.
You're going to have to be
all alone in the dark.
That is a mess.
Your models will be completely
submerged in a water tank.
Something's wrong.
We're in big trouble.
Everything here
is incredibly dangerous.
I find the application of
color shockingly inadequate.
- The pressure is more intense.
- I'm ready to pull my hair out.
My heart is racing.
And our celebrity guests
are blown away.
Very, very inventive.
All of that was just working for me.
It's great.
Scary, but funny.
But to come out on top,
they will have to impress
our award-winning
panel of judges.
Ve neill.
Three-time oscar-winning
makeup artist
whose work include beetlejuice,
the pirates of the caribbean films,
and upcoming releases
the amazing spider-man
and the hunger games.
I have one thing to say
about it... spectacular.
Patrick tatopoulos.
Production designer on
independence day,
i, robot, this summer's total recall,
and director of underworld:
rise of the lycans.
It's fantastic.
I'm very, very impressm very, v.
And glenn hetrick,
cutting edge makeup artist
the hunger games,
and custom designer for lady gaga.
This is an absolutely
fantastic makeup.
Only one will win the title.
I don't lose.
This is such an exciting,
amazing experience.
And claim the largest prize
package in face off history.
$25,000 worth of makeup from alcone,
the all-new reinvented
2012 toyota camry hybrid,
and $100,000.
Only one will win...
face off.
Our cast has just arrived
in los angeles,
and they're already
in a caravan of cars
with blacked out windows on
their way to a mystery location.
They have no idea where they are
or where they're going,
but they're about to find out.
My name is rj.
I used to work as a makeup
artist in l. a.,
but my dad got sick, so i moved home
and i've been a teacher
for the last eight years now.
Shout out to my kids.
To get on the show,
i was up for the internet vote.
I had to do this makeup at comic-con
and pray that enough people
voted for me to win.
I am so grateful to be here
it is like winning the lottery.
My name is tara.
I've been doing makeup for 4 1/2 now.
I don't wanna be making things
in my kitchen anymore.
IT'S A DISASTER.
my name's ian cromer.
I'm a baby in effects.
I just got out of school.
I wanna learn from those people.
My name is brea joseph.
Oh, wow.
I own a special
effects/makeup company.
We supply simulated injuries
to law enforcement
and medical support forces.
This is go time.
I have practiced and practiced
with a baby on my hip.
So i'm ready to bring it on, man.
My name is heather.
I've been a professional makeup
artist for nine years now.
People underestimate me based
on my appearance and my voice.
People think i'm all sunshine
and butterscotch.
I could use that to my advantage.
How you doing?
What's up?
- Jerry.
- Hi. You look like a rock star.
I am positive that i am
gonna be the old guy.
I have 20 years of experience.
But i'm actually excited to see
if any of them have the chops
to challenge me.
Hi.
My name is sue lee.
I just graduated from
special effects school.
What i really love
about special effects makeup
is i can make creatures
from my world of fantasy
and have other people look at it
and inspire them.
My name is miranda.
I won a couple of competitions
after graduating
from makeup school,
and my work was featured
in makeup artist magazine
a few times.
It's actually on the back cover
right now.
My name is greg lightner.
Hey, guys!
I've been doing special effects
and makeup since 2007.
Monsters are my favorite.
I love my zombies.
What's going on, man?
How you doing? Nix.
I'm known for my body paint.
This is the ultimate challenge.
I like to compete against
people that are the best.
So the bigger the competition,
the better.
All the contestants finally arrived.
Yeah!
Then we see this long
stretch black limo,
and i'm like, it has to be her.
Hey, everybody.
And there's mckenzie.
Oh, my gosh.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to face off.
Season two is going to be
full of surprises,
and your first challenge starts now.
We're about to do this, really?
My heart is beating like crazy.
Behind that door
lies a whole other world.
It's one of the world's
largest back lots...
universal studios hollywood.
Follow me.
Universal studios.
The lot.
This is every makeup artist's dream.
Oh, wow.
Tons of movies have been
filmed here...
and now to be on the back lot
as an artist
in universal studios
is just... it's amazing.
One side's a giant building.
The other side's a cafe.
There is all these cameras,
trailers, and lights.
Then you look further down
and you see this tent.
Our models are already there
sitting and waiting for us
with their kits in front of them.
My palms instantly start sweating.
You are now standing
on the famed new york city set.
Just like thousands of makeup
artists before you,
you'll be working here on set
during your first
foundation challenge.
Foundation challenges
give you an advantage
going into the spotlight challenge
where someone will be
eliminated each week.
Inside these trailers is
everything that you need
to complete your looks.
Wardrobe, makeup, and even props.
Before we get started,
i've got a surprise for you.
Guys, come on out.
You all know ve neill,
three-time oscar winning
makeup artist
and our series judge.
And of course, you know conor,
the winner of the first season
of face off.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
Oh, my god, i'm crying
'cause i'm so excited.
They're my idols.
They both just flew in
from north carolina
where they were working together
on the upcoming film
the hunger games.
Wow.
Conor was in the shoes
that i'm standing in right now,
and now he's working with ve.
It's a dream.
So ve, what made you choose
to hire conor?
Conor is an exceptionally
talented makeup artist.
And it was a no-brainer for me.
Ve actually placed
a lot of faith in me
from the get-go,
and i really appreciated
the opportunity.
Ve and conor will be your
judges for today's challenge.
You'll be creating
an entire character
complete from head to toe.
Now what you create today
should really show us
who you are as an artist.
But you must use something
from each of the three trailers
to complete your final look.
The winner will receive immunity
in this week's spotlight challenge
and cannot be eliminated.
I need that immunity.
All these people voted for me.
So i don't wanna be the first person
that gets sent home.
You have 2 1/2 hours
for this challenge.
2 1/2 hours to do a full character.
It's gonna be nuts.
Your time starts now.
- Tim, nice to meet you.
- Evan, hi.
It is completely hectic.
I'm just trying to get something
that'll work for a mermaid.
We can do this yellow skirt.
Let's go over there to wardrobe,
find you something.
My name is rayce.
Currently i'm working
as a tattoo artist.
I've been married for ten years,
and we have four kids.
This is a huge opportunity
for me and my family.
We're gonna turn you into a cat.
My name is athena,
and i'm originally from the ukraine.
I've been doing body painting
for about seven years.
I won several awards,
but the more i start leaing
special effects
the more i realize
that's what i wanna do.
I see this awesome cat nose
prosthetic.
Now my character is coming to life.
It's perfect.
My name is matt.
I've been working in the special
effects makeup world
for five years.
I'm completely self-taught,
and i'm a big fan of
the horror industry.
So i'm thinking my makeup's
gotta be something horror based.
I'm going for a high-end zombie.
Working on like a voodoo
witch doctor.
My name is beki ingram.
I've been an artist all of my life.
I was drawing before i could talk.
I can turn anything
into a piece of art.
Body paint, beauty, cirque.
It's gonna be glorious.
Here we go.
Have you ever worn
false eyelashes before?
I'm really into zombies
and beauty makeup.
So i guess we're going burlesque.
Stripper, zombie.
Blood, guts... that is my thing.
I'm gonna turn you into like
i'm zipping your skin off you.
So if i can get it to look
like he's being zipped
out of his own skin,
i'm hoping that'll take me
over the edge.
We're gonna do a ghoulish biker girl.
Okay.
My model is tiny.
I instantly see elf for my character.
As i look around,
i can't imagine myself losing.
The zippers that i chose
are way too heavy.
I go to get better zippers,
and all the wardrobe's gone now.
How? How?
And the more i'm stressing out,
the worse it's getting.
I'm not gonna give up.
20 minutes left.
Be right back.
It's drop dead time.
The countdown is getting closer
and closer and closer.
All right, everybody.
Time is up!
Brushes down.
Hey, rj.
So tell us about your creation here.
Well, she's kind of like
a ghoulish sandy, i think,
from grease.
My boyfriend's back, but he's
in that helmet kind of thing.
The complete picture is terrific.
You did great on the blood
and everything.
- I like it.
- Thanks.
Nice job.
This is a leopard/humanoid warrior.
You did a nice job.
Do you do a lot of body painting?
Yes, this is kinda my forte.
I'm really impressed
by all the detail
and your color choices.
But up close, you see a lot
of the streaks and stuff
from the paint brushes.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, guys.
- Hi, brea.
- Hello.
Why don't you tell us
about your creation here?
He is actually... his costume,
the human skin.
I like your concept,
but you tried to do too much,
i think.
Using the teeth
on the outside of the face
was a really bad choice,
and everything
is very poorly blended.
- Thank you, brea.
- All right, thank you.
I'm a little intimidated of ve.
She doesn't mince words.
Kinda went for a little elf queen.
I had a feeling there'd be
a lot of monstery stuff,
so i wanted to do something
a little different than that.
It's all very cohesive
and really well put together.
I agree with ve.
You blended your edges nicely.
Made some cool color choices.
Nice job.
Hi, nix.
How does this reflect you
as an artist?
I wanted to go more of like
an avant garde,
desert circus.
I figured with the mustache,
i'd become the ringleader.
Nothing seems to be going together.
I think if you could've
followed through
with a similar design
that you have on her face
like on the tops of
her shoulders or her knees
or something, then i think you'd have
- a cohesive design.
- Right, i understand.
I came here with my "a" game.
But after seeing
everybody else's work,
i'm worried.
Honestly, i even feel
a little intimidated now.
For sure.
Judges...
how do you think they did?
I think everybody did
a pretty great job.
I think some of you might have
missed it a little bit.
Who didn't do so well?
Brea...
i think you bit off a little
more than you could chew.
And nix.
I just feel that it was
completed incohesive.
Who were your top picks?
Rj.
You did a great application.
Liked your colors.
Overall, great look.
And jerry.
Very clean makeup job,
and i think that makeup
could be put on film
flattered.
So who's our winner?
The winner is...
who were your top picks?
Rj, great job today.
Overall, great look.
And jerry, that makeup
could be put on film.
Who's our winner?
The winner is...
jerry.
Thank you.
I don't mean to sound cocky
or arrogant,
but my goal is to win
every single challenge.
I'm off to a really good start here.
Jerry, congratulations.
You have earned immunity in
this week's spotlight challenge
and cannot be eliminated.
Well, i know it was a tough day
for all of you,
so why don't you go to the house
and i will see you tomorrow.
- The house was so awesome.
- Wow.
- Oh, my god.
- Look at that!
There's a gigantic blow-up
of anthony's body painting
from the last season.
Look at this.
So many of these contestants are...
- oh, my god.
- Kids.
I'm thinking the absolute
worst part of this
is living with these people.
So yesterday, we're at
universal studios back lot.
And today we're
on hollywood boulevard.
So we walk towards
the grauman's chinese theater.
So i'm super excited already
because it's like
a legendary theater.
It's really cool
to be walking in here,
and i'm ready to find out
what the challenge is gonna be.
Welcome the iconic
grauman's chinese theater.
Beautiful.
I'm so excited.
My feet are standing on top
of stars of famous people,
and it's just... wow.
Well, this has been the setting
for countless movie premieres,
including one of the all-time
greats, the wizard of oz.
Now every great film begins
with a great idea.
In this case, it was a book.
Published in 1900,
original copies of the book
are now valued at over $150,000.
I present to you a first edition copy
of l. Frank baum's
the wonderful wizard of oz.
We got like the book.
Not just a printing.
It's the book.
Now working in teams, you're
going to have to re-imagine
and modernize four of the iconic
main characters from the book:
the tin woodman, the scarecrow,
the wicked witch of the west,
and the cowardly lion.
You will be split
into two teams of seven.
But the teams are gonna be
a little different
than what you're used to.
Because this week,
it's the men versus the women.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
I'm like excited it's girl
against boys.
Fellas, watch out,
'cause we're about to bring it.
Come on!
This being our theme,
it's gonna be amazing.
And guys versus girls.
From what i've seen,
our team is gonna take it.
Now because you'll be reimagining
these iconic characters,
the judges will definitely
be looking for originality
in addition to clean execution
of your make-ups.
They'll also be paying
special attention
to the continuity of your makeup.
So in other words,
your characters have to look
like they all belong together.
All right, guys,
you can head to the lab,
select your models, and get started.
Wow.
Walking into the lab
for the first time
is so exciting.
We have every single product
that you could ever fathom.
So we immediately group up
and choose the life casts,
which are plaster molds
of a model's face.
We get to choose the head casts
that we think would be best suited
for our particular character.
Go.
This is a really huge challenge.
We have to reinterpret four
of these classic characters.
Is that who we picked for scarecrow?
We start using this visio tablet.
It's crazy.
We got perfect measurements
for each person.
And i was like
"yeah, this is awesome."
We really need to represent
all the female special effects
artists out there.
We wanna show we're girls,
we can do prosthetics well.
Okay, so what are the themes?
I was the first loser
on the first day.
The foundation challenge.
So i'm thinking okay,
they're probably looking at me
like they don't wanna be on my team.
So now i know i have to work
twice as hard.
Let's start one at a time.
We'll all put our ideas
and design onto one,
then we'll go to the next,
go to the next.
Who's a good sketcher?
You are?
During the design phase,
we conceptualize and sketch out
these characters on paper.
And from there, we can take the
concepts and narrow 'em down.
- What is the theme?
- Tribal.
Tribal african mysticism.
Let's make the witch
freaky with scarification.
That's when it gets tricky
and starts looking cheesy.
I'm not for tribal at all.
We start brainstorming
different themes.
I want it to be horror.
We were thinking heavily
corroded post-apocalyptic.
There's all kinds of ideas
bouncing around,
and people automatically
start attacking.
What the hell?
Come on, guys.
Tribal doesn't have to be primitive.
But we compromised fairly quickly,
and we decided that our concept
is tribal post-apocalyptic.
We are all gonna add these
elements of metal
to our characters.
It seems like we're all
breaking into groups.
It seems like like you and i
are on the witch group.
I'm not scared to work with brea.
Brea's not gonna hold me down.
I'm gonna amp her up.
I think if we were to elongate
the chin out,
the lips would definitely
look fuller.
- That's what i was picturing.
- All right, cool.
Visually, i want
the wicked witch to come off
beautiful, almost like poison ivy,
where it looks nice
but you don't wanna touch it
because you could get hurt.
Do we wanna give her ears,
or we just biting off too much?
When creating by committee,
it's awful.
Is he still kind of human
underneath, or is he all straw?
Time keeps ticking away,
and i'm trying to be a team player
even though the more
we're getting into it,
the more i'm fearful that...
this is just not the direction
we should be going.
- Do you wanna do the lion?
- I'll go and do the lion, yeah.
So athena's my partner,
and we're doing this repressed lion
that's been in servitude.
He finally escapes,
he's aged, he's not pretty.
That's my style.
Let's do the vacuum forms
first before anything else.
The girls immediately start working.
Power, heat.
With the power tools
and the sculpting.
Sculpting is laying clay on the
replica of your model's face
to create a prosthetic.
So we're going full throttle.
And we notice that the guys
are still talking.
I think we need to figure out tone.
You guys wanna go steam punk, right?
Well, no, no, no, no, no.
It's frustrating
that jerry's contradicting
stuff that we're saying,
and he has immunity.
Let's break down the pieces.
We're still going in circles,
trying to figure out
what we're doing and where we're at.
We're doing too much deliberation.
Okay, let's just be decisive.
What are we thinking?
WE'RE...
coming up...
who's doing what?
We haven't gotten that far yet.
Instead of sitting,
how about doing something?
I'm still on my own.
It's making me crazy.
This is the best design.
Let's just focus on a few
particular atrocities.
And who's going home tonight?
You guys wanna go steam punk, right?
Well, no, no, no, no, no.
We're wasting time.
The team is undecided
on which direction
we're gonna go in because we keep...
coming up with one idea and
then changing it to another.
A guy like clive barker
does wizard of oz.
Let's just be decisive.
We finally decide
our concept is a horror look...
a dark feel to the characters.
So the overall tones
are supposed to be
very desaturated.
Who here feels they're
the strongest sculptor?
- Or who wants which project?
- I'll sculpt anything.
Honestly, i'd like to do
an appliance,
but if...
i'm gonna handle the witch's face.
Okay.
The witch is afraid of water,
water kills the witch.
So she should be
kind of dried out and huskish.
Is that your sketch for the lion?
- Yeah.
- I love that, dude.
I think you should do the lion.
I mean, your concept's beautiful.
Rj, you're doing hands and claws
for the witch and for the lion.
I'm feeling a little steamrolled here
because they assigned the four faces,
and ian and i got what was left over.
Whatever you want me to do i'll do.
Should i even carve around her ear?
Yeah, yeah, leave her ears exposed.
You guys wanna give an opinion
before i start putting detail
into it?
I kinda miss these angles.
So does everyone agree to do
a straight line here
instead of having it rounded?
- I like straight line.
- All right.
The tin woodman
severed his arms and head,
and they come back as tin.
So we're like oh, well,
maybe his torso's still human.
You like where this is going
at least?
Very much, actually.
Oh, thanks.
Go, team.
So i end up with the scarecrow
on my own.
Old-fashioned scarecrows were
just made with a pumpkin,
but i wanted to do it with a twist.
So there's a piece of metal over
his eyes and over his mouth.
If you're a cowardly lion,
you're probably starving.
You'll have a smaller frame,
you'll be a little nicked up.
I heard you're casting your own foot.
Oh, i am, yeah.
I am casting my fist
and my feet for the lion,
and it's a little hard
to do it for one person.
That's why it's taking me a while.
My concept is a different
take on the scarecrow
with a cone head
and an elongated mouth
that goes to his collarbone
with teeth.
I'm working with heather
on the tin woodman.
We're going more towards steam punk.
So he's having to go
steal human hearts,
and those are decomposing
so he has to keep going
and getting more.
I've already got the forms down.
I'm good with time, and i look over.
And i see athena... what's she doing?
Why isn't she sculpting the feet yet?
Did you sculpt those
for articulation?
I did it on my hands.
He might not fit in this.
Athena wasted all this time
making a cast of her hands
when it's gonna be
on a big male model.
Still trying to figure out
like what's going on in here.
I really like it.
At one point,
i decided to walk around.
- That is really cool.
- Thank you.
- 'cause he looks aged.
- That's what we're going for.
The girls are better sculptors
than the men.
I would definitely go check it out.
- OH, THAT'S... COOL.
- YOU LIKE IT?
- yeah.
- Damn, you're doing a good job.
Thank you.
We're gonna have
to figure out something.
- They've got some bad-ass stuff.
- I know.
We've got a pretty good idea
of where we stand,
and then we look over
at the girls' side,
and oh, my god...
we're in trouble.
The girls are kicking our ass
right now.
The guys are not gonna win
if it comes down to sculpture.
It's gonna be about putting
in that extra 10% creatively.
So we need to really examine
what we're doing.
Can we have a little pow-wow
for a second?
Sure.
I'm just worrying a little bit now
that the tin man
only has mouth open and closed,
and on our scarecrow
the mouth doesn't move at all.
They're both basically masks.
Okay, so what's your solution?
It needs to be resculpted.
I hate to say it.
I'm sculpting the scarecrow,
creating my drawing,
and all of a sudden
this concept's not gonna work.
It ticks me off a little bit.
I thought we all agreed
that this was the concept.
But i wanna be a team player
and i just know that this
is gonna bite me in the ass,
especially since there's
only minutes left
before the end of the day.
- Drill a hole here...
- okay.
'cause we should be able to...
you think that will shine
all the way through?
- Yes.
- Hey, guys?
We've got five minutes.
Guys, time is up!
Let's go!
It's the second day of the challenge,
and it's men versus women.
Our theme is tribal post-apocalyptic.
Today, we need to get our molds made
and everything prepped and ready
because tomorrow's application day.
Brea and i are creating
a very beautiful witch.
We have a scepter with a light in it,
which is pretty cool.
And since she's got these like
almost like tibetan talons.
And then we'll be painting 'em
a metallic color.
The guys' wonderful
wizard of oz concept
has a horror tone.
It's dark, a little twisted,
a little disturbing.
As a team, it feels like we
finally got our groove on.
Hey, everybody.
I have glenn hetrick,
one of our series judges,
here with me today.
All of a sudden, glenn walks in.
We're gonna do a walk-through
and see how you're doing.
That is very intimidating
to have someone of that stature
and experience come in
and look over your work.
Right now, i'm working
on the lower bottom half
of the tin woodsman.
This is your concept?
No, i contributed the scarecrow.
Why are you doing this one then?
Um, we actually are delegating
the responsibilities.
We're all all over the place.
Is this sketch you have here
your original concept?
I went through a few
different variations.
We ended up going with this one.
But we took pieces from that.
- Who's in charge?
- We have jerry right now.
Seeing as how he has immunity,
do you think he's the best
person to be in charge right now?
Not... not really.
Is there a team leader.
No, we decided to be
total open democracy.
Everything's voted.
I'm working on the witch's fingers.
And i'm also working on
a piece for the lion's chest.
Kinda doing a little bit
of everything.
Would you say there is one person
that has taken the lead on all this?
- There isn't a lead.
- No.
I'm getting confused,
because we've asked this question,
and i'm getting two completely
different answers.
Is there a leader
or is there not a leader?
Okay, that's it.
I'm not gonna get my ass chewed
because we have no plan.
This is gonna be a huge disaster.
Would you say there is one person
that has taken the lead on all this?
- There isn't a lead.
- No.
I'm getting confused.
Is there a leader
or is there not a leader?
There wasn't a clearly defined
"okay, i'm gonna be
the leader of this group."
Yeah.
Okay, on the day
when you're applying,
who's doing what?
We haven't gotten that far yet.
Pick something.
Come up with a battle plan
so you know what you're doing
on the day.
Good luck, guys.
Thank you.
How are you feeling
about your symmetry decision?
The straight line down the middle.
Heather and i are kinda confused.
Does he want it to be
more symmetrical?
less symmetrical?
He's like couple king pumpkins
pushed together
and then he'll have like a metal eye.
What material are you using
to create the final makeup?
- Foam latex.
- Okay, it's all gonna be foam.
And then you're just going to
pull out all your metal pieces
- and imbed it?
- Mm-hmm.
- Interesting.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
- Nice work.
- Good luck, thank you.
So far i have to say
i'm extremely impressed
with what's going on with the women.
They approached the challenge
the right way.
The synthesized this main concept
and then they allowed
themselves to go
and pick a certain element
and really run with it,
which is exactly what they
should be doing.
Is there one particular
concept with the girls team
that you like?
- I'd have to say the scarecrow.
- Yeah.
It's just...
there's so many subtle nuances
and details to the idea,
and it's all working.
A little concerned about
the tin woodman.
It's just straight down the middle.
That tends to look like
a cheap halloween mask.
Okay, so let's talk about the guys.
Very concerned about
what's going on over there.
Because no one's in charge
of their own project,
it seems like there's more
going on with the power struggle
than there is with the makeups
that are happening,
which is gonna hurt 'em.
Well, i guess we'll see how
it all comes together tomorrow.
Could we all talk?
Glenn made it clear
how disorganized we've been.
So rj and i took the reins.
We walked over to the other
teammates because we realized
we had to come up with
a team assessment immediately.
I think one of the things
that the girls have us over on
is they are each doing a character.
We're doing like a little bit here,
and a little bit here.
We've gotta stick to teams.
Okay, there's seven of us.
There's four characters.
The witch only requires one person.
You split up into pairs,
figure out what are your strengths
in terms of application.
I'll deal with the witch.
It felt like we got
everything figured out.
We started to get
teams of two together
so we can really focus
on our characters individually.
That really helped out a lot.
Greg did a full chest piece,
and we still have no idea
how that's gonna turn out.
Is it gonna be too thin?
Is it gonna be too thick?
I'm making the witch's cape
by painting black liquid latex
on the floor
because i wanted the cape
to be very thin,
and i wanted to be able to just
roll that up once it dried.
You don't need to.
It peels right off.
Mm-hmm.
Mad skill, girl.
Time, guys!
By the end of day two,
i'm a little nervous
for application day,
because there are still some things
that we didn't get finished.
We got turkey too.
Okay, i'm making a salad.
How about that?
- I'm just physically tired.
- I feel you.
Our tin man tomorrow
has to be amazing,
because you and i are the ones
working less on that.
- Do you feel threatened?
- Mm-hmm.
I feel the same way.
But seeing what the girls did today,
i think we're even
if not back and forth.
Here we go.
So we arrive at the lab
on application day.
We have four hours to work
on our model,
and then we have one hour of touch-up
before they go onstage.
I'm worried...
'cause there's too much to do
by myself.
So hopefully my teammates
will be able to step in
at some point.
Big man, how you doing, buddy?
You're our model today.
You're gonna be the wicked witch.
So when our models come
the third day for application,
we don't have any room for error.
We're gonna cover you in warts.
Communication, work, and go.
Are we gonna do a bald cap?
What did you decide on?
No, let's put a wig cap on her.
The way me and ian are breaking down
our concept and design
is we're both going to do
the chest piece,
and he's gonna do the hair while
i do the overall paint job.
- Sue?
- They're cute.
Yeah, they're gonna be awesome.
Those paws look so cartoony
and gimmicky,
and that's all she was worried about.
Oh, this is beautiful.
This is even better.
Instead of sitting, how about
doing something to help out?
Jerry has immunity.
So he has nothing to lose,
where the rest of us,
if it comes down to it,
we're the ones
that would be going home.
Hey, guys, i could use some help.
I feel bad for tara because i know
that she's doing the scarecrow
by herself.
But my partner athena is dead weight.
So i can't walk over and help her.
I'm sorry.
We're running out of time,
so greg and i start cutting corners.
I decide to not use the cod piece,
the knees, and arms.
So now the main focus is the
head, chest, and nothing else.
15 minutes, guys.
15 minutes left.
Shove it up underneath there.
Time is up and i have so much to do.
I'm still on my own,
and it's making me crazy.
- Tara.
- Yes?
- Are you good?
- No.
Do you need help with something?
I haven't been good for a long time.
Coming up...
welcome to the face off reveal stage.
He's just awesome, and i'm stoked.
- That is a mess.
- Shockingly inadequate.
I feel like i am going
to throw up on the stage.
We've got one hour for last looks,
and on our scarecrow,
we still have hands,
stomach, and coloring to get done.
Which is almost impossible.
If anybody has a hand
to help me over here,
it's just putting him together.
I'm not angry that
they're not helping me.
I'm just hoping that i can just
get everything done on my own.
15 minutes, everybody.
Time's up, everybody.
Welcome to the face off reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you will be
eliminated.
First, let's say hello
to your judges.
Owner of optic nerve makeup
effects studio glenn hetrick.
Hello.
Three-time oscar-winning
makeup artist ve neill.
Welcome, everyone.
And creature designer
and director patrick tatopoulos.
Hello, everybody.
This week, your spotlight challenge
was to re-imagine
the iconic characters
from the wonderful wizard of oz.
First up is the women's team.
I'm so happy.
It looks great.
I feel like it's
a complete character.
I see ve smiling,
which is also a good sign.
He's not making as much of an impact
as i felt like he was gonna make.
So i'm a little nervous.
Athena didn't manage her time well.
The body painter
did not paint the body.
She was supposed to age the skin.
That's why we didn't have a shirt.
She looks striking.
She looks exactly how i pictured her.
That gold skin looks beautiful.
And then all of a sudden
we see dorothy,
skipping out onstage, being all cute,
with all of our characters
follow behind.
It's such a neat little picture
to see it all come together.
Next is the men's team.
He's just shiny and awesome,
and i'm stoked.
I think it looks really cool.
I feel like we have
the strongest character
among the boys' team.
So me and ian are feeling
really good right now.
Judges...
why don't you take a closer look?
When the judges go
for their up-close look,
it's very nerve-wracking.
They could either be
praising your work,
or picking it apart... you never know.
Oh, that's creepy.
As the judges look
at our tin woodsman,
i feel like i am going
to throw up on the stage.
I just really, really,
really don't wanna go home.
When the judges walk up
to our tin woodsman,
i am feeling really nervous.
They're poking, they're prodding.
I'm freaking out.
I just really, really,
really don't wanna go home.
Can you move your face around?
I wanna see how the makeup moves
when you try to emote through it.
Hairy metal.
Glenn immediately noticed
the tin woodman's arms,
then he goes to the mask.
Is he trying to pull it off his face?
This is way more involved
than i thought it was gonna be.
Well, the judges would like
to speak with both teams
to learn more about your work.
Ladies, let's start with you.
Let's start with the scarecrow,
and that was tara.
I know that you were working
on your own on a lot of this.
So that makes it
even more impressive.
Love what you've done with the hands.
And your integrating the crows
themselves.
I think you pulled it off
really well.
Thank you.
I like the makeup very much too.
The way you aged the costume,
everything fits together.
I agree.
Integrating the crows
into the makeup was really cool,
and i think the overall
design was really fabulous.
- Thank you so much.
- Well done.
Why don't we move on
to the tin woodman?
Which is heather and miranda.
Okay, who did what in this makeup?
Miranda sculpted the face,
and then i sculpted
the chest and the arm.
I gotta tell ya, ladies,
it's probably my least favorite
makeup in the group.
It's very dodgy.
The paint job's not very good.
I don't understand
why you've got this thing
straight down the middle of his face.
If you would've pulled
the forehead over,
it would start to feel like
it comes together.
I liked the moisture
in the eye bubble.
That's about all that i like
about this makeup.
They didn't seem to like any aspect
except for the condensation
that was on the plastic eye,
which was not deliberate.
I think there's a very good
chance that i'm going home.
All right, let's talk about
the cowardly lion.
That was sue and athena.
All in all, i think
your sculpture of the lion
is really fabulous.
I love his ears.
They're all chewed up like
he's been in lots of fights.
But i'm kinda disappointed
that he doesn't have claws.
I wish you had also used
textures of the skin
the same way you used it on the face
so there was a bit of a transition.
Time management...
a lot had to do with it.
Right.
Time management?
I did everything that i said i
was going to do from the get-go.
Finally, the wicked witch
of the west.
That was beki and brea.
First, can you guys
tell me witch part that you did?
I sculpted the hat
and the chin, molded the warts.
Beki did her shawl.
We kinda collectively did the train.
She did the fingers...
the wonderful fingers.
And i sculpted her
broom/eye to the world.
You guys have gone so far
away from a traditional idea
in coming up with the gold,
and there's this very drow
sort of aesthetic to the neckpiece
and the headpiece.
I really, really like it.
It looks very cohesive.
It looks like
the same person created it,
and it has direction.
I have one thing to say about it.
Spectacular.
It's always so difficult
to hide an edge on a woman.
And the fact that you used
those fabulous moles
was really a good idea.
A lot of the conceptual work
from that witch was my work.
But i wanted brea to shine
after her loss
in the foundation challenge.
Let's look at the guys' creations.
Why don't we start
with the scarecrow?
That was matt and rj.
I know i saw a sketch
on your desk, right?
- And did you do that?
- Yes.
I think that original concept
was maybe stronger to begin with.
I agree.
I kinda wish you would've
stuck with that.
Because his facial design
is something i've seen before.
It's so familiar to me.
It's almost like one of those masks
you sell for halloween.
It looks like a very dry
character, very dry.
And you put gloss on the face.
And that gloss takes away all
the realism of this character.
But i do like the proportion
of him very much.
And i like the fingers very much,
because you created shapes
that were beyond human almost.
Okay, let's move on
to the tin woodman.
That was greg and nix.
Ve, let's start with you.
Who was responsible for that chest?
I was.
Oh, darling.
I'm so sorry,
'cause the chest is funky.
For the chest part,
we wanted to have a opening
for where the heart
had been removed from him.
No.
I could go on all day about things
that i don't like about this,
so let's just focus on
a few particular atrocities.
I find the application of the chest
shockingly inadequate.
And the other choice
to bring metal in the chest...
even around the wound of the heart,
you didn't even bring metal in there.
We did have vacuum form
pieces of metal,
but it didn't fit quite around it.
Figure out a way
to put your work on the model.
Also, that guy has really hairy arms.
That's one of the first things...
we walked up and went,
"oh, it's hairy metal."
Hairy metal is not good.
Okay, let's move on
to the cowardly lion.
That was ian and rayce's work.
Patrick?
So who did what in this character?
I sculpted the lion face
and did the majority
of the paint job.
Ian did a lot of the hair work.
- All the hair work.
This is the best design tonight.
I'm really, really impressed
with the styling.
I love the face.
It's beyond lion.
It's almost like a monkey face.
That appeals to me.
- Thank you.
I really love the idea
of it being gray.
So expected to be this beige-y
flesh tone.
Very well done.
I'm happy with that.
Thank you very much.
Um, i do love the paws.
You have the paws in there.
That was great.
I love the paint job on the face.
I think you did a great job, guys.
I feel like if the men's team wins,
me and ian could have the top look.
Let's move on to the wicked witch.
Which was jerry's.
I really dig the shapes
that you pulled off
in the chin area.
And i like the way
that the nose works
against the curve of the chin.
Thanks.
Jerry, i'm not a huge fan
of the way this makeup looks
because when you get up close to it,
the paint job is not good.
I mean, it looks like you did it
with pencils or something.
I don't know why you put
the teeth on the outside.
If you wanted her to look
all shriveled up,
wouldn't it almost
have been better to make
her mouth look like
it was caving in on itself.
That was a group decision.
We thought that the lips
would have pulled back
and disintegrated
from the lack of moisture.
Okay.
Well, the judges have
heard what you've had to say.
Please head back to the makeup room
so they can make their decisions.
Let's talk about
some of your favorite makeups
of the night.
Which ones are they?
I personally think the girls'
scarecrow is stronger.
It's very cohesive,
he's cool and creepy looking.
That's a very solid idea,
and i think tara pulled it off
really well.
I really like the witch
on the women's team.
She was spectacular.
When she walked out,
she commanded the stage.
I agree.
I think the women had a better witch.
I think that the men
had a better lion.
Just not going with a flesh tone
to begin with...
it's bold, it's really thinking.
Okay, judges, let's talk
about your least favorite looks.
Well, you know, there's no question
that both of these tin woodmen
were absolutely atrocious.
I think both were badly sculpted.
It seems the easiest
to conceptualize.
Two bad sculptures,
but for the guys, it was
a very bad conceptual idea.
So judges, have you reached
your decision yet?
- Yeah, we have.
- All right then.
Let's bring them back out.
All right, glenn.
Why don't you tell us
which team came out on top?
The team that has won
tonight's challenge is...
all right, glenn.
Why don't you tell us
which team came out on top?
The team that we decided has
won tonight's challenge is...
the women.
Thank you.
We're all very happy with
all the work that went into
that very collaborative effort.
Girls won.
God heard our prayers.
Congratulations, ladies.
But we can only have one winner.
So glenn, who would that be?
The winner is...
brea.
Thank you.
We felt that the headpiece
was probably the thing
that set the tone
for the overall look the most.
Well done.
To know that i went from the bottom
all the way to the top
in one challenge...
who's ever done that?
I think i made a mark for myself,
and that's what i came here to do.
Brea, congratulations.
You and your team can
head back to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Well done, ladies.
Congratulations.
Jerry, as the winner
of the foundation challenge,
you have earned immunity
and cannot be eliminated.
You can head back to the makeup room.
Rayce... ian...
rj...
matt...
you're also safe.
You can head back to the makeup room.
Greg, nix, would you please
step forward?
Nix, we definitely had some problems
with the structure and form
of your sculpture
in the details and lack thereof.
Greg struggled with this chest piece,
and it just did not work out
in the end.
And who's going home tonight?
The person leaving tonight is...
greg.
We felt that the chest piece
was the major contributing factor
to the failure of this
particular makeup.
Greg, you have been
eliminated tonight.
Please head back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
The hardest part is
i wasn't true to myself.
And i was really trying to be
a team player.
I wasn't assertive.
You're all awesome.
I wish i could've shown
a little bit more,
but i think my best work
is still yet to come.
So i'm hoping it's only gonna
get better from here.
www.tvsubtitles.net