Previously on Face Off...
14 talented special-effects
make up artists came
to Los Angeles to compete
to join the world's elite.
You're going to have
to re-imagine and modernize
four of the iconic
main characters from
the wonderful Wizard Of Oz.
Jerry has immunity,
but I'm not gonna
let him push me around.
The strongest makeup was Brea.
Who's going home tonight?
Greg.
Now 13 artists remain.
And tonight...
Your models will be
completely submerged
in a water tank.
Something's wrong.
He can't breathe.
But to make it to the top,
they'll have to impress
our award-winning
panel of judges--
Ve Neill,
three time Oscar-winning
makeup artist
whose work includes Beetlejuice
and The Amazing Spiderman.
Patrick Tatopoulos,
production designer on
this summer's total recall,
and director of
Underworld: Rise Of The Lycans.
And Glenn Hetrick,
cutting-edge makeup artist
on The Hunger Games and
custom designer for Lady Gaga.
Who will be the next
great name in movie gic
and earn $25,000 worth
of makeup from Alcone,
the reinvented 2012
Toyota camry hybrid,
and $100,000?
Get ready for Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
I still feel down
about everything.
Yeah.
I feel like I've
let my team down...
And I've helped
send home a friend.
Since I'm still here,
I feel like
I definitely have
to redeem myself.
I was pissed because
at one point,
Jerry was sitting in the chair.
Hell, no.
Because if you and I were
teamed up together,
that'd be it.
What if I keep on
getting second place
because I'm helping
other people look good?
When I lost to Brea, I realized
I allowed someone else
to get that win by
riding on my coattails.
And damn if that's
gonna happen again.
Let's do this day, man.
- We got this.
- Yeah, we got it, man.
Good morning, everybody.
Good morning.
Welcome to the Aquarium
of the Pacific.
This place features
over 11,000 animals,
including sharks,
jellyfish, sea dragons,
even giant crabs.
This truly is
a world-class experience.
This spotlight challenge,
you're gonna be working
in teams of two.
You are going to
search the aquarium
to find fish or other
creatures to inspire
your very own
sea creature makeup.
I actually went
to college for marine biology.
So this is right up my alley.
I know my fish.
Your teams have been
randomly selected
and they are...
Team one-- Sue and Rayce.
Yeah.
Dang.
Team two...Jerry and Nix.
Jerry is the last person
I wanna be teamed up with,
because him and I are
gonna be bumping heads.
Team three is Miranda and Beki.
I'm paired up with the
greenest person on the block.
This is gonna be interesting.
Team four...Ian and RJ.
Yes!
Team five...
Matt and Tara.
Team six...
Heather and Athena.
All the teams are picked
and I'm thinking,
why is my name
not getting called?
Brea?
Why don't you come and stand
next to me for a minute?
All right.
The rest of you can now go
stand with your teammates.
Well, as the winner of last
week's spotlight challenge,
you get to choose
which team you'd like to join.
Yes.
So your team will
have three people.
Go ahead and make your choice.
Well, I feel pretty strong
as a sculptor,
and I was really impressed
with Rayce's painting skills
so I'm gonna have to
choose Rayce and Sue.
Fantastic, go and
join your teammates.
Well, I can't wait to see
what everyone comes up with.
But there is one more thing
you should know.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Of course.
On reveal day, your models
will be completely submerged
in a water tank.
So your makeups are now going
to have to be waterproof.
Oh!
- That's hard-core.
I've done a body paint once,
submerged in water
for a few hours,
and that was a big challenge.
But to do something
with prosthetics?
That's a whole
nother ball game.
You all have 30 minutes
to go find
something that inspires you.
So, grab your cameras,
your sketchpads,
because your time starts now.
Oh, that's nice, that's nice.
Wow.
Looks like he's frontin',
- he's like...
- Yeah.
I really like the frog idea
and I think it lets
you paint like crazy--
- I just don't think
the frog is
exactly the way to go, though.
Out of everyone in the group,
Nix and I are really the only
two that don't really get along.
Texture is what we need.
At the same time, Nix knows
I'm a great sculptor
and I've heard Nix is
a fantastic painter.
Because we're gonna
butt heads on this,
I think the easiest way
to do it
is ultimately you'll
be in charge of paint
and I'll be
in charge of sculpture.
If we don't do it that way,
I guarantee we don't win,
I guarantee it.
Wait, look at the stingray.
Mm-hmm.
I'm pretty much immediately
thinking a lionfish
because they're one of
my favorite fish.
There's lots of appendages.
Oh, that's what--
That's what we want.
Yes, this is the one
I was talking about.
I love it, I love
the sculpture of it.
I'm so glad that
you're a pro at fishes.
Awesome.
Looks like plants.
- I like this one, you know why?
- You do?
'Cause they look like a dragon.
Leafy sea dragon.
I like the colors of this
but I also like this fin.
It looks like an antenna
or something on top.
- Yeah.
- Lyretail fairy basslet.
It changes color,
behavior and sex.
Oh, yeah, it's androgynous.
It starts out as a female
and then morphs into a male.
I think he or she
will be fierce.
No doubt.
Yeah. Fierce.
Beki, look how cool they are.
Yeah, those two look beautiful.
This thing would all
flow in the water
in a really interesting way.
Yeah.
Do you think this
might be the one?
Yeah.
Are you guys picking
this thing?
Yeah.
Don't pick what we're picking
'cause you don't
wanna be next to us.
Well, all right.
Beki and Miranda are doing
the same fish as us.
But I don't want our fish
coming out looking the same.
So I'm ready
to bring it on, man.
Wow, that's cool,
look at that shark.
I like the ridges
down the back.
And then they have
an easy texture to sculpt.
I-- I think the zebra shark
is a good choice for us.
Turtle.
We see this turtle and
he's floating past us,
and at that point,
we looked at each other,
and we knew that that
was gonna be our animal.
I mean, it's got great texture,
it's got great color.
- I think it'll be good.
- I think it'll be awesome.
We get back to the lab.
We get to choose
our model for the makeup.
On each of our stations,
there's an aquarium
so that we can test
different materials,
see how things
move in the water,
see if they float
or if they sink.
We can't build
a really big
head piece, unfortunately,
but we're just gonna keep
that mohawk going on.
We have three and a half
hours in the lab
to figure out the design
that we're going to do.
What do you wanna do?
I'm really nervous
about it, actually.
Well, let's talk about it,
what are you worried--
I mean, we gotta get started.
Having it hold up underwater
is a huge twist.
We don't even know
where to begin.
I think we should have, like...
Something okay, well lawyers are
known as sharks, right?
Well what if he's a lawyer?
We'll take a risk and we'll say,
if this works, awesome,
and if it doesn't
send me home.
- Cowl first?
- Cowl first.
We'll work on the face tomorrow.
All right.
Do we wanna cover her eyes
or do we wanna keep
her real eyes?
We should keep her real eyes.
I've never done something
under the water before.
To me, the challenge then became
it has to be a beautiful
creature in the water, you know?
We have to use fabrics and
things that are going to float
and be beautiful in the water.
So, we've got a head.
One arm, one sheet with texture.
These are the things
for sure we're sculpting.
I'm feeling really
great about today.
We both agree foam latex
is the best for this.
Silicone doesn't
breathe underwater.
We know that if we
glue it on well,
it's not gonna come off.
My greatest strengths lie
in conceptualizing
and sculpting.
I believe that you need
that base sculpt
to really wow those judges.
Apparently, Matt likes to
slip these sex symbolism things
into all of his makeup,
which is fine by me.
For this character,
I'll be working primarily
on the face sculpture.
Sue is working on the chest
piece and the back piece.
And Brea is working
on the arm pieces
as well as the appendages that
come off of the character.
Mine looks a little
more delicate.
- Yeah.
- And this just looks like
"I'm gonna kick
your ass right now."
Totally.
The concept is
going to be about
this sea goddess has come out,
and instead of
camouflaging with the water,
she's going to be just embodied
with anger
and fire and passion.
Should I make him a little
more meaner or something, or...
I think stay away from the mean
because I think a lot of
people tend to go that way.
- So just kinda leave him?
- Yeah.
We're working surprisingly
well together.
We have some molds to make
and some latex arms to pull.
I mean, it's, you know,
it's high school stuff.
The lionfish that we chose
has a very, very,
very broad mouth.
So we tried to capture that.
While I'm sculpting,
Athena is making long spines
that are going to work
almost like a glove.
Gonna make a really big
impact in the display tank.
I'm worried if we
have too much of,
like, the lip thing going on,
it's bent out like that.
The sea dragon has a really long
snout, or nose, or whatever,
and she starts putting on
this really short
little stubby thing
that looks like a duck
and it's just
a big sloppy mess.
Can I-- Can I
just do one thing?
- Go ahead.
- I just think maybe--
- Like, if we just...
So she wants to come over
and sculpt on it.
Instantly, she wipes
the face off
and starts doing this little
tiny chicken nose on it.
You don't think it
looked like a duck before?
Nope. I think it looks
like a chicken now.
Becky and Miranda are having
some intense...Dialogue.
Okay, then I'm gonna
leave the snout up to you.
'Cause the way that
you're responding to me
is stressing me out a little
bit, like, so I just--
I'd rather just
leave it to you.
I'm over here sculpting,
waiting for you to
show me something that doesn't
look like a chicken or a duck.
Maybe you could
help me out rather than
just yelling at me
that you don't like it.
She definitely
underestimating me,
so it's kind of gonna
bite her in the ass
if we can't get
something out that works.
You gotta show me what's
going on in your brain.
Oh, my God, this is
gonna be a disaster.
You just have
bad things to say,
but you don't wanna
help me out.
Well, maybe you could
help me out
rather than just yelling at me
that you don't like it.
The end of day one, Miranda
starts basically shutting down.
So, I had a front
and a back piece,
a chicken staring at us.
I guess I'm 20% of
the way where I wanna be.
The start of the day
is very nerve-wracking.
We'd have to take
into consideration,
is this gonna float?
Is the paint gonna
bleed into the water?
Really makes me nervous.
I like the white one
to be honest.
I haven't done a latex skin
like this before.
What jobs have you worked on?
I sculpted for this guy's film.
- What was the name of the film?
- And I helped around--
I don't remember.
Did you go on set
for that at all?
No.
And how long did it
take you to do--
Why are you, like,
drilling me right now?
I'm trying to figure out
what you've done.
I don't know you.
She obviously
doesn't respect me,
and she doesn't really
give me a chance.
I don't understand why
it was such a big deal
in what I was doing.
You-- you became
defensive when
I started asking you what your
credentials were, okay?
Because it seemed
like you were asking me
in a way that was indicating,
"oh, you haven't done anything."
- Hey, guys.
- Hello.
Patrick and I are here
to check out your work.
So here comes
McKenzie and Patrick.
I'm a little nervous because
he's a great artist,
and anything he says,
you've gotta listen to it.
Hey!
So our team of three.
I am so excited to see
Patrick in the lab.
I love his work,
I love underworld.
We wanted this dragon to be
a representative of the sea
and a guardian of the sea.
You guys have
a plan for the legs?
We have-- Already have
molding the arms,
- the whole texture on the arms.
- Uh-huh.
What we're gonna do is maybe
just do a brush-up
with the latex
- and...
- And use some of those pieces?
Yes, and use some of
the pieces on the legs.
- Hey, Matt and Tara.
- Hey.
- Hi, guys.
- How you doing?
Great.
Something about the water
that makes things move,
are you planning that as well?
We're running around
those ideas, but we're, uh,
we're kinda iffy on the material
to use right now.
- Right, right.
- And we just need to hammer
down on the--
the exact concept
of the certain fins
and the shape.
So you're basically
conceptualizing
as you're moving forward.
Yeah.
- All right.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you.
- How are you doing?
- Hi.
It's coming along.
He's gonna be wearing
a three-piece suit, actually.
- Yeah.
- Really?
He's a lawyer.
Looking good.
Good luck, guys.
- Good luck.
- Awesome.
- Hey, Nix, hey, Jerry.
- How's it going?
We're doing
a Ridley's sea turtle.
It's an interesting choice.
The turtle is
a pretty streamlined shape.
It's underwater.
The same sort of the appeal
of all the things
that are flowing
just sell the water better.
We did talk about that.
One of the benefits of water
is undulating, trailing--
- Mm-hmm, right, right.
- Materials.
But then we thought,
everyone's gonna do that.
We're not putting
too many twists
and turns into our pieces.
There's just gonna be
cool textures and paint job.
It looks to me like you paid
attention to the fish quite,
and I think it's important that
there definitely is
a fish face.
I know some people were going
kinda more of a character,
but we-we've decided to take
a more literal approach.
Those pieces are what?
They're gonna be
those little, uh--
This is where we're
gonna anchor the big fin.
That's it, got you.
So you guys are
working well together?
Feel it's all happening?
I think we sat down,
kind of talked about
exactly what
we wanted to get done,
so we're on the same page.
You feel
you're on the same page.
- Very good.
- Well, good.
It's funny because Miranda
just instantly lies.
She's like, "oh,
everything's great."
You can't just say
something that's not true.
- All right, good luck.
- Thank you.
So, let's start with Sue,
Brea and Rayce,
who are doing
the leafy sea dragon.
Um, what are your thoughts?
Those are guys
are creating something
that to me looks
absolutely great.
Who are you most
concerned about?
Matt and Tara,
I think are the one
that would concern me.
- Why?
- Because they don't have
a full-blown plan.
They have a lot of things that
they haven't resolved yet.
Okay, so Nix
and Jerry's sea turtle?
I'm not crazy about the sculpt
on the face of the turtle.
It's a little cartoony.
What are your thoughts on
Athena and Heather's lion fish?
I'm a little bit
concerned about how much
we're gonna see
that mouth opening.
You don't want
this thing to look like
a big pull-on mask
for Halloween.
Right.
All right, guys.
Can't wait to see
what you come up with.
- Thank you, guys.
- Thank you.
Take care, bye.
I think the only way this isn't
gonna work is if
we don't get finished.
Yeah.
Um...
I don't wanna have them say
it looks like
three people doing it.
To make this
a cohesive character,
all of our sculptures
have to have
some kind of element
that's relatable.
As long as there's
none that bend back in,
so that if they're underwater,
they can have like,
a flow off of them,
kinda that aerodynamic...
Okay.
After I finish the sculpture,
I make a mold of it.
So that you're left with
a negative impression
of your original sculpture.
Once you pour foam latex in,
it has to bake
for quite a few hours.
We wanna have that baking
by the time we leave tonight.
All right, what do you
want me to do now?
Uh, mold that arm.
I can sculpt.
Plan was to have the head
totally finished
and I'm willing to let him
run the paint job.
I've heard how good he is,
but I haven't seen it.
- Hey, Beki?
- Yeah?
I have a question.
Should I, like, build a wall?
I'm just worried it'll--
It won't be able to stay.
I start getting very concerned.
I'm realizing how very little
experience she really has.
You think you could
help me open this?
I can't figure out
how to open it.
She's just killing me.
Are you guys feeling confident?
No, because time is the only
thing that will make her-- Me
feel comfortable with her.
I'm frustrated.
I feel like I've been working
as fast as I possibly can.
Also, coaching Miranda
is making me a little bit
anxiety-ridden
simply because I can't hold
the whole boat on my own.
The way Beki is saying
everything to me
is just rude and mean,
and it's kind of a nightmare.
This is not finished yet here.
I put that in
and you called me over
to help you with that,
so I did.
Then I'll blow dry them
and they'll be ready
to pop out.
You're sure
there's nothing else
you'd rather me
be doing that this?
Because if so, speak now.
Miranda is getting really
aggressive with me.
And honestly, I don't feel like
I need to prove myself to you,
like...
You don't need to
prove yourself to me.
You need to prove
yourself to the nation
because you're on Face Off.
Beki and Miranda aren't
gelling together
very well at this point.
Communication isn't quite there.
Just, ugh!
If you feel
I'm being so inadequate
with my time,
then I'll do something else.
- I think you should pre-paint
because it might take you
a little while
to get what you want.
Miranda's pretty adamant
about doing the painting,
and if she paints
as fast as she sculpts,
that thing's never
gonna get painted.
Day two's almost done.
Got the face molded,
ready for foam.
Got a lot of our fins cast up.
Should be doing
pretty good for tomorrow.
All right, guys, time's up.
Come on, peeps, let's go!
Look at Athena, skipping in
like she doesn't even have
a ten-hour day.
That's cute.
So it looked like
you were stressing a little.
Uh, just a little.
Miranda and I had a fight,
and I feel like
that showed some of
the worst parts of both of us.
She's still new, though,
isn't she?
Today I'm asking her
what her credentials are,
and she started just,
immediately getting defensive.
It's just like,
she's so threatened by me.
Beki told Miranda to her face
that she was incompetent
and that she should not be here.
I caught Beki scolding
Miranda like a child,
and...You just-- You should
never do that to someone.
And if something takes you
longer than so and so hours,
- you shouldn't be here.
- Look at you.
If you didn't have
me on your team
doing the work, you would
have nothing done, homegirl.
Hoo!
She's jealous
'cause she didn't win.
She's walking around
saying, "I let you win
because I wanted you
to redeem yourself."
You're not
letting me win anything.
I'm dope.
That's why I'm here.
For your information, that's why
I have my own company.
Because I'm dope.
So application day--
We have four hours
to apply our prosthetics,
get it painted,
have everything finished,
with an hour
to do final touch-ups.
I'll tell you what, dude,
I cannot wait
to paint this turtle.
Beautiful.
Beautiful, beautiful.
Hi, how are you doing?
- Good, I'm Sara.
- I'm Beki.
It's so nice to meet you.
Are you our model?
- I think so.
- Perfect.
Four hours seems like a long
time to do a makeup application,
but when you're doing a full
body with multiple pieces
it-- it goes by in a flash.
There'll be a--
One prosthetic piece,
and this will go all the way
down to your...Crotch area.
This part goes here, okay.
- My hoo-hah.
- Yes, and then...
If it's cool with you,
it'd be awesome
- if you could shave your legs.
- Yeah, yeah.
So you're-- you're a lawyer.
- Shark lawyer.
- That's clever, dude.
We really have
to bring something extra
with this leafy sea dragon.
Being that a team of two
picked it as well.
Now it's a duel of whose leafy
sea dragon's gonna be better?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
We have over 15 appliances,
plus the paint job.
Holy crap, half of that
would have sufficed
for a team of three.
I'm getting
a little worried now.
I'm gonna glue it
in the side of the foam.
Gonna have you grab and hold
onto this kind of a little bit.
We have to apply bald cap.
We have to apply
facial prosthetic,
two arm pieces,
and two leg pieces.
It's a lot of stuff to apply,
and I hope that I'll be able
to get the paint job
done on time.
So our model, Ethan,
he keeps kind of nodding off.
Wake up.
"Huh?"
I can't believe
he, like, passes out
in, like, three seconds.
We have a narcoleptic
lionfish man today.
I'm gonna kill you right now.
I don't know what happened.
There's so many chunks
missing from the edges.
First thing the judges are
gonna look at is the edges.
When you have
a nice blended edge,
you shouldn't see it at all.
And it just makes
the character more real.
I'm really stressing that
we're not gonna be able to
get these edges down.
How are we gonna hide these?
So we're feeling
a little nervous
that we're not gonna be able
to pull off this makeup.
Look at that, dude,
custom color, bro.
What do you think, dude?
It's a little cartoony.
So you don't like
the paint job,
or you just think it
needs to be tweaked?
I don't actually
like it, but, you know...
I'm starting to get that queasy
feeling in my stomach,
thinking that I just knocked out
some really cool sculpts
in a short amount of time,
and now, they're going to get
saddled with an awful paint job.
I mean, because of time,
would you mind
if I just kinda
wrapped up the back?
Yeah, that's fine.
One hour left.
So we're just doing a...
I don't know yet.
My whole mantra with makeup is
if you can't hide it,
flaunt it.
So, my brilliant plan is to
cover these massive edges
with fabric.
I don't wanna cover up
your sculpt too much,
'cause it's pretty,
but I--
We just have
to do the edge that way.
Since we don't have much time,
the fabric has to be
applied at the last looks.
It'll be okay, Matt,
it'll be okay.
All right, all right.
I'm really thinking
she's out of her mind.
Coming up...
Let's put your
makeups to the test
in our water tank.
We're in big trouble.
This is an incredible look.
The paintjob was amazing.
I did not like this makeup.
It's last looks.
Whoo, the last hour.
We got a lot of detailing to do
and finishing stuff.
Shell is on, baby.
That ain't going anywhere.
We should start
fabric-ing I guess.
We're scrapping
blending the seams,
which is a big no-no in my book.
And Tara's trying
to reassure me that
we can hide those
with the fabric.
How lo2 would you say
till you're ready
to help me with the paint?
'Cause I can't paint
the whole thing alone.
I will help you paint
as soon as I get these fins on.
Just like I said I would.
You think we should
lose the fins?
Yeah.
They just turned out
to look like.
We have no choice,
we have to do it.
And pose with your fists.
Hey, guys, time's up.
I was really disappointed.
It was definitely one of
the key parts of our makeup,
and we had to take it off.
It's not a finished work.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Now, tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
But let's say hello
to your judges.
Owner of optic nerve
makeup effects studio,
- Glenn Hetrick.
- Hello.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist,
- Ve Neill.
- Welcome back.
And creature designer
and director,
Patrick Tatopoulos.
Hi, guys.
So, guys, this week,
your spotlight challenge
was to work in teams.
And to find a sea creature
from the aquarium
of the pacific
to use as inspiration
for your unique makeups.
You were also asked
to make them waterproof.
I'm standing there, and I'm
looking over at this huge tank,
and I'm getting
a little nervous.
Let's take a look
at your makeups
before they go
in our water tank.
I'm glad we decided to go with
the fabric and hide the edges,
because it looks
like colorful scales.
It doesn't look good.
As soon as his back faces us,
I notice that
there's skin showing.
We feel like our
character's execution
is a little lacking right now.
But she's gonna be going out
in the water in a few minutes,
and we're really gonna
see that ethereal look.
I know he's still really
visually striking,
but I'm a little nervous that
maybe now we don't
have enough pieces.
Despite all of the shenanigans
between Miranda and I,
we actually created
an amazing creature.
And I can visualize what it's
gonna look like in the water.
It will be beautiful.
I see big grins
on people's faces
when they see our shark dude.
I think we might have this.
So let's put
your makeups to the test
by submerging your models
in our water tank.
First up is Tara
and Matt's creation.
Judges, why don't you
take a closer look?
We're a little worried,
because...
We never even tested
the makeup that we used.
It may crack.
I'm also a little worried
how well the model will do
in the water.
She may freak out
and rip off the prosthetic.
This is it, guys, sink or swim.
Wow.
Everybody gasped
when she got in the water.
That looks really cool
in the water.
Everything's staying on,
she's sparkling,
you can't see the edges--they're
all disguised by the fabric.
Yeah, it looks terrific.
Well, this was
a really clever way
to hide all their edges.
Next up is Nix
and Jerry's creation.
When our turtle
gets into the water,
it's already kind of awkward.
You can see the back part of
the shell starting to lift up.
He goes underwater for a moment
and comes right back up.
The water is just
caving in on him.
He can't breathe.
We're in big trouble.
Next up is Nix
and Jerry's creation.
Something's wrong.
He goes underwater
for a moment,
and he comes right back up.
Gee, he's having
some major blowouts.
A cloud starts
forming around him of paint.
Everything
but the shoulders is up.
We're in big trouble.
The shell is completely
floating off.
I don't enjoy
doing mediocre work.
Hey!
I'm pretty good.
But you're as strong
as your weakest link.
Next, we have Sue,
Rayce, and Brea's creation.
I think that
if those weren't made
with such thick, stiff wire,
they'd be lighter
and they'd be moving a lot.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The model is
selling the makeup.
It's beautiful.
All right, let's look
at Heather and Athena's
creation.
Okay.
- Nice.
- Whoo hoo, yes.
As soon as he jumps
into that water tank,
he, like, becomes
like a fish in the water.
The mouth is actually
really fantastic.
Oh, look at the little things
around him, all moving.
- Right.
- Good.
Oh, yes.
Now we need to applaud.
Yeah, this is good.
Now, let's see Ian and RJ's.
He gets into the water, and
immediately his clothes pop up.
All right, let's see
Beki and Miranda's.
This looks way better
underwater than it did out.
Totally, totally.
Well, the judges have scored
your creations, so...
Let's see what they thought.
Beki and Miranda...
Brea, Rayce, and Sue...
Your teams are safe.
You can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Me and Beki worked
horribly as a team,
so I'm excited that
we were called safe.
All right, the rest
of you were the best
and the worst of this week.
So the judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Heather and Athena,
would you please step forward?
I did not like this makeup.
I actually loved it.
I thought it was really cool.
Oh, my God, thank you.
You made some really,
really brave decisions.
Could you tell us
a little bit about
who did what on this makeup?
I sculpted the face
and the backs of the legs, and--
And I did the whole paint job,
from head to toes.
I think it came out
really well.
All in all, it was really
successful as far as,
you know, holding up
in the water,
which was one of the challenges,
so good job, ladies.
- Thank you.
- I love it.
I walk yesterday in the shop,
and I saw your work,
and I thought those were
the only two that decided
to do something that's
very much of a fish,
and not some kind
of hybrid man-fish face.
And I thought that
was a very bold choice.
- Great work.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
You can both step back.
Jerry and Nix, if you
would please step forward.
Okay, who did what
on this fiasco, guys?
I led sculpturally,
then Nix led painting.
I gotta tell you, your turtle
was a turd, I'm sorry.
I think the best thing on your
turtle was his shoulders,
and unfortunately,
the minute he got in the water,
everything blew off,
which was kind of a bummer.
I mean, was it glued on at all?
- Yeah.
- And it all blew off anyway?
Damn!
One of the key thing
about this sculpt
is it looks very,
very cartoonish,
which is actually
very dangerous because
the paint job using green
and brown together
on the same character
was very risky.
If one of you is the person
who ends up hanging tonight,
which do you
think it should be?
Just for application,
I would say Jerry.
He threw me under the bus.
I can't believe
you just did that, dude.
- Jerry?
- Uh...
I'm not gonna throw
Nix under the bus.
You know, I'm gonna say
we're equally responsible.
I will agree with that.
We are both
equally responsible.
Thank you, guys.
You can step back.
Tara and Matt, you're next.
Tell me who did
what on this makeup.
Uh, I handled the sculpting
of the prosthetic,
the chest and the fins.
Um, I headed up the paint job,
and I also wanna say he came up
with the creature idea.
I'll tell you right away that
this is an incredible work.
I'm very impressed with it.
I think your color scheme,
the way you played
with the appliance,
the way this functions
in the water,
it's a gorgeous piece.
Thank you.
I agree, and I think this is
an absolutely fantastic makeup.
The little filigree work
that's in the sculpture
absolutely thrilled me.
Well done.
The idea that you took that
iridescent fabric and
put it around the edges
of all your appliances
was a very clever way
to hide your edges,
and it did nothing
but enhance the makeup.
Yeah.
All right, thank you.
You can step back.
Rj and Ian,
please come to the center.
Glenn, let's start with you.
Please start by telling us
a little bit about the concept.
It's a zebra shark.
Uh, he's a lawyer.
And a shark lawyer.
In your opinions,
how well do you feel
you did with this makeup?
I actually was really happy
with how it turned out.
I think that
the hands could have been
executed a little bit better.
I'll go so far as to agree
with you on that wholeheartedly.
If you're gonna put
clothes on somebody
that's going into the water,
you should have sewn him
into those things
because the minute
he hit the water,
everything covered up
your makeup job.
Uh, I think that kind of
blew it for you.
If I go home over
a terrible wardrobe choice
and having a clean makeup,
I'm gonna be pretty upset.
All right, guys,
can you please step back?
Thank you.
Okay, the judges have heard
what you've all had to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they make their decision.
All right, judges.
Okay, let's talk about
some of the best and
the worst looks of the night.
Let's start with
Heather and Athena.
What are you thoughts?
I really liked that lionfish.
I thought it was really
well-done.
Heather was a very big driver.
She was the one in charge
of the sculpt of the face.
Kudos to her for being able
to let go of the wheel
when it came
to the body painting,
because it
was the right choice.
Athena killed that paintjob.
Matt and Tara's?
It was Matt's design
and direction.
Where do we bring Tara into this
as far as her contributions?
Well, I think she's mainly
responsible for the coloring.
As beautiful as the sculpt
is and the design...
Yeah.
A bad paint job could have
sank that thing.
Yeah, it could have.
And the paint job was amazing.
Jerry and Nix.
It was a turd-le.
They were the guys that said
that they wanted to play safe,
and I don't know they realize
that they played the opposite.
They played very risky to me.
Why would they paint it
that bright green
when they had everything
else in the beige tones?
That-- It didn't go.
Ultimately, the result
shows you that there was
a complete disconnection
between both sides of the work,
and it's just terrible.
Okay, so any thoughts
on Ian and RJ, then?
It was just kind of a mess.
They didn't glue
his clothes down,
they didn't put the fins
in the right place.
That idea seems
like one of those
first ideas that you blurt out.
Yeah, yeah,
I couldn't agree more.
So, judges, have you
reached your decision yet?
I think we did.
- Yeah, we have.
- Yep.
Okay, let's bring
them back out.
All right, Glenn, why don't you
tell us about
the top looks tonight?
Our top teams are...
Heather and Athena,
with the lionfish.
Really bold decisions and
an extremely even collaboration
between the two of you.
And Matt and Tara
with the basslet.
A unique concept and
extremely clean execution.
So then, which team
came out on top?
The top team tonight is...
Matt and Tara with the basslet.
- Congratulations, Matt, Tara.
- Thank you.
But we can only
have one winner,
so, Glenn, who would that be?
Tonight's winner is...
Matt.
Thank you.
We felt that you contributed
the defining conceptual element
that really drove the piece
to its final form.
- Congratulations, Matt.
- Thank you.
You and Tara can head back
to the makeup room.
I can't believe it.
This is my first win.
To me, it's like
a dream come true.
Yay, we knew it.
He the-- He's
the ultimate winner though.
Just to hear the judges
comment positively on my work
and praise it
is all I really wanted.
Athena, Heather,
you are also safe.
You can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you.
- Hell of a job.
- Good luck, guys.
Thanks.
Unfortunately, this means you
are bottom looks this week.
So, one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step to the center.
Glenn?
Ian and RJ,
the random fin placement
and inadequate anatomy
of your creation,
combined with the fact
that you blew the opportunity
to work with the entire body--
We had a guy in a suit getting
into a tank of water--
Didn't really add up for us.
Jerry and Nix,
with your sea turtle...
Poor decision-making,
I think, from the beginning,
and an overall lack of quality
in the work in its final form.
So who's going home tonight?
The person
going home tonight is...
Nix.
It just felt like you had
this huge opportunity
to show us your
body painting skills tonight,
and it wasn't there.
It just didn't happen for you.
It's definitely, uh,
a lot-- A lot harder
than I thought it was gonna be.
Nix, I have seen your work,
and I know you're amazing.
I'm sorry to see you go, honey.
I really am.
That means a lot
coming from you. Thank you.
Nix, I'm sorry, but you
have been eliminated.
It's been great having you
here with us.
But if you would please head
back to the makeup room,
and pack up your kit.
It's been an honor.
Sorry.
Aww...
Yeah, I'm-- I'm
going home, guys.
Really, I'm not
ready to go home.
I don't feel like
I've had the chance
to really show people
what I'm capable of.
I'm an artist established
for body painting,
and I'm just gonna have to work
a little harder to show
I'm capable of doing
special effects as well.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net