Previously on Face Off...
14 talented special effects
makeup artists
came to Los Angeles to compete
to join the world's elite.
Your makeups are now going
to have to be waterproof.
Oh, my gosh.
He goes underwater for a moment
and he comes right back up.
He can't breathe.
Tonight's winner is...
Matt.
And who's going home tonight?
Nix.
Now, 12 artists remain.
And tonight...
Please welcome hip-hop star
Asher Roth.
Oh,
Oh, my gosh, this is awesome.
All completely nude models,
flopping in the wind.
And it goes from bad to worse,
like, real quick.
To make it to the top,
they'll have to impress
our award-winning
panel of judges.
Ve Neill,
three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist
whose work includes Beetlejuice
and The Amazing Spiderman.
Patrick Tatopoulos,
production designer on this
summer's Total Recall
and director of
Underworld: Rise Of The Lycans.
And Glenn Hetrick,
cutting-edge makeup artist on
The Hunger Games
and custom designer
for Lady Gaga.
Who will be the next
great name in movie magic
and earn $25,000 worth
of makeup from Alcone,
the reinvented 2012
Toyota Camry hybrid,
and $100,000?
Get ready for Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- I think Jerry.
- I know.
- It's like Jerry's a virus.
- Yeah.
- A parasite that he
attaches to anybody--
- Thank you.
- And whoever's associated
with him, goes home.
And then he's like,
Yeah.
It's the Jerry curse.
If you work with him,
he's gonna
sap any of your creativity
and bring your makeup down.
I'm just upset because
he's always telling people
how to do this, how to do that,
and his stuff doesn't work.
And you're on
the bottom every time.
Ooh.
We walk in and our models are
standing there
with sunglasses on
and we're like,
"what's going on?"
I'm a little confused.
Why are there only
four makeup stations
and only four models?
Hey, guys.
Life on the set
of a Hollywood movie
or a primetime television show
is fast-paced,
and time is money.
Makeup artists are often pulled
in many different directions,
forcing them to pass off
what they've started
onto a team member.
Well, that is the basis
for this week's
foundation challenge...
A timed relay race.
Oh...
Working in teams of three,
you will take turns creating
a single face makeup.
Each team member will get
two 15 minute turns.
When the 15 minutes are up,
you will run back to the start
and hand this brush
to your next teammate.
Oh, man.
You also will not be able
to see what your
teammates are doing.
What?!
Models.
Underneath your
models' sunglasses
are a pair of specialty
contact lenses.
Your makeups must
be built around
the lenses
your model is wearing.
And you won't know what
they are until you start.
Your guest judge
this week is best known
for the fast-paced world
of sketch comedy shows.
Not only was she the department
head on Saturday Night Live
and Mad TV,
but she has won an emmy and
has been nominated 14 times.
Please say hello
to Jennifer Aspinall.
Jennifer Aspinall is so
respected in the makeup world.
She has to do so many different
looks on Saturday night live.
I want to impress her!
So, Jennifer, you know what it
takes to thrive under pressure.
What advice can you
give to these guys?
This challenge is a really
good opportunity for you guys
to fine tune your
decision-making skills.
You will have to follow the lead
that was put before you.
Stay focused,
make choices really quickly,
and work as a unit.
Okay, so Jennifer will select
the winner of this challenge.
That person will then win
immunity, and, of course,
cannot be eliminated this week.
Every time there's an
immunity, I'm dying to get it,
because the stress level
on the judging days
is just sending me
through the roof.
She will be judging on
creativity, technique,
and overall contribution
to the team's final look.
Everything else has been
selected randomly for you.
Team one--
Jerry, Miranda, and Sue.
Team two-- Tara,
Brea, Heather.
Team three--
Rayce, Beki, and Ian.
And our last team is
Matt, RJ, and Athena.
Please head back
to the starting line
and pick who's gonna go first.
Let me go first because I can
throw down some
pieces real quick.
Okay, your time starts...
Now.
I'm faster.
Look at me.
My model looked at me,
and there were these
yellow contacts
with green and black spots.
And I'm like, "all right,
cool, Alien." Out the gate.
Ooh.
The contacts
my team has are fiery,
so I thought we'll do a zombie.
God, those are gorgeous.
You have gorgeous eyes.
I look at the contacts
and immediately I'm thinking,
fantasy beauty, why not?
Come on, Jerry,
you got this, you got this.
I run over to the prosthetics
and I just rip the appliances
out of RJ's hands,
and I'm like, dude,
you just gotta go.
Okay, that's how
we're gonna play, all right.
I immediately grabbed
blue eyelashes,
thinking we're going with
blue star princess here.
Oh, my God, gorgeous,
gorgeous, gorgeous.
I only have 15 minutes to set
a foundation for
where we're going.
I lay down nasolabial
fold prosthetics.
We're off to
a really good start here.
Send me the concept, RJ.
You can do it, RJ.
Beki's first because
she's really good at
applying prosthetics
and she's really fast at it.
But I just don't know what
to expect when it's my turn.
And switch!
Ah, go!
All right, what are we doing?
The prosthetic piece
that's already been applied
looks like a zombie
so I start hitting the eyes,
shadowing it
with some dark reds.
Well, hello.
I turn around the corner,
I'm pretty shocked
by what I see.
All the other teams
has prosthetic pieces
and we have eyelashes
and blue glitter.
Now I'm gonna
go over your eyes.
Just keep drying.
Perfect.
Thank you, sir.
I wanna do more things
but I'm worried
that ours is just
gonna be a wacky beauty makeup.
And switch!
Hi, friend.
I don't know who did what.
What is happening here?
I just know what
it looks like now,
and it's different.
Look up.
All right, can you lean
your head back a little bit?
We need more texture,
so I actually lay paper towel
on his nose and his lips.
By the time I'm done with that,
it's, uh, next person up.
And switch!
Round two, I run up...
Wow, they're doing a good job.
I-- I don't know
if it was Miranda or Sue,
but it looks good.
Oh, wow.
I'm really enjoying the way
the piece is coming together.
We're awesome.
I feel pretty
confident about ours.
I just have to paint this
as fast as possible
so that they can do
some detail work on it.
Ooh, ooh, um...
The vision I see is
getting a little jumbled.
But I'm hoping the blue wig
will lead these girls
into the right direction.
Wow, you look
really pretty, actually.
Turn your head this way.
And switch!
Oh, beautiful.
Switch!
No.
My God.
Look up.
Time's up!
Brushes down.
I know where we stand.
And it's not the top.
Pretty.
- Hey, you three.
- Hi.
Cool.
- Creepy.
- Yeah.
What was your concept?
I came over, I saw his eyes.
I had it in my head
we were going demon.
Did you know what direction
he was going in
when you saw it?
I saw where it was going.
I was like,
"my job is just to get it
all blended in."
You guys did a great paintjob.
I like your spackling.
- Thank you.
Hi, ladies.
So, who exactly did what?
I put the eyelashes.
I did the wig.
- Mm-hmm.
- The lips...
You did
the three dimensional stuff?
Yes.
Then I came in
and did the highlighting
and changed the eye shape
a little bit underneath.
I think you guys
had a couple of
different directions
going at the same time.
So tell us a little bit
about your makeup.
I was the first one up,
so I came over,
I saw that they were
sort of alien eyes,
and so I laid down the brow,
the chin and the ears.
I could see
where you were leading,
and these guys
were doing a good job
of following you
down that path.
So I feel like
it really worked.
Thank you.
- Hey, guys.
- Hello.
Wow.
I'm not sure
what it's supposed to be.
Maybe she got hit
with a paintball?
No, it's a zombie.
I'm not sure that those lenses
would have said "zombie" to me.
Blood looks great.
The blood was a good call.
Gave it some dimension.
Thank you very much.
- Thanks, you guys.
- Thank you.
So, Jennifer,
how did they do overall?
I think you guys
did a really good job
with a really hard challenge.
But I do think
some of the teams
worked a little better
than others.
Which team won this challenge?
I'm gonna go with...
The green alien.
- Aw, thank you.
- Awesome, thank you.
It's okay.
We can only have
one winner this week,
and, remember,
immunity is at stake.
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner of
this challenge is...
Beki.
Thank you very much.
I think Beki had a really
clear vision from the beginning,
and I think she set it up
so that her team could really
follow that vision,
and they did a great job.
- Congratulations, Beki.
- Whoo, thank you.
With that,
you have won immunity this week
and cannot be eliminated.
Whoo!
I will see you all tomorrow
for the spotlight challenge.
But for now,
head back to the house.
Going into this next
challenge with immunity,
I'm feeling pretty confident.
We're back in the lab again.
We see McKenzie and
a bunch of covered black boards.
Welcome to
your next spotlight challenge.
Today I have
a very special guest.
He's a hot new artist
whose innovative music videos
have been viewed over
20 million times on YouTube.
And his last album
reached number five
on both the R&B charts
and billboard's hot 100.
Wow.
His hit single, I love college,
has sold over 2 million copies.
So if you would please welcome
Asher Roth.
♪ I wanna go to college
♪ for the rest of my life
♪ sit back in this club
and drink Miller light ♪
This is ridiculous, wow.
I have his first albums.
How you guys doing?
I'm pretty excited to meet him.
Asher has a new album
coming out very soon.
It's called,
is this too orange?
Oh, cool.
Today,
you're going to be creating
an original piece
of artwork for him
that should be worthy
of an album cover.
So, Asher,
why don't you tell them
a little bit
about the new album?
I found out
along the way that orange
is the color of
the creative chakra.
So it's just warm,
fun, creative music.
I want you guys to get weird.
Have fun with it,
and just see how twisted
your minds are.
- We need to break you into
randomly-selected teams of two.
Oh, gosh.
Team one-- Jerry and Tara.
Team two--
Rayce and Beki.
Awesome.
Team three--
Ian and Miranda.
Team four-- Sue and Heather.
Team five--
RJ and Athena.
Team six--Brea and Matt.
Behind these pieces of fabric
are the backgrounds
that you will be working with.
So why don't I bring in
some friends
to help us uncover these?
Whoa.
Oh, my God, don't look.
- Okay.
- You okay, Sue?
I'm gonna turn.
I can't stand in the front.
We get to the lab today
and McKenzie is standing
with Asher Roth,
in front of all
these huge boards.
So, why don't I
bring in some friends
to help us uncover these?
Oh, my God.
They have no clothes on
and I can't look at them.
You okay, Sue?
My face is getting
hotter and hotter
and I'm just looking up
at the sky.
I'm gonna turn.
I can't stand in the front.
I just can't do this right now.
This is
a nude body painting challenge.
Yay!
I'm very excited
because everybody knows
that I am basically
a master body-painter.
So I finally
get a chance to shine.
All right, guys,
you need to select an element
of what Asher
just told you about his album
as the inspiration
for your designs.
Each team
must paint two models.
One must
blend into the background
and the other one needs to be
a character that interacts
- with the background somehow.
- Okay.
Each member of your team
must be responsible
for one of your models and
cannot work on the other one,
so it's very important
that you are both
on the same page, conceptually.
All right, guys,
pull down the sheets.
Oh, sweet.
Oh...
As you can see,
the models have been
pre-assigned
two backgrounds.
Keep that in mind
when you make your pick.
Models,
you can put your robes on.
Tara and Jerry, go ahead
and make your pick first.
We're checking out
the canvases.
On one side
we have this elephant
that's skateboarding
in the middle of the air.
Another one is a park bench.
There's one with a pool.
Then there's
the wall of sneakers.
And finally,
there's an old abandoned barn
with a noose hanging
in the middle of it.
I like this.
Tara and I
decide on the brick wall.
We both feel this one.
Although I'm not sure why.
Rayce, Beki.
Nobody wants
the shoe background.
In order to make that blend,
you have to paint
every individual shoe,
and there's
no getting around that.
Ian and Miranda.
Very nice to meet you.
Sue and Heather.
- Hi, Sue.
- Heather.
Nice to meet you.
RJ and Athena.
Yes, relief.
We are going straight
to the pool backdrop.
It's not an elephant,
but it's better than sneakers.
Brea and Matt, go ahead.
All I'm thinking is, "great,
"how are we gonna make
a wall of sneakers
into an album cover?"
Well, our photographer
will be here later
to capture your work.
And Asher will be
joining our judges onstage
to see what you've created.
Keep in mind,
the judges will be looking
not only at
the final image overall,
but your individual
contributions as well.
You have one day
to complete this challenge.
Good luck, because your time
starts now.
Athena is really good
at body paint,
and this is her thing. I don't
want to take that from her,
so I let her do the character
that was going to be
standing out,
and I'm going to take
the character that has to be
sunken in and
camouflaged to the background.
What if she's standing here
and does this pose?
We create these balls
coming out of the sky
that represent chakras.
Like-- like you're basically
reaching for something.
That's a great idea.
Okay, well, we need
some sort of dynamic pose.
We need to be thinking of--
It's gotta be an album.
I'm trying to draw some things
and come up with a design.
And incorporate it.
I mean, it's a park bench
with some bushes
and a drink on it, you know?
We may not be
the best body-painters here,
but we're certainly not
the worst.
Nope.
Tara and I come up
with a concept fairly quickly.
We want to blend the male
into the background of the wall
and have the female be
a graffiti tagger.
I like that she's gonna be
in color...
- Oh, yeah. No, that's--
- And you're gonna be
all black and white.
Tara says she's
a really strong body-painter,
so she should do the clothing
on the girl,
because that's gonna be harder
than doing the blend.
What if she's
spraying something orange too?
Like,
the finishing color's orange.
I was thinking of making her
into another elephant.
What's more fun than
an elephant on a skateboard?
I don't know.
- What do elephants eat?
- Peanuts.
- Peanuts!
Yeah, let's make him
hold a big peanut!
Still, that doesn't matter.
We have to figure out what it is
that we're using and stuff.
Well, it does matter,
because if they're interacting,
they can hold props
which interact with the coke,
or whatever the hell it is,
you know?
It's hard to think of
what you could possibly do
that would have anything
to do with Asher Roth
or an album cover.
We're looking at them,
and we have no idea
where to go with this.
We see sneakers, and I think,
"what can you do with sneakers?
"Hey, basketball player."
Does an ass cheek
make a better basketball,
or a stomach?
What do you think?
Ass cheek.
I ended up thinking, let's put
a basketball on her buttocks,
and just have him palm it.
'Cause if it's, like, her hair--
We haven't figured that out.
The concept
is definitely abstract.
These characters
are both trying to rip away.
He's part of the warehouse,
and he's trying to
bring her back in,
and because
she's freed herself from this,
she's become
this whole other entity,
so she's gonna be
almost glowing.
My biggest concern
is that the judges
might not get this at all.
Everyone else has started,
but Miranda and I, we're having
some pretty big struggles
with the conceptual design.
We can't figure out how to make
an album cover of this at all.
I'm throwing out ideas
to Miranda,
and she's not liking
any of them.
What the hell am I gonna do?
We gotta make an album cover
out of this,
and it's gonna be
a pretty difficult thing to do.
She could be like--
We have no ideas.
Could they be, like, someone's
peeking out of the bushes,
or like, I don't know, like,
something like that?
We just don't have the time
to continue conceptualizing.
And we're not really
getting anywhere.
We only have six hours
to do this,
so we really just have to
start getting painted.
We finally chose to go with
some kind of
hip-hop roller girl,
so I'm painting the tank top
and some sporty shorts
and some socks on her.
That's about the best
I could do.
I want to do the blend,
just because I feel like
it'll be easier
to match something
than it will be
to paint something else.
We are mixing color,
I mean--
- No, I think we're good.
- Not bad, yeah.
I said I thought
an hour for color, and...
- I think that's great.
- And we're doing it.
It feels almost like
we're wasting time,
but on the other hand, if
this color-matching isn't right,
everything's thrown off.
All right, let's see.
We're gonna try to incorporate
the title of the album,
"is this 2 orange,"
and the "2" being
the number on the Jersey.
The majority of the body
will be covered in paint,
because it's a naked
body-painting challenge,
but I'm using
a piece of rubber to create
his three-dimensional-looking
shorts.
How are you doing, you good?
- Great.
- Okay, tell me
if you're thirsty or anything.
Yeah.
I'm really still unsure
of myself with this elephant,
but as soon as I think I'm
heading in a right direction,
here comes McKenzie
and Ve Neill.
I am a little worried, because
I'm not used to body-painting.
What did you make
your elephant ears out of?
Uh, latex, cotton,
and armature wire.
- You're air-brushing?
I'm air-brushing
most of it, so--
And you're hand-painting,
for now?
I'm laying in with hand paint,
and then I'll make a little
stencil and clean up, and--
Got ya.
I'll be interested
to see how it turns out.
Me too.
"Me, too," well, that's scary.
First time
body painting, so--
Yeah, me, too, yeah.
Well, what's your concept?
The guy who is gonna be
blending in
would ultimately have his hand
being body-painted into the cup,
and then she's gonna be
reaching for the cup,
- so also reaching for his hand.
- Oh, okay.
So tell us about your concept.
We went towards
the spiritual side of it,
because when we were
talking to Asher,
he told us
it's all about the chakras,
and the color orange
is the color of the chakras.
- Hi.
- Hey, Matt, how are you doing?
- Great.
- How are you doing?
So, Matt, what's your
whole take on this thing,
are you happy
with what you're doing?
Um, it's a daunting task.
Um, but...
- Definitely--
- You got the hard job.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I'm just trying to--
I got everything planned out
so it's all, you know,
coordinated accordingly
to the racks,
and then traced a shoe,
and then created a stencil,
and then we airbrush.
Got ya.
What is your concept?
What we thought we would do
is take our male model
and blend him in
with the environment,
and what's
gonna be happening is,
he's going to be reaching out,
and so
she has already escaped
from this environment,
so she's very bright
and vibrant.
So both of them are
kind of an energy.
- Yeah.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
Okay, Ve,
which one do you think
looks the most promising?
I like
Rayce and Beki's concept.
I love the colors
in the female model,
and it looks like he's starting
on the back of her,
which means she probably is
gonna be turned sideways
a little bit,
so that would be very helpful.
I think everybody's
doing really well
except for Ian and Miranda
with their picnic table.
You know, if they had
a strong concept,
it might have helped them
a lot more.
And I think Matt really has
his work cut out for him.
He's gotta, you know,
detail all those tennis shoes.
I'm on the fence
with those guys.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Good.
Yeah.
Maybe an hour and a half
goes by,
and I'm starting to
worry a little bit about Tara.
Tara, come here.
I don't feel her colors
are pink enough.
There's too much flesh tone
showing through.
I just don't think
it's coming together.
And I'm-- I'm getting
a little worried about you.
- I'm not done yet.
- Okay.
I mean, if you love it,
then ignore me.
I don't love it yet,
but I'm not done yet.
I just-- I just think it needs
a lot more contrast.
Our characters are in this
black and white, gray world,
so if I paint
something colorful,
I'm worried the black and white
concept will be lost,
I've never even
painted on canvas,
so this is, like,
a whole new world.
"Is...This...Too...Orange?"
We are fifth hour
into our challenge,
and I am looking
to the right of me,
and I see Brea's model
getting light-headed.
That's why I'm thinking that
something is not going right.
You're doing great.
Almost done.
Yeah.
Things are going awesome.
I look at the clock,
we have 17 minutes left.
Next thing you know,
he takes a seat.
I'm like,
"why are you sitting down?"
Actually, will you stand up?
No, you gotta--
Okay.
You feel like you're
gonna pass out?
Are you okay?
I turn and I look,
and I see that Brea's model
is sitting on a chair,
and he kinda looks like
he's passed out.
I'm gonna get you some water,
okay?
Oh, great..
It goes from bad to worse,
like, real quick.
That's when I started
to freak out.
I have no idea
what he's going through.
No, this is not happening.
You've gotta be kidding me
right now.
- Coming up...
- This is like a bad dream.
Some people
really took chances,
and others played it
a little bit more safe.
I'm freaking out inside.
The body-painting
that you did here on the model
isn't good enough
for a face-painting booth
at a county fair.
Brea has been
working on this guy all day.
14 minutes
left in the challenge
and he's down for the count.
Everybody really freaking out
that this poor guy
just passed out
in front of everyone.
Okay, what about the oxygen?
Is that
helping your breathing at all?
Is he okay?
Uh, no, I guess they're just
gonna take him away.
The ambulance is coming.
Paramedics show up,
and they've got
a breathing tube on this kid.
They're rubbing my makeup off.
It is so depressing.
My world feels like
it's crumbling right now.
There goes my masterpiece...
Off to the hospital.
After they haul Brea's model
out, I start to worry a lot.
I start to wonder
if I should even finish my work.
Hey...
Don't worry about it,
it's not your fault.
These things happen.
And we're, like, almost done.
Everyone's freaking out,
but we all have to
maintain our composure
and get our makeups finished.
Guys, time is up!
This challenge is unique
in that
we won't be presenting the final
makeup in front of the judges.
They'll be judging
off a photograph.
We'll have ten minutes to take
pictures and do touch-ups.
- This is his girlfriend.
- Okay.
And he is going to hand him
a peanut with her nose.
Ooh, I like it.
I think you have to
move in more.
As the photographer
starts taking the pictures,
I'm a little worried,
because I didn't know
what was going to happen.
I was thinking, if I need to,
I will paint my body,
and stand there
and hold her ass,
'cause I'm not
losing this competition
'cause a model passes out.
Ready when you are, Miranda.
Perfect.
One...Two...Three...
Go.
Can you, like, bend your knees
and, like, really move?
Yup, yeah. Step away
and stretch over, yeah.
There are many horizontal lines
that are not gonna line up
if this thing is not
shot properly with the camera,
and I'm really
starting to sweat this.
Nice.
Go for him
and go away from him.
No, no, right hand away,
as it was.
Camouflaging
is very difficult to do.
I am extremely worried
that it's not gonna work.
So after everyone
gets their photos taken,
everyone heads home
and I'm in limbo with Brea,
wondering what's gonna happen.
The producers tell me
I'm getting a new model.
I'm thinking, "okay,
maybe the next day I'll do it."
Oh, no, no, no.
They tell me
I'm doing it right now.
Six more hours.
And my heart drops to my feet.
When we come back to the house,
and we all felt really bad
for Brea.
Now she's gotta do it again.
It's like, she's gonna be there
till midnight.
- Matt!
- Ooh, it's Matt!
Walking into the house,
everyone wants to know
what's going on, what happened.
Was there any, like, thing
actually stated
about what happened
to your model?
He wasn't hydrated,
and he was just out.
I feel bad for him,
but at least he's okay.
Brea will actually
be able to recreate
only what she made originally
and superimpose him
on the picture
that I've taken with my model.
She has an extra six hours?
- Right.
- That's 12 hours.
She's gonna be exhausted.
I'm really worried.
You know,
I did my part of the job,
I just want to make sure
Brea can pull it through.
Welcome to
the Face Off reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
Say hello to your judges.
Owner of optic nerve makeup
effects studio, Glenn Hetrick.
Hello.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
Hi, everybody.
Creature designer and
director, Patrick Tatopoulos.
Hi, guys.
And joining our panel this week
is chart-topping hip-hop star,
Asher Roth.
- What's up, guys?
- Hi.
So this week,
your spotlight challenge
was to work in teams
and create a piece of artwork
worthy of an album cover,
but you also had to
incorporate two nude models.
One blended
into the background,
and the other one
as a character.
Now as everyone knows,
there was an issue
with Brea's model yesterday.
Brea, the judges have been
made aware of what happened.
With that said, let's see what
you all came up with.
First up,
Tara and Jerry's creation.
When I see my picture blown up,
I could see
straight through the paint.
The airbrush
was not heavy enough.
My biggest concern
is the judges
won't get the abstract concept
that I'm going for.
It's not the best,
most elaborate concept,
and that might kill us.
Is it what they're looking for?
I don't know.
I'm really not sure
where we stand,
so I'm kinda scared
at this point.
I'm a little nervous
that the judges are gonna think,
"these girls went
way too kooky."
So we could definitely
be on the bottom.
When our photo comes up,
I am wowed.
I'm like,
"yes, that looks beautiful."
My model totally pops out
of the whole photograph.
At this point, I'm just,
"hey, what will be will be."
I tried my best.
I don't even know
what to expect at this point.
So, Asher, how do you think
they turned out overall?
I think there's some
really, really amazing stuff.
Some people
really took chances,
and others played it
a little bit more safe.
All right, everybody.
The judges
have scored your art,
so let's find out
what they thought.
RJ and Athena,
Sue and Heather,
congratulations, you are safe.
You can head back
to the makeup room.
The rest of you were the best
and the worst of this week.
So the judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Tara and Jerry, if you would
please step forward.
The colors are completely off.
To the eye it was perfect,
but in the photo
it looks absolutely awful.
I really don't want to be
at the bottom again.
I have no idea.
Maybe it is okay,
maybe it's not. I don't know.
I see all the problems with it.
I'm freaking out inside.
To start, could you tell me
a little bit about the concept
that you were
working with here?
We had this black and white
background,
and originally, you know, it was
Jerry's idea to do a tagger.
We decided to make her part of
this black and white world,
and since he mentioned orange
is the color of inspiration,
it's the orange paint that's
giving her life in her hand,
but fades away into her
little black and white world.
That said, I think that
the blend is the more successful
of the two, but I really don't
understand what's going on.
The body-painting that you did
here on the model,
in my opinion,
isn't good enough
for a face-painting booth
at a county fair.
It just completely fails.
The shadows and the highlights
don't work at all.
The character
this particular photograph
in black and white was
a really poor decision.
- You know?
- Yeah.
The whole thing about
black and white,
if you don't have a contrast
with it, then it's pointless.
Feels careful.
Nobody tags like that.
That's not happening at all.
Um, but, yeah,
it just feels like you guys put
these unnecessary restrictions
on yourself
when doing this piece.
Jerry, Tara, please step back.
Rayce and Beki, you're next.
Judges, as a reminder,
Beki has immunity this week.
Ve, let's start with you.
You told me your concept.
Can you revisit that for me?
Instead of taking, like,
the literal approach
and try to fit something
into that picture,
we took
the emotional value of it.
So we said, "that's a dark,
ominous background,
"we want to make our characters
have some kind of
opposite reaction."
We wanted her to be, like,
she's ripping away,
and she's actually
trying to pull him
out of the ominous environment.
So that's why his hand's
starting to shake and crumble
and turn that white color.
I really like your concept,
and I think you've pretty much
effectively created
the look
that you were trying to achieve.
And I do like her paint job.
Taking that all
into consideration,
I think it's
a very effective image.
One of the great quality
of this image for me
is the fact that you're using
different techniques.
You're using a lot of airbrush
and you're using the sponge,
I assume.
I went in a little bit
with the airbrush.
- A little bit.
- To give me some of that--
The blending technique.
But texturally,
they feel quite different,
and I feel that was--
One of the most appealing things
about this image for me
- is actually that.
- Thank you very much.
From just
a high-concept standpoint,
it's tempting, it's alluring.
I like it a lot, I think
it's really, really cool.
- Thank you.
All right, Rayce, Beki,
can you please step back?
Ian and Miranda,
please step forward.
Did you guys have a concept
for this piece?
I live in New York, so, uh,
I see a lot of girls skating,
and it's usually hip-hop
they listen to,
and we also wanted them
to interact as well.
That's why we made
his hand the cup,
and she's skating
towards the cup
to try and grab it.
Maybe she was skating around
and got tired.
Overall, the concept was very
difficult to come up with.
Well, whatever time you spent
on conceptualizing it
was an utter waste of time.
Your character on the left
is actually holding the cup,
yet we're trying to make him
blend with the background.
Either you choose to make him
a part of the cup language
or you just make him disappear.
It's a little confusing to me.
- Since I never
body-painted before ever,
it was--
It was difficult for me
to figure out how to attack it.
Ultimately, the thing
I dislike about it the most
is the lack of passion.
You didn't pick
because you thought
you had a strong concept
to work with.
You picked because
you thought it might be
the easiest thing to
integrate body-painting with.
You aimed
for perfectly adequate
and didn't even get there.
Miranda and Ian,
if you'd please step back.
Matt and Brea.
So which one did what?
Tell me.
I did the basketball player
and he did the background,
blending it in.
We constructed a stencil
with the outline of a shoe,
and just airbrushed
the, uh, white shoes
to start for a base,
and went in and detailed
all the fine details
on the shoes.
It's actually,
uh, quite remarkable.
Uh, the whole--
The whole piece is.
- Thank you.
- Very, very impressive.
Matt, you're the man, dude,
seriously.
Job well done.
Uh, working with
what you were given,
uh, this is very, very conducive
with the hip-hop culture
and with shoes and athletics,
and using the butt
for the basketball
that's just-- It's funny.
It's got a sense of humor and
it-- it grasps your attention.
So job well done.
I really, really,
really like it.
The shoe integration
is just insane.
I still-- I'm staring at it
for how long now,
and I still don't know
exactly where the edges are.
That's impressive.
You know, my only criticism,
I think, of this,
is the fact that
the lettering is just
a little bit dodgy.
You probably could have cut out
a stencil of some sort.
But everything else,
I think you guys both did
a pretty great job on it.
Well done.
Okay, Matt and Brea,
will you please step back?
The judges have heard
what you've had to say,
so if you'd please
head back to the makeup room
while they make
their final decision.
Okay, judges,
so let's start with
some of the looks
you liked the most.
Beki and Rayce.
Conceptually, it was
a really, really amazing piece.
You know, they took a chance and
I think they really exceeded.
Technically, it was
really beautifully executed.
The only thing is,
part of the job was to create
a great integration
to a background,
and I don't think
Beki succeeded at that.
Okay, so let's move on
to Brea and Matt.
I think Matt did an amazing job
with his blend of the tennis
shoes was just phenomenal.
You know, even Brea,
she had a huge setback.
- Absolutely.
- She worked 12 hours yesterday.
- Right.
- To do that.
That's a lot of painting
to expect somebody to do.
Okay, so let's talk about
some of the bottom looks then.
Jerry and Tara.
It's very lopsided
in terms of whose fault it is.
Such a squandered opportunity
to do something so amazing
and really incorporate it
into the hip-hop world,
especially when
the taggers are the idea.
It turns out to be
quite a boring
and very uneventful image.
Okay, what do you think
about Ian and Miranda?
I think Ian an Miranda just
totally blew it on this deal.
You know, the blend for me,
uh, didn't really cut it.
If you're not
going to bring it,
if you're not gonna
take on every challenge
as hard as you can,
then why are you here?
Very forgettable.
It's forgettable.
- Yeah.
- All right then.
Judges, have you
made your decisions?
- Yeah.
- I think so.
- Believe so.
- All right.
Let's bring 'em back out.
Okay, Asher, why don't you
tell us about the top teams?
The top teams...
Rayce and Beki.
I loved it...
Conceptually, technically,
job well done.
Thank you.
And Brea and Matt.
Overall, everything just tied in
and blended together very well.
Mission accomplished
all the way around.
Thank you.
Which team came out on top?
The top, top, top team is...
Okay, then which team
came out on top?
The top, top, top team is...
Brea and Matt.
Yay, high five!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations, Brea and Matt.
But, as you know,
we can have only one winner.
So, who will that be?
Every single artist
ran away from those shoes.
Matt, you killed it, man.
Congratulations.
You got it.
Yay.
I'm feeling really great.
And I'm so excited to hear
that they love what I created.
I'm so thrilled
about that piece
I'm gonna-- I'm gonna go home
and I'm gonna figure out
how to get so many people
to see that piece,
because it's really cool.
I'm excited about it.
It's great.
- Congratulations, Matt.
- Thank you.
You and Brea can head
back to the makeup room.
Thank you.
Beki, Rayce, you are also safe.
Please head back
to the makeup room.
Unfortunately,
that means that you were
our bottom looks this week.
If you would please
all step forward.
Glenn.
Jerry and Tara,
your poor technique
and lack of color
resulted in
an incoherent image.
And, Ian and Miranda,
we felt you had an
unacceptable lack of passion
and an absence of direction.
So then, who is
going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Miranda.
I just feel that you
are not yet prepared
to meet this level
of challenge.
I really, really appreciate the opportunity,
it's been a great learning experience
- Good luck.
- Miranda I am so sorry
that you happen eliminated.
If you'd please head
back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
I'm going home.
Aww.
I'm frustrated that I didn't
showcase what I'm capable of.
I'm gonna miss
all these people here.
We've formed some
really strong friendships.
It's been awesome
to be able to come here
and just be given
this opportunity.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net