Previously on Face Off...
The artists were
asked to create
an original horror villain.
Don't do that!
Ian claimed victory,
but Brea's villain
failed to impress,
and she was sent home.
Now ten artists remain.
And tonight...
The artists face their
most dangerous challenge yet.
Oh, my gosh.
And tempers flare
like never before.
It looks too clean.
That looks like [Bleep].
I'm filled right now
with revenge.
Leading to a dramatic
showdown onstage.
That's really [Bleep]
that you're throwing her
under the bus.
Like all of that was just
working for me.
I'm going to be brief:
Shameful.
It's one of the best
I've ever seen.
And to make it to the top,
they'll have to impress
our award-winning
panel of judges.
Ve Neill, three-time
Oscar-winning makeup artist
whose work includes
Beetlejuice,
and The Amazing Spiderman.
Patrick Tatopoulos,
production designer
on this summer's Total Recall
and director of Underworld:
Rise Of The Lycans.
And Glenn Hetrick,
cutting-edge makeup artist
on The Hunger Games
and custom designer
for Lady Gaga.
Who will be the next great
name in movie magic
and earn $25,000 in makeup
supplies from Alcone,
the reinvented 2012
Toyota Camry hybrid,
and $100,000?
Only one will win Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Brea's gone, and I'm so upset.
She's my best friend
at the house.
I love her.
Makes it real.
Now I feel very lonely.
As long as I'm here, I'm
always gonna be here for you.
It was always us against them,
and now it's just me and Matt.
Just say that you wanna
win the next one.
I wanna win the next one.
Victory would mean a lot to me,
and my dad as well.
'Cause before he passed away,
he always used to tell me,
"I'm gonna get you back
to California someday."
And I think that my being here
is him keeping his promise.
My dad's been pulling strings
since this whole thing started.
Right, talking to God.
Him and God have coffee
every morning.
"Let's talk about my son RJ.
He's a good boy,
a good boy!"
You have him down.
Are you sure
you didn't know him?
We're walking through
this very dense woods,
and it feels like huge forests.
It's a big, intense atmosphere.
We see a bunch of wild animals.
It's creepy and woodsy,
and we're looking around like,
"what the heck
are we gonna do?"
Hey, guys.
Good morning.
Please welcome our
guest judge, Sam Huntington.
He's currently starring
as the werewolf character, Josh,
on SyFy's smash hit series
Being Human.
Hi, guys.
Oh, my God,
it's Sam Huntington.
We're in the woods,
and he plays a werewolf.
There has to be
something up here.
Sam has worn a tremendous amount
of special effects makeups
and also has
a very unique perspective
on today's
foundation challenge,
which is to create
an original trauma makeup--
Wounds that would have been
inflicted by a werewolf.
In your opinion,
what do you think it takes
to make a great trauma makeup?
Well, there's a lot.
Realism of placement,
where on the body
the werewolf would attack?
How old the wound is,
timeframe,
how long ago did it happen?
Maybe it's started to heal.
If that's the case,
maybe the person is starting
to transform themselves.
There's been a million
werewolf movies,
so a different approach
is what I'm looking for.
- Thank you, Sam.
- Yeah.
All right, guys, you got
90 minutes for this challenge.
Your models
and your workstations
have been randomly
assigned to you.
The winner of this challenge
will receive immunity
and cannot be eliminated
this week.
Good luck,
because your time starts now.
Now!
Go! Go!
Run! No, I'm sorry.
I get excited.
- Gonna get me some cuts.
- Excuse me.
So we all run to the table,
and we see a bunch
of foam appliances,
and so I immediately
grab three of them.
How open to getting
disgusting are you?
Whatever you want.
I see some tubing
and some syringes,
and I thought,
oh, this is awesome.
We're gonna do
a blood tube gag.
I love the foundation
challenges.
Being fast is one of my assets.
I've worked on some projects
where we had to do traumas
really fast.
Are you ready to be bitten
by the werewolf?
I'm doing a lot
of 3rd degreeing,
which is the skin-safe
silicone.
And then I'm going to use
some vinyl gloves
to dangle some skin down.
- Can you take your shirt off?
- Sure.
Yay.
Creating wounds is a fundamental
aspect of special effects.
You have to know
the underlying anatomy
if you're gonna create
huge tears.
All right, guys,
you have an hour left.
Pulling back the lip
is something that no one else
is gonna do.
I liked Sam Huntington's
suggestion
about transitioning
into a werewolf.
So I'm gonna go with hair
spreading out from his wound.
30 minutes.
First I put down the tubing
and make it stick out
a little bit
so it looks like a severed
jugular vein.
Then I have this idea, okay,
I'm gonna make an eyeball
hang out of her face.
And that's what
I wanted to see.
Werewolf snack.
Argh!
All right, 15 minutes left.
I'm doing a werewolf
that he's been bitten
or he's fighting,
and as he's still trying
to fight for his life
he's starting
to change already.
We're running out of time.
We only have one minute.
Lift your arms up.
Beki's model is bloody.
She's gonna need
several showers.
Time is up, everybody.
Stop your work.
Sam and I are going to see
how you did.
- Hi, Tara.
- Hi, Sam.
Tell us about
your werewolf attack.
He was putting up a good fight.
First he got hit,
and then he starts turning,
he starts healing up.
- And you hand-laid the hair.
- Mm-hmm.
It looks very nice.
What we've got going on
is a laceration
across the throat,
and then on the right side
we've got a claw mark
across the eyes.
I love that it's over her eye.
The only critique I would have
is there's no hint of her eye
underneath there.
Exactly, that's what--
It looks like she never
had an eye.
I like that you made his ear
pointy with the hair.
Yeah, there weren't
any ears, so...
Yeah, and I like
the transformation.
It's all focused
around the wound too.
That's neat.
So if I was the werewolf, argh!
- Nice!
- Grabbed her.
Oh, my God, that's disgusting.
It's pretty awful.
Oh, man, she definitely gross.
I really like
that you incorporated
the bite mark in there,
and it's really successful.
It looks really great.
Thank you, thank you.
This is lunch.
She's not even gonna turn
into a werewolf.
She's just a snack.
And I put these little guys
in the back.
- Oh.
- Oh, yeah.
I'm no doctor,
but I can tell you right now
that's gonna be
an issue for you.
Yes.
People don't realize
how much actors know
about the special effects
industry.
Sam is constantly
in makeup all the time,
and he's surrounded by this,
so he's an expert.
So that is a completely
original prosthetic right there,
this piece right here?
Yes.
Gross.
All right, Sam,
so what did you think?
I think you guys are amazing.
Doing what you did
in 90 minutes, mind-blowing.
Who do you think did the best?
Heather, very, very cool.
I loved how the transformation
that you had started
was localized around the wound
and how the depth changes
from the ear down to the chest.
Bravo.
I'm one of the top makeups,
so that's pretty exciting.
It's my first time to really get
called out for good things.
And, uh, and Beki.
Beki, of course.
It's always Beki.
Really cool.
The depth of all your wounds.
Really like the concept.
I loved your bite mark.
I thought it was
really, really cool.
And who is our winner?
The winner is...
Beki.
- Thank you very much.
- Beautiful job.
Yes, yes, it was tremendous.
I really, really enjoyed
all of it.
Going into the spotlight
challenge with immunity,
I'm gonna be here
for another week.
That's awesome.
Beki, congratulations.
You have won immunity this week
and cannot be eliminated.
All right, everybody,
I will meet you
back at the lab
for your spotlight challenge.
Oh, my gosh.
Everything's changed.
All our tables are moved,
and there's animals
and plants everywhere.
There's aquariums with lizards.
There's an owl.
There's a bunch
of really big wolves.
There's not a big barrier
between me and any of them.
At any point, they can just
rip our heads off.
There's a bear
and a guy with a gun.
Hey, guys.
As you can see,
we've made a few changes
to the lab this week.
You are now standing amongst
some of the most beautiful
plants and animals on earth.
But don't let that fool you,
because this is nature's
way of warning you,
of luring you into a trap.
Because all of these things
are extremely dangerous.
Some of these things
can even kill you.
That is this week's
spotlight challenge,
to create something
not only stunningly beautiful
but also extremely deadly.
You'll be working
in teams of two.
Each team will select
a plant and an animal
and use elements from them
to make your final
creature makeup.
Your teams have been
randomly selected,
and they are Heather and Rayce.
RJ and Ian.
Jerry and Matt.
Athena and Tara.
And Beki and Sue.
My partner is Beki,
and I'm not thrilled at all,
because she thinks
too highly of herself
and she has immunity.
Now if you would please stand
next to your team members.
Obviously we're standing
amidst an incredible
array of animals,
but I do have one more for you.
Guys.
- Oh, my God.
- No way.
So today
is the spotlight challenge.
McKenzie's introducing
all these different
plants and animals.
They are some
of the most beautiful
and some of the most deadly.
And there's something moving
around behind this green wall.
Guys.
Oh, my God.
No way.
That is awesome.
- Damn.
- Oh, my goodness.
I'll be damned if there's
not a rhinoceros in the shop.
Wow.
That is a southern white rhino.
- Holy crap.
- It looks like a dinosaur.
Its head is as large as me.
It's insane.
- Pretty amazing, huh?
- It's cool.
You will now select
a plant and an animal
and use elements from them
to make your final
creature makeup.
Heather, Rayce,
make your choice.
The water monitor's
right in front of us,
and we loved the wrinkles
in his skin and his pattern,
so don't even look
at the others.
All right.
Shoot.
Yeah.
Slipper orchid I really like.
Look at the face.
Oh, my God, this is so neat.
Athena really likes
the bright colors of the snake.
Her paint jobs have been
so phenomenal
that if she has a plan,
I'm gonna go with it.
What do you say?
You afraid of it?
Uh...
What goes with that color?
Yellow iris.
That's what I was thinking.
Oh, wow.
This is pretty incredible.
I want to do the white rhino.
Sue thinks that
it might not translate,
and I've got immunity.
I should really let her do
what she wants to do.
And the bird of paradise,
right?
Let's do it.
All right,
so it looks like you have
everything that you need.
You will have half an hour to
look at your plants and animals
to draw inspiration
for your designs.
Good luck, everybody.
Your time starts now.
I'm letting Rayce
do the sketching.
I don't wanna sketch
next to him
- because that man's amazing.
- Good grief.
We have no appendages.
What will we do
with his arms and legs?
Do we wanna go for realistic
or do we wanna go for, like--
80% realistic,
20% theatrical.
It's gotta be subtle.
It can't be this overdone
Halloween [Bleep].
That's really cool.
I'm thinking, what if the
chameleon camouflages itself
as the orchid?
- It's up to here.
- Exactly.
Beki and I were sketching,
and I'm surprised
it's going so well.
We both want to have
a female tarantula
just to give that
beautifully dangerous aspect.
Yes, perfect.
Right on the same page.
Crazy.
At the end of the day,
I'm a little worried
about our creature.
I feel like we have some ideas,
but it doesn't feel like
a complete picture.
Time's up, we gotta go, guy
so I'm hoping we'll still
be able to pull it out.
- We start
our 12-hour lab day,
which is all we've got
for this challenge.
What if we make it
a Mayan Aztec warrior?
My goals today are to sculpt,
mold, and cast in foam
the cat face.
For the sculpt, you take clay
and work on the stone positive
of the model.
Your sculpture is going to be
what your prosthetic
will end up looking like.
Our concept is 80% lizard
and 20% firestick.
I was gonna make some holes too
so we could, like,
put some stuff in front.
Oh, yeah, I agree.
Rayce and I are working
really well together,
and we decide
that he will sculpt the face,
and I'll do the headpiece
and the tail.
I like the profile.
Yeah, I'm liking
the profile too.
All right, you take over
on this sculpture.
I'm gonna work on the flowers.
The orchid has
those three leaves.
There's a big main leaf
and two leaves off to the side.
And then there's a couple
at the bottom.
So I go ahead
and I start fabricating
the back piece out of
vacuform plastic
and a heat gun.
And I'm making the shapes
of the petal as I go.
We come up with
what I consider to be
a great concept.
It's got this spider face
and an exoskeleton
and arms with these
petaled leaves.
Sue is very adamant about
just sculpting the face.
I just wanna make sure
that we have a costume
for our creature.
You think the petal
is not a good idea?
- Yeah, no.
- Okay.
I think it should be
a spike like,
psh, psh, psh, psh.
I'm getting apprehensive
about her direction style.
One of the ideas
that I came up with
was to put petals on the back.
And if he, like,
curled up into a ball,
it would, like, spike out
from the curve of his back.
Hey, guys.
I'm here with ve to do
a little walkthrough today.
I'm always excited to see ve.
I'm very starstruck
when she comes in the room.
It's a chameleon, right?
So he's camouflaging himself
as the flower.
And it secretes, like, a poison
ivy kind of rash thing, yeah.
- Poison Ivy, I did her.
- Yeah, I know you did.
You have immunity, right?
That's true.
Are you worried about that?
Um, I believe that Beki
always puts 110%.
And what's his tail
gonna be made out of?
Foam latex.
It's a big piece.
You guys are so bloody brave.
- I know.
- Wow.
Is this gonna be
something fabricated
- or is this gonna be--
- It's gonna be foam latex.
- It's gonna be foam.
- Yes.
Okay, let's talk
about Heather and Rayce.
She's got that big old
tail in there.
That freaks me out.
Why does that make you nervous?
'Cause it's a big mold,
especially to do out of foam.
But I think
with Tara and Athena,
it might have looked really
cool to do the snake
in silicone.
Foam has a tendency
to give things
- a very matte look.
- Matte, dull.
And the silicone
would have given it
that creepy,
shiny effect, you know?
All right, Sue and Beki.
I think they have
some really cool ideas
as far as the design
of it goes.
As long as they remember
to incorporate the flower,
it should be really cool.
All right, well,
I cannot wait for tomorrow.
Me too.
Hey, Rayce.
I'm making pincers out of foam,
and I'm gonna make it
look textured.
But I look over and I see Beki
is already painting her suit,
so I realize
that we're diverging
off of different styles.
Are you gonna shave it?
No, I'm not.
What kind of texture
are you going for then?
Not that texture.
That looks like [Bleep].
I thought you were gonna
make those a lot smoother.
Hey, do you think that this
would look more real
or this would look more real?
I would say if you're
gonna go with this,
then your whole spider
needs to have that.
Right.
Sue comes over and she
wants some advice from Rayce.
And I'm thinking,
maybe you should
go ask your partner
these things.
He said that this looks
a little bit too clean,
but maybe we can put
flocking on it.
To tie in her two elements,
she wants me to texturize
the entire exoskeleton
of this creature.
My opinion doesn't matter.
Sure, no problem.
I'm about to lose it.
I cannot handle that Sue
is so unaware
of how terrible
this is going to look.
That looks like [Bleep].
Beki is working on
a full-body creature suit,
but it looks too clean
and suity.
I'm sorry, what were
you discussing with Rayce?
Oh, I was just asking him
what would look better.
So my opinion doesn't matter.
- Dude, I need your advice.
- Huh?
Beki's not cooperating.
I feel like she's slowing down.
I think you should just do
what you need to do
to get it done, even if you have
to downsize it a little bit.
Okay.
I think we are creating
a big pile of [Bleep].
When the sculpture is finished,
it's time to make the mold.
You do this by putting cement
on top of the sculpture.
Once it hardens,
you fill it with foam
or silicone,
which eventually becomes
the prosthetic.
My creature's flower petal
is painted from the back
so that the paint's
foggy matte finish
doesn't cloud the plastic,
and then that way the inside
is still glossy and shiny
and looks very wet
and plant-like.
I really want
to impress the judges.
So instead of just doing
regular body painting,
I'm going to make
every single scale
any apply them all on the body.
To cut all these and glue
all these individually,
you know, I think
they should go on in sheets,
not one by one.
It's gonna kill us.
I know Athena gets
carried away in the lab,
she happens to regularly
put all this effort
into a project
that she doesn't end up using.
Like, I see where
you're going with it,
and I like it,
but I think it needs
to have, like,
a little bit of
the smoothness with it.
I just wish that we were
on the same page.
After this, I mean, it's gonna
be cohesive anyway.
I hope that I didn't
offend you or anything.
Oh, my God,
she won't stop talking.
This one thing's not being
cooperative and I hope that--
I think I am being cooperative,
am I not?
I'm adding texture.
You went over and asked
somebody else their opinion.
That's not working with me.
That's working
with somebody else.
I'm feeling like Sue
has misdirected me.
Sue wanted it to match
with the two little pincers
that she made.
I'm regretting the fact
that I allowed her to take
the alpha role
in this situation.
It's the end of the day.
I look up and I'm like, ugh!
This could turn out horrible.
I know Ian isn't really
enthused about this,
but I have been the underdog
this entire time,
so I have to step it up
a notch.
If it doesn't work out,
send me packing.
One minute, everyone.
One minute.
That's time, everyone.
So it's application day.
We only have four hours
with our models
and one hour
of last looks onstage.
That come out okay?
I'm a little worried
about Beki.
- It came out all right.
- Yeah.
Risking my staying
in this competition on her
is a little scary.
What's up, Ticia?
Whoo-Whoo.
Oh, ladies.
At least we got a tail.
I'm pretty nervous.
We have so much to do today.
Immediately I get started
on the application.
I do the bald cap,
I apply the face,
apply the head.
All this time, Rayce is
trimming up the tail,
painting the tail.
Going as fast as we can.
Do you want to pre-paint
while I'm putting
the bald cap on?
I could start, yeah.
I can throw a piece down
like nobody's business
in about 20 minutes.
So Ian took over the paint.
But I was getting concerned
because he was taking more
time than he should be.
Hour and 20 minutes.
The application
is taking way too long.
With the fully body to paint,
we need a lot of time.
Look way, way up.
We have the cowl piece
and the prosthetic piece
and palm pieces to apply.
But our model
seems very irritated.
She has really dry skin.
While applying the prostate
on under her eye,
she's twitching and
moving her body repeatedly.
It's really stressing
Jerry and myself out.
And we're just wondering
if we can get this done in time.
I have to go to the bathroom.
15 minutes, everyone.
I'm in this panic mode,
and I'm thinking,
oh, my God, are we gonna
get done in time?
I'm franticly rolling
up these spines
while she's painting.
And I barely get them done,
and I'm like,
oh, God, I hope
these things stick.
What do you think
about this so far?
It's all right.
This is not going
to be a pretty thing
when it gets done.
I think her face
looks like blue mud.
I feel like I just made
like a Disney character spider
or some [Bleep].
Sue and Beki, theirs is--
It's just not looking good.
She spent, you know,
two hours pre-painting it,
and that's what it looks like.
- No.
- Yeah.
Beki's spent all day
in the spray room,
and we still have to get
the entire body suit on
during last looks.
Time's up.
Gotta go.
I honestly believe
Beki's sabotaging the project
'cause she has immunity.
Coming up...
- Please welcome Vivica A. Fox.
- Wow.
It's one of the best
I've ever seen.
It's got rubber barf
all over it.
I'm going to be brief.
Shameful.
It's last looks,
or the last 60 minutes of doom
if I like to put it.
This might be a little painful.
We are so far behind that
I don't even have time
to breathe
in this next 60 minutes.
Are you gonna
cover it with leaves?
No, we only have
three more leaves,
so paint it up with as much
blue as possible.
I don't think we should do
this hard of lines.
What?
The one thing I'm worried about
is it can't be body paint.
It's beautiful,
but less body paint
and more real.
Body painting is just
a different type of look.
It's a little less realistic,
but luckily the spines are
gonna make this look good.
His eyes are mean-looking.
You're ready for a spidey
mardi gras right now.
Everything looks like
it's coming together.
I looks good for how much
time we had.
It's a full--
Full-length makeup.
These things are falling out.
Can't get the spines to stick.
Ian, Ian, Ian, come on.
Turn, turn, turn.
Well, guys, that's it.
Time's up!
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
Say hello to your judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve makeup
effects studio, Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
Hi, everybody.
And creature designer and
director, Patrick Tatopoulos.
Hi, guys.
And our guest judge this week.
You know her from her
blockbuster films
Independence Day,
Kill Bill Volume One,
where she was the beautiful
but deadly assassin
Vernita Green, AKA Copperhead.
Please welcome
Vivica A. Fox.
Hi, guys.
Vivica A. Fox
is on our stage this week.
Vivica, thank you so much
for joining us tonight.
I'm very happy
to be here, McKenzie.
And I've had the pleasure
of working with Ve
on Batman & Robin
where I played Ms. B. Haven.
Another beautiful
but deadly creature.
Absolutely, she was.
All right, guys, this week
your spotlight challenge
was to work in teams
and create a creature
that was not only
stunningly beautiful
but also deadly.
Let's see what
you came up with.
♪
Little guy comes out
and he sells this thing.
Turns out exactly the way
I conceptualized it.
It's beautiful and deadly.
And we're like, "yes."
I feel like he definitely
has a presence.
But I feel like
we missed an opportunity
to really take advantage
of the plant.
Our model is the only one
that has painting.
It's a complete look.
Compared to everybody else's,
who just decided to do
half a body and just put
some sheets on the bottom.
I'm really happy
about our collaboration
because it's
a very innovative design
and very cool to look at.
Our leopard woman is pretty.
Her character is the only one
that might be in a real movie.
The rest of them
are Halloween costumes.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look.
Why don't you go ahead
and open your arms up
so we can look at everything
and just keep them open.
Can you move your mouth
up a little bit, yeah?
Don't put
your fingers in there.
- That's right.
- Might miss one.
This is pretty tight.
For the time that they had,
that's a lot of detail.
We've had to really
cut a lot of corners,
so I'm really worried
about what the judges
are gonna think.
The hair fascinates me
more than anything else.
I like the hair.
I was worried that this tail
wasn't gonna come out.
- It did.
- It came out good.
It's all stencils
and it repeated
over and over and over again.
The judges walk up,
and it's just no smiles.
Oh, God.
I feel awful.
And the paint job,
it's not popping.
We shouldn't have chosen
a snake.
I get this whole thing
that's going on right here.
Open and close your mouth.
Thanks for the cat noise.
It helps.
It does help.
I don't know what to say.
The judges have scored
your creations
and would like to speak
with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Athena, Tara, you are up first.
Let's start with who did what.
I sculpted the face.
I did the chest, the shoulders,
the legs, and the back.
I think you both know
that you're in some trouble
- here on this one.
- Yeah.
I've seen you sculpt better.
I've seen you paint better,
so I expected more.
The colors are one
of the biggest problems.
Very disharmonious.
We had talked about
putting pants on him
so that we didn't have
to cover so much body.
But now he looks like he
has underoos on, right?
This is comical.
Why in the heck didn't
you use silicone?
It would have given it that
slimy look to him, you know?
It's really flat.
It's nothing, you guys.
You totally blew it.
I'm gonna be honest with you,
I love the color.
But then when we got up close,
especially along the back,
you guys could have used
a little bit more iridescence
to make it look wet.
I wish we'd had more time.
Well, you don't.
It's a challenge.
Yep.
Athena, Tara, please step back.
Heather, Rayce,
please step forward.
This is another
good design from you, Rayce,
and I'm actually
very impressed with the mouth.
I think it's one of the best
reptilian mouths I've ever seen,
because this mouth does not
look human at all.
It's stunning.
Thank you.
I wanna compliment you
on that rock star
hair style right there.
That is very modern.
Yes, rock on, babe.
However, my biggest complaint
is gonna be them toga pants.
You coulda figured out
some kinda way
to spray paint 'em,
to do something,
instead of them being
so bright white.
I know.
Heather, Rayce, will you
please step back?
Matt and Jerry, you're next.
Tell me a little bit
about your concept.
Why did you decide to dress it
with floral elements
rather than integrating
the creature?
We didn't want to go mutant.
We thought beautiful, leopard.
It was different
from everybody else,
and it just felt right.
I see what you've done,
but in the front
it looks like someone
in a bathing suit.
And maybe not introducing
white on the face,
because it feels
a bit more cartoony
because of that.
I have to agree with Patrick
that you guys missed on using
more of the yellow iris.
This thing that's going on
around the neck,
is this something
that you sculpted?
It's supposed to be
an armor mantelpiece.
I get it,
but it seems like that time
would have been better spent
finding a way
to sculpt something
that had to do with
the plant and the animal, yeah?
Jerry, Matt, please step back.
Sue and Beki, you are next.
I'm going to be brief.
Shameful.
I think you both know that.
The safety pylons on his arms
and big, giant floaty tubes
coming out of his back.
I really don't think
that could have won
a costume contest at
a third grade Halloween party.
It looks like it's got
rubber barf all over it.
At the last moment,
Sue suggested that we texturize
the entire piece.
What, you have a gorgeous
model under there.
Where's the beauty in this?
I'm so bummed out, 'cause
I was really expecting it
to be so cool.
Unfortunately, I did take
heavy direction from my partner.
That's really [Bleep]
that you're throwing her
under the bus 'cause you have
immunity this week.
Well, I disagreed with this,
so I have to defend the fact--
That is the least
of your worries.
All right, Beki, Sue,
step back.
I didn't work this hard
to be thrown under the bus
and be thrown out
this competition unfairly.
That's not right.
I want to win this competition
more than ever.
RJ, Ian, please step forward.
Could you guys start by
explaining who did what?
I sculpted and painted
the piece as well.
I did all the preform
with the heat gun
and the sculpted piece
over the forearms.
Overall, I really
was not thrilled
about anybody's work
in this challenge.
That said, I think that this
was extremely successful
in combining the plant
and the animal.
The thing I like about it
the most is solid direction.
It came out arms together.
You've got this flower shape
that then opens up
and reveals your animal's
head underneath it.
And it was very simple,
but oftentimes
things that work best on set
are exactly that,
just clever and simple.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
It's very reminiscent
of another one of those
Batman films I did
or poison ivy where she opens
up out of the orchid,
and I know that's what
you were going for.
And you did a great job.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
The successful aspect
of this piece for me
is the fact that he doesn't
look like a human,
and that is key for me.
If I was to play this
as a character,
I would love to open it up,
blow out some dust,
hittin' with them tentacles.
Like, all of that was
just working for me.
Thank you.
Ian, RJ, you can step back.
All right, the judges have
heard what you had to say.
Please head back
to the makeup room
while they make
their decisions.
Well, that was interesting.
Talk about being dangerous
and beautiful.
I'm filled right now
with revenge.
Thanks for throwing me
under the bus there.
I don't think
I threw you under the bus.
I think you gave me
such heavy direction,
and I followed your direction.
Okay, so let's talk about
all of tonight's looks.
Why don't we start
with some of the better ones.
I did like RJ and Ian's.
That is absolutely this week,
for me,
the only one
that if developed further
would have succeeded
as a character.
What I really like is when
you saw that piece unfolding
there was not much
of a human left.
That was cool to me.
I also thought that
Heather and Rayce,
I thought they did
a really good job
with the rock star hairdo
that they did on top.
Yeah.
Okay, so let's move on
to some of the ones
that weren't quite
so successful tonight.
Why don't we start
with Tara and Athena.
I don't know,
she's had a lot of chances
to show us her body painting,
and there's always
been an excuse
why it hasn't come off
the way she wanted it.
I don't get it.
They failed miserably.
I mean, I don't know how
they couldn't look around
and see how much
any of the other teams,
they all at least did more.
All right, let's move on
to Sue and Beki.
Your thoughts there?
That's a team that didn't seem
to work well together,
that's for sure.
She looked like
a mean old walrus.
I really can't understand
how anyone who wants
to be in this business
could have looked at that
and not done something.
Both teams were directionless.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
Yeah.
Let's bring 'em back out.
♪
All right, Glenn, who is
the winner of this challenge?
The top team tonight is...
All right, Glenn,
why don't you tell us
which team came out on top.
The top team tonight is...
RJ and Ian.
For successful integration
of the plant
and animal concept,
which was the point
to our challenge.
- Thank you.
Great job, guys.
But we can only
have one winner.
So, Glenn, who's that?
Our winner tonight is...
♪
RJ.
For providing
the driving concept
and also the successful
fabrication
of all the plant elements.
Winning this validates
my entire life.
And I just keep thinking
about my dad.
I know he's here for me.
And this feels amazing.
- Congratulations, RJ.
- Thank you.
You and Ian can now head
back to the makeup room.
Heather, Rayce,
Jerry, and Matt,
you guys are also safe.
Please head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you.
So that means the rest of you
were on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Beki, you have immunity.
Please head back
to the makeup room.
The rest of you,
please step forward.
♪
Sue, the decision making
with your creation
was just crippling.
And, Athena, Tara,
quite simply,
there's a profound
lack of quality
in the work that you
put out this week.
All right, so who's
going home tonight?
The person that's
going home tonight is...
♪
Athena.
This was your third opportunity
to show off your skills
as a body painter,
which we do believe
that you have,
but we're just not seeing it
and we can't go any further.
Athena, I'm sorry
that you've been eliminated.
If you would please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- We wish you the best.
- Thank you.
- No! No way!
- Yep.
I am definitely
proud of myself,
'cause I have not been doing
special effect makeup
for a long time.
And I'm a little bummed
that I didn't get a chance
to really show off
my full potential,
but every rejection
makes me stronger.
- Hey, guys.
- What are you doing here?
- We are not quite done yet.
- No.
- Ooh.
- What?
Oh, hell, what's going on?
I think somebody else
is going home tonight.
Come on with me.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net