Tonight, on the season finale
of Face Off...
Three artists remain,
but only one can come out
on top.
Rayce.
I'm a tattoo artist from Idaho.
I shouldn't even have got
on the show,
and yet, I'm in the finale.
This is crazy.
It's very elegant
and pretty, and I like that.
I'm so close, I can taste it.
- Ian.
- I just got out of school.
I'm the youngest person here,
and I've got a couple of wins
under my belt.
I'm starting
to actually believe in myself.
This is a stellar makeup.
I feel like
I've grown exponentially.
- RJ.
- Been teaching high school
in west Virginia
for eight years.
I need the money,
I need this exposure
to get back and do this
for a living again.
This whole design
is so clever and cute.
I have a good shot
at winning this.
They'll battle
in one epic final challenge.
I've never done a prosthetic
for a dance routine.
My heart's just, like,
boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
- Wow!
- I think it's even worse.
I'm really bummed right now.
All of my characters
had something wrong with them.
- My brain is fried.
- RJ is getting overwhelmed.
- I don't care.
- Do you want to switch?
It is a disaster.
Help me.
- You can't glue that down yet.
- Take this off.
- I love it.
- It all goes down
on the biggest stage
in Face Off history.
There are so many people
there, it's overwhelming.
- I'm almost shaking.
- This is the moment of truth.
Now it's time
to put them all to the test.
I'm a nervous wreck right now.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic and win it all?
Find out tonight
on the season finale
of Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
the hell
out of the people we love.
This is the longest I've ever
been away from my kids.
And it's really messing with me.
And then today,
I'm walking down the hall--
And I see my family.
Oh, my gosh!
Ahh.
I see my girlfriend Alana.
I miss you too.
My little sister
is on the computer!
I miss you.
To just hear their voices,
and seeing their faces--
I couldn't ask
for anything more.
I miss you guys so much.
Seeing her really justified,
to me, what I'm doing here.
I'm trying
to make a name for myself,
so that I can better take care
of the people that I love.
You guys look fantastic.
You look like
you're all a year older.
This whole competition
is for them.
And I need to really step it up
for this last challenge.
This is the finale,
and one of us is gonna win
100 grand.
Alana and I
could really use that.
We're looking to move
to California.
Ahh, this is crazy.
All right, I love you guys.
Bye-bye.
It was neat
to have us all reconnect
with the people back home.
Big guy.
It's the last challenge
of the season,
and we all have this spark now.
I think we all need to vent.
Good morning, guys.
Good morning.
There's only one challenge
standing between you
and our grand prize.
Your final spotlight challenge
will not only test your ability
to create incredible makeups,
but also create
highly functional ones.
That's because
they will be tested,
three days from now,
performing
a choreographed dance routine...
- Whoa.
- In front of a live audience
at the historic Alex Theater.
Whew.
I've never done a prosthetic
for a dance routine,
never done
a makeup for a dance routine.
So I don't really know
what to do.
Each of you will pick one
of three film genres--
Fantasy, horror, and sci-fi.
This is awesome.
Based on your genre,
you're going to have to create
three characters to go with it.
There is no way I'm gonna
be able to do three makeups
and get them onstage,
ready to dance, by myself.
Let's pick your genres.
I would really love
to have fantasy,
which is the basis
of what I love to do.
- RJ.
- I'm gonna take fantasy.
All right,
I can live with sci-fi.
You know, grew up
with old Star Trek.
- Rayce.
- Sci-fi.
Damn.
Great.
Well, then I guess, Ian--
Horror.
Ooh.
I'm just not a big horror fan.
So we realize
that creating three characters
is too much work
for one person.
So we brought in some help
for you.
Whoo!
All our fallen brothers
and sisters come walking in.
Look at all
your beautiful faces.
Oh.
Okay, so you will each get
to choose three
of your former competitors
to join your team.
Rayce, you get to pick first.
- Jerry.
- Yes.
- Ian.
- Think I'll go with Matt.
- He's good with horror.
- I've been absolved.
- RJ?
- Got to take my roommate.
- Give me a hug.
- Miranda.
We all chose people
that are going to play
to our genre really well.
- I'm ready to win?
- To win.
Okay, so you all
will be meeting
with our choreographers
Lindsay and Craig
a little bit later on
to go over your designs.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
Before we really get going,
I want to get
a good, hard, strong concept.
The stakes are high,
so I have to give it my all.
We have two females, one male.
We came up with
a luciferian character.
We could have one owner
of these two chained-up beings.
The two hellhounds
will be fallen angels.
We need some rib-cage appliances
and also hands
for the luciferian character.
And we could break the chains,
so they could do
their dance routine as well.
I think that's pretty solid.
Let's draw, girls.
My team is called "RJ's Angels."
They could be fairies.
- Trolls.
- Mermaids.
All three of us are
just tossing these ideas out.
- Vampires.
- Mutants.
- Two-headed elves.
- RJ is getting overwhelmed.
He doesn't want to step
on anybody's toes.
- I don't know.
- He doesn't understand
that he's not hurting
our feelings,
but he needs to make decisions.
You got to help us.
- You got to direct us right now.
- I think-- Okay.
Let me get that for you, sir.
If any time I'm gonna do
my style, it's the finale.
It's got to be all me,
at this point.
I want to have
a very light entity,
and I want to have
a very dark entity
that represent
two different worlds.
And then there's gonna be
the woman character.
She's gonna be split
down the middle,
pulled into
two different dimensions.
What do you guys think?
Too weird?
- No, not at all.
I think it's really good,
actually.
I couldn't have
come up with that.
We immediately start working.
Miranda is sculpting faster than
I've seen her sculpt before.
Which is great, because
the stakes are amped up on this,
and I want Rayce to win.
My brain is fried
from this season.
Hi.
How're you guys doing?
How are you doing?
All the dancers
will be dancing together.
But each trio will have a moment
where they get to shine.
We want to break the chains.
And then have them
do their own dances.
You guys are
kind of choreographers.
- This is nice.
- I'm loving it.
Craig and Lindsay
gave us the okay,
and it was just awesome.
Thank you.
We've got this mask that's
gonna be velcroed together.
And then they're actually
gonna rip it apart
- and then reveal her face.
- It's pretty cool.
I just want to make sure
that they have full vision.
- Cool.
- How're you guys doing?
Hey, everybody.
I finally decided
on my concept.
We had this idea
where he would be wrapped up
in these ribbon things
and they would be
actually pulling on it.
It won't work.
'Cause you wouldn't want them
to be restricted.
They need to be able to move
around as much as possible.
Okay.
So we realize
we have to start from scratch.
And we have six hours left.
- We got to start sculpting.
- Yeah.
I don't think RJ sees
how much needs to be done
in the little time frame
that we have.
Come on, you can make up
a fantasy character, RJ.
Eventually, I go,
"Okay, forget it.
Here's what we're doing."
There's a Phoenix
being fought over
by an evil alchemist,
and this good Mother Earth
is trying
to protect the Phoenix
from this evil dude.
Okay.
And then we finally start
to sculpt.
What if we just had a skeleton,
and the muscles are coming out?
Yeah, that looks perfect.
I'm feeling pretty good.
We have a lot to do still.
And I'm giving each artist
creative freedom.
Hey, boss man, want to come
take a look at this?
These first two days,
I really want
to get everything molded,
because that gives us
the third day
to pre-paint everything.
Then we're gonna be sitting
really well for application day.
I like it.
Athena's sculpting the Phoenix.
But when I look over there
and I see this cartoon parrot,
I get freaked out.
Do you think you'd be okay
with more of a realistic thing?
RJ needs to say,
"Hey, this looks like a parrot,
not like a Phoenix."
This is looking
really good, though.
And I'm like,
"Oh, my God!"
Looks like a hot mess.
Beki's sort of kicked me
in the butt.
So I start to take apart
Athena's beak.
But time is running out.
I'm getting very nervous.
By the time
the clock strikes zero,
I'm freaking out, because
if we're this far behind,
we're not gonna get
everything done in time.
Coming up...
I've actually brought somebody
to mentor you through this.
Holy shit.
Fuck, it is a disaster.
Welcome to the Face Off finale.
This is it.
Day two--
and we only have ten hours
to bust all this stuff out.
But I feel like
we're a little behind.
Athena's beak kind of
reminded me of a parrot's.
So I was like, "Let me
tweak this just a little bit."
I made the beak
a little bit more streamlined.
- Yeah, I like it.
- I don't know about that.
I don't think
it's too big, honestly.
I think that'll move fine.
Because this is a lot
of surface area.
Matt's continuing on that cowl,
and then Sue's working
on the face of Lucifer.
And Tara and I are gonna work
on the two hellhounds.
I want to really nail
these forms,
'cause these are the things
that are gonna sell my concept.
But I also know that the colors
have to be just perfect.
Okay, check out
the color schemes.
The only thing I worry about,
conceptually,
is Rayce's choice
to go with gray scale.
I think it might be a mistake,
because it's not
very theatrical
and they're gonna be dancing
on a stage
with lights and sound effects
and smoke.
Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I know you've got
a lot going on,
but I've actually brought
some help in for you--
Somebody to mentor you
through this.
- It's my dad.
- Oh.
- Hi.
- Whee!
Michael Westmore is "the guy."
He is an Oscar winner,
Emmy winner.
I mean, so many
wonderful things have come
from his incredible imagination.
It's just awesome
to finally get to meet him.
- Hi.
- Hi, Michael Westmore.
Nice to meet you, wow.
So tell us about your designs,
your concept.
We have one male figure,
which is the dominant
Lucifer character,
holding two hellhounds
on leashes.
Also, I just thought of putting
leds into the eyes, here.
On Star Trek,
we had leds everywhere.
And we actually put it someplace
where you have enough overhang
where it'll actually put
a glow against the eyes.
Cool, cool.
This is gonna be
our luciferian character.
I blocked it out,
and Sue's working on it.
And also Matt is working
on the headpiece.
- We're all collaborating.
- In the end, though,
if it didn't work out,
you're responsible.
You're the one that
wears the hat.
The concept is fantasy.
I really like the idea
of a Phoenix.
If you want to keep out
of trouble,
you might extend it more,
'cause it isn't gonna take you
that much longer to glue it.
Fine, I was gonna take
this beak area
and do the vacuform,
so it's actually hard.
It would hold up, with foam.
Put a high gloss over
the top of it,
- which firms it up a little bit.
- Thank you so much.
We're playing a little bit
with fourth dimension
- and alternate realities.
- This, I really like.
Is there anything
that goes back here at all?
I'm staying away
from that part of the neck,
just because we know there's
gonna be a lot of movement.
She will have a bald cap.
Make sure
you get that down good.
What else do you have?
This is our ethereal character.
I like it already.
I do.
Do you think that it needs
a skin texture over it?
I like it smooth.
I really do.
Okay, so why don't we start
with Ian?
He's got a great concept,
but his sculpt needs
more smoothing down.
They looked more like witches
than they did beautiful--
- Demons.
- Demon women, yeah.
- Okay, let's move on to RJ.
- I love his design,
with all the little flame pieces
of sculpture that he's doing.
My only concern with him is he
has a lot of different textures.
That's kind of, for me,
would be the downfall
or the success of his makeup.
Okay, let's move on to Rayce.
It's gonna depend
on how the paint job goes.
My only concern
is with his leading lady's face,
because he's got two faces
going there,
that they both stay individual.
- That it doesn't become--
- A muddy mess.
A muddy mess, exactly.
I can't wait
to see the final looks.
Good luck, everybody.
Thank you.
I think maybe
the nose should go back more.
Like, wait.
Isn't it pointy, like that?
Like, once you see the front?
No, you can see through
on the side.
That's something
you haven't said yet.
- And it's not in the drawings.
- It's in all the drawings.
No, it's not.
Tara's got a little bit
of an issue
with the sculpt on the face.
Okay, no, see,
you were just telling me
that this part was see-through.
And I'm, like, "No, no."
- No, no, no.
- That's what I was asking.
I don't like to tell people
when they're messing up.
- Ugh!
- So, I'm just like,
"Yeah," you know,
and then I'll fix it.
- I don't care.
- Do you want to switch?
Sure.
I just wish I hadn't wasted
so many hours.
Different position
for me to be in.
Just got out of school--
I was always told what to do.
Hey, guys, that's time.
We're done.
Let's get out of here.
Day three--
we come in,
and I definitely have my head
back in the game.
All you have to do
to put that mold on correctly
is to slide it
and then put it down.
I got in there, and I told
everyone what needed to happen,
so I think we're getting back
on track.
You know what would be
kind of deep?
If the mask looked like a baby.
Holy shit.
I love it.
Jerry is phenomenal.
I have a lot to learn
from his experience.
Make sure you paint
that shit today.
Okay.
My main goal in this group
is to keep RJ on track.
We are here for him,
so he can win this challenge.
We're creating things
that are beautiful.
But I'm worried the Phoenix
could go from pretty to gaudy...
- In 5 seconds.
- In 2.5 seconds, yeah.
I'm letting Athena do her thing
with this wig.
But it's looking pretty freaky
at this point.
So I needed to say something,
because there's a lot at stake.
We could do four more
little ones in these spaces.
You got it.
I know, I know.
On day three, I am noticing
what RJ and his team are doing.
And it's so gorgeous.
RJ's making a concerted effort
to incorporate
every type of makeup.
He's got silicone prosthetics,
foam prosthetics,
body pieces, face pieces.
He's got headpieces, lace wigs.
I'm like,
"Wow, I'm impressed."
Shit.
I look over
and Ian's hand molds
are not wanting to open.
And I see the color is,
like, drained out of his face.
We're running out of time.
And these hands are a big part
of the luciferian character.
I don't even know what happened.
We've got, like,
five minutes left
and my heart's just, like,
boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Coming up...
We're so behind
on our paint schedule.
Help me.
It is a disaster.
The winner of Face Off is...
This whole season
boils down to this.
I look over,
and Ian's hand molds
are not wanting to open.
I don't even know
what happened.
And these hands are a big part
of the luciferian character.
We've got, like,
five minutes left.
My heart's just, like,
boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
We finally get it to open.
These hands are like shit.
It is a disaster.
The fingers are breaking.
These hands
are not gonna happen.
I don't have the time
to do it again.
So my main focus
is gonna be on my fabrication.
Time's up.
We got to go, guys.
Damn, we have a lot of work
ahead of us.
It's gonna be intense.
Today is application day.
This is it, you know.
This is the last day.
We have four hours
to work on our model.
And then we have one hour
of touch up,
before they go onstage.
- We have chest pieces!
- Oh, yeah.
I really got to bring it today
and I've got the team to do it.
But we've got
a lot of work to do.
Wow!
This is all supposed
to not be here.
Hmm.
This one, I think,
is even worse.
It's so thick.
The chest pieces
came out too thick.
And so I go in and manually cut
nice, clean edges.
Ah, it's so much time,
but I guess we don't really
have much of another choice.
I hold, you cut.
Oh, shit, people are here.
Hi, you guys.
How're you doing?
He's gonna be Lucifer
and you're gonna be
his two hellhounds.
You're our Phoenix, okay?
And the Phoenix
is the centerpiece
of the entire, uh, costume.
I pick up the Lucifer
character's tailpiece.
That thing weighs
a good five pounds.
And it should weigh
just a couple pounds.
That's like...
That's hella heavy.
For a dancer that has
to wear this thing,
it's gonna look like
a water balloon on his head.
This is crazy.
I decided to cut some
of the inside of the foam out
and it'll take a lot
of that weight out.
That's a lot lighter.
Okay, RJ, do you mind?
I'm gonna start
these arm things now.
Wait, oh, wait.
You can't glue that down yet.
The application of the Phoenix
has to be perfect
the first time.
Because it's a thin piece.
There's no peeling it up
and putting it back down.
All right, wait.
The headpiece has
to go on first,
and then the face has to go on.
And that's got to go up
underneath these pieces.
That's true.
So take this off.
Pieces went down out of order.
And we have
to peel some stuff up
to get the neck down
underneath the shoulder,
- or it'll pop right back off.
- You want to get in here?
- Open this up.
- Okay.
Everything has to be perfect.
I really want to win,
at this point.
Teamwork makes the dream work.
Here is your face.
All right, you can go ahead
and turn like this.
At the start of this day,
I wanted everything
to be glued down in two hours.
And two hours has passed
on the clock,
- and we're not there.
- Rayce,
do you want this
to cover his nipples?
Or does this go under?
You worried about it--
How it stretches up?
I'm worried about his earrings.
We've just begun eating
into our paint schedule,
which is not good.
Okay, do you want me
to color the beak?
I think we're gonna look good.
You finish what you're doing.
- Look at the time.
- We got it.
I believe
everything's glued on, right?
Uh, yeah.
Paint time, now.
- Are you liking it?
- Looks really good.
- All right, help me--
all right.
Right now, we're behind.
We don't have any appliances
pre-painted.
- Where do you want it to end?
- That would be perfect.
You can gray out these.
How are we gonna hide that?
- Five minutes.
- Holy shit.
Yeah.
You fit him,
and I'll pack my kit.
Hey, guys, that's it.
Time's up.
I'm looking around,
I'm like, "Great."
RJ seems to be almost done.
We still have a hell
of a lot of costume,
hell of a lot
of painting to do.
Last looks is gonna be rough.
We come to the Alex theater
and, of all the last looks
we've had,
this is the most important.
Last looks--
It's totally different.
Each team has
their own makeup trailer.
It's like being on
a real film set.
Damn, this just got real.
Oh, lord,
this is gonna be cramped.
- Behind you guys.
- Ready?
We're an hour away
from this thing being over,
so we really need to bring it
right now.
Face me.
If you could blend around
her eyes, that would be great.
Dry brush these veins too.
This is actually
supposed to be white.
Oh, shit.
We're so behind
on our paint schedule.
- The whole chest in red?
- Yep.
Okay.
What do you want me to do?
All this skin underneath needs
to be airbrushed black.
I am so proud of these girls.
I'm feeling a lot of love.
Just wish we had more time.
Sue, just fucking do something.
Just paint it?
There's not even time to think.
We just have to do 'em.
Okay, I'm gonna glue
your beak in.
You ready?
Are you gonna be able
to dance in those?
Yeah.
Now, that'll stay on
through the dance routine.
Hey, guys, that's it.
Time's up.
This whole season
boils down to this.
I really hope
the judges give me some leeway
with the paint jobs.
It's, like,
an hour left of work.
I'm really bummed, right now.
All of my characters
had something wrong with them.
Hey, we did what
we could do, right?
There's $100,000
hanging over my head,
and it's huge.
This is where I win
or I lose the competition.
Brushes are down
and I finally start to think,
"Holy shit,
I could really win this."
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome your host,
McKenzie Westmore.
Hey, everybody.
Welcome to the Face Off finale.
And now,
please welcome our artists.
We walk into the theater,
and there are so many people
there, it's overwhelming.
This is the spire.
I made it to the finale,
and I didn't expect
to get this far.
This is it.
It's gonna be the end
for two of us,
and one of us is gonna win.
Tonight, you are going
to see some amazing work
from our
extremely talented finalists.
For their spotlight challenge,
we asked each artist
to create three original makeups
based on a specific film genre.
Now, there's a huge
prize package on the line--
$25,000 dollars worth of makeup
from Alcone,
the reinvented
2012 Toyota Camry hybrid,
and $100,000 cash.
Before we see the makeups,
I would like to introduce
you all to our panel of judges.
First, we have
the owner of Optic Nerve
makeup effects studio--
Glenn Hetrick.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
Oh, yeah.
And creature designer
and director,
Patrick Tatopoulos.
Okay, tonight, our studio
audience will have the chance
to vote for their favorite group
of characters.
And the judges are going to take
that number into consideration
when they decide on the winner.
So let's get to it.
Tonight's first creations
are from Ian.
He had "horror."
Our guys come out,
the lights are hitting 'em--
It looks awesome.
The demons are creepy
and very disturbing.
The judges really seem
to like what I did.
The feeling I wanted to portray
in the makeups
is definitely there.
But, the paint jobs
aren't anywhere
like I wanted them to be.
Next up is RJ, with his take
on the fantasy genre.
I'm getting a little worried,
because when my makeup comes out
I'm not hearing
the crowd response
that I was hoping to get.
I'm really happy
with the skin tone
on the Earth Mother,
but I would've liked
to have seen
a little bit more brown
in the leg area.
But overall I can't be more
happy with the way they look,
because, in my head,
that's exactly what I saw.
And finally, we have Rayce
and his characters
from the sci-fi genre.
They look cool.
They look so much better
onstage
than they did when they were
walking away from the trailer.
My in-between character has
that weirdness that I wanted.
They're pulling off this look.
I'm liking what I'm seeing.
The dark character's spikes
are looking cool,
and I'm feeling really good,
right now.
Now, that is just
the beginning.
Because now it's time
to put them all to the test.
They're performing in a number
choreographed
by Lindsay and Craig,
to the track Cinema
by Benny Benassi,
featuring Gary Go.
Let's check it out.
This is the moment of truth.
My models are gonna
be moving quickly.
I'm a nervous wreck right now.
♪ I could watch you
for a lifetime ♪
♪ you're my favorite movie ♪
♪ 1,000 endings ♪
♪ you mean everything to me ♪
♪ I never know what's coming ♪
♪ forever fascinated ♪
♪ hope you don't stop running
to me ♪
♪ 'cause I'll always
be waiting ♪
♪ you are my cinema ♪
♪ I could watch you forever ♪
♪ action thriller ♪
♪ a cinema, a cinema ♪
♪ You are my cinema ♪
♪ I could watch you forever ♪
♪ love you
just the way you are ♪
♪ my cinema, my cinema ♪
♪ cinema, cinema ♪
♪ cinema ♪
The dance is one of
the coolest things
I've ever seen.
Yeah!
Whoo!
And I think the roar
of the crowd
really gave me a big boost
of confidence.
Then, all of a sudden,
I see some places where
the prosthetics have come up.
My gut just sinks.
This could be it.
The dance routine was pretty
vigorous on the makeups.
And the abomination guy--
He's actually starting
to lift up on the elbow.
I see some places where
the bald caps have come up.
This could be it.
All right, everybody,
it is time for you to vote for
your favorite group of makeups.
Please make your selections now.
To our studio audience,
you have all helped to make this
a wonderful evening.
Our judges will take your votes
into consideration,
but now it's time for them
to take a closer look
and deliberate in private.
Thank you all for being here.
Have a great night.
All right, judges.
I'm sure you're dying
to take a closer look,
so come on up.
I'm first up, and that's
pretty nerve-racking.
I really hope the judges give me
some leeway with the paint.
Ooh, the nails are all eroded.
I really like that little
bat thing-- It's fantastic.
He sculpted the whole thing?
Oh, and his wings come out
to the side.
- Exactly.
- Wow.
Quite striking with the makeup.
My blood pressure's
through the roof.
It's beautiful.
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
The judges would like to speak
with each of you,
to learn more about your work.
Ian, if you would please
step up.
Hi, guys.
Tell us a bit
about the backstory.
That's our Lucifer character,
on the right.
He is the angel of light,
the illuminator,
that's why we chose to go white.
And these two women represent
fallen angels which he enslaved.
The chains represent
the Lucifer character
almost unleashing them
on mankind.
I think that you have
some exceptional concepts,
but I'm not sure how
they integrate together.
There's a massive contrast
of color.
They're too far apart--
The three of them
aren't married.
- But I love the sculpture.
- Thank you.
I've never seen
that makeup before.
I don't believe
I've ever seen a makeup
- like that before either.
- Wow.
And that pushed up face
with the muzzle coming out.
And I love the fact
that the horns are poking out
and they're starting to bleed.
I just wish you would have given
it just a little bit of sheen
somewhere along the line.
Probably would have
made them look a lot scarier.
- It was just time.
- Well, Ian,
I'm always looking for someone
to do something different,
unique.
I like that the Lucifer
character is actually in white.
I think it's great.
You took a chance that way--
It doesn't bother me.
Again, what I will remember
about your work tonight,
is how original
and unique it is.
Thank you very much.
All right, thank you so much.
- You can step back.
- Thank you all.
Good job, Ian.
I'm almost shaking.
I'm like, brr...
All right, RJ.
Okay, RJ, tell me
what the backstory is
on your fantasy characters.
The Phoenix represents me,
through Face Off,
like the Phoenix rising
out of the ashes.
You guys have given me
a second chance
at a life
that I always wanted to have.
Well, this is really
interesting and unique.
Every, single character is
a complete makeup, head to toe.
- Fabulous job.
- Thanks.
How did you come about
building that headpiece
for Mother Earth?
That's all hemp.
And there's a plastic
vacuform shell in there.
Well, all of your headpieces
are really great.
My only complaint
is I would have liked
to have seen
Mother Earth pretty.
We did want to go
for a more matronly look.
It would have been nice if she
would have been a pretty matron.
Kind of like me.
RJ, you could put any makeup
on there,
I'll always know
which one is yours,
because you have a style.
You could put the vines
in multiple ways,
but the way they were put,
it really follows
the shape of the muscle.
It's like it's very organic--
you pay attention to the body.
That's super important.
Even little details,
like your sorcerer's hair--
The way you pulled it out
to the side and it--
Very, very cool.
The Phoenix character
is cool from the front,
but is even cooler
from the side.
I love the fiber optics,
I love the profile
of the feathers.
If I have any concerns at all,
it is some of the airbrushing
seems a bit directionless.
You've got, like,
a lot of heavy flames.
And then there's some areas
that sort of go to circles.
That is a minor complaint,
with the amount of work
that you guys accomplished.
RJ, thank you so much.
- Rayce, you're up next.
- Awesome.
We looked very closely
at the erosion of the makeups,
over the evening, and
throughout the dance routine,
which was another element
in this challenge.
And it seemed to me
that perhaps you had
the greatest struggle with that.
- Yeah.
- But...
You've come up
with three amazing makeups.
They are exceptional.
The sculptures are exceptional.
And when they stand there,
it actually creates an illusion
that there's a shadow
cast upon... The dark half,
and it goes from dark to light.
And that is so awesome.
Thank you.
There's an element texture
I wanted to keep on both sides
so that it helped identify
the different dimensions.
It's very, very effective.
It's so fantastic that you have
a third character in the middle
that shows us that moment
of transformation.
You feel like
it's happening right now.
- Very cool.
- Thank you so much.
I think my favorite one,
out of the group of them,
is the middle one.
Even looking straight at her,
there was three complete heads.
I mean, it just was creepy.
- Well, thank you.
- Rayce, you can step back.
Job well done,
every single one of you.
You have made our jobs
very, very difficult.
Well, the judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you would please head back
to the makeup trailers,
while they make their decisions.
Before we go into deliberation,
you should know
that the audience picked Rayce
as their favorite.
- They did?
- Yes.
What are your thoughts on Ian?
The head
on the luciferian character--
Such a great sculpt,
such a great design.
- Creativity.
- The whole thing, creatively,
- was so great.
- Creatively, was powerful.
The paint, across the board,
was kind of flat for me.
Yeah, but he also manages
to bring something different
- every week.
- He's a natural.
And what about RJ?
It's very powerful
at a distance.
I think when you get closer,
it feels less
like a realistic makeup.
I think he does really fun
characters.
They have that whimsical quality
that I really like.
He's a kind guy.
And it reflects--
- Yeah, and it pisses me off.
- Become creative--
I can imagine.
All right,
let's talk about Rayce.
He knocked it out
of the park, for me.
I loved the way those two
characters came together
in that middle character.
It totally blew me away.
And the paint job was amazing.
Clearly, he goes
beyond the two dimensions,
thinks three-dimensionally
as well.
That's very rare.
All right, judges,
have you chosen your winner?
I believe so.
Glenn, who is the winner
of Face Off?
The winner of Face Off is...
Glenn, who is the winner
of Face Off?
The winner of Face Off is...
Rayce.
Ohh!
Oh, my gosh.
Whoo!
Oh, my gosh!
You're kidding me.
Thank you, guys, so much.
Oh, my gosh.
I can't believe it.
I understand how huge
winning Face Off is,
and how it's gonna
change my life
and change my family's life.
I am so grateful
for this experience.
I love that Rayce won.
He is so talented.
And I don't think my future
has ever looked this bright.
I'm happy for Rayce,
because he's a hell
of an artist.
This experience
has been amazing.
Give me ten years--
I want to see where I'm at.
Congratulations, Rayce.
We do have one last piece
of business.
Want to go see your new car?
- Yeah.
- Come with me.
- Whoo!
It's just a dream.
I'm waiting for someone
to poke me with a fork
and wake me up, right now.
It's too nice.
I don't think I've ever sat
in anything that nice.
It's all yours--
the all-new
2012 Toyota Camry hybrid.
I can't go back
to being a tattoo artist.
Now there's this ambition spark
that's just burning inside me,
and I wanna go to make movies right now.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net