Previously on Face Off...
The artists were asked to create
- a Tim Burton-inspired character.
- Yes.
I feel like a crazy toy maker
right now.
- Rayce claimed the victory.
- Cool.
But Beki fell short
and was sent home.
Now five artists remain.
And tonight
they'll face a challenge
of Jurassic proportions.
Did not see that coming.
This is to get into the finals.
These stakes are so high,
everything has to be on target.
It's "Go big or go home,"
at this point.
This was like a kick
in the face.
I decided to tear off
the sculpt.
It sucks to be me.
Who will triumph
and earn a spot
- in the series finale?
- I'm going home on my birthday.
My God, it's fabulous.
I think you might have
overextended yourself.
I'm just shattered right now.
To make it to the top,
they'll have to impress
our award-winning panel
of judges.
Ve Neill-- Three-time
Oscar-winning makeup artist,
whose work includes Beetlejuice
and The Amazing Spiderman.
Patrick Tatopoulos--
Production designer
on this summer's Total Recall,
and director of
Underworld, Rise of the Lycans.
And Glenn Hetrick--
Cutting-edge makeup artist
on The Hunger Games
and custom designer
for Lady Gaga.
Only one will win Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- Very quiet now.
- Too quiet.
I'm starting to realize
I do have a chance
of getting to the finale.
And I want to win.
'Cause I could really
use that money
to hopefully get out
of a lot of debt
and really start a life.
I was was very shocked
Beki got eliminated.
Wow, that was pretty crazy
last night, huh?
That means that they were
probably expecting me
to, like, utterly fail.
I want to make my fiance
proud of me.
That's my dream.
He's the one
who actually told me
"This is your one shot.
Just go ahead and do it."
I really want to take this one.
I believe it is anyone's game.
But winning this competition
would be awesome for me.
I would be able to expand
my makeup and effects business.
And I want to bring
that championship back
to Austin, Texas.
- Morning, everybody.
- Good morning.
Congratulations.
The five of you
are all within reach
of the season finale.
I'm so close, I can taste it.
But this isn't about me.
It's about providing
a better life for my family.
Now there's no question that
you are all extremely talented.
But we only have room
for three of you
- in the finale.
- We all just look at each other
and we're like,
"You got to be kidding me."
Did not see that coming.
Double elimination--
This was like a kick
in the face.
- Whoa.
- Rayce, you okay with that?
Shocked.
A little bit
of pressure now, huh?
Okay, so let's talk about
this week's spotlight challenge.
We're gonna do things
a little bit differently.
I'm sending you on a field trip
to a mystery location.
Oh, man.
Every time we had a field trip,
I didn't do too well.
So I don't really want
to go anywhere.
When you arrive,
I want you to head inside,
take a look around,
and choose an option
that is laid out for you.
After you make your choice,
I want you to spend
just a little time
taking photos,
working on your designs.
There's a van waiting
for you outside.
Good luck,
and I want you all
to think big.
We've already done
big, elaborate makeups.
How much bigger can we get?
We rode up in the van,
for our field trip,
and none of us know
where we're going.
I love surprises,
so I can't wait
to see where we're going.
We're at
the Natural History Museum!
That's my favorite museum
of all time.
Man, that's awesome.
It's dinosaurs.
I'm walking through
the hallways
of these huge, giant behemoths,
and those teeth
are, like, the size of my arm.
There's two things
that I started off drawing
when I was
five or six years old--
He-man was the main one,
and then dinosaurs
was the other.
I love dinosaurs.
"Your spotlight challenge
this week is"--
"To create a dinosaur-human hybrid."
"Judges want you to embrace
the scale and scope
of these creatures."
"Fabricated elements
are strongly encouraged."
It's so important
that you get the right dinosaur
that's going to be perfect
for you,
especially when the stakes
are so high.
Everything has to be on target.
I want to go triceratops,
but it's a lot of work.
That is a lot of work.
I chose the carnotaurus.
And I start sketching.
One of the most important parts
of any good makeup
is the design.
And my dinosaur
has these huge horns
that are just pointing outward
on top of his head.
So I want to keep
the massive scale
of the dinosaur
with the human aspect--
Like an ancient warrior.
Ooh, this guy's fuzzy.
I finally see
this brightly rainbow-colored,
little tiny dinosaur
that's really cute
with a cool, like,
black-and-white mohawk.
And it's so colorful.
And I'm colorful.
So let's make this
a dinosaur version of me--
Pop rock-inspired.
Let's have it
like a crazy hipster dinosaur.
I don't know
how we'd do something
that doesn't
already look like something
we've already done, though--
That's the thing.
The whole point of being here
is to challenge yourself
as an artist
and to try and do new things.
Unfortunately, I've already done
two lizardy-looking
human-hybrid creatures.
This is going
to be very difficult.
I chose the corythosaurus.
It's just got
interesting shapes,
and I like the paint patterns
that are on there.
Think that I can do
a lot with it.
My concept is big lips,
top round head,
with a hump,
and the tail pokes straight out.
Almost a camel-like shape to it.
I end up going
to the velociraptor
and I see the feathers.
And I think,
"Well, that could be fun."
We head back to the lab
and we pick our models.
Everyone wants this so bad,
so it's very stressful
because the stakes are so high
and the talent's so intense.
Everyone's bringing
their "A" game.
We have five hours in the lab,
and I start
sculpting the features
where I had drawn them.
Your sculpture is going to be
what your prosthetic
is gonna end up looking like.
As soon as I start sculpting,
I'm trying to think
about a story line
to go along
with this character.
So velociraptor turns
into veloci-rapper.
Instead of being
a little bit fresh prince
and old-school,
he's a little bit more modern.
What's his story?
I'm pretty much doing
Island Of Dr. Moreau.
Just kind of creepy,
almost diseased,
with a humanoid type
paint scheme.
I'd try to find some kind
of a back story
- for him, you know.
- Why is that?
'Cause they might
bust your balls for it.
- Yeah.
- Think there's
always further thought
that has to go into things,
especially because this
is the most intense challenge.
I mean, this is to get
into the finals.
I'm noticing that the mood
is definitely different.
RJ is a very
happy-go-lucky guy.
But he's getting frustrated
with his design.
At the end of the day,
I'm legitimately starting
to get scared.
Everything that I'm sculpting
is starting to look
like the orchid chameleon.
I have to bring something new
to the table.
So I decide to tear off
the sculpt.
Now I have to completely start
all over again tomorrow.
Time's up.
That's it.
It sucks to be me.
Coming up...
I'm just shattered right now.
It would be devastating
to lose at this point.
I wish that you had pushed it
a little further.
What it is that you've
achieved here this week
is truly impressive.
Day two at the shop--
We have 12 hours.
We have to create
a human-dinosaur hybrid.
You're doing poly or foam?
Foam, yeah, foam.
There's a lot depending
on this day,
and I think that's going
for everyone.
Yesterday,
I had to scrap my sculpture.
Today, I have to bring a design
that is not reminiscent
of something
that I've already done.
So I have
to completely rework the idea
of this creature in my head.
Hey, guys.
I am here
with Cleve and Constance Hall--
the stars of SyFy's new show
Monster Man.
They're fabrication specialists.
They want to walk through
and help consult with you guys
on your designs.
I'm just looking
at them like, "wow."
They're expert fabricators,
and we're going to get great
feedback and advice from them.
So I'm really excited to hear
what they have to say.
- Ian.
- Wow, looks like you're doing
- my favorite dinosaur.
- Really? Triceratops?
- It's always been my favorite.
- Awesome.
Me too, actually.
The only fabricated pieces
are going to be his horns,
and I'm fabricating his tail
as well.
So what are you--how are you
gonna fabricate the horns?
I've got these.
I was--
Yeah, I was thinking
I could heat 'em up
a little bit and shape 'em
- and carve 'em and--
- Be careful, it melts fast.
Be careful,
that melts really easily.
Cleve and Constance
gave me some tips
on how to make horns
and things of that sort,
which was very helpful.
Very nice meeting you.
Good luck.
Take care.
I'm fabricating the back
of the head
out of latex and polyfoam
so that those feathers
really have something
to really stick into.
And what are you using
to assemble it all?
- What type of glues?
- I was gonna use some barge.
Do you have trouble with
your barge sticking sometimes?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Tip for people
who use contact cements--
When you buy it,
turn your can upside down,
leave it there,
because the stuff separates.
- Cool.
- Shake the hell out of it.
Mix the stuff,
and it'll work a lot better.
Nice. Okay.
Cleve tells me
about using my barge,
which is this glue that I use.
He gives me this tip
about turning it upside down
and letting the chemicals
separate.
Good idea.
His armor is actually fossils.
Uh-huh. What are you making
the costume from?
I decided to go
with cotton fabric.
- For the armor?
- Armor--
We're gonna use,
actually, polyfoam.
And it's due when?
Um, by the end
of the day today.
- This seems a little nut-sy
by our standards
- for time lines.
- Yeah.
I've got, like,
a duct-tape buildup.
- And I wrap this--
- Batting.
Yeah, with batting.
It's got to have something
on there, though.
I asked constance
about the best way
- to texture this tail.
- I personally find it better
to cut it into small things
like around the scales--
- Piece it around.
- Oh, that's a good idea.
They're really smart.
They know a lot of stuff.
Well, I appreciate all the help.
That was great.
I kind of wish it was longer
and I could actually
just sit there
and pick their brains.
- Hey, Sue.
- Hello.
- Tell us what you got going on.
- Ta-da.
- Bringin' it out.
- Wow.
Okay, I love you already.
That's awesome.
Immediately,
constance loves
my dino-hipster girl.
It's going to have piercings,
- dinosaur piercings.
- Absolutely.
Constance is
a great fabricator and artist.
She gave me a confidence boost.
All right, guys,
it's looking good.
- Good luck.
- Thanks for coming by, guys.
Oh, my God,
we're so close to the finale.
Everyone's really stressed.
I feel exhausted,
but there's still so much to do.
I'm doing foam batting
and duct tape
for the hump and the huge tail.
- Check this out.
- Ha.
I am the least experienced
in the entire group.
I'm a tattoo artist from Idaho.
And I'm really starting
to feel the weight
of this competition.
I got the body done already,
but I still have the tail,
the face, and cowl.
On top of that,
I'm making a prop.
I have to make a skateboard.
I'm really feeling confident.
I'm feeling this challenge.
My concept's strong.
I'm working as fast as I can.
And I can taste, you know,
that 100 grand right there.
Hey, guys.
Boom. In comes Glenn.
I'm a little nervous
at this point.
If I can get a good review
out of Glenn,
if you can get Glenn to say,
"Hmm, that looks cool,"
or "Can't wait to see it,"
then I know I'm on
the right track.
Tell me about
what you're doing here.
I'm trying to do
something different
that you guys
haven't seen me do yet.
I'm kind of keeping
the mouth really tight.
Pushing the jawbone back
a little bit further,
so that the elongated head
doesn't seem out of place.
What is the rest
of the look then?
- So his wardrobe or--
- Oh, he's--
He's gonna be
a velociraptor-rapper.
- A veloci-rapper.
- Copy that.
- I like it.
- All right, well,
- look forward to seeing it.
- Let you get back.
- Appreciate it.
- Good luck.
He walks off and I'm like,
"hmm, shit."
I can't really change
my idea, at this point.
He's an ancient deity
of the reptilian race.
Oh, that's very cool.
Color-wise?
I'm going for a more...
Tan, flesh color
and possibly some orange.
This is probably
the most extensive effort
that you've made so far, right?
It's the most pieces.
It's "Go big or go home,"
at this point.
- Hey, Sue.
- Hello.
Hipster dino-girl, yeah.
It's "girl power."
"Girl power" dinosaur. Okay.
Even though Glenn's
rolling his eyes at my idea,
I'm not going to change it.
I mean, it's totally me.
As you can see,
I'm not sculpting scales.
He's gonna be more flesh-like.
But with the spot design--
is kind of what I'm thinking.
I'm gonna bring in colors
of the human flesh.
We've got to ask,
at this point--
So we've talked
to several of you guys.
And I don't know
if you're listening
to what all
your paint jobs are.
I think maybe
you should all pay attention
- to each other.
- The last thing we want
is everyone have their dinosaurs
up there
and they're all
the exact same color scheme.
So I'm not feeling good
about the visit.
So far,
what I have seen of your work--
You stick really close
to what your designs are.
This seems to be changing
a lot as you go.
So why are you changing so much
as you go?
I was worried about it
being too dinosaur-y.
And so I had to pull back
a little bit.
And so I actually took my sketch
and my design
and kind of sunk in more
into the face.
I feel, without Glenn
really saying anything,
that he wishes that
I had gone with the sketch.
So, at this point,
I'm really starting
to doubt myself.
So? Thoughts?
The double elimination,
I think, is taking its toll.
It's making them do more work
than they would normally do.
Okay, so let's start with RJ.
I'm concerned with the fact
that it's sort of playful.
I'm not sure that
that's going to work.
I could be wrong.
We might see this come out there
and it completely clicks.
Moving on, then, to Matt.
The sculpt is looking
really, really good.
So hopefully he's really
familiar
with some
of the sort of rough techniques
for painting wardrobe
which he can do--
Rubouts or dry brushing,
making it look cool the armor.
Really concentrate
- on coloring his makeup.
- The face.
All right, let's discuss Ian's.
The profile already
is way further along
than anyone else's.
So I think he's right on track.
- And seems to have a very...
- Sense of confidence.
Clear direction. Yeah.
Let's move on to Rayce.
- What are your thoughts there?
- Not the best work
that I've seen him do.
I think the pressure
is getting to him
and I think he's
second-guessing himself.
And he's scaling back
what it is that he's doing.
Your thoughts there
with the hipster dino-girl?
I love that she's trying
to do things
with the entire body--
That's great.
And I think
that was a wise decision.
Out of everyone,
she's the only one
that purposely picked something
for the color.
All right, thank you, Glenn.
I finally finished my cowl.
I'm gonna do
a large two-piece mold.
You do this by putting
a cement-like substance
on top of the sculpture.
Once it hardens,
you can clean out the clay
and fill it
with foam or silicone,
which eventually becomes
a prosthetic.
Now the big-ass moment.
So I'm looking around--
No one else is making a prop.
And I'm just thinking,
"How the hell am I going
to make a skateboard?"
So I take some lightweight foam
and I start carving it out
like a skateboard.
And it's coming together.
Nothing worked out the way
I wanted it to today.
I start to peel off
the latex tail,
and I notice that there's chunks
of uncured latex
in a lot of the trenches.
Big chunks were taken out.
Some of the latex is ripping,
so it doesn't lay
like it's supposed to.
And it looks
significantly different
than the head
that I've been sculpting.
Looks like ass, man.
It's a disaster.
It's just ugly, dude.
And there's no fast way
to fix all this
and make it look awesome.
I'm really down at this point.
I feel like I've failed,
and I could easily see myself
going home.
I'm just shattered right now.
My tail looks like crap.
There's chunks of uncured latex
in a lot of the trenches.
It's ripping in some areas.
I don't know how
I could help that.
I'm not gonna sit there
and cut out pieces of foam
and put it back there.
I'm well into day two,
and I can't change
what I'm doing.
And I've just got
to make it work.
The ten hours are winding down,
and I've got the cowl molded.
I've got my prosthetic
already molded--
Chest piece, shoulder piece,
and my tail.
Okay, guys, time's up!
Brushes down.
I got everything knocked out
that I wanted to do
and accomplish.
It's just,
is it gonna be cohesive?
You never know.
It's always in your mind,
but it could be something
tally different
once you put it all together.
Oh, my back.
That was a beast.
We get home--
Everyone's really exhausted.
RJ's cooking dinner,
but I don't even feel
like eating at this point.
- Today was rough.
- I'm excited to see yours, RJ.
Glenn did not seem interested
in seeing it.
I really feel
like I'm going home,
because I'm making
a veloci-rapper.
It's just a play on the name.
Uh, veloci-rapper.
It's just...
Rapper-- Raptor,
you know?
- Oh, I see.
- Thought it would be a funny--
I have this horrible feeling
that all this comedy stuff
is not jiving with anybody.
Today when all my stuff
went to...
To crap, you know,
all my latex
gave me issues all day,
I got really depressed
and I started thinking
of my kids back home.
They're always the ones
that comfort me
when I'm having my down times,
you know.
I feel like I sucked all day.
And the only thing
that can stop this from sucking
is to talk to my family,
and I can't talk to them either.
Tonight's the last night we're
all gonna be five in the house.
I mean, the pressure's on.
It's like, "Go big or go home."
Just try to pull out
all the stops.
We're so close
to the finals right now.
I can taste it,
I'm hungry for it.
I'll do everything in my power
to stay here.
I've really got to
pull something
out of my butt tomorrow
to stay safe.
Today's application day--
Our models
will be arriving soon.
This is undeniably
the most important day
since the entire contest
started.
Cape.
On top of everything else,
today is my birthday.
So today is gonna be
the best birthday ever
or the worst birthday ever.
We're doing
dinosaur-human hybrids.
So you're going
to be velociraptor-rapper.
Work with me here on this.
Ready?
I made this elongated headpiece.
We have talons
and I made you
special dino-bling.
Today's always nervous--
You know what I mean?--
Application day.
Everything has got
to go perfect.
You're gonna be a triceratops.
So you got, like,
big-ass horns
and, like, a beak and stuff.
We're going all out on this.
You're gonna be
a dino-hipster girl.
I still need
to finish fabricating.
Immediately, I asked
my wonderful model Linda
to help me deck out
the skateboard.
The models are there
to help you.
They're on your side.
They want you to do well.
The texture on the tail
is terrible-- It sucks so bad.
Every time I look at it,
I just want to throw up on it.
The only way I'm gonna save this
is by some killer paint job
that hides everything
and pops out the things
I want to pop out.
This is kind of a base.
Bring it to life
with the airbrush.
It's a risky plan,
because it's colors
that shouldn't necessarily
go together.
I'm just sinking.
It just feels like
the world is closing in
on me right now.
This could be it.
I'm taking time
to actually airbrush
the base piece
before I apply it.
That way I know, for sure,
I have a strong paint job on it.
Which the judges have been
deducting me for.
All right,
we got to get this on.
I have this fat suit
I have Tommy put on.
I figured, like,
triceratops, you know--
Kind of big, cow-like.
They'd have weight on them.
But he's just looking
a little too chubby.
You look a lot fatter
than what
I thought you would have.
So I try and pad his shoulders--
Make him look bigger all around.
But it's not
what I wanted at all.
It's not looking right.
It's no bueno.
I finally take it off of him.
Yeah, I kind of like that.
I think it might work.
That's nice.
- Thank God.
- Hell, yeah.
I put the face on.
I start painting.
And I stop for a minute...
And I'm thinking,
"This will be the last time
I'm working in this place."
And it's really upsetting me.
I've come so far,
and it's proven to me
that I really am doing
a good job.
It would be devastating
to me to lose
at this point.
As the four hours near the end,
I start worrying
about the chest piece
and the armor pieces
that I have to apply.
Pretty good.
It's really just the armor.
It's daunting to get those done,
but if I screw up--
If I make him look
too costume-y--
That's the axe.
Hey, guys, that's time.
Let's go.
Leaving for the stage,
I see that everyone
still has a lot to do.
We only have one hour
to pull everything together.
Two people are
gonna be eliminated.
Two people?
I'm really worried now.
Coming up...
My heart's just pounding.
Two of you will be eliminated.
I think you might have
overextended yourself.
I'm going home on my birthday.
Oh, my God, it's fabulous.
We're at the stage
for our last looks.
We only have one hour
to pull everything together.
Um, stoop down a little bit.
All I'm doing is painting
like a mad woman.
Okay.
Let me get it all.
Drop your jaw
just a little bit.
During the last looks, I need
to put on
the tail and the hump.
And I've got
this nice duct-tape vest,
and the wardrobe
will cover up the duct tape.
I have a lot
of painting left to do.
And it starts looking
really good.
I think
I actually can finish this.
- Look at this ghetto affixing.
- Turn your arms, Phil.
Turn to this side...
I'm starting
to feather the tail...
I don't like this.
RJ, man,
this hot glue does wonders.
- Told you.
- Turn them both over.
Nobody's gonna beat me.
I'm gonna stay.
I'm gonna stay, I'm gonna stay.
Five minutes, guys.
I was a little frantic.
But I think my model
looks phenomenal.
Hey, guys, that's it!
Time's up!
Brushes down.
Two people are leaving.
This is our last chance
to impress the judges
before the finale.
I am petrified.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight, two of you
will be eliminated.
And three of you will make it
to the finale.
Say hello to your judges.
Owner of optic nerve makeup
effects studio--
- Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist-- Ve Neill.
Evening, everybody.
And creature designer
and director--
- Patrick Tatopoulos.
- Hello.
All right, guys,
so this week
your spotlight challenge
was to create
a dinosaur-human hybrid.
So let's see
what you come up with.
First up--
Sue's creation.
She's so flamboyant,
and all the eyes are just drawn
to her in that color
and her attitude
and her swagger.
It's totally me.
I love it.
I'm legitimately starting
to get scared.
I'm thinking I'm going home
on my birthday,
because I know
that Glenn doesn't like it.
He already said it before.
I think he looks intimidating.
He's phenomenal.
He has a whole presence
of a T-Rex.
It just works-- He's solid.
He's opening his mouth
and, like, moving his hands,
because he can flex 'em
and stuff.
He's looking really cool.
I think
everyone else's is good,
and then mine is just
a step under all of them.
I've never been this nervous
in any of the other challenges.
And my heart's just pounding.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look?
She was only doing this shape
like it was
going to be a partial,
but it looks like she decided
to go with a whole face.
Are you able
to open your mouth a bit?
- Yeah?
- I'm excited.
There's a whole bunch
of details on there
that they haven't gotten
a chance to see.
She's got
a whole spine thing going.
Oh, look--
Piercings.
It is kind of--
Something went wrong here.
Collapsed.
Can you open and close
your mouth?
- That's pretty cool.
- Yeah.
Pretty rough edge here.
You always get really nervous
when they do their looks,
because you don't know
what they're saying.
He started to do some,
like, vein-y breakup.
- This is a good idea.
- To break it up, yeah.
Wish he would have
done it more.
Kind of Damien-like,
you know?
- This is cool.
- Uh-huh.
Nice.
I like the tail.
Oh, yes, like a little,
stubby tail, huh?
- Yeah, it's cute.
- Which they add, by the way--
I like when I see them
paying attention
to the original characteristic.
I can't believe
we all did this.
This was a hell of a challenge.
She's got huge eyes.
Give us some gestures--
I want to see
how the makeup moves.
This is
the most intense challenge,
because there's so much
riding on it.
I could go home
because my latex on my tail
looks like crap.
She's got huge eyes.
It's so cool.
Ve, Patrick, and Glenn
go up for close looks,
and this is
the most intense challenge,
because there's so much
riding on it.
Give us some gestures--
I want to see
how the makeup moves.
Thank you.
Well, the judges
would like to speak
with each of you
to learn more about your work.
RJ.
Are you happy
with this character?
How well do you think
you've done?
Um, I'd give it
a solid six, seven.
You probably could have done
a little bit more
more with the paint job.
A little bit more break up
would have pulled this look
together really well.
That being said,
it does not detract
from the fact that I think
he's a really successful
character.
Can you give us a profile?
Can you show us your profile?
There's a lot
of a raptor vibe in there.
And he creates that back--
It's not human anymore,
the back.
I think that's
very, very important.
The purposeful hard edge
to the lip,
and then you can see his mouth
inside--
So often can go horribly wrong,
but it works really well
in this makeup.
RJ, thank you.
You can step back.
Matt, you're next.
- Glenn, let's start with you.
- How do you feel
- about what you've accomplished?
- Um, I would say,
I think I knocked out
a lot of stuff that I wanted to.
I could have done more
with certain pieces.
I love the chest piece.
I think all that's
really cool and creepy.
And I think it's interesting
that you chose to paint him
in a skeletal way,
which is like a dinosaur
exoskeleton-type look.
- I like it.
- Thank you.
Although
it's a very cool character
with the chest plate,
it took a bit of the effort away
from your sculpt on the face,
and I wish you had pushed it
a little further.
Feeling like you missed
the dinosaur thing a little bit.
I think
it would actually benefit
from not having
the chest plate on it.
I wish I could see
underneath there.
Think it would help it read
as a part human-part dinosaur.
Some really cool stuff
going on.
I think you might have
overextended yourself, though.
Matt, thank you very much.
You may step back.
Ian.
Would you give us
a little bit of information
about your character here?
Basically, I was going with
an Island Of Dr. Moreau feeling.
I chose the triceratops,
because he has a great profile.
I like this guy.
I think the major problem
with this
is the fact that there's just
not quite enough paint on it.
But, all in all,
I think you did a great job
and it's a great character.
Your sculpt is really good.
I like the way
the mouth functions.
You paid attention
to the wrinkle--
They make sense
when the mouth opens.
I agree with Ve--
You've done a great job again.
- Wow, thank you.
- I really wish
you would have gone and done
some simple buildup
underneath your wardrobe
to make the chest
really barreled.
That's a suggestion,
not a criticism.
I really think
that you succeeded this week.
- Thank you.
- Ian, thank you very much.
You can step back.
Rayce, you're up.
- Patrick, let's start with you.
- Tell us about the character.
The dinosaur I chose
was the corythosaurus.
First thing,
when we went to the museum,
is I looked at the silhouette
and I thought,
"This is such a powerful
silhouette in itself,
that I wanted to achieve that
on my character."
That's interesting
you talk about the silhouette,
because, for me,
this is a very successful job
of creating a new silhouette
that's less anthropomorphic,
especially when your model
gets into the right position.
Like the hump on the back,
the tail--
It really works for me.
What it is that you've
achieved here this week
is truly impressive--
Wicked accurate decisions.
I love that you integrated
the shape of the dinosaur
into the profile--
Not just aspects of it
jammed into the color.
- How did you make that tail?
- Ha.
I used to sit with my kids
and make duct-tape characters.
And it's just duct tape
with foam batting...
- Get out.
- Like snow batting, yeah.
- Duct tape?
- Duct tape.
Oh, my God, it's fabulous.
Spin around for us.
Look at that.
I have to eat my own words
about not liking blue makeups,
- 'cause this one's really cool.
- Thank you so much.
Rayce, you can step back.
Sue.
Glenn, let's start with you.
Sue, could you tell everyone
about your basic concept?
My dinosaur is named
a tianyulong.
It was the most flamboyant
in color.
I kind of made my creature
into a dinosaur version of me
as, like, a hipster
"girl power" dinosaur.
You created
a very cool little character.
It really strikes me,
among the whole group here,
you are the only one
that made something
that feels really fun.
And the colors actually
really work well together.
It was really wise to pick
a very colorful dinosaur.
It helped you zone in
on this concept
that you wanted to work with.
I think that's where it is
for me,
that it's a little too colorful
and it's a little too vibrant,
but overall I think
that you're pretty successful.
He's just not a girl,
that's all.
We have matching shoes.
I think it's very cute.
I think
your color scheme's wonderful
and very whimsical.
And you did a great job
this week.
And, you know, I'm not a girl,
but I'm still digging it.
So there's maybe
something wrong with me,
I don't know, but I think
it really works for me.
Thank you, Sue.
All right, everybody,
the judges have heard
what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they make their decisions.
So why don't we start
with Matt's work tonight.
What are your thoughts?
I liked the character.
I just think that, um,
it didn't really look
like a dinosaur.
I agree-- That was
so essential to the challenge.
He kind of has, like,
a demon look to him
as opposed to
an actual dinosaur.
We talk about those horns
staying so big.
When you shrink
the proportion of the dinosaur,
you need to shrink them as well.
But I still really think
it's a cool makeup.
Yeah, it is.
All right,
let's move on to Ian.
I think Ian might have been
the most successful
in putting the dinosaur
on a person.
Yeah, he got the feet
and the hands going.
And he got a hard-shell effect
on those pieces
that actually needed to be hard.
Yes. To me it's almost
too much
of a dinosaur face,
dinosaur hands,
on a silhouette
that's purely human.
All right, so with that
let's move on to Rayce then.
Really super-strong idea.
And one of my big fears--
The giant, round apertures
where the eyeballs were in.
And it's one of the strongest
pieces of the makeup
is that he created this
really cool, round shape there.
He worked with his model.
This is a new skill
that we really haven't seen
out of anyone--
Using the model
to the best advantage
in order to accentuate something
in the makeup.
- You saw that mouth moving.
- Yeah.
And the mouth
was absolutely stunning.
I didn't like
the wardrobe, though.
Yes, quasimodo belt-rope
was a little disappointing.
Yeah, that was disappointing
I got to say.
All right, let's move on
to Sue.
I think Sue did
a really great job this week.
I mean, she came up
with a really cute
little sassy character
for herself.
The colors all worked
really well together.
I really don't like
this makeup.
I don't like
the "girl power" idea.
- Doesn't like "girl power."
- Oh, come on!
I don't like the skateboard.
I just don't like it.
It doesn't work for me.
It was the perfect thing
for her to do.
You only like it because
it is "girl power."
Nah--
It has nothing to do with that.
- Holy smoke.
- I'm sorry.
I can't even back myself up
on that one.
I just don't like it.
All right, let's move on to RJ.
I would say
that the raptor was in the face,
which was actually important
to me.
Although it's completely human,
there was still
the characteristic
of the raptor.
And the nice line
from this side.
When you see the feathers
go down into the back--
The human back--
And the tail,
it flows really nicely.
Yeah, nicely together--
It's true.
Yeah, I thought the
raptor-rapper thing was cute.
I mean, he even did the sculpt
of the little disc.
That wasn't good,
that was great!
- I thought it was funny.
- There's a few issue though,
like the toes just being
way too long.
We know this important,
to pay attention
to stuff like this.
The guy walks
like he's coming back
- from a scuba diving lesson.
- Like clown shoes, yeah.
- They are like clown shoes.
- That's not a good thin
you want them to-- And you
have to pay attention to that.
I can't believe we have
to eliminate two people.
- This is freaking me out.
- Yeah, I don't envy you guys.
I think what we're really
trying to decide tonight
isn't so much who are
the two people
that are going home--
It's knowing
that there's only three slots
for next week,
and who are the three people
that we most want to see.
Very difficult, no doubt.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- Yeah.
- We have.
- Fantastic.
Let's bring them back out.
All right, Glenn,
who is the winner
of this challenge
and the first person joining us
in the finale?
The winner
of tonight's challenge...
is...
All right, Glenn,
who is the winner
of this challenge
and the first person joining us
in the finale?
The winner
of tonight's challenge...
is...
Rayce.
Wow.
You very successfully merged
the human and dinosaur forms
in your creation, and it was
- a beautifully executed makeup.
- Thank you so much.
Rayce, congratulations.
You are the first person
- joining us in the finale.
- Thank you all.
I can't believe this right now.
Inside I'm just freaking out,
thinking,
there's no way
that I'm in the finale.
Like, wow.
All right, Glenn,
who is the second person
to join us?
The second person
moving on to the finale is...
Ian.
Ian, congratulations.
Great job.
Thank you.
I'm very proud.
I made it to the finale.
Um... damn.
It's surreal and...
I couldn't be happier.
Well, we have
three artists left,
but only one of you
can continue on with us.
So, Glenn, who has
the final spot in the finale?
The third person that will be
competing in the finale is...
- RJ.
- Oh, God.
Ooh.
Thank you guys so much.
- Wow.
- Well, RJ, congratulations.
You have final spot
in the finale.
- Happy birthday.
- Thanks.
Best birthday present ever.
Ha!
I can't believe it.
I'm-- I just am in awe
that I got through.
Unfortunately that means,
Matt, Sue,
you will be leaving us tonight.
Judges, is there anything that
you would like to say to them?
Just want to tell you both--
Nothing to be ashamed of.
This was
a very tough decision tonight.
And you should both be
very proud of yourselves.
Sue, right from the beginning,
I knew that you had
some serious sculpting talent.
So don't give up.
This is just the beginning.
What I like about you
is your originality.
You're just fresh,
full of energy.
You bring a lot of realism
in your sculpture.
- It's not easy.
- Thank you.
Matt,
extremely impressed with you.
Really, really strong--
Strong design skills.
And I cannot wait
to see what you come up with
in the future.
You're like an incredible artist and
your work here has been phenomenal.
We look forward to see
great things from you.
Thank you.
Sue and Matt, it's really been great having
you here with us and seeing your work.
You, please, head back to the
make up room and pack up your kits.
- Thank you both.
- Good job, guys. - Good luck guys.
I'm not really sad...
I feel I've done my best.
And leaving here definitely felt
I'm ready to go.
I've got, uhm, a ton of
other creatures in my mind
that want to get out.
I love you, guys!
It hurts, but, now I know
what I'm capable of doing,
I only have one way to go and that's it.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net