Previously onFace Off...
Laura's ode to cubism
brought her to victory.
Perhaps your best work yet.
But Scott's tribute
to surrealism sent him home.
Now, eight artists remain,
and they'll take on
a high-flying challenge
that is out of this world.
It's exciting.
This is gonna be
a really cool challenge.
But for some artists,
the strain will bring them
to the breaking point.
Do you like the cowl,
or you don't?
I didn't want to say
I didn't like it.
- Well, you should have.
- Maybe take the jaw down a bit?
Mm, no.
- Oh, fuck.
- That's awesome.
I do love the paints,
but it's just muddy as a design.
Something went haywire.
In the end,
one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Makeup
to one of their 85
international locations,
a 2013 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Only one will win Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- Are you proud?
- I am proud.
Last night,
I got top looks again.
It's time for you
to get kicked off.
You've been in the top too much.
I'm really happy I haven't
been on bottom looks,
but I really just want
to win a challenge.
Let's go, guys!
- It's dark again in here.
- Ooh, spooky!
So, we walk into the lab
and it's completely dark,
and there's a spotlight
on McKenzie.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Before movies and television,
people from all over the world
found entertainment
under the big top.
- Oh!
- They were mesmerized
by jaw-dropping performances
that seemed otherworldly.
To this day, the circus
continues to evolve.
Take a look at this.
Oh!
- Oh, my God.
- Oh! Ooh.
Oh, that's so cool!
What?
Oh, yay!
All right,
I'd now like to introduce you
to the co-owner
and creative director
of the cutting-edge
circus troupe
Cirque Berzerk.
Please welcome Suzanne Bernel.
I love Cirque Berzerk,
so this is extremely
exciting to me.
- Hi.
- Hi, McKenzie.
Thank you so much
for being here.
Thank you.
Hi, everyone.
Can you tell these guys
a little bit more
about Cirque Berzerk?
We wanted
to re-invent the circus.
While we tip our hats
to our Vaudeville,
big top, dust bowl roots,
we wanted to bring
the sexy and the dark
and the punk rock
back to circus.
- Nice.
- That is so rad.
I love this.
Cirque Berzerk
has successfully re-invented
the circus here on planet Earth,
but for this challenge,
we want you to take things
out of this world.
- Hmm.
- Oh.
Working together
in teams of two,
your spotlight challenge
is to create
a dark and sexy
alien circus performer.
Oh, I'm so excited.
I love the whole circus aspect.
I love aliens.
I love dark and sexy.
And I think that this is gonna
be a really cool challenge.
All right, guys, go ahead,
and you can choose
your teammate.
- Really?
- Let's do it.
I picked Laura because we
always wanted to work together.
I mean, ever since season three,
we would always say,
"You know, we would be
a really good team,
and it'd be
something incredible."
This is gonna be awesome!
I'm excited.
Dude, this is our challenge.
We got this.
_
Everyone's really excited
about doing an alien.
They've been waiting
for this challenge,
and it's just the one
I've been loathing.
Now, there's only one more
thing that you should know.
Oh, gosh.
The performance
that you just saw today
was just a tiny little glimpse
of what will happen
on the reveal stage.
The models you will select
are actually performers
from Cirque Berzerk,
and will take part
in a spectacular performance
as members of
an intergalactic circus troupe.
Fuck yeah.
Oh, this is gonna be fun.
All right, Suzanne.
So, what things
should these artists
keep in mind while
creating their aliens?
Well, we need to have people
be able to jump and flip
and fly through the air,
so they need to be able
to move in their makeup and have
their makeup not come off.
I've never done a makeup
on an actor who had to do
this much movement, and so
it's gonna be a challenge.
All right, guys, go ahead
and choose your models
and get started
on your designs.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you, guys.
Thank you, guys.
Day one, we got six hours
in the lab.
We pick our models
and get to work.
On our Samsung Galaxy tabs,
we get to see what
our models actually do.
So our model
is a contortionist,
so she has to be really free,
so we're going tight,
thin appliances.
And we can do, like,
some sort of suggestion of,
like, the punk rock mohawk.
So our concept is that
a manned space mission landed on
one of the moons of Neptune,
and an alien
got a punk band tape recorder
from the astronaut,
so our alien's
gonna have a mohawk
and, like, all kinds
of cool punk-rock things.
That's super punk rock.
It's, like, old school
Sex Pistols.
How about something like that?
Almost like an alien
facehugger-type thing?
Yeah, except
it's on its stomach.
So, our character
is a alien animal trainer,
and somehow, he has
a parasite attached to him
from his many years
of training aliens.
I really like that.
Oh, he's on the thing.
That's, like, my favorite.
I'd love to make our character
into a ringmaster because
I feel like that's
a really sexy position
to be in a circus,
and because our performer
is on the ring,
it's kind of a little play
on words.
What if we do, like, scales?
I decide we should do scales.
That might look really cool,
and they'll be thin pieces,
and they'll be able to move
on the body well.
That's not a bad idea.
There's this group of carnies,
and she's potentially
the leader.
Our character
is a space contortionist,
and she's the leader
of a circus
and lures in
other space travelers
to become a part
of this circus.
We need to think
about the shape
of the head and the face,
'cause that's what
- we've got to get started today.
- Yeah.
Our performer is doing
all sorts of backbends
and everything,
so it can't be
this big crazy head
'cause she almost
does headstands,
but we want her
to look very regal,
and we come up with this kind
of crown-like, round head shape,
so we're just gonna go with that
and get started sculpting.
Eddie starts blocking out
the cowl,
and I start working
on the face.
Do you think we should
take it back more,
or do you think we should--
'Cause I think it would be cool
if it flows into this...
- Yeah, I think maybe.
- ...jaw bone right here.
Yeah.
I'm gonna work on the face
while Roy works on the cowl.
We want to take
both of our sketches
and try to combine them
into one alien.
Why is everybody so quiet?
It's not art, it's aliens.
- Whoo!
- Let's hear some noise!
I'm excited.
I can tell
you're excited, Frank.
Team Banana Fingers over here.
You would get stuck
with the gimp
on this one, wouldn't you?
Roy, my other hand
still works pretty good, bro.
On the art challenge,
I injured my finger.
And I ended up with 13 stitches,
and I still can't feel
most of my finger, and the part
that I can feel
hurts really bad,
so I'm really happy
to have Frank on my team.
While Frank blocks up the cowl,
I start the chest
by laying aluminum foil over
a female mannequin torso.
I secure those shapes
by putting duct tape over it.
We pull it off and lay it
down flat on a board.
I trace it with a marker,
and it allows you to do
a one-piece flat mold.
Hey, guys!
Here for a walk-through.
Gonna check on your work.
- Yay!
- It's circus time.
Show us dark and sexy.
We want to bring
a little bit of wrinkling,
but not too much
that it looks old age.
You've got these lines
going here,
the eyebrows, and you've got
your cheeks going into here.
You might even just
combine this into a smooth piece
as opposed to getting
wrinkles into it.
What are you gonna make
the mohawk out of?
We-- we haven't really gone
and looked yet,
but it's not gonna be fun fur,
I promise.
- Or porcupine spines.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Nothing that can--
you know, they do a head spin
and stab themselves, and--
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, let's not
hurt the performers.
We got stuck with a male
who has a ton of hair.
Work with the hair,
- as opposed to trying to...
- Yeah.
...put a cowl
over the top of it.
Otherwise, you're gonna wind up
with a big head like this.
Hair is sexy.
I like the shape of the head.
It's different and good,
as opposed to this.
I'm concerned about your face
as far as the sexy goes.
Yeah.
Okay, there's a problem.
How do you bring out
the sexy in your aliens?
Because a pair of eyelashes
isn't going to change that.
Maybe taking
the jaw down a bit?
Mm, no.
Oh, fuck.
I think it's the giant nostrils
that are looking out at me.
The other thing too,
this mouth isn't sexy either.
I like that piece.
But then,
I've liked pieces in the past
and I was on the bottom for it.
It's too busy.
Needs to be smooth out.
I-I don't know.
I...
Coming up...
You don't think it looks good?
We're just not
on the same page.
Fuck.
I hate poly foam.
It's just a big, gobby mess.
That's awesome.
- Something went haywire.
- I don't read him as alien.
I'm concerned about your face
as far as the sexy goes.
- Yeah.
- Day one, Mr. Westmore
comes by
and he's not digging it.
I'm seeing a really
intricate skull structure
going on underneath there,
as opposed to a softer one.
It's too busy.
I would smooth it out
a little bit.
- Just smooth it out?
- Yeah.
Okay.
If Michael Westmore
says do it, you listen.
- All right, good luck.
- Thank you.
- Good luck, guys. Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
All right, everybody,
we're heading out,
but cannot wait to see
your performers.
- Thanks, guys.
- Bye, guys.
Bye-bye.
So, we need to go
into a different direction.
I'm trying to think
of all the sexy aliens
that I've ever seen, and I
can't think of, really, a lot.
You got any ideas?
'Cause now we're back kind of
square one on the face.
I know.
The parameters
for this challenge
are so very specific
about being alien and sexy,
and what does
that exactly mean?
Let's see here.
Maybe if I take away the brow,
and make it a bit softer
that way.
It's something about the mouth.
It just looks so reptilian.
- It's just--
- Yeah, I know.
I make everything
a little bit more round,
make everything
a little bit more sleek,
and a little bit more sexy.
- It's sexier.
- That looks good.
- Yeah.
- It's more alien now.
Yeah.
I can't wait to paint this.
We want to do
this really kind of cool
tree frog/fish painting.
We want to use
really bright colors--
purple, green, yellow, blue.
The paint job is so fun.
I agree.
While Laura's
working on the sculpt,
I decide to create
a laser whip,
so I go ahead and grab EL wire.
It's a very flexible piece
of wire that lights up.
So I take that and take
some L200 and some vacuum form,
and start creating
a laser whip.
And then I also start
cutting out pieces and shaping
parts of the rest
of the costume.
You know what
this reminds me of?
The things in Hellboy.
Wasn't it, like, the Angel
Of Death or something like that,
that-- that had the head
like that?
I totally know
what you're talking about.
I spent quite a while
getting the contours
to a point that
it looked really cool,
but I don't want it
to look like something
that's already been done.
Time is running out,
so we're gonna
think about it tonight
and move forward tomorrow.
Ten minutes!
That's time, guys!
- Let's go home!
- Yay!
I'm worried because I know that
we have to change
this cowl shape.
I just hope that I have
enough time to sculpt it
to a level
it needs to be tomorrow.
But I'm not happy
with the character,
and I don't know what
I'm gonna do to make it work.
- Bam, bam!
- I'm gonna go look
- at the teeth really quick.
- Okay.
It's day two in the lab.
We have 9 1/2 hours.
Our design is very reminiscent
of another design,
and we're gonna have
to change the sculpture.
I'll redesign this front view.
If you want
to just attack that face.
I don't want to mold a sculpture
I'm not happy with,
so we need to change it
as quickly as possible.
- I'm gonna put the--
- Is this sexy enough?
Yeah, I-I think so.
The face looks really sexy,
and I'm liking it.
I'm feeling really good
about the makeup.
Mr. Westmore
said that we should utilize
our model's hair, but all
I sculpted so far are scales.
Scales are just texture,
and I could go home
if that's all I do.
So I'm thinking
that I should do a cowl.
I'm gonna make it split
at the top like a mohawk
and have all
of his dreads come out,
so we'll still
be using his dreads,
but we'll just have more
of an alien look to him.
- Top look, top look!
Got to keep the Laney
and 'Lana tradition up.
I don't think that we should
spend time sculpting
the cowl all over again,
so instead, I add little nubs
and cut into the top of it,
and rather than having it be
one continuous circle,
make it into two forms.
And I think that
looks pretty cool, honestly.
I'm with ya.
I think that's awesome, yeah.
- I almost like that better.
- Yeah, me too.
Our alien has all these
subdermal piercings,
and these pyramid spikes
I embedded in her chest.
And because of my injury,
I'd rather stay out
of the mold room,
so I start sending pieces
to Frank.
He's molding them up.
I'm gonna go make this mold,
you see.
All together, I'm gonna
be making seven molds
all by myself.
If it was somebody
like Alana or Miranda,
they'd probably
have a meltdown,
but I'm pretty good
at managing my time,
so this doesn't worry me
at all.
- Ten blenders.
- We decided to make
blender pieces, which
are just really thin pieces
of foam latex that have
a little build up in the middle
that smooth down
to all the sides,
and you use them to blend
any edges that show,
like the cowl and the face
on our alien animal trainer.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
That's really cool.
Quit sculptin' so damn good.
You guys really made
that departure nicely.
Yay, thank God.
I hope that these
don't read too fish-like.
I don't think they will.
I'm just a little nervous
now about it.
Some scales look a certain way,
and some scales
look another way.
I'm just worried
that it's not gonna blend well
or be cohesive.
Well, I want to add in
this shape going back on that,
so it's not just scales
on the head.
Do what you want,
just own it onstage tomorrow.
So, what do you mean
you want me to own that onstage?
You don't think it looks good?
I just know
it could look better.
Alana's second-guessing
everything that I do.
I'm just, like, hoping that
all of this goes together,
you know?
She's really not trusting me
on this one.
Well, it doesn't matter
about the sculpture
as long as you
can paint it right.
So, I'm confused.
You don't like my sculpture?
Oh, God.
We're just not on the same page.
Is that what you're saying?
So, you don't like
my sculpture?
Is that what you're saying?
It's day two,
and I'm pretty stressed.
Alana's not liking anything
that I'm doing.
I-I just thought that's
what we decided on sculpting.
I just don't want this to look,
like, helmet-y
if we don't blend it.
She's so negative.
Everything I do or say,
she's not happy with.
So what would you like me to do
different right now, Alana?
I have one intention
and she has another
for this alien ringmaster,
and I think we're
just trying so hard to mesh
these ideas together
when it's not really happening.
You want to bring
that same thing,
like the big to small,
or do you want to do it
from small to big?
I just want them
to be on the head
so it's not just a scale head.
I want there
to be something else.
Yeah, I think it needs,
like, more form for sure,
so maybe that'll do it.
I'm confused about how
it's gonna blend onto the face,
but I have faith in Laney,
so I'm just ready
to keep moving forward.
That's looking dope, Eddie.
Thanks, man.
It's like intergalactic
Wonder Woman.
Yeah.
I could add some light purple.
Like, a periwinkle purple,
like, in the back here?
Hopefully I'll have something
you can play with
- in a little bit and see.
- Okay.
We want to run our pieces,
except for the face,
in poly foam so we can go ahead
and get everything
pre-painted.
So I take the cowl,
put latex in it,
and start running it
in the poly foam.
While Roy
works on the poly foam,
I'm testing paint.
We do want to go in
a blue route,
but also put some greens
in there as well,
and I think that'll read alien.
It's, like, getting close
to the end of the day,
and I go to open up the mold,
and it's just a big,
gobby mess of just stickiness.
Fuck.
I hate poly foam.
It's like sticking
your hand in honey.
I've already been burned
by poly foam this season.
Now I'm burned on it again,
and I've got to get
this thing cleaned up
so I can get
my foam running in it.
Poly foam is just not
liking me this season.
Yeah, it is
just not curing well.
No, it's not.
I'm just gonna peel it and we'll
take it and run it for foam.
Yeah.
I've never had this much
problem with poly foam.
All the teams are still
cleaning their shit out.
All I got do is to write
our name on it.
Right?
Time, everybody!
That's time.
I guess we ought
to get out of here.
End of day two, Tate and I
are right on schedule.
Up top.
We got everything
about as ready as possible.
I think we're ready
for application tomorrow.
Let's go!
Let's go get it.
Let's go get it!
So, it's application day.
We have four hours in the lab,
and then one hour of last looks
at the stage, and we have
a ton of work to do today.
How'd that cowl turn out?
It's got a couple
of funny spots, but it's fine.
Tate will pretty much spend
the first two hours
working on makeup,
and then I'll jump in
and spend the second two hours
applying the cowl and face,
and getting the paint job going
on our cool, punk rock alien.
So you're
the galactic contortionist.
We're turning you into, like,
a-a crust punk sort
of uh, circus alien, so...
- Nice.
- You're a reptilian alien.
We saw that you do
a lot of this,
so we've got a giant bug
on your chest.
We're under a crazy time
crunch, so we'll probably be
flying around like chickens
with our heads cut off today.
Let me see how you have yours.
We want to make sure
they're even.
We start applying,
and we get the chest
and cowl down together.
We've got kind of
a complex headpiece,
so it takes some time.
I have to kind of cut back
in certain areas.
That is all second skinned.
Yeah, it's ridiculous.
A second skin is when you have
the foam latex and then the skin
and they're not attached.
- But we'll have to...
- Make it work.
Like, definitely pack--
Yeah, make it work.
Just like real effects artists.
Okay, I need to go check
on my bug head.
Okay, yeah.
Go for it.
The head
on this little creature
that we have on the belly
is a bit heavy,
so I can make an upholstery foam
mold of the head piece.
While that's setting up,
I figure out that I can run
a simple tension device
attached to his thigh,
so whenever he bends,
it creates that tension
so that the head will pop up.
Oh, jeez.
He's getting excited.
Really bad edges.
I'm really worried
about this cowl.
Whatever, the judges
are used to bad edges.
The last time I was
in this competition,
the judges said quite often
that my face and my cowl
didn't meet up correctly,
and that's exactly
what's happening on this piece.
I think that we maybe have to
blend the edge of the cowl
und-- like, underneath.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I don't think
we have time for that.
It's gonna look like
shit if we don't.
I went home
for something like that.
I feel like Alana and I
just aren't on the same page.
This piece is not working.
Even though it's Laney's piece,
Laney's never been on bottom,
but I have, and they'll
send me home for this.
Do you like the cowl
or you don't?
I just think it's too wide.
That's-- When I was looking
at it yesterday,
I didn't want to say, like,
I didn't like it.
Well, you should have,
because that's when
I was sculpting it
before we molded it.
These edges are so awful.
Well, what do you
want me to do?
Make the call.
I know that if we're on bottom,
I'm gonna go home, she's not.
Tell me what to do.
Coming up...
I can't read your mind
right now.
I am so stressed.
This makeup's a mess.
It falls short.
I think she's quite beautiful.
Now it's time to put
your makeups to the test.
Tell me what to do.
It's application day,
and Alana's just not
into the cowl at all.
Honestly, if I was doing
this makeup by myself,
I'd scrap the cowl.
If I scrap the cowl,
then all I did was scales,
so if I'm in bottom looks,
then I'm gonna go home.
Let me Frankenstein it.
I'll own it.
Like, just let me do this.
The cowl looks so big
compared to the face.
Like, step back.
This cowl's not gonna fly.
Even though it's Laney's piece,
I know the judges
are gonna call me out.
All right.
Let's use his hair.
We're running out of time,
so I just finally agree,
let's not use the cowl.
Don't you think
that's what's right to do?
Yeah.
Let's-- let's do it.
I think this
should be your call,
'cause you really feel like
if we're on bottom,
you're going home,
and I want this
to turn into your makeup now.
That's not fair.
That's fucked up.
Well, I know you're not gonna
be confident unless this is off.
So we're scrapping the cowl.
We're gonna go something crazy
with the hair
and do an awesome paint job.
Let's do this.
Let's-- let's keep you here.
All right,
that's 30 minutes, everybody.
That's it!
Time's up!
- Thank you so much.
I think it looks really good.
I'm confident about this one,
but my model's
not just gonna be
standing there.
He's gonna
actually be performing,
and my makeup has to stay on
all through the performance.
There's so many things
that could go wrong,
and if it does,
you're instantly on bottom.
Let's do it, guys.
- Good luck, everyone!
- Good luck.
We get to last looks,
and we've got quite a lot
still to do.
So I'm going to finish
painting the face
and Eddie's gonna work
on the chest
and the body and the wardrobe.
You might want to mix a little
more white into it, maybe.
The first thing we got to do
is the eyes and the mouth,
and while Laura's
working on that,
I take it and I start basing out
his hands and his feet.
- He's still popping up.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna cover that
with a blender.
I've never dealt
with anything like this before.
Why don't we go like this?
In last-looks, I start
with getting some color
onto the alien's head,
and I'm adding more contrast
around her eyes.
I also have
to finish the mouth.
15 minutes, guys!
You see all these white dots
that I just put in?
The yellow needs to be
brought down into it.
We're so far behind,
and it feels like
I'm a little bit on my own here.
I can't read your mind
right now, and I don't--
I can't see
what's in your head.
I don't know,
I-I feel like I said it.
_
That's time, everybody!
There's so much more depth
that needs to be
in that paint job,
but, at this point,
I can only just try to own
what we've put together.
Oy vey.
Welcome to theFace Off
reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
Let's say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening, guys.
- Hey, Glenn.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
- Hi, guys.
- Hey, Ve.
Creature and concept designer,
Neville Page.
- Hello.
Hey, Neville.
So this week,
your spotlight challenge
was to create dark and sexy
alien circus performers.
Now, I also told you
that your characters
would participate
in a spectacular performance
here on our reveal stage.
But before we see
our sci-fi circus,
let's take a look
at your creations.
I'm really happy with it.
I know Laura is too,
so I don't care
what anybody else thinks.
This is a cool-looking alien.
Our piece
isn't pulled together,
and I know we're
about to be ripped up for it.
I'm very happy.
I think this galactic
contortionist
captured our vision.
I think it looks pretty cool.
It's got the punk rock element.
It feels circus-y,
even sexy.
All right.
It's time to watch
your creations perform
with Cirque Berzerk
in our very own sci-fi circus.
I think our character
looks great,
but her makeup has
to withstand the performance,
so I'm nervous because you
never know what could happen.
What do you think of tonight's
alien circus performers?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
Now it's time to put
your makeups to the test.
Ooh! Ooh.
That's crazy.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
Judges, I'm sure you're anxious
to take a closer look
at these aliens.
Funny stuff going on here.
It's a parasite.
I don't understand it
at all, actually.
The head I like,
and there's
a lot of really nice details.
It's really asymmetrical,
isn't it?
Is it, or is it crooked?
Thanks.
The face feels very minimal
in terms of anatomy.
You know what's really weird?
It's the way they painted this.
It doesn't really go with
the scale work they put on it.
I am so stressed out right now.
It's a mess.
I'm terrified I'm gonna go home.
She held together pretty well.
Scrunch your forehead.
There you go.
That's kind of neat looking.
_
Look how symmetrical this is.
That's really hard to do that.
- Oh, yeah.
- I think it's beautiful.
Just all this around
the eye here. Great job.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
This is just so confusing
as a detail.
_
I do like some of the paint work
going on through here.
I absolutely love
a lot of the paint work
going on on that head.
But the belly is very muddy,
difficult to read.
Thank you.
The judges would now like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Tate and Frank, you're up.
Tell us about your design
this week, guys.
She's from one of the moons
of Neptune.
A space mission
crashed into it.
Her tribe was sifting
through the wreckage,
and they came across
the walkman,
which had a punk band in it
called "Dumpster Duck,"
which is the name
of our character.
There's some definite
high points on this makeup.
Who did what on this?
I sculpted the face
and painted the head.
Tate sculpted the chest,
made the mohawk, the tattoos,
and lot of the painting,
and we both worked on wardrobe.
I love the clean execution
of the head,
particularly in the paint.
For the time that you had,
that's pretty impressive.
The best part about this
makeup is the awesome paint job
that you did
all throughout her body.
Under her skin, where
it looks like stained ink,
it actually looks like
that's the coloring of her skin.
From chin down to waist,
it's muddy visually.
I do love the paints,
but it's just muddy as a design.
Frank and Tate,
you can step back.
Miranda and Eddie, you're next.
So tell us about your concept
for your alien
circus performer.
Our character is known
as the "Galactic Contortionist."
She is a space siren who lures
in other space travelers
to become part of the circus.
I sculpted the front
of the cowl,
and Eddie sculpted
the back of the cowl.
I sculpted the face.
Eddie sculpted the chest.
He painted the majority
of the body,
and I painted the head.
I think she's quite beautiful
in a very alien way.
She is very regal.
I love the crown.
I think the paint job
is beautiful.
I do, however,
think she could have been made
to look a little bit
more feminine and sexy.
The sexy, I think,
is very apparent here,
and here's why.
The more symmetrical
a person's face is,
generally speaking,
the more beautiful we find them,
and this
is beautifully symmetrical
with fine fades
and transitions with the paint.
Can we see the back please?
That's awesome.
It looks like a combination
of plant and perhaps sea life.
It works as splendidly
as the front of the head does.
There's some gorgeous things
happening.
The way you flow up
from the cheekbone.
You create the illusion
of an ear,
and it wraps itself back down
into the mandible.
That whole zone
is just handled so beautifully
in regards to form language.
- Thank you, guys.
- Thank you.
Please step back.
Alana and Laney, you're up.
So tell us about the concept.
He is a space womanizer,
and he started the circus
to entertain women
around the galaxy.
Who specifically did what?
Alana sculpted the face,
and I sculpted all the scales.
Alana helped refine them.
I also sculpted a cowl
that we scrapped
'cause of really bad edges,
so my big piece of work
didn't make it
to the stage today.
It falls short in feeling
like a dark, sexy alien.
I get that you're trying
to do something different
with the skin, but the scales
don't transition in
its surface quality or utility.
Who did the facial sculpt?
- I did.
- It's interesting.
But I don't think that
that bottom lip
lends itself to him
looking sexy or an alien.
I very much like
the beginning of the idea
of what started on the side
of the nose,
where you started to do, like,
some layers around his nostrils,
but the nose is the only thing
that started to go
in the right direction, and even
that's not a complete idea.
Most frustrating is the fact
that he looks goofy carnival,
so I don't read him as alien.
I just really wish
that you would have painted it
so that it made sense.
The colors are gorgeous,
but the purple
is just kind of like--
Psht! Psht!--
all over the place.
I think something went haywire.
Alana and Laney,
please step back.
Laura and Roy.
Tell me about this concept.
Our character is
a creature-tamer and performer,
and he also has a parasite-host
relationship going on.
I sculpted the cowl.
Laura did the face.
We both worked on the chest.
Laura did the majority
of the sculpting on that,
and I fabricated the outfit
and mechanized the head
on the parasite.
As much as I love the idea,
it just feels like it
could have been done better.
Taking that parasite
off his chest,
putting it onto his neck
and the upper back
would have integrated
better there,
and it would have solved
a lot of the design problems
that I have.
But I do like the shape
and color choices of the head,
so this is a mixed bag for me.
I'm not really fond of
the blue coloring on this alien.
More color in different areas
to break up that blue
would have been really helpful
in this makeup.
The overall vibe of the head
and some of the form choices,
I think, are good,
but I see no point
and a total waste of effort
in the insect
just hugging him perfectly
on his chest.
It's not your best effort.
Laura, Roy, please step back.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you'd please
head back to makeup room
while they deliberate
and the home audience
tweets about their favorites
using #FaceOff.
All right, judges.
Why don't we talk
about tonight's makeups.
Let's start
with Tate and Frank.
It's sculpted well,
it's applied well,
and the color is gorgeous.
I love that paint job.
It looked like
that's what her skin was.
And it was a good compensation
for the lack
of physical texture
on the face.
All right, let's move on
to Eddie and Miranda.
Ooh, I think this one was cool.
I loved that framework
around the face.
It was like a beautiful crown.
I think the sculpting
was really beautifully done.
I thought Miranda
was gonna tell me
that she sculpted
the whole head, front to back.
Eddie did a great job
continuing that aesthetic
into the back of the head.
I did really appreciate
the fact that it looked like
it was one cohesive sculpture.
All right, let's move on
to Alana and Laney.
He didn't really
look like an alien,
and the paint job was crap.
The scales as a pattern,
I don't think
they were done very well.
Their efforts this week
were hopeless.
The facial sculpt,
which sets the tone
for the whole makeup,
is not alien, is not dark,
and is not sexy.
All right.
Let's move on to Laura and Roy.
This is a concept
I cannot get behind.
This symbiotic relationship
with an insect-like thing
that was poorly designed
and executed.
An overwhelming display
of poor self-editing.
They jumped on this concept of
"Let's stick something
right there.
How genius is that?"
The color palette
was so boring.
- I know.
- It was just a pale blue alien.
All right, judges.
Have you made your decisions?
Yes, we have.
- We good?
- Yeah.
Okay, let's bring 'em back out.
Glenn, tell us about
the top teams.
We really liked several
of the makeups tonight,
but there was one that stood out
above the rest for us.
All right, Glenn.
Tell us about the top teams.
We really liked several
of the makeups tonight,
but there was one that stood out
above the rest for us.
Eddie and Miranda.
We loved the shape of the head,
and we thought
that the paint job
just worked to accentuate it.
Well done.
- Thank you.
- Thank you guys so much.
Eddie and Miranda, great job,
but, as you know,
we can only have one winner.
Glenn?
The winner of this challenge
is... Miranda.
Once again,
a brilliant application.
Your sculpting, blending,
and painting, all superior.
- Really well done.
- Thank you.
I feel so proud to win
my fourth challenge.
I think that that's quite
amazing, and I'm so honored.
_
Miranda, congratulations.
You and Eddie
can head backstage.
Thank you, guys.
Good job, Miranda.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom teams.
There was only one bottom look
for us tonight.
Alana and Laney.
All right,
that means Laura and Roy,
Tate and Frank,
you guys are all safe.
Please head back
to the makeup room.
Congrats, guys.
Alana and Laney,
if you'd please step forward.
Laney and Alana.
Despite the obstacles
you faced,
you missed some
really simple opportunities
to correct course,
and therefore delivered
a subpar makeup.
All right,
so who is going home tonight?
The person
going home tonight is...
Alana.
No!
I'm so sorry, Alana.
I'm so sorry.
Alana, we didn't think
that the character looked like
a dark, sexy alien,
and that started with the face.
I said this once before,
and I'll say it again.
This is the best stress
I've ever been under,
and I've learned
so much from everyone here,
especially you guys.
Alana, I'm so sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
Laney you are safe
for this week.
If you'd please head backstage.
Alana, I'm so proud
of what you've achieved.
I love your hunger.
I love your passion for this.
I also know
that we have not seen
nor heard the last of you,
sweetie.
I may be gone,
but I'm not over.
Alana...
it's been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head backstage
and pack up your kit.
Thank you.
I'm sad, I'm disappointed,
but I'm proud.
It's me.
I really do believe in myself.
That's something I couldn't
ever say before Face Off.
I know that this is just
gonna be a motivating factor
for me to go home and keep
sculpting, keep painting,
and keep being inspired
by the wonderful people
that I'm surrounded with.
I'm not gonna stop after this.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net