Previously, on Face Off...
Roy's comedic ghost
brought him his first win...
Hey!
And Eddie was sent home.
Now just five artists remain,
and tonight,
they will delve into the world
of lore and mysticism.
Oh, sweet.
I'm instantly excited.
Yes!
But an unprecedented event
leaves our artists
in a state of shock.
- Everything okay?
- I don't think so.
So the question is,
now, what does this do
about this challenge?
It's a disaster
on so many levels.
Why would you even go there?
And the judges are forced
to make a surprising decision.
Very tough decision this week.
Mm, horrible.
In the end,
one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Makeup
to one of their
85 international locations,
a 2013 Fiat 500, and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Only one will win Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
It's kind of weird, Eddie
not being here this morning.
Yeah.
I miss his smile already.
Eddie is such a good person,
and I'm gonna miss him smiling
and always having
something good to say.
He just-- he has
such a great attitude,
- you know what I mean?
- Yeah.
Yo.
How you doing?
- Not feeling so hot?
- Mm-mmm.
Last night,
after Eddie went home
and I was on bottom with him,
something really changed in me.
Being on bottom was weird.
I'm not having fun anymore.
I like it here.
I love all the challenges,
but I'm also
just really homesick.
What do you think
you're gonna do?
Maybe this challenge
will wake me up.
I'm really gonna try and focus.
I want to put it all aside
and just get today over with.
We're at Kenneth Hahn
state park.
I don't know what it is,
but it's cool.
There's McKenzie standing
by all these giant stones,
and it looks like Stonehenge,
and I really have no idea
what this challenge
is gonna be,
but I can't wait to find out.
- Hey, guys.
- Good morning.
From Mayan temples
to Egyptian pyramids,
ancient stone structures
are covered in images
depicting very different
mythologies
and showcasing traditions
filled with magic and mystery.
The stones and symbols
that you see here
are no different and come
from another very rich culture.
You'll be creating one of
the most recognizable creatures
seen in Norse mythology,
dark elves.
Ah, yes!
Sorry.
If there's one thing
that I know really well,
it's elves.
I'm gonna sound
like the biggest nerd,
but I've studied them
extensively, and I think
I might have an advantage
on this particular challenge.
While elves have become popular
in films like
The Lord Of The Rings trilogy,
they have roots
in Norse mythology,
like in the upcoming film
Thor The Dark World.
The Norse tradition
describes the use of runes,
which are symbols
that the Vikings believed
would grant them special powers
or abilities in battle.
This week,
your spotlight challenge
is to select one of these runes
and use it to inspire
a dark elf warrior that embodies
the symbol's attributes.
Oh, sweet.
I love old, mythical stuff,
so I'm instantly excited.
But of course,
there's the catch.
I'm not gonna tell you
what any of the symbols mean
until after you've
made your selections.
So we have no idea
what it is that we're pickin'.
Right off the bat, I'm having
a bad feeling about this.
Laura, you're up first.
Stand next to your selection.
Okay.
Laney.
Roy.
Tate.
Miranda.
Laney,
you've selected "Eihwaz."
It means immortality.
Tate,
you have "Berkano."
- It means regeneration.
- Wow.
Roy, you have "Laguz,"
and it means psychic powers.
Miranda, you have "Thurisaz,"
and it means chaos.
Laura, you have "Perthro."
It means occult abilities.
All right, it's time
to get started on your designs.
These rune stones should serve
as fantastic inspiration
for your dark elves.
Good luck, you guys.
I'll see you later at the lab.
Good-bye.
My rune means
"occult abilities,"
which means magic.
In Nordic culture, they believed
when you wrote a rune down,
it would imbue that object
with magic,
so I'm going to try
to incorporate the runes
into the helm
as if it's a magical helm.
It's gonna have armor, a corset,
and of course, ears.
I'm feeling like
I already did two dark elves.
I did the pixie
with the pointy ears, and then
an elf-like character on
the seven deadly sins challenge,
so I'm feeling kind of confused
as to how I can
make something different.
So when I see my symbol,
it looks very Mayan,
so I take inspiration
immediately
from the symbol itself,
and I am going to make him
this God-like warrior
that everybody worships
in a civilization that's already
chaotic and war-driven.
So the rune I pick
symbolizes immortality,
so I want to keep it
really young,
and I want to give him
lots of armor
that'll look like human bones
have been dipped in gold
for the people
that he has killed.
All right, everybody,
let's head back to the lab!
Whew.
Thank you.
We get back to the lab,
and we have 5 1/2 hours today.
I'm not gonna go
the route of doing
the traditional cowl
and then separate face piece.
I want to do it
all in one piece
and sculpt the face
really, really thin
so I can get the movement
that I need,
and the rune that I picked
is "Laguz."
It symbolizes psychic power.
The easiest way to convey
psychic power is enlarged head.
I've seen
The Lord Of The Rings,
and so I know that elves
are supposed to be human-like,
so I'm thinking I can
de-evolve them a little bit.
You know, maybe they
came from a primate.
The rune that I selected
symbolizes regeneration.
I want to do
a female character.
She's the queen of her tribe
of elves.
The regeneration is she selects
the strongest male elves
and breeds with them
to create a stronger race.
Also they're metal smiths,
so they're constantly
around heat,
and I want her to have
this burnt-and-new flesh,
like a snake skin, which is also
a play on the regeneration.
I really don't want to go
with the typical elf
because usually, the judges
are looking for us
to do something different,
and so my character
is going to do have
this Mayan headpiece.
And it's pretty much mandatory
for an elf to have pointy ears,
so I'm also gonna
have to incorporate the ears.
I feel a tremendous amount
of pressure with this challenge,
more than any other, because
I know a lot about dark elves.
That might actually hinder me
from doing a good job,
and that worries me
tremendously.
I look over at Laney,
and she's just kind of
pushing her sculpture around.
She's not her inspired self.
I start sculpting the face,
and I'm not even into it.
Like, I love
my character's sketch,
but I just don't want
to be doing this.
Tate has already sculpted
this most beautiful cowl,
and Miranda's, like,
halfway done with her cowl,
and it looks amazing.
I can feel, like, my passion's
just not there today.
- Laura?
- Yeah?
More elf-like quality,
big ear or smaller ear?
I want to make it
to the finale,
and this challenge
is totally out of my element.
I couldn't tell you an elf
from a dwarf from anything else.
I like the smaller one.
I've seen people
dress as dark elves
at conventions
and things like that,
but I'm not really
into that genre.
Yeah, I think
the big one's too orc-ish.
Yeah, yeah, there's a fine line
between goblin and elf.
Yeah.
I don't know what's gonna
happen with this makeup,
so yeah, I'm worried
about this one.
Gotta line up this ear.
Tate, where's Laney?
Well, I'll just check.
I walk by the bathroom
and I hear crying.
_
She's breaking down.
It sucks.
I don't know how to help her.
She just wants to be left alone.
Just give her some time.
- Hey, everything okay?
- I-I don't think so.
Worried about her.
I don't know what's going on
with Laney or if she's okay,
but if she doesn't come back,
I don't know if she
can finish this makeup,
and I think she'll be through.
Coming up...
I have to get my head
back in the game.
I am disappointed in myself.
It's a disaster
on so many levels.
Why would you even go there?
Today's the first day
of our dark elves challenge,
and I'm gettin' worried.
Laney don't seem to be
doing too well.
_
I just decide to just,
like, give it one more shot.
So Laney comes back out,
and she seems collected,
and she starts
back on her sculpture.
_
I'm fine.
I know that she's still
going through things,
but I'm happy that she's
come back to her work.
Hey, guys,
here for a walkthrough.
- Let's take a look.
- Ready?
I got occult abilities.
I'm definitely going
more traditional.
Probably do some scarification
runes around her collar,
maybe along the helm as well.
- What do these symbolize?
- In most Celtic mythologies,
they worship, like,
deer and stags,
and so I wanted to represent
all of that.
You've got so much
going on here
that you want to be able
for those to read.
- You can't paint everything dark.
- Okay.
I picked chaos.
I wanted to do
something different
than the typical elven armor
for my character.
- Wow.
- Mm-hmm.
- My symbol looks like this...
And when I saw it,
it felt very Mayan,
so I was thinking
I would do a Mayan warrior.
Interesting.
I chose regeneration,
which led me to the queen
of these dark elves.
She's responsible for
the reproduction of the hive.
- What about color?
- Yeah.
The flesh is gonna be black
and crackly,
and the metal itself,
I wanted to go
with sort of an antiqued bronze
of that nature.
Well, that'll be
a great contrast.
- Nice.
- Oh, cool.
Yeah, because you'll
definitely see the difference
between what's skin and what
you have created as a helmet.
- Absolutely.
- Yeah.
I have "Laguz,"
and it is psychic power,
so I enlarged the head to show
that the brain is larger
and has the psychic abilities.
You've got so much contour
going on here
that by going to, say, black,
you're gonna lose
a lot of your good detail,
so you need to keep that
on a lighter shade
in this part of the face here.
I've got "Eihwaz."
He is the dark elf
of immortality.
I like what you're doing
in the forehead and the nose,
but as opposed to putting
a lot of human face
just over human face,
do something
to take it away from the model.
Okay, cool.
All right, everybody,
we're heading out.
- Thank you!
- Keep the clay goin'.
- Have a good one.
- Bye!
What you doin', Tate?
Ooh, that's pretty.
Thanks, man.
Ten minutes!
Holy fuck,
you sculpted that fast.
Oh, cool.
Traditional.
Maybe too traditional.
Time's up, everybody!
Let's go home.
At the end of day one,
I'm a little nervous.
There are some people in there
taking their concepts
in a different direction,
and I'm staying so traditional
that it might not be
interesting.
So I'm leaving a lot of time
tomorrow to experiment.
I have all the tools I need.
Now, I just need to figure out
how to utilize them.
I wake up in the morning,
and there's a note on the table.
My first reaction
is maybe McKenzie left it
and there's a new twist
to this dark elf challenge.
What's that?
Unfortunately, it's not that.
She's gone.
It's a letter from Laney
saying that she's quit.
She didn't expect to stay here
as long as she did.
I just have
this decision in my head,
right when I wake up,
that I'm gonna
be leaving today.
I just know that I can't stay
any longer.
At this point,
she'd pay $100,000
just to see her family again.
Wow.
It's hard being homesick,
but, you know, I mean,
you know what you sign up for
whenever you come
and do something like this.
- What's going on?
- Laney left.
- Laney left?
- Yup.
I'm sad that she walked away.
It's one of those experiences
in life
that most people
will never have.
So the question is now,
what does this do
about this challenge?
With Laney leaving,
it creates a big issue.
Everybody gonna be safe
this challenge,
or are they gonna go ahead
and eliminate somebody?
We have no idea, and,
I mean, my thought is,
you know, just treat it
like everything was normal,
'cause honestly, she's gone,
but that's not my problem.
My problem
is winning this challenge.
I'm gonna get dressed,
'cause...
- Yeah.
- We gotta be at the lab
- in a little bit.
- Got a lot of work to do.
Day two in the lab,
and we have 9 1/2 hours,
and today is gonna be hard
after finding
this note from Laney.
I think there's a lot going
through all of our heads,
and I miss her already,
but I have so much to do today,
so I just got to keep moving
forward and focus
on what I need to do,
so I have to start on this face.
- That's really sweet.
- Thank you.
I'm still a little confused
about the whole Mayan direction,
but hopefully,
they're gonna like it,
'cause I'm not changing it now.
I have to finish my sculpts.
I need to get those sculpts
in the molding room
as fast as possible so that
I can get them ready for foam,
'cause I got a lot
of other stuff to do.
I'm a little off my game
today, to be honest.
Laney's work is still there.
It's a bit, um--
I don't know, it's like
a headstone or something,
but I have to get my head
back in the game.
I finish up my sculpts and I go
back to the molding room
and start molding.
- Wow, that looks sick.
- Thanks, dude.
I really want
to get the mold done
so I can go ahead and run maybe,
like, a poly foam copy of it
so I can start trying
to work my paint scheme out.
I want to make a lot
of scarification prosthetics
in order to imbue her
with a sense of magic,
so I start working
on my Pros-Aide transfers.
All you have to do is sculpt
something on a flat surface
and then make a mold
out of silicone.
Once the silicone sets,
you pour Pros-Aide,
which is the medical adhesive
that we use,
inside the compartment.
You put it in a refrigerator,
and once that's sat
for 24 hours,
it can look like some
really kickass-looking scars.
It's a little difficult
to know where to go
with this challenge,
and I'm just fiddling
with this cowl
over and over again,
and I know I'm taking
way too long.
It's like I keep putting things
on and then wiping them off,
and I don't like
anything I'm doing.
All of a sudden, I realize
I am the only one
who's not in the mold room.
This mold is gonna take
quite a while,
and I've never been so scared.
I don't know
if I'm gonna have anything
to put on the stage.
_
It's day two,
and I'm just so behind.
Everyone else
is in the mold room.
I need to start molding,
or else I won't have anything
to put on the stage.
I just start molding this
faster than I've ever molded
anything in my life.
Like, I am literally throwing
Ultracal at the mold.
I can't run this
in latex and poly foam.
This piece has to move.
Okay.
My poly foam is done
and it looks great,
so I can do a little,
you know, paint test on it.
The judges have really
been giving me a lot of crap
about having rough paint jobs,
and so I want to give 'em
a lot of detail in this.
Down to the last minute, huh?
Oh, my God.
It's only a few minutes
before the end of the day
and there's no way
that I'm gonna
get this cowl finished.
All right, guys, that's time.
Let's get out of here.
So now, I have to figure out
somehow to make this cowl work
with latex.
Tomorrow's gonna be
the hardest application day
I've ever had by far,
and I don't even know
if I'm gonna have a piece
to show the judges,
and at this point,
I am pretty much sure
that I'm going home.
All right,
let's see what we got.
Application day,
we have four hours in the lab
and one hour in last looks,
and I'm going to have
to get that facial prosthetic
and that cowl down
as quickly as possible,
'cause there is
a lot of painting to do.
Hello!
What's up, girl?
Hey, Kirk.
How you doing?
So I'm extremely behind today.
And I need help opening a mold.
Thank God Vince is here,
thank God he's strong,
because I am so in trouble today
and I physically can't lift--
even lift this mold,
much less open it on my own.
Keep pulling.
Awesome.
Fuck yes.
Here, I'll show you
how this power washer works.
I feel terrible to be
putting him in this position,
but I only have one shot
at this now,
because I'm doing it today,
and if I mess it up,
it's not gonna work at all.
You can just hang on to that.
We're just gonna carry him in.
Thank God
he's such a good sport.
I notice that, you know,
Miranda is running around
and so is her model.
Here, you can--
Yeah, you can do that.
And as thick as possible.
Maybe could you
blow-dry this one?
I'm pretty sure he'll
be a contestant on season eight,
'cause he's learning so much
in the lab today.
Is this your first season here?
Yeah.
- How do you like it?
- Oh, I love it.
I'm right on schedule.
Let's do this.
Let's get it on there.
The piece, you know,
goes on fairly easy,
and it's almost flawless,
but I don't know
if it's a dark elf.
Hmm.
The Pros-Aide transfers
that I had made for the arms
are not as stiff
as I had intended.
These didn't work out.
I'm going to have
to physically paint them on
when I get to last looks.
It's a good thing I have backup
options for everything I do,
'cause otherwise,
I would be capital "F."
Could you start
putting on your costume?
Let me get you
into your body texture.
In order to achieve
the regenerative
snake-like texture,
I put down a base layer
of prosthetic adhesive,
and then I smear a wet layer
of powder over the top of it,
and then I take a hair dryer
and I dry the moisture
out of it,
which causes it
to crack and spread.
_
Then you can powder it
with charcoal power.
It grabs in in the cracks,
so you just have
this really successful-looking
cracked finish.
Try not to bend your arms
too much until that dries, okay?
- Like, my whole hand too?
- Uh, you can wait on the hand,
just 'cause you might
need to use it.
At this point,
really all I can do is laugh.
I mean, I even have Vince
trying to paint his own legs.
Vince, like, has done
as much of this as I have,
and I feel like a failure.
Ten minutes!
Ten minutes left!
Help me grab 'em by the door.
That's time, everybody!
I really am scared
at this point.
It's not painted.
It's not even blended.
This was my idea, originally.
I'm going home tonight,
but I'm not gonna just
give up on the makeup,
because that's not who I am.
I'm gonna do the best I can
and hope for the best.
Coming up...
That's really messed up.
I can't find
my airbrush compressor.
- Yeah, that's really good.
- It looks fantastic.
If you try to do that
to a director,
you won't be there tomorrow.
We're at last looks,
and we got one hour left.
All that I really got to do
is touch-ups.
I still have to paint all
of the symbols all over my elf,
and that's gonna take up
the majority of my time.
Ugh, it's stressful.
I can barely pull this cowl
out of the mold,
and I'm trying to cut the seam
off as quickly as I can.
I think I've set a record
for most behind ever
for last looks.
This is a disaster.
That's really messed up.
I can't find
my airbrush compressor.
Now, I have to hand-paint
everything,
and it's definitely hurting me,
but I have to make
with what I have.
I'm freaking out.
That's time!
Fuck.
I never thought
I would ever do a makeup
that was this unfinished.
I'm so embarrassed.
It's the worst makeup
I have ever, ever done.
Welcome
to the Face Off reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
Let's first say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening, guys.
- Hi.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
Hi, everybody.
- Hey, Ve.
- Hey.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
- Hello.
- Hey, Neville.
This week,
your spotlight challenge
was to choose a Norse rune
and create a dark elf warrior
that embodies
the symbol's attributes.
Let's see
what you've come up with.
I really, really love
the fact that my dark elf
is a full character
from top to bottom.
She looks beautiful.
She looks elegant,
so I'm excited to hear
what the judges have to say.
I'm really happy and impressed
with the overall look,
the silhouette.
I think I have
one of the best ones.
This is so painful.
I don't want to look.
I just want to go
to a different place in my head
and pretend
that this is not mine
and I didn't do this.
It looks
a little un-proportioned.
He's got a big head,
so I'm concerned about that,
but overall, I'm happy
with the way that it looks.
Judges, it's time
to take a closer look
at our elven warriors.
Look at how beautiful
that blends up around there.
Is this all one piece?
Yeah, it's a face piece,
and then the cowl
glues down to it, so she gets
all those nice blending edges.
- Man, that's really good.
- Yeah.
That foam edge there
is so nice.
Look at on the nose
and above her eye.
Oh, yeah,
it goes down the nose.
- Can't even tell.
- Seamless.
Really solid too, she's not
getting any rub on anything,
- it's sealed nicely.
- Yeah, it's good.
Very clean.
Thank you.
This is beautifully weathered.
- These colors here are great.
- Yeah.
I really, really, really love
the way that the color
of the makeup goes
into the color of the armor.
I think the armor could have
more color on it...
- Yeah, yeah.
- But they work so well together.
Open your mouth for us.
- Can we just see that bottom?
- Oh, that's cool.
- And that is you, right?
- No, no.
Okay, thank you.
- Thank you.
Didn't finish up the paint job.
The gold comes down--
I thought I saw that
from far away-- like,
onto the ear for some reason.
- Like, what the--
- Is it part of the same sculpt?
- Interesting.
- Is it separated?
- All over it?
- I don't know.
What the hell
was she doing this week?
I don't know.
- Can you turn sideways?
- Sideways?
Yeah.
Oh, no, don't look at the back.
Oh, yeah, bizarre.
It's so bad.
I am totally, totally disgusted
and disappointed in myself.
It looked bad from afar,
but it is inexcusable up close,
and this will be
my first time on the bottom
and probably my last.
Who made your favorite
elven warrior tonight?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
- Yeah, bizarre.
- Yeah.
The whole thing is quite bizarre.
I don't understand
the mousy shape of the nose.
Turn all the way around for us.
Okay.
Eesh.
I screwed up so badly,
and there's only
four of us here,
so there's no scraping by.
I know I'm going home.
- Okay.
- All right.
What are we looking at?
I mean, basically,
it's just this head, really.
I mean, clearly,
he fabricated this.
- Yeah, he did that too.
- Yeah.
It's a good silhouette.
This is a hairpiece
that wasn't even laid in.
Those are all hair pieces.
I do actually like
the form language,
it's just the proportions.
I just hope that the judges
take it for what it is.
I'm happy with it,
so I guess we'll find out.
The judges would like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Laura, please step up.
Laura, tell us
about your character.
The rune that I was given
meant occult abilities.
I translated
occult ability in that
I would put runes
on various parts of the armor
to imbue my warrior with magic.
I think it's stunning.
You understood the concept
so well
that it allowed you to flow
right into the construction
of your character,
and it shows.
Tell us why
you chose that color.
I wanted to get that dark elf
aesthetic in there, so--
because they're underground,
the skin tone
is a light lavender.
- It's beautifully done.
- Thank you.
My ignorance really
is enjoying your awareness,
and also how you back up
those choices.
Your intellect,
and the way you think through
why she would be that color,
is spot-on.
Thank you.
One of my favorite things
on this makeup
is the aesthetic of that
tribal tattooing you did.
I love the swirling effect
of it.
It's so graceful and really
subtle and really pretty.
- Beautiful makeup.
- Thank you.
Laura, please step back.
Roy, please come forward.
Tell us about your elf
and your concept
behind your creation, please.
The rune
that I chose was "Laguz,"
which is psychic power,
which is the reason
for the enlarged head.
This, to me,
doesn't really work as an elf.
It looks more
like a creature as opposed
to something that has
more of a humanistic form.
Because you made his head
so big,
you didn't adapt
the rest of his physique
to carry that big,
giant head around,
so it's made his body
look very small.
It's a pretty cool makeup,
I just don't think
it's for this challenge, honey.
Okay.
I think of the elf
almost as a toy,
and this is
a dullsville action figure.
I appreciate the concept
of the paint technique
that you were trying
to apply here.
I think that
that was right thinking.
That's the good part.
What in the hell caused you
to make a decision
to go so far away from
the very core of this challenge?
You were asked to do an elf.
I'm not familiar
with dark elves.
You know the idea
of what an elf looks like,
long ears, pointy nose.
If you do that
to a director--
he asks for an elf
and you give him this--
you won't be there tomorrow.
My apologies.
Roy, please step back.
Tate, you're next.
- Hi, guys.
- Hi, Tate.
So tell us about your elf
and your rune choice.
Well, my rune
symbolized regeneration,
so I decided to go
with my interpretation
of what would be
the queen of the dark elves.
It's her job to find
the healthiest specimen
and sire
the rest of their tribes.
'Cause I know that
they're master metal workers,
they're constantly around heat,
I really wanted to do
the dry, cracked skin
and to make it look
like the skin regenerates.
It looks fantastic.
The helmet design
that you've done,
I love the fact
that it's starting
to almost integrate
into her face,
and some of the details
that you have,
like this flaky, dry skin,
it looks authentic
at a distance, even up close.
You have a very successful
makeup in here.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
I absolutely adore the fact
that you've taken your rune
and allowed it to motivate you
to go so much further
with the character.
You were able to do all this
cool stuff with her body.
I love what you've done
with the armor.
I appreciate it.
I think the choice
of that gorgeous red
against all this silver
is just really cool.
That a great decision that was.
She looks really dark.
She's sexy, she's strong.
She really says
"dark, warrior elf" to me.
Thank you very much, Ve.
Tate, please step back.
Let's talk to Miranda.
Miranda, tell us
about your character
and how you integrated
the rune.
Well, my symbol was chaos,
and I was really
initially inspired
by the actual symbol itself.
It had a Mayan vibe to it.
It's obviously very incomplete.
What happened this week?
Why is this such a wreck?
I-I don't really
have a good answer.
I feel like I just really
messed up this week,
and I'm really disappointed
in myself.
There is what
I'm going to kindly call
an inadequate decision
regarding the ears
and their support
of the headdress.
It seems to me
like you've done it
so that you could split the mold
with a two-piece
so that it's the ears
and the helmet and the-- it--
Horrible decision.
The planes
that the ears lie upon
no longer work at all,
anatomically.
This is kind of
a blue-ish green makeup
that I really don't like.
Why would you even go there
knowing that you
couldn't finish this color?
I mean, you didn't even
get the base color
on him all the way today.
I'm just so disappointed.
You've done so many
awesome makeups,
and now, all of a sudden,
you put this out here.
It's a disaster
on so many levels
that you've already addressed
and accepted,
but I don't want you
to lose sight of the successes
that actually have occurred
within it.
The overall sculpt,
pretty good,
but it's just a sketch.
If this was due on the day
as a final design,
camera-ready,
you're screwed.
I feel really bad about this.
I just hope that I get
the chance to continue.
Miranda, please step back.
Sorry, girl.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
- Thank you, guys.
All right, judges,
let's talk about the looks
you liked the most this week.
Why don't we start with Laura?
I particularly like her
intelligence behind her choices.
Her justification
is so spot-on.
I especially liked that sort
of tribal paint job she did.
Absolutely perfectly blended.
One thing I think was lacking
was her ability
to integrate her rune.
It was there in an incredibly
just basic, rudimentary way.
Yeah, I don't think it had
a real dark connotation to me.
I-- It sort of just felt
sort of elfen.
All right,
let's move on to Tate.
For me, that is a dark elf.
The skin was dark.
It was aged.
The fact that he used his rune
to create another level
of the makeup,
to make it look like
cracking flesh, was brilliant.
What a great way
to integrate the rune.
That, to me,
was a really good-looking,
complete character.
All right,
let's move on to the looks
you liked the least this week.
Why don't we start with Roy?
It was an interesting design
for a completely different
challenge altogether.
He did do a pretty decent job
of painting that thing,
and at least he finished
his character.
It just doesn't matter
how good the paint
is on something.
When it doesn't even fit
into the challenge,
it's sort of the end
of the conversation for me.
All right,
let's move on to Miranda.
Oh, man, I don't know
what happened to her this week.
- Wow.
- What was she doing?
It was an atrocity.
That felt so atypical,
to be so incredibly indecisive.
How is it that she
mismanaged her time so badly
to allow just a few minutes
to paint it?
It is one of, if not the,
worst time management issues
we've ever seen on the show.
She had a good idea, but guys,
that's as far as it went.
All right, so now,
with Laney's departure,
it begs the question,
what happens now?
Since we have somebody
who has left,
we've essentially
got a free elimination.
Do we end up
allowing someone to progress
even though they've done
less than acceptable
- with their makeup this week?
- Right.
That seems unfair as well.
If you do a substandard makeup,
typically,
what we do is let them go.
It's a very, very,
very tough decision this week.
- Mm.
- Horrible.
All right then, judges,
have you made your decisions?
Very difficult one,
but yes, we have.
Let's bring 'em back out.
Glenn, tell us
about the top looks.
Laura, we love
how well-thought-out
all of your
creative decisions were,
and we were blown away
by the quality
of your edge work tonight.
Thank you.
Tate, the shapes
in your armor were so cool,
and your character's story
was both obvious and impactful
- at first glance.
- Thank you.
Glenn, who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
Glenn, who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
Tate.
Wow.
We love how you
incorporated the rune
by adding a second level
to your makeup.
- Smart decision.
- Thank you very much.
I'm really blown away.
I've won three challenges
and I'm feeling pretty good.
Tate, congratulations.
You and Laura can head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you, guys.
Unfortunately,
that means Roy and Miranda,
you are on the bottom
this week.
Please step forward.
All right, Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Roy, the proportions
and sculpture of the head
were way off,
and the design decisions
were wholly inappropriate
for this challenge.
Miranda, you really struggled
with time management this week,
and it's almost impossible
for us to get past the fact
that it was so unfinished.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
No one is going home tonight.
Thank you, guys.
In light of Laney's departure,
you will move forward this week
for one reason only.
You did not give up.
We cannot express to you
strongly enough
how hard you both
need to work next week
to redeem yourselves.
- Thank you guys so much.
- Thank you.
All right, guys,
that means you are both safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you very much.
- Get ready to kill it, guys.
We will.
I deserve to go home this week
for that disaster
that I put forward on the stage,
so I'm just thankful
that I have one more chance,
and this one's got to count.
Well, you got us both
for one more challenge.
It's a huge relief, you know,
knowing that neither one of us
are gonna go home tonight.
Oh, my God.
The top four is where
I made it in season three
and I'm not gonna be
in that spot again.
It's really exciting
that we're the final four.
I feel honored to be here
with you guys.
Here's to second chances.
That's right.
That works for me.
The person that doesn't give up
is the one that will
make it through,
you know, to the final three,
and "Quit"
is not in my vocabulary.
Congratulations to everyone.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net