Previously onFace Off...
Miranda's creepy mole rat
brought her her third win.
Your creature
worked on every level.
Thank you guys so much.
Adolfo's piece fell short,
and he was sent home.
Now 11 artists remain,
and tonight,
they'll face the mother
of all challenges...
The ultimate giver of life,
Mother Nature.
That's my babe.
I love her!
But some will lose their heads.
Head came off the mannequin.
I've never seen anything
like it.
So bad.
It's really hard to focus.
My head's in the wrong place.
It sucks.
Have you ever done
a beauty makeup?
I mean, the eyelashes
aren't even on properly.
I do love the overall nature
of this piece very much.
It is only with contempt
that I regard
that particular decision.
In the end, one will win
a VIP trip from
Kryolan Professional Make-Up
to one of their
85 international locations,
a 2013 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Only one will win Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
How are you feeling
this morning?
Still a little shaky.
I didn't sleep very well.
Yeah, me neither.
I was embarrassed.
After the last challenge,
I feel like I dodged a bullet.
I just felt awful
because it wasn't what I wanted
to put out there,
and it was a piece of crap.
I was prepared to hear my name.
Me too.
I'm sorry it was Adolfo, but I'm
glad it was him instead of me.
Yeah, I thought
for a split second there
we were gonna have
two middle-aged men
with heart attacks.
Now I'm trying to get my head
back in the game
for this next challenge.
If I don't get serious,
I will be going home quick,
and I don't want
to go home quick.
So we're at the LA Arboretum...
Oh, it's beautiful out here.
I'm just like,
"Planting flowers, oh, my God"
I am so ready for
this challenge, whatever it is.
Good morning, guys.
- Good morning, girl.
- Morning.
Welcome
to the Los Angeles County
Arboretum & Botanic Garden.
Featuring plants
from all around the world,
it's also been seen
in hundreds of movies,
such as Jurassic Park,
Meet The Fockers, and Tarzan.
Wow.
This week's
spotlight challenge is based
on one of the most well-known
mythological characters
of all time.
She's the ultimate giver
of life, Mother Nature.
That's my babe.
I love her!
For this week's
spotlight challenge,
you will each create an original
Mother Nature goddess...
But I want these characters
to be really personal
for you guys too,
so I want each of you
to include a feature
in your makeup that represents
your mom.
Aw.
This is so sweet.
Honestly, I'm inspired
by my mother
every single challenge.
She's an incredible artist
herself.
Now, before you get started
on your designs,
I'd like to introduce you
to a special guest
who knows exactly what it takes
to impress the judges--
last season's Face Off champion,
Anthony Kosar.
Aw.
Cool.
- Great to see you again.
- Great to see you too.
I'm very excited
because I watched
every episode of season four,
and Anthony was one
of the best artists
to be on Face Off.
And to have his feedback
and advice
in this challenge
is incredible.
You created a couple
of winning makeups
that showcased
nature and beauty,
so how can these artists
make sure
that their goddesses stand out?
You really want to bring out
the feminine features,
make all the forms soft, subtle,
and really elegant.
Great. Thank you.
- Anthony, thank you very much.
- Thank you.
And thank you
for being here today.
Thanks for having me.
All right, guys, keep in mind,
the judges will be looking
for beautiful characters.
Now go ahead and explore
these amazing gardens.
- Thank you.
- Bye!
Laura and I head off
to the rose garden.
I love my mom very much,
and she's very hardworking,
so being in the rose garden
inspired me
to incorporate thorns resembling
her strength and hard work.
I'm playing around
with the idea
of making her skin
a tree texture.
My mother, she's been
such an inspiration to me,
and she's so into music,
so I'm gonna try to incorporate
a trumpet-looking flower
into the design.
I love my mom, and we've had
a really rough year,
and it's clouding
this challenge.
We lost my dad.
My mom has Parkinson's.
It's been getting
progressively worse,
so it's hard to separate
what I'm supposed
to try to do on this,
so I'm just doodling.
I can't really focus
on what I need to do.
My mom, she's known
for her hair like I am,
and her silhouette
really comes forward,
so I want to put that
in my design.
I love my mom,
and I want to bring that emotion
into my character as well.
My mom used to have
a green thumb.
She could take a snip
of any plant and make it grow.
Mother Nature
is like the giver of life,
from the roots
all the way to the top,
so I'm gonna incorporate
a little bit of all that.
My mom is a florist,
and we worked in the gardens,
and she taught me
the beauty of nature,
like spiders that are beautiful
and how they're meant
to be here.
So my idea is to incorporate
a lot of beautiful insects
into my makeup.
Okay, guys,
let's head back to the lab.
Whew.
So we have six hours today
in the lab.
First thing we have to do
is pick our models.
I start right off the bat
with sculpting out the wood
textures on my chest piece.
The wood textures
remind me of my mom
because she grew up on a farm,
and she loves wood in her home.
I've already done this makeup
on this show.
On season two finale,
I did an Earth Mother goddess,
so I have no idea
what to do at this point.
First thing that pops
into my head is
my mother was really pretty
in the '60s,
when she had
these beehive hairdo pictures.
And I'm thinking,
let's do
a 1960s retro, crazy mama.
My mother raises deer,
so I decide to go with a deer.
I want to keep a lot
of the feminine qualities alive
in the face.
My mother is also
a very spiritual person,
so based
on my mother's spirituality,
I'm going to do a tree of life.
I may be getting too far away
from Mother Nature,
but I can't pass up
this opportunity
to do something great
for my mom.
My concept is
a feminine-shaped tree
that's gonna have a belly,
so I'm thinking
it could be pregnant.
For me, being pregnant
brought me together
so tight with my mom.
It's a very magical thing
in a woman's life.
Hey, guys, my dad and I
are here for a walk-through.
- Oh, my God, yes!
- Hi.
Anthony's joining us.
How you guys doing?
It's really cool
to have Anthony here
because he's been where we are.
- Hey, Miranda.
- Hey, guys.
Tell us about
your Mother Nature goddess.
I'm going
with a leaf-inspired makeup.
I'm gonna do a cowl...
Is this gonna come down
around the head?
I'm thinking
I'll try to cover her eyebrows.
Eyebrows create expression,
and if you don't
make them right,
you can either make them
look sad or clown-like
- or happy or something...
- Yeah.
So I would suggest bringing
your forehead down
to where you could literally
get rid of them then.
I want to have
a pregnant belly.
I want to make it clear,
so I can have something inside
that you can see.
One thing you might want
to consider is,
you know,
how animals live inside trees.
That's an idea.
Thank you.
My plan was to add a wig
or some hair
and transition that hair
into this river
and then that river carry on
through armpieces.
I would even airbrush
some green into the wig
to tie it in
to what you're doing here.
At this point, I'm unsure
as to whether I'm gonna take
Mr. Westmore's advice.
It's fair to say
that I'm not sure what to do.
I'm going
for this caterpillar motif.
I didn't really get
a caterpillar out of it.
I actually got more
of, like, a Venus flytrap.
Mm.
Keep it very feminine
so that people can get
a first glance,
see the beauty in it.
So keep
some of the features softer.
Okay.
- Good luck!
- Good luck, guys.
- Bye-bye.
- Thank you.
Bye.
I'm in such a weird headspace,
it's hard for me to come up
with anything beyond just--
I got a drawing down.
I'm just gonna build this.
So the first drawing
I come up with
is kind of what I stick to,
incorporating the flower
and those leaves,
and that's pretty much it.
As the day keeps going on,
I'm just getting
more and more frazzled.
It's just--
my head's in the wrong place.
This is a new one for me,
being one of the first people
into the mold room,
and I feel good about it
'cause I'll have these things
all ready to paint tomorrow.
I could see Frankie's
not feeling this challenge,
and I think I know why.
He just lost his father
this year.
His mom is not
in the greatest health.
I just keep thinking
about my mom.
She's having the hardest year
of her life,
and it's really hard
for me to focus.
Coming up...
I'm starting to have
a panic attack.
Damn!
What in the hell is she doing?
This is gorgeous makeup.
I think it was a grave mistake
this week.
This is
a Mother Nature challenge,
and our design needs to be
influenced by our mothers.
Frank's had a rough year.
His mom is not
in the greatest health,
and I could see
that he is losing it.
If this were a job
in the real world,
I probably would've passed.
It's too close to home
right now, too fresh.
I really don't want to see
my friend lose himself.
He really needs
to stand up straight
and stiffen up that upper lip,
like, just do
what he needs to do.
I can't stop
because I'm in a sad place.
If I did throw in the towel,
like, that doesn't
serve anybody.
That's not gonna make
my mom happy.
That's not honoring my dad.
So I just keep pushing
and pushing
and just praying
that I can at least be safe.
- What's the time?
- 30 minutes left, guys!
And that's time!
Time's up. We gotta go.
End of day one, I'm exhausted,
but the last thing I want
is to try and make an excuse
for my makeup or my concept
or my design.
At the end of the day,
I just have to do it.
- Gots a lots to do today.
- Over here.
It's day two of our challenge,
we have 9 1/2 hours,
and I need to get
my cowl and my face
completely finished,
both molds made,
and I need to get started
on this bodice
that I'm going to create.
I got a lot of work to do.
Everything you do
is always so pretty.
- Thank you.
- Hire me someday, please.
I'm looking
at everybody else's things,
and I'm going, I'm not making
anything like that.
I'm starting to get
a little nervous
maybe I'm going
the wrong direction,
but it's way too late
to shift gears at this point.
So this is a calculated risk,
and they're either
gonna love this,
or they're gonna hate it.
I'm taking the advice
of Anthony,
and I'm using a bunny
inside the belly.
I'm making this pregnant belly
by using heat
to shape this plastic onto it.
And I like the fact that
it's wrinkling in certain spots,
because it's giving it
that realism of having veins
and wood texture.
I think
it's working out perfectly.
4 hours and 14 till end of day.
It took me a bit longer
than I wanted
to finish all my sculptures,
and everyone is
in the mold room.
And some people are already
cleaning out their mold,
which starts
to really freak me out,
because maybe I didn't
give myself enough time,
but I gotta get it done.
You're getting
a lot of work done, huh?
I don't want to hear what
I heard last week ever again.
I'm trying to figure out
what's gonna be
the best way
to make my orchids,
so what I do is
I take my orchid,
and then I put it
on the vacuform machine,
which pulls out all of the air
that's in the space in between,
so you get a perfect copy
of your sculpture.
And it actually looks
really good,
so I spend the next hour
making 12 of them.
I'm gonna add a lot of stuff.
I've fabricated the arms,
so I take two spandex gloves,
and I put them over the arms
and hands of a mannequin.
And from there,
I begin to build up
liquid latex and cotton
to form the shape
that I desire.
I really try to match
the textures
on the arms and the cowl.
Unfortunately, I don't have
much time to pre-paint,
so I have a lot of work
to do tomorrow.
- That's sick, man.
- Thanks, dude.
You got some talent, dude.
I've got to start to do
some fabrication
because these trumpet flowers
are a pretty important part
of the overall design.
They're the symbol of my mother
and her love of music,
so I take some foam,
and I start fabricating
as best to my ability.
I don't know much
about this foam,
but I'm hoping it'll turn out.
I thought my wig
was over the top.
That wig is
definitely over the top.
I don't feel so bad.
I thought my wig was large,
and I look over at Lyma,
and I'm going,
what in the hell is she doing?
It's huge.
I mean, it's cool, but...
- But it's too big?
- Damn!
It's almost like
we're having a big wig contest
in this part of the lab.
Yeah, it's cracked
on this side.
I'm starting to get
really worried about time
because I'm starting to realize
I'm not sure
if my mold's gonna open.
If I don't have a cowl,
all I have is
my butterfly face sculpture,
and that is not enough
for a makeup at all.
All right, go ahead
and go start cleaning that out.
I'll get this off.
Finally, Tate opens it up,
he gets one side off,
and I run outside
and start cleaning it out.
I'm trying to hurry up
and get the mannequin's head
out of the mold.
I ripped
her mannequin's head off.
It's an "Oh, shit" moment.
I've never seen anything
like it.
It's made out of fiberglass.
They make boats
out of this shit,
so I don't know what happened.
I don't like to break
other people's stuff,
so I've got, like, 15 minutes
to help this girl get her stuff
ready for foam.
And if we just grab
another mannequin,
it's guaranteed,
even though they're
carbon copies of each other,
there's gonna be
something different,
and it's not gonna register
the same.
Head came off the mannequin.
Tate comes outside,
and the entire mannequin head
is ripped off of my mannequin.
I am just freaking out.
Head came off the mannequin.
Tate comes outside,
and the entire mannequin head
is ripped off of my mannequin.
The head snaps off,
and I've never seen
anything like it.
I am so scared.
I do not think I'm going to have
a good piece tomorrow.
Oh, my God, so bad.
I've got, like, 15 minutes
to help this girl get her stuff
ready for foam.
And if we just grab another
mannequin, it's guaranteed,
even though they're
carbon copies of each other,
there's gonna be
something different,
and it's not gonna register
the same.
And I can't have that
on my conscience.
I'll put epoxy on it and then
just wrap it in duct tape.
It should cast fine.
He says that he can fix it,
no problem.
I trust him,
so I'm just gonna let him do it
and just hold my breath.
- Thank you so much.
- You got it.
That's amazing!
So by the end of day two,
I get the idea of making
a crown of leaves,
and so I grab some L200 foam
and some raffia.
And I have to paint some leaves
because all we have
were some deep red ones,
so I want them to be orange.
Just sprayed them
with a little light toner
- and some yellow...
- Yeah.
And they came out pretty good,
actually.
Hopefully, I'll have time
to finish it.
What's that time say, Frankie?
- 17.
- 17?
Thank you.
So you're, like, gonna
literally make her a flower.
Like, blend--
Yeah, a flowery petal thing.
I dig it, man.
Nice work.
That's time, everybody!
Ooh.
All right, well--
- So it's the end of day two,
and I'm pretty stressed.
I don't know how my foam
is gonna come out,
since my mold wasn't very good,
but I guess I'm just gonna have
to sleep on it
and pray for the best.
It's application day.
I have four hours in the lab
and one hour last looks,
and I need to apply the cowl,
two armpieces,
and a backpiece,
paint everything,
and I need to make
this character beautiful,
or I'll be in trouble.
My foam piece
actually didn't turn out so bad.
There are some really bad edges
on it,
but I was planning
on hiding those in moss anyways.
They're here!
You're gonna be Mother Nature.
You're gonna have branches
coming out,
and it goes from, like-- from
spring, summer, fall, winter--
so, yeah,
we got some pretty cool stuff.
What is this?
- It's so ugly!
- Yeah, it's pretty ugly.
The wardrobe I requested
is not what I got.
'Cause I have so much to do,
I'm just gonna start
on my application
and hope
that I can finish quickly
and construct a new wardrobe.
Hopefully this fits you okay.
All right, let's get
this thing glued down.
I start applying her chin.
_
Even though I'm working
on her chin, she keeps talking.
_
I'm like, okay, shh.
Shh, shh.
I'm losing time
when I need to be spending it
on other aspects
of this character.
I'm gonna spin you around
this way.
My game plan today is
to just get it all done
as fast as possible.
The first thing I gotta do
is get the branches applied
to my cowl.
I definitely want to make sure
that these branches are secure,
'cause that'd be embarrassing
to have her walk out onstage,
and she starts losing limbs.
But they seem to be holding
pretty well,
and it's not as heavy
as I thought it was gonna be.
I have to apply
the pregnant belly,
but this was supposed to be
a bunny nest with baby bunnies,
but I only get two,
and they're really big.
They don't fit together
in the belly.
I'm deciding to only use one,
and it looks a lot like
a stuffed bunny,
so it could be a very big risk.
But if I don't put anything
in there,
it's just gonna be
an empty belly,
and it won't make sense.
Two hours, everybody!
Two hours left on the clock!
_
It's me, Scott,
Lyma, and Laney.
_
Yeah, it's nerve-racking.
First I apply
the facial prosthetic,
and then I move on
to the chest piece.
Things seem to be falling
into place...
♪ Here comes some color ♪
...and as long as the paint job
is on par,
I might actually have a chance
at winning this.
I like this.
All right,
we'll keep those there for now.
that's 30 minutes, everybody!
I want to put the wig on her
at last looks.
I don't want to put it on her
at the shop
because there's no way
that wig would make it
over to the studio.
But that's making me
a little nervous
because I didn't want to save
something that big and important
to chance it
in that hectic last hour.
Unfortunately,
I don't think there's gonna be
any other way around it.
The clock is ticking,
and I'm starting to get
a little nervous
because I know my character
is not the strongest here.
My mom is one
of my biggest fans,
and I really don't want
to let her down.
Time's up!
How you feeling, dude?
I wish I was farther along
in the paint job.
I still have to make
an entire costume.
Oh, really?
I don't know if I'll have time,
but I want to do
a full body painting
during last looks.
I want this to be beautiful.
I want this for my mother,
and if it sucks,
I'm gonna feel really terrible.
Coming up...
I think you made a lot
of really smart decisions.
She's freaking gorgeous.
This is a total failure.
♪ I'm gonna get the chair
I want ♪
So there's one hour left.
We're at last looks,
and this is the most work
I've ever had to do.
I still have to lighten up
all the colors.
I still have to add moss
and leaves
and all this other stuff.
A part of me is freaking out.
Crap.
As soon as she sits down,
I realize
that little-bitty wrinkle
has turned into a big crack,
and I know they're just gonna
bust me wide open for that
if I don't fix it.
That's 15 minutes, everybody!
Can we get a dust mask?
My model, she tells me
she's getting sick
and not to do
the finishing touches.
_
I went to spray glitter on her,
and that made her sick.
And I went to airbrush her,
And then she decides
that she can no longer be
in my makeup chair,
that she has to leave,
and I'm not gonna get
the full amount of time
to do this makeup,
and it really bums me out.
That's time, guys, that's time!
- I didn't see yours.
- She had to leave early.
- Why?
- She got super sick.
I could have a top look,
and now I might not even have
a makeup at all.
Welcome
to theFace Offreveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
Let's say hello
to our talented panel of judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio Glenn Hetrick...
Hi, guys.
- Hi, Glenn.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill...
- Good evening.
- Hi, Ve.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
Hello, everyone.
- Hi, Neville.
So, guys, this week,
your spotlight challenge
was to create a beautiful
Mother Nature goddess
inspired by the beautiful plants
and flowers
at the Los Angeles County
Arboretum.
I also asked you
to incorporate an element
that represented
your own mother
to give your goddess
a personal touch.
Let's take a look
at your creations
while the audience at home
tweets about their favorites,
using #FaceOff.
First up is Laney's goddess.
I'm worried my model's
not gonna walk onstage,
and I'm freaked out
a little bit.
And finally, she walks out,
thank goodness.
Even though I didn't get to put
everything that I wanted on her,
she still looks beautiful.
I'm happy with it.
I don't think I'm going home.
My goddess looks
exactly the way
that I planned for her to look.
I'm extremely pleased
with this makeup.
If I would've painted
the face gold
to complement the wardrobe,
that would have been better.
I really hope I don't go home
this week.
I'm so taken back
by her presence,
and I can see my mother
in this.
I'm pleased with how she looks.
She stands out as being
a unique color,
and I'm hoping that that works
in my benefit.
I'm not the kind of person
that's gonna regurgitate
a makeup that I've already done,
and I wanted to do
something humorous.
I love this character.
I just feel like
she's so beautiful,
and it's like a breath
of fresh air.
I feel that this makeup
came together well,
and I think my mom's
really gonna like this makeup,
so I'm proud of it.
I think she's stunning,
and I'm feeling very proud.
I love the bright color
in the center
going out into darker colors.
Maybe it's too colorful.
Oh, well,
that's the risks you take.
It's not the strongest piece
out there,
and it's definitely
not the weakest.
So I'm feeling pretty good,
but I'm still nervous,
'cause I never know which way
the judges are gonna decide.
Judges, it's time to take
a closer look at these beauties.
This is kind of cool,
the honey dripping down.
Actually, there's more
metallic on the left side
than there is the right.
I'm so nervous.
I'm worried the judges are gonna
think it's a bit incomplete.
This is pretty cool.
I love the color choices
of flowers.
Love the colors.
- I love--
- I like this.
They're totally
into the leaves,
and the balance
is so important.
The only thing that says
femininity is the dress.
This shape is
absolutely confounding to me.
I'm watching the judges,
and I don't think
they're saying good things.
I have a feeling I might be
going home this week.
Who made
your favorite beauty tonight?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
Very confused by this.
A cheap vacuum-form
topographical map.
Yeah.
I see Glenn
shake his hand frantically.
I know that's not a good sign.
The choice of this barky shape
is just a mystery.
Yeah.
- What is this?
- It's all bronzy.
I just don't know what to say.
It's a curiosity.
I see the judges
walk up to the makeup
and just keep on going.
I feel like
I really screwed up.
This is a really cool shape.
And her head thing
is groovy too.
This is
really intelligent design.
She even airbrushed
into the hair.
That's cool.
Can you give us a profile?
I don't even want to look
in their direction.
I don't want to even try
and guess what they're thinking.
This is all constructed,
which is pretty difficult.
Yeah.
Okay, the judges
have scored your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Alana...
Miranda...
Laney...
Tate...
Frank...
Congratulations.
You are all safe and can head
back to the makeup room.
The rest of you are the best
and the worst this week.
The judges would like to speak
with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Roy, please step forward.
Roy, tell us about your design
this week
and also how you incorporated
your mother.
My mother's one of those people
that can take any kind of plant
and make it grow.
She is also, like, the root
and foundation of our family,
so I used the roots
to represent my mother.
This is a beautiful treatment
of the goddess concept.
Thank you.
I think that you made
a lot of really smart decisions
within the design.
I love the choice of colors.
I think
she's absolutely stunning.
I love the way the pink
is peeking through on her face,
which ties
all of these other pinks,
this beautiful pale lavender
you have on the chiffon--
Beautiful makeup job this week.
It is one of my favorites
as well.
It's elegant and balanced.
Thank you very much.
Please step back.
Eddie, you're next.
Tell me about the concept
of your Mother Earth.
I wanted the overall look
to resemble a warrior goddess.
It's a metaphor about my mom
being the most important thing
in the world to me.
This was a really great time
for you guys
to show us what you could do
with beauty makeup.
Unfortunately,
you did not show me that.
You left her
completely natural,
so it falls a little short
for me tonight.
So much stuff, and you
just didn't get it all done.
The sculpture's very rough,
and these are
not difficult textures.
I think you were trying
to do too much.
Eddie, please step back.
Lyma.
So tell us about your concept
and also what aspects
of your mother you used.
When I think about my mom,
I think about permanence.
And when it comes to family,
she's a tree of life.
My first impression
in silhouette
was very, very good.
It was bold,
with that huge hair
and the tree bark
around her hips.
I do love the overall nature
of this piece very much.
- Thank you.
- This is cool.
Unlike anyone else,
you've managed to create
this heavenly approach
to the hair,
and the vines reach
so far to the sky.
And this use of a rabbit
as a symbol of fertility
is genius.
Thank you so much.
Lyma, please step back.
RJ.
RJ, tell us about your design
and how you incorporated
your mother.
As you know, the last time
I was on this show,
I did a Mother Earth character.
I did not want to do
a regurgitation
of those themes,
so instead of going a goddess,
I thought that it would be cute
to incorporate
a 1960s spritely character.
To essentially dismiss
core elements of the challenge
because you've done
something similar in the past,
it is only with contempt
that I regard
that particular decision.
It ends up being
an almost unnerving display
of design deficiency.
I thought, "My God, 1965.
I'm not sure
where we are with this."
I just wanted to do
something different
than what everybody else
was doing.
Okay, have you ever done
a beauty makeup?
Yeah.
Could you have done
a beauty makeup
on this gorgeous woman?
Yeah.
This is a total failure
this week, honey.
RJ, please step back.
Laura, you're up.
Tell us about your concept
for your goddess.
Well, we went
to the rose garden.
I found a particular rose
that I decided to incorporate,
as far as the color
was concerned.
My mother loves music,
so I put the trumpet flowers
to represent that.
She's also into buddhism,
so I thought, "caterpillar,"
and I merged the flower
with the caterpillar idea,
which explains the chest piece.
Well, I gotta tell you,
this is
astonishingly gorgeous makeup.
The paint job is probably
one of the most amazing
- we've had on this show.
- Thank you.
She's freaking gorgeous.
This is such a sublime palette.
I want to use it
because it is so beautiful,
and I can't get over it.
Thank you.
Laura, please step back.
Scott, please step up.
So tell us about your concept.
Well, I saw a lot of wood,
and the first thing
that jumped into my mind
was my mother,
who grew up on a farm,
and harvest.
I can't get
beyond the chest plate,
'cause it feels as if skin
has been flayed back,
revealing something underneath.
It borders on
horror makeup or design,
versus beauty.
Okay.
It's not very feminine,
some of the shapes
that you've created.
If you're asked
to do a goddess,
then you have to really think
about beautiful details,
and I think there's
just too much orange in it.
Scott, thank you very much.
Please step back.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you'd please head
back to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
Thank you.
All right, why don't we talk
about the looks
you liked the most?
- Let's start with Roy.
- So well done.
It's not a likely palette.
Who's gonna choose
a gray tree to do?
Yeah.
But it was so clever to use
that really pale color
'cause it's so feminine.
He used his model's eyes,
and they were the perfect color
with the makeup.
All right,
let's move on to Lyma.
She made
some really interesting choices.
I mean, to put
that white hair in there
and the tree branches
and the fertility bunny.
That idea of creating
a window into her belly
and the womb of Earth--
I'd like to see that idea
expanded upon, personally.
All right,
let's move on to Laura.
Stunning.
I so want an image of that.
The paint job
is absolutely unbelievable.
Sick, yeah.
If this was a group challenge,
I would have been thrilled
with the level of detail,
- and she did it by herself.
- Yeah.
All right,
let's talk about the looks
you liked the least.
Why don't we start with Eddie?
Really, really unhappy
with this makeup.
Yeah, for me,
it wasn't a makeup at all.
It was just like
a big rubber suit
and completely lacking
feminine qualities.
All right, let's move on to RJ.
I don't know what the heck
he was thinking of tonight.
Just because you've done
something once
doesn't mean
that you can't find variation.
I would hope that
he would have done something
like this once
and then learned from it.
He didn't even attempt
to do a beauty makeup.
Everything was a bad decision.
All right,
let's move on to Scott.
I think Scott doesn't have
a lot of experience
doing beauty,
plus the bad decision
with the breastplate--
- I couldn't get past that.
Yeah, I think
this is just not his genre.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- Yeah, I think we have.
- Yeah.
All right,
let's bring them back out.
Glenn, tell us
about the top looks.
Roy, we loved the tonality
of your character's
color palette,
and she had
a magnificent overall balance.
Laura, we were very impressed
with your design decisions
and the way that you managed
to seamlessly blend colors.
Lyma,
you made some very,
very bold choices this week,
and that really paid off
in an eye-catching makeup.
All right, who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
All right, who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of tonight's challenge is...
Laura.
Thank you.
You made some cool
and interesting
sculptural decisions,
and they were complemented
by a beautiful
and intricate paint job.
This was a true accomplishment.
Thank you.
This feels really good,
and I'm happy
that I could show the world
how much I love my mom.
Laura, congratulations.
You, Lyma, and Roy
can head backstage.
- Thank you.
Unfortunately,
that means the rest of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Scott, despite
some good technical painting,
your makeup fell down
in its design
and color decisions.
RJ, we had issues
with your character
in terms of both execution
and concept.
It boiled down to poor choices.
Eddie, you had some really
interesting ideas this week,
but you took on too much,
and ultimately,
it just didn't come fruition.
So who's going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
RJ.
We didn't understand
your decision
to diverge so far
from this week's challenge,
and what little makeup
you did do
wasn't well applied.
RJ, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
And Scott, Eddie,
you are safe this week
and can head
back to the makeup room.
RJ, you know that we love you,
and I can't wait to see
more of your fantastic creations
in the future,
and I know that we will.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
RJ, it's been so great
having you here with us.
If you'd please
head back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
I gotta do this.
- Real pleasure to meet you, Neville.
- Thank you.
I am disappointed in myself,
and I know
that I'm capable of better.
I'm sorry I disappointed
my family and my friends
and my fans, especially.
Me.
- No!
This competition has become
mentally
and artistically harder,
but it's an honor
just to be asked to come back.
It's very touching.
Makeup is part of who I am,
so I'm gonna just work harder
to be successful.
I've been doing this
since I was 12 years old,
and I won't give this up.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net