I love this makeup.
It's-- it's a stunning makeup.
You did a great job.
It is so good.
This is camera-ready.
Tonight, the all-time
best makeups
ever featured on Face Off.
Throughout five amazing seasons,
60 talented artists have created
nearly 700 works of living art.
From cyborgs to
extraterrestrials...
and underwater creatures
to things
that go bump in the night,
our judges have seen it all--
Ve Neill, Glenn Hetrick,
and Neville Page.
I'm really blown away.
Now, they'll count down
their personal favorites,
and you don't want
to miss number one.
There will be lots of awesome,
bitchin', and groovy.
And creations that
almost defy description.
This one is focused, myopic,
truly deranged.
What? Oh, man.
We'll hear from our judges
like never before...
Is that you laughing?
- It is.
- Wow!
And see exclusive new content
fromFace Off.
Find out which of
your favorite makeups made
the judge's list right now
on the Face Off Top 20
Countdown, Judges' Favorites.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
We kick off the countdown with
an eye-popping makeup
from Face Off's season five
champion, Laura.
Number 20 on our list shows off
her artist within.
The challenge was
to bring Classic art to life,
and Laura had chosen Cubism.
I loved it,
Laura's Cubism piece.
She really dialed it in
perfectly.
The colors were amazing.
The fact that she fabricated
on top of the suit,
and the construction on the back
of the head,
it was just so well done.
Laura's Cubism makeup is
a perfect synthesis of sculpture
and fabrication.
I feel like Cubism was created
because people wanted
to transcend 2-D art.
Cubism is three-dimensional
squares.
You can't think of this as
a makeup.
You have to think of this as
a work of art.
One of the things that you see
Laura demonstrating here is
her uncanny ability
to do hard color transition.
- Amazing paint job.
- It really is.
There's so many colors on the
thing, and at no point do they
slam against one another
in an obtuse way.
They just flow.
It was so asymmetrical
and so well developed.
Just the whole Cubism idea
was just so well put together.
The face that she designed
and sculpted
really looked like
it was trapped
within a moment of Cubism.
This is an immaculate makeup.
Stunning job.
Everything they said,
times ten.
You perfectly met
this challenge
and integrated your movement.
It truly is living art.
My Ve rating, two bitchin's.
From avant-garde art
to strange new worlds,
next is one of the best silicone
creations ever seen on Face Off.
Check out this elegant
extraterrestrial
that earned the number 19 spot.
All right, guys.
This is your chance
to do something literally out
of this world.
You will work in teams
of two and create
an alien species that
might actually exist on what
appears to be the first planet,
besides Earth,
capable of sustaining life.
Conor and Jo's alien
automatically feels like
it belongs to a world.
It, to me, was very reminiscent
of some of
the Star Trek, Next Generation
makeups that Mr. Westmore did.
This was our third episode
in our first season.
The thing that made it
so unique was the fact
that they used silicone,
which very few
makeup artists in
a starting-out period
of their career would attempt.
I would have guessed that they
bit off more than they can chew
taking this approach.
It doesn't seem like they should
have been able to do it
as quickly as they did,
but they did.
They really did far beyond
what we ever had expected.
This was an incredible makeup.
You did a beautiful job.
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- It's got a great profile.
It's got a great level of detail
in terms of texturing,
and then one of
the most important things that
so many people forget to do
is graphic design
that nature does with stripes,
patterns, dots, what have you,
and this makeup encapsulates
all of that.
And this was only the third
episode for this makeup?
Damn.
Next, a makeup that added
royal flare
to the world of Resident Evil.
Number 18 on our countdown comes
from a competitor
who was a fan-favorite in season
three and again in season five.
Roy's red queen zombie is
a multi-layered beauty.
This was important for us
to see Roy do because
of his ability to fabricate,
be stellar, that--
We needed to see
a makeup from him.
He finally delivered.
This is the queen, and she's
been infected with a virus
and so she's starting to mutate.
It was a really great concept
that her flesh turned into
this crown.
And Roy, the fabrication king,
where did this come from,
from him?
I was totally blown away.
The character really feels
like it stepped out of
a Resident Evil or Silent Hill,
cutting-edge video game.
Paul WS Anderson was
so impressed with this makeup.
If I was making a movie,
I'd be delighted to see
a design like this,
but also I'd be expecting
a team of, like,
six or seven people
to execute it.
I think Paul was accurate,
saying that
it would take six people,
because Roy, everything he does
is the power of some multiple,
so unique in his ability
to pull off
the "un-pull-off-able."
Roy, we loved
your hyper-stylized queen,
and we thought that
you accomplished
an absolutely amazing amount of
work in the time that you had.
The winner is... Roy.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
This is the best moment
I've had on the show.
My Ve rating
for Roy's queen is--
I'd have to give it, like,
at least three bitchin's.
Since our premier,
Face Offartists
have created 280 incredible
foundation challenge makeups.
One memorable creation
from season three
earned an artist her ticket back
into the competition.
That spectacular look is
the judges' pick
for the very best foundation
challenge makeup.
The best foundation challenge
goes to Nicole
for her Day Of The Dead makeup.
- They're back! They're back!
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
The winner of today's
foundation challenge will
rejoin the cast and earn
another chance at winning
our grand prize.
It's the first glimmer of hope
that we see out of her.
She goes into that challenge and
really decides that she's going
to do better than
she was previously.
I'm thinking mariachi guy.
The first thing I'm gonna do is
I'm gonna draw out
the shapes that I want,
and then go into the color.
This is obviously
the best foundation challenge.
It was colorful.
They were at Olvera Street.
- It was really, really fun.
- It was precise.
It was beautiful.
It encapsulated all the things
that we recognize
as the Day Of The Dead makeup.
- This is really cool.
- Thank you.
So, who is the winner
of today's foundation challenge?
Nicole.
Oh, my God!
I'm back!
You first see Nicole working
at what her true level is
in that foundation challenge.
We just saw the best
foundation challenge makeup,
courtesy of our season three
champion, Nicole.
Now, let's check out one of
her signature makeups
that became an instant
audience favorite.
It's number 17 on our top 20.
Welcome to the junk yard.
This week's challenge is
to create
an original cyborg character.
- Oh, all right.
- Oh, my gosh!
Yay!
That's cool, yeah.
Nicole's cyborg is
a truly unique piece of art,
but at the same time, it really
had a lot of composite elements
from beloved science fiction
sources.
Also, Nicole managed
to integrate the piece
from the junkyard seamlessly.
It didn't feel obtuse
or glued on.
She used it to inspire her,
so when the whole thing was done
it didn't really feel
like that was an element that
was forced upon her,
or that it was requisite
to use it.
It felt very natural within
the build.
I want her to be basically
this, like, cyborg princess
from another planet.
Elegant and tough.
I have a mechanism on her eye
which has a-- all different types
of plugs, but, like, she can
hook herself up and, like,
through her eye, like, have
different types of,
like, way of seeing.
I thought that was one of
the coolest things
I'd seen on the show.
Gale Anne Hurd and I
both loved it.
It was elegant,
and it read cyborg to me.
It was real delicate
and real female-looking.
It didn't shout at you.
Everything looked really
beautiful.
I wanted to write
a story around it.
I mean, that's how inspiring
I think it was.
- Awesome.
- Wow.
The junkyard cyborg for Nicole
was a turning point,
and she proved it on
this particular makeup,
and those who saw this makeup
fell in love with it.
It's a fan-favorite, obviously.
Up next, it was a makeup
from season two that looked like
it was headed for disaster, but
wound up winning the challenge.
It earns the number 16 spot
on our judges' countdown.
So, this week, your
spotlight challenge was to use
one of Patrick's
concept sketches
as the basis for
an original alien.
Ian's bat alien was certainly
one of the best things
he did on the show.
Bringing Patrick's drawings
to life is really difficult.
I'm nervous as heck.
It's gonna be a hell of
a challenge to do this.
Well, I know that Ian
was having some hesitation
about this makeup,
but he was smart enough
to turn around
his things that went wrong
and really make it
a positive attribute
to the character.
This piece did not come out
at all.
Immediately I can see both ears
are missing.
They didn't fill.
It's got a huge tear in
the shoulder to the neck.
It's fucked up.
I'm doin' everything I can
to hold this thing together.
I take the ears that are torn
off and I glue one back on,
and the other one
is just not salvageable,
so it's got to be
a wound or something.
So many points of that makeup
I was gonna give up.
I think this is
a stellar makeup.
Awesome, bitchin', and groovy.
The hands were as beautiful as
the face.
The character felt lived-in.
It felt like it had a story.
I wasn't a judge
on this particular season,
but I was a fan.
I sat back
impressed with the amount
of work that he did on it.
Ian's bat alien chick
was so cool.
Got to give him a ten
on the creepy scale for sure.
As the countdown continues,
let us know if you agree with
our judges' choices
on Twitter using #FaceOff.
Coming up, we'll find out
which Star Wars makeup landed
a spot in our top 20,
and we'll see what
Tim Burton-inspired look
still makes Ve laugh today.
These and many more incredible
Face Off makeups
as we count down to
number one on
Face Off's Top 20 Countdown,
Judges' Favorites.
Welcome back.
We're counting down
our judges' top 20 favorite
Face Off makeups.
For our expert panel to pick
the very best creations,
they chose from over
120 zombies and ghosts,
31 demons, 28 hybrid creatures,
and 43 aliens.
Number 15 on our countdown is an
out-of-this world alien makeup
inspired by our season three's
epic premier challenge.
Your first spotlight challenge
is based on the most influential
film franchise in history,
Star Wars.
- Oh, yeah!
- Oh, my God.
All right.
You're going to need
to create an alien
that would fit in
a modern version
of that classic cantina scene.
Wow.
Roy and Rod'sStar Warsalien
was probably the biggest
fabrication we had seen.
I start right in
on sculpting the face
and the little fat body that's
gonna be in the exoskeleton.
You've got Roy, who is, like,
the king of fabrication,
who can build that whole critter
around that little baby thing,
and then Rod with that kind
of sculpting sense that he had.
It was like
a perfect combination.
Those two worked
so well together.
Roy is describing
his exoskeleton.
I'm describing my little guy,
and they fit perfectly together.
This was really fun.
These two guys decided to be
a little bit lighthearted
about the whole thing,
and that's wise.
When you look back at those
films and you look at some
of the characters,
they're not all super serious.
Just the idea, the approach
of putting a small man
inside of a big robot body
is genius.
There were so many
moving parts, and the fact
that they pulled this off in
the time that they did
and still did a good makeup,
which was the face, of course,
it was really impressive.
Winning the spotlight
challenge feels great
to have my work acknowledged
in that way.
Your character will be featured
on the official Star Wars
website in its original design,
and re-created in the style of
The Clone Wars.
To have won and now have
their designs that were
originally a Face Off creation
on the Star Wars site?
That's pretty special.
Our next makeup unleashed some
ancient magic in season three
of Face Off, and now this
inspired Chinese dragon
brings good fortune to our
judges' countdown at number 14.
Tommy and Derek's
monkey-ox creation
just hit the nail on the head.
Your spotlight challenge
is to create
a completely original take
on the traditional Chinese
new year dragon.
Awesome.
For our concept,
it's the face of a dragon with
a bull ring out of
a baboon nose.
Derek starts painting
the face piece,
and I'm gonna focus
on painting the cowl.
It's a huge risk to have
two different paint jobs.
You're just really counting on
each other to pull it together.
When it came out onto
the stage,
the whole stage just lit up.
That gold train,
great color choices.
I love that whisker detail.
- Yeah.
- Especially in profile.
It's just badass.
When these guys did
the dragon dance,
they were doing summersaults
and jumping over one another
and landing on each other.
This makeup held up
extraordinarily well.
Awesome!
I'm pretty thrilled
with this thing.
I also feel that it has
a Japanese aesthetic.
I'm a tattoo artist and a lot
of the stuff I draw
- is Japanese style.
- That's awesome!
That seems to me like
it's transcending what it is
that we asked you to do.
Derek, being a tattoo artist,
he's obviously studied dragons
quite a bit.
He knew what triggers to pull.
It was spectacular.
I can't even
put a bitchin' to it
'cause it was just
too beautiful.
For this makeup?
Terrifying, titillating
tenacity.
From the mystical
to the whimsical,
coming in at number 13,
it's one of Face Off's most
iconic and humorous makeups.
Your spotlight challenge
this week is to create
a whimsical character inspired
by an everyday profession
worthy of being featured in
a Tim Burton film.
- RJ.
- Bellhop.
RJ's bellhop is
a perfect example
of success through forethought.
I'm thinking the bellhop has
become part of the luggage,
so he has drawers in his chest
like a trunk would have,
and he can open his drawers
and pull out clothing.
RJ, your makeup was
a very complete vision
and had some really great
stylistic elements.
This guy gets the challenge.
He looks at it and he goes,
"Look, I know Burton,
and I know how to do it.
I can do it with simple
form language.
I can do it with simple colors,
so I'm gonna do that,
and it's gonna feel like
a Burton character
when you look at the face,
but I'm not going to spend all
of my time on it.
I'm gonna spend
a lot of time fabricating
this really intricate
and extraordinary costume
that's as much a part of
the character as the makeup."
It was so cute, so well done,
so Burton-esque.
When we went up for
closer inspection, oh, my God.
He just started pulling all
these things out of this drawer.
At one point he took out a bra
and put it over my head.
I thought I was gonna die.
It was so bloody funny.
Thank you.
He didn't need to strap
that bra over her head.
RJ's bellhop is the embodiment
of Tim Burton aesthetic,
but where this really
came together was
in his overall
character development.
The little details and
in directing the performer...
...to also convey
a Burton-esque type
of performance.
RJ's bellhop is the embodiment
of Dark Whimsy.
The laughter continues
on our countdown
as we check out a comedic look
that won over our expert panel.
Here it is, the judges' pick for
the funniest makeup of all time.
Roy's laughing-dead character,
hands down,
wins for the funniest makeup.
It's a humorous concept,
but none of it really got to me
until it started dancing.
Glenn's even crackin' a smile.
Look it.
Is that you laughing?
- It is.
- Wow!
Roy's stacked ghost character,
so funny.
- Shows he has a sense of humor.
- Oh, my God!
Hee-hee-hee-hee-hee!
These are the Caine Brothers,
and they were Vaudevillian
performers.
They had a drinkin' problem,
and one night they stepped
into traffic and got hit by
a street car,
so this is how they have to live
in the afterlife.
This is a quintessential
Vaudevillian trick.
They would put two little kids
on top of each other
to create an adult, and you
pulled it off with one person.
When we first saw it,
all three of us,
it was a complete
laugh-out-loud moment.
Well, I chuckled.
I wouldn't say laughed out loud.
- I think I screamed.
- Glenn--
Glenn was crying like
a little girl with laughter.
Coming up, we'll see how
a season one
body paint challenge inspired
both a jaw-dropping work of art
and one of the most bewildering
makeups ever on Face Off.
All this and more dazzling
creations when
Face Off's Top 20 Countdown,
Judges' Favorites returns.
We're back, counting down our
judges' top 20 favorite makeups
in the history of Face Off.
Whether it's distant planets,
desert plains,
or eerie wastelands, Face Off's
77 spotlight challenges
have taken us to every kind
of destination.
The number 12 spot is a makeup
from a season two challenge
that took the competition to one
of the most difficult places
a makeup artist can go--
underwater.
Tara and Matt's fish creature
was really spectacular.
So beautiful.
I really love this.
Your spotlight challenge was
to find a sea creature
to use as inspiration
for your unique makeups.
You were also asked
to make them waterproof.
It's very nerve-wracking.
Is this gonna float?
Is the paint gonna
bleed into the water?
I don't know what happened.
There's so many chunks missing
from the edges.
I'm really stressing that
we're not gonna be able
to get these edges down.
How are we gonna hide these?
My brilliant plan is to cover
these massive edges with fabric.
- Oh, wow.
- Wow.
- That looks so cool.
Everybody gasped when she got
in the water.
Oh, it looks really cool.
The colors are beautiful.
Massive range of iridescence
head to toe.
The little filigree work that's
in the sculpture,
absolutely thrilled me.
Well done.
I'm glad we decided to go with
the fabric and hide the edges
because it looks
like colorful scales.
Well, this was a really clever
way to hide all their edges.
They're thinkin' on their feet
and they're turning challenges
around and making them
attributes.
Tara and Matt's fish creature,
aquatic, sensual beauty.
From under the sea to outer
space, it's the second makeup
in our top 20 from season
three's Star Wars challenge.
Let's head back
to Mos Eisley and meet
this unforgettable cantina alien
taking the number 11 spot.
This week, your spotlight
challenge was to create
an original alien that would fit
into a modern version
of the classic Star Wars
cantina scene.
Let's see what
you've come up with.
Talk about coming out swinging.
Laura and Sarah's Star Wars
cantina alien
is the first episode,
and it's perfectly executed.
She comes from the Dagobah
System, which is very moist,
but she lives on Tatooine.
That's why she's got
the breathing apparatus.
And her costume helps retain
that moisture.
It's a whole suit get-up.
This is the type of design
that we're working towards
in production all the time,
with room to design it.
They pulled it off in two days.
One of the coolest things
was when she walked out,
she had her hood up,
so we really couldn't see
what she looked like.
Would you mind removing
the cowl for us?
And when she pulled
that hood down,
it was so regal and so gorgeous.
Really excellent job, ladies.
Laura and Sarah nailed it
with this one.
I like the fact that you
mentioned the Dagobah System.
She has a specific origin,
so you've been doing
your homework, which is great.
We're such geeks.
You know,
it's so important that
when you're going to do
a head-to-toe makeup
that it feels like
it's connected,
and the hands related perfectly
to the head,
both in its texturing and,
of course, its coloration.
This makeup is one of
the cleanest that we have seen
in all five seasons on the show.
Up next, we travel to
the World Of Oz.
Coming in at number ten is
a winning collaboration
from a pair
of season two finalists,
one of whom became
that season's champion.
Rayce and Ian's Cowardly Lion,
it's a very contemporary way
to approach
a very traditional character.
If you're a Cowardly Lion,
you're probably starving.
You'll have a smaller frame.
You'll be a little nicked up.
The way me and Ian are breaking
down our concept and design
is we're both going to do
the chest piece,
and he's gonna do the hair while
I do the overall paint job.
It was weird, and cool,
and exceptionally done.
- I do love the paws.
- What makes it work, beyond
all the obvious makeup work that
they did, was the hair work.
Its silhouette was so strong,
and that was a huge head
of hair.
That's not easy to work with
unless you're Fabio.
I really love the idea
of it being gray.
So expect it to be
this beige-y flesh tone.
- Very well done.
- Thank you very much.
They didn't allow their paint
to get in the way of
the sculpture,
so the shading
and counter-shading
that they're using and the
highlighting to make those ribs
feel really nice and sunken in,
it was all gorgeous.
It was such a unique character
and such a bizarre take.
That makeup really
has staying power.
Rayce and Ian's Cowardly Lion,
courage personified.
It's time to peel off
the clothes
as we take a look at the best
body painting ever featured
on Face Off.
This season one makeup
not only won the challenge,
but it joins our top 20
at number nine.
Welcome to your next
spotlight challenge.
Everybody?
Drop 'em.
Oh, my God!
It is birthday suits as far as
the eye can see.
Okay.
Anthony killed this challenge.
I mean, the guy's never done
a body painting before
in his life, and then
he rolls this thing out?
We're just shocked.
To come on the show
and discover an attribute
that he may not have ever known
that he had as an artist?
I think that's so awesome.
The idea is that she's pickin'
her bark apart.
Anthony's burnt wood makeup,
holy smoke.
I don't even think he knew
he could do that.
- This was awesome.
- Thank you.
I loved the way that
he did that very clever thing
where it looked like she
was holding part of her stomach.
If you hadn't have had
those open spaces,
I think it would have been
very difficult
to pick out where
your person was.
It's like she ripped a piece of
her body off and is screaming.
I just really love it.
To see that huge piece of art
up there was just--
oh, it was breathtaking.
That was one of the most
happiest moments of my life.
I'm ready to cry.
I-- It was-- Honestly?
That right there was better
than winning any Academy Award.
The detail and the precision
in mimicking his paint
with the environment
was uncanny.
Anthony's burnt wood
was both invisible
and self-demonstrative.
For aFace Offcompetitor,
the final presentation can make
or break your chances.
Our season one body paint
challenge not only gave us
one of the judges' favorites,
it also offered one of
the most amusing moments
in Face Off history.
This is the judges' pick for
the longest makeup description
in the history of Face Off.
The most complicated
and convoluted description of
a makeup
goes to Sergio.
I looked at all
the backgrounds and I saw this,
uh, big tornado comin' up from
a very desolate area...
It kind of speaks about real
life because we have
a lot of events that happen
that we--
We're not aware of here...
When you're overrun and you have
all this stuff, you know,
I mean, it's something that he's
not gonna be able to escape,
you know-- but there's droughts
and stuff like that
in other places of the world,
and so I got an image
real quick of...
But he still has that,
like, look of hope,
and I wanted my image
to really be able
to tell people a story
and have them ask questions...
Almost like a fetal position,
because...
I gotta laugh.
Sergio gave us the longest
description of a makeup job
in the history of Face Off.
And that's kind of what
I was going for.
Uh-huh.
Boy, that's a long story for
a very short makeup.
And it was an orange body
painting and white stripes.
Hello?
Too long.
I thought about maybe
darkening his skin even more.
Sergio's description of
his naked ambition makeup,
uh, I don't know.
Fell asleep, don't recall.
Face off'sseason two
Tim Burton challenge
inspired three looks among
our judges' countdown,
and two are still to come.
Which ones are they
and where did they rank?
It's coming up on
Face Off Top 20 Countdown,
Judges' Favorites.
Welcome back.
We're counting down
our judges' top 20
Face Off makeups of all time.
Let us know if you agree with
our judges' choices
on Twitter using #FaceOff.
Coming in at number eight
is this tasty treat
from the season two
Tim Burton challenge.
Its clever design and evocative
image had all the judges raving.
Matt's ice cream man from
the Tim Burton challenge,
oh, so creepy.
It was kind of like you take
Burton's dark side, and you add
nothing but dark chocolate
and make it darker and darker,
'cause he went so south on this.
I love the ice cream man.
He's so colorful,
so delicious looking,
and he's just a feast
for the eyes.
It has so much going on,
there's so much story,
that you're almost afraid
to ask.
He's an ice cream inventor.
His lab exploded,
fusing his anatomy and DNA
with his own creation, so now
he's this chocolaty,
ice cream-sprinkled,
waffle cone-headed clown.
Matt's attention to detail
was pretty inspiring.
Sprinkles around its mouth,
a little cherry on its nose.
Phew.
Spooky.
Oh, no, thanks.
I ate.
There's something so wrong
about this twisted vision
of the perennial classic
that it's right.
This is more of what I've been
looking for out of you.
The balance of what you did
integrating the actual
cones into the makeup
is very wise.
If Tim Burton was gonna make
a horror movie,
this guy would be in it.
This thing still
has life today.
People are always
talking about it online.
This thing is really
a psychotic--
I don't want to have
ice cream again.
Now we've got the stunning
makeup that earned its creator
the title of Face Off champion.
From season one,
this haunting creation
comes in at number seven.
Your final challenge is
to reinvent
two characters from
a classic fairy tale.
You will also
be choosing a theme
to go along with
your fairy tale.
I knew a little bit about
the Frog Prince fairy tale,
and I knew that there was
a lot of potential there.
Conor's Frog Prince,
when you look at it,
it really is feature-film
quality.
The design captures a moment
of metamorphosis so brilliantly.
It is the quintessence of
the pain of transformation.
And, on top of everything else,
he decides to go ahead
and integrate
a very rudimentary mechanical
element to give it some life.
Blow into that tube.
Oh, my God.
That bladder that
he stuck in there?
It's genius in its simplicity,
and it worked perfectly.
I took the foam run
and I cut out all this
and built latex and
a tube right into the mold.
Hid the tube up underneath
the lip.
Well done.
I didn't come here just for
the hell of it.
I came here to win.
Conor is a really good
technician.
He has a great design sense.
His applications are flawless.
Look at the top of the head.
That's a great paint job too.
Conor's Frog Prince,
and the fact that this is
a season one winner,
it's incredible.
It's why he was the winner.
The eye of the frog is one of
the best eyes that I've seen.
Conor, in this challenge,
achieved a "ribbeting"
amphibious delight.
From cursed frogs
to enchanted swans,
it's the crowning achievement
from season five champion,
Laura, and it holds the number
six spot on our all-time top 20.
Laura's season five
finale makeup
was the manifestation
of beauty and power.
So incredible.
Laura's Renaissance swan
and sorcerer is breathtaking.
Unbelievably gorgeous.
Renaissance, Baroque,
whatever you want to call it.
Pearls, swirls.
Oh, my God.
She had everything in it.
I absolutely love how her bodice
looks like it's morphing
into something, and then
the shoulder pieces, like,
the start of wings.
You've got some great
texturing happening.
There's a real beautiful,
classic silhouette that she has.
To have a figure dancing
with that aesthetic
on their body was so beautiful.
When you're designing,
you cannot do it alone,
so Laura divides up the labor
but guides it,
so that when it's done
it all looks like it was done
by one person.
Clearly she's a good artist.
She has an incredible
design sense.
She's a really seasoned
technician.
She is a focused beam
of talent.
It's clear that
she's gonna do the same
professionally and
in her career.
She's phenomenal.
This is an awe-inspiring
conglomerate
of multiple different techniques
and multiple different
influences
that are blended
seamlessly together
to create truly amazing
characters.
Next up, Las Vegas was
the backdrop
for one Face Off competitor's
crowning achievement.
The number five spot on
our judges' countdown belongs
to these amazing makeups created
for the mind-blowing production,
Le Reve.
Anthony's sinister performers
from theLe Reveshow
were probably
the most definitive characters.
I don't know how
they could have been beaten.
The thing with this challenge
is to keep it very minimal
and not have anything
restrictive on their bodies.
I decided to keep it to a cowl,
face, and a minor chest piece.
TheLe Revechallenge was,
by far,
the most physically difficult
challenge to work a makeup on.
These guys were falling
from 50, 60 feet above water,
so creating anything
that didn't fall off
was extremely challenging
to begin with,
but to be able to design
something that looks beautiful
as a makeup, performs
under extreme circumstances,
and happens to just fit in
to a rich environment
that he could not have access
to prior to the challenge?
Killer work.
So, we're basically doing
a prosthetic face piece,
and we're gonna be working
into the cowl.
And then for
our female character,
it's gonna be the same species
but a lot softer.
The characters look like
they belong together.
I love the coloring
on both of them.
The paint job was
- absolutely gorgeous.
- Thank you.
Anthony'sLe Revecharacters
were perfection.
This is, by far,
- my absolute favorite profile.
- Of course it is, because
it's so naturally looking.
I can believe this thing
- exists somewhere.
- Yes.
The execution of the makeup from
a design standpoint,
application, paint, costume,
all of it, is the reason he won
that particular challenge, and
the entire season of Face Off.
Have your favorite competitors
made the list?
We're working our way
to number one.
It's coming up,
when Face Off Top 20 Countdown,
Judges' Favorites returns.
Welcome back to the Top 20
Countdown, Judges' Favorites,
where we reveal the best
special effects makeup
in the history of Face Off.
Our number four makeup comes
from a season one challenge
where the artists were shocked
to learn their zombie creations
would be put to the test in
an expected dance routine,
and one of those zombies
has been haunting
our judges ever since.
Conor's zombie.
Crap, was that bitchin'.
Particularly since
so many zombies have been done,
we know what they're supposed
to look like.
This one is zombie perfection.
Wow.
First of all,
it's a really cool opportunity
to do something that every
makeup artist wants to do,
create this really
awesome zombie
in a dance video situation.
It was the quintessential
zombie.
She was skinny.
She was dry.
She was everything
a zombie should be.
The proportions
are beautifully handled.
You want to create
a sucked-in skeletal frame,
but to build that framework over
and then put skin over that
that looks sunken in,
it can easily get away from you.
This does not.
He works those notes
to perfection.
I want to do, like,
kind of a classic
'80s style zombie who's
now just a dried out husk.
Conor's another one of
our artists who has
a great design sense.
A really great applicator.
This is his third in our top 20.
You name it, he can do it.
You got every detail
absolutely perfect,
right down to her arms,
her fingernails.
You even aged her hair
to the right color.
- It's a stunning makeup.
- Thank you.
It never becomes silly.
It never parodies itself.
It somehow manages to pull off
a dancing zombie
and still be super cool.
Conor's zombie
is roadkill beauty.
Everybody loves a zombie.
From zombie dancers
to cursed musicians.
Earning the number three spot
on our top 20,
here is the winning look
from Face Off's
Tim Burton challenge.
This week, your spotlight
challenge was to take
an ordinary profession
and create a character
worthy of being featured
in a Tim Burton film.
With Rayce's cellist,
you see him really
working at his highest capacity.
He writes these stories inside
of his head while
he's sculpting.
It's a unique thing.
I wanted to see if I could
bring in another character,
almost like the cello
was morphed into
a human and it's her love.
The idea that her playing it
was keeping alive
the spirit within the cello,
and the melancholy on her face,
which is so appropriate
for that type of instrument.
This is an unparalleled design
executed without fear.
Actually, I went through
a few different designs.
It's just a face prosthetic.
Sometimes less is more.
I mean, you know,
you don't necessarily
have to cover their,
you know, face with prosthetics
to get a Tim Burton character.
That design was really unique,
and I imagine it could be in
a Burton film.
Oh, beautifully executed.
Your airbrush work
is really great.
You had airbrushed her clothing
as well, which was
a good idea, because it
homogenized the whole look.
It's just beautiful.
Thank you so much.
Rayce's cellist
really did capture
other elements of
the Tim Burton style.
The stripes, the curved,
concentric lines,
but it's also the fact that
he included the relationship.
That was a really smart move,
which is why he won.
Our top 20 countdown goes
to the underworld
as we check out a chilling
creation from season four.
Here's the second best makeup
in the history of Face Off.
Anthony and Alam's ice demon,
so pretty.
Anthony and Alam.
Ice demon.
What?
How are they managing something
so perfect for the challenge?
Create a demon character
from somewhere around the world
and bring it to life.
Then we threw you a twist.
Hell had frozen over.
So, we got "Deumus,"
a Hindu goddess.
We both really want
to make this demon
beautiful to take it away from
a grotesque nature.
- It's very beautiful.
- Yeah.
It's pretty.
- I like the turquoise.
- Yeah.
I mean, it was so great
to see them
doing a beauty makeup on top of
a creature makeup,
and just pulling it all together
from head to toe.
The feet on this thing
were beautiful.
These are some of
the best details
that we've seen in any makeup.
What's remarkable
about this makeup
is the flow of the line from
horn down through
the zygomatic arch.
It's a perfect example of how
to move your eye throughout
the sculpture.
Alam does like beauty
and Anthony
does like the creature-y side
of things,
so that hybrid of their comfort
zone, of their wheelhouse,
really lent itself
to a perfect vision.
There's a very strong
synthesis between
your demon's attributes
and the region that it was from.
We could immediately tell a lot
about it just looking at it.
Everything that
you guys did worked
so extremely well together.
Well done.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, guys.
Five awesomes.
This one totally blew me away.
We've seen 19 of the best
creations ever onFace Off.
When we come back, we reveal
the judges' top pick.
The number one makeup is next.
Over five seasons
of intense competition,
Face Off artists have created
almost 700 special effects
makeups.
So far, our judges have revealed
19 of their top 20 picks.
Now we are moments away from
the number one makeup
in the history of Face Off,
but first,
let's see the largest.
The largest makeup goes
to Eric F and Kris
for their two-headed giant.
What the fuck is that?
I don't know, but it was funny.
It was so big, and then
they had this little guy,
who was actually
the real life-sized guy.
This poor little guy
held there,
like a little baby
like an adult baby.
It was weird.
They probably rang up the
biggest bill in material costs
on the history of the show.
This thing is like trying
to plaster a hot tub.
I mean, it is massive.
Kris and I want to execute
the biggest character
as possible.
It's gonna be ten-foot tall!
It's filling up half the stage,
and the looks on
the judges' faces is amazing.
This thing is so huge,
so impressive, but funny.
- They switched it back.
- This is so great.
Look, he's stabbin' his hand.
You guys should definitely
be impressed with yourselves.
I think it's the biggest makeup
we've ever seen on the show.
Yes.
That was one of our goals.
So...
The top creation of all time
comes from a season five team,
and it's the most camera-ready
creature
to spring out of your garden.
Here it is,
the number one makeup
in the history of Face Off.
Miranda and Tate's
Peter Pumpkin Eater.
Wow.
This is my favorite makeup
I have ever seen
on the show, period.
There are a ton of awesome
sculptural decisions
in the head.
It is so good that Ve, myself,
and Glenn
all agreed that this
is camera-ready.
Every little detail on this
reads whimsy and fantastical,
and I think you did a great job.
Terrific costume,
impeccable fabrication.
Miranda did a spectacular job
on the sculpting.
I'm sure Tate helped her with
all that fabrication and cowl.
What do you think about this
coming out of her dress
from behind?
Tate and I are just really
bouncing back and forth ideas
past each other with everything.
Like that, but pull
the whole thing up higher.
Oh, okay.
Should we extend, like,
a long line in that?
So, I start adding little bits
of clay right here,
and that is already helping,
making her look more like
she's smiling
rather than gaping.
We tell them not
to bake in expressions, right?
They did exactly that,
but it's such a cool expression
that it doesn't matter.
The paint job, so authentic.
It just felt like this fetid,
rotted pumpkin
that's laying out in the field,
and the combination of that
with the wardrobe
and the vines coming
all the way down on the hands,
it's this huge story
that demands not only
to be in a film
but to be the star
of its own film.
The reason this is my top
is because there's
nuanced layers.
The use of pumpkins seeds,
the gloss, but they used it
in reserve,
which gave it
a realistic sensibility.
I think you knocked it out
of the park.
This is my greatest moment
onFace Off.
I've never felt so much pride.
It is what we wanted to make.
It was such a team effort,
and I feel so honored.
We absolutely loved
the sculpture, the paint,
and the overall harmony
of the piece.
Yeah, girl!
Oh, wow.
This is an obvious rating.
This probably has at least
100 bitchin's in it.
Miranda and Tate's
Peter Pumpkin Eater
is off the squash hook.
Looking back at these top 20
makeups, I just cannot wait
to see what happens next
on Face Off.
There you go.
The top 20 makeups
in the history of Face Off
according to our expert judges.
But the movie magic
doesn't stop there.
The jaw-dropping
creations continue
on our next blockbuster season
of Face Off.
We'll see you then.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net