Previously, on Face Off...
Tate's spooky skeleton
brought him to victory...
Yeah.
And Lyma was sent home.
Now, nine artists remain,
and tonight, they'll
greet a bombshell guest...
Elvira.
Get the fuck out.
And face a challenge
of artistic sophistication...
There's these beautiful
paintings.
I'm really excited.
And for some,
it spells disaster.
Mr. Westmore,
where are you?
Oh, shit.
- Medic!
- There is blood everywhere.
- So damn good.
- For me, it doesn't work.
I think the entire thing
was a mistake.
In the end,
one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Makeup
to one of their 85
international locations,
a 2013 Fiat 500,
and $100,000 dollars.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Only one will win Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Ay, yi-yi-yi.
At this point, we've been
through six challenges.
I'm 52 years old,
and, boy, right now,
my body feels every day
of those years.
Bottom three times in a row,
so I'm going to try and go big.
Go big or go home?
Yeah.
I'm walking into the lab,
and there's candelabras
everywhere,
and all of the models are here,
so I'm wondering what
this challenge is going to be.
From Batman to Sherlock Holmes,
makeup artists
are often asked to reinvent
an iconic character
for new audiences,
so in this challenge,
you'll reinvent
one of the most unforgettable
characters of all time.
She'll be appearing soon
on SyFy's new series, Fangasm,
but you know her
as the Hostess of Horror
and Mistress of the Dark,
Elvira.
Oh, my God.
Get the fuck out.
- I have chills.
- Oh, I love her.
Elvira is an icon
of sex, beauty,
and all the things I love most.
Thank you so much
for being here.
It's a thrill to be here.
It's one of my favorite shows.
Well, your look is so iconic.
What is it that makes it
so classic and memorable?
Well, there's, you know,
a couple of big things.
That would probably be
my eyes, which, you know,
have a lot of color going on,
and of course,
my vivacious personality.
All right,
so your foundation challenge
is to create your own
Mistress of the Dark
worthy of Elvira's legacy.
So awesome.
So, as the judge
of today's challenge,
what are you going to be
looking for from these guys?
I am going to be looking
for a hip, young, cool,
edgy take on my look.
All right, now each of you
will get some assistance
from a professional hair stylist
to complete your looks...
- Ooh, wow.
- Oh, wow.
I don't do hair,
so it's going to be really cool
to have somebody there
that we can tell what we want
and have them create it for us.
And we have two big prizes
at stake today.
The winner will
take home immunity,
and you will also get
an incredible Kryolan Makeup kit
full of supplies.
- Ooh, that's cool.
- Oh, wow.
I could definitely use that
prize, and I'm dying for it.
Kryolan has also
generously stocked the lab
with everything that you
could possibly need
to accomplish this challenge.
You'll have two hours
to complete your looks.
Good luck, guys,
because your time starts...
- now.
- Eek!
Maybe kind of bring this up
and twist it?
My hair stylist knows
more beauty makeup than I do,
so I'm taking advice from her.
I like what you're doing
with the hair right now, though.
Good, good, good.
For my modern Elvira,
I grabbed some awesome
Kryolan eyelashes.
I think they'll be
a fun addition.
I remember watching Elvira
with my dad when I was younger,
so my concept's the creature
from the Black Lagoon.
I got a lot of area to cover,
so to be able to do it
in two hours,
it's going to be really hard.
Elvira's known for her comedy,
so I'm thinking
bride of Frankenstein
meets sexy nurse.
So my concept
is to create Elvira's
long-lost cousin, Elmira.
Look there for me.
The idea's to do bat wings
into the makeup
and cut a wig that has
the bat wing scallops into it,
and fabricate a little
bat epaulet for the shoulder.
Ten minutes, guys!
Time is up!
Put your brushes down!
- Hi, Miranda.
- Hi.
So explain to us
what you did today.
I saw this dress,
and I thought it was stunning,
and I wanted to make the makeup
glamorous as well.
I love the shading.
I wish I could do it that way.
It sort of looks like Elvira
meets Metropolis.
Thank you so much.
This is Nurse Cutter.
She hosts the late-night
horror double feature
at the local insane asylum.
I love this, like, like,
Nurse Elvira,
creepy and scary.
The thing around the neck
is amazing.
I didn't want any
real healthy color in her face.
I love, love the outfit
and the skin color.
I'm not quite getting as much
of the whole gothic look.
You're going edgier
and more modern, so I get it.
I looked up your family tree
and found your
long-lost cousin, Elmira.
- Hey.
And Elmira really loves bats,
and so she has
this whole bat motif going on.
Yeah.
I really like...
You can see
the bat motif there.
I love the bottom lashes.
I should flip mine upside down.
I'm getting makeup tips here.
Anyway, awesome job.
Very cool take.
It's so cool to look
around the room and see
where everybody's creativity has
taken them on this challenge.
I love it.
So who created your favorites?
I think they all did
fantastic, but with Roy,
there was the spooky,
there was the sexy,
and there was the humor.
And, Tate, the nurse
was very scary,
also had an element of humor.
A great mix
that captured Elvira.
All right, then.
Who is the winner
of today's challenge?
The winner
of today's challenge is...
Roy.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe it.
Roy won because
that combination of sexy,
spooky, and funny.
I love it.
Roy, congratulations.
Thank you so much.
As the winner of today's
foundation challenge,
you not only have immunity,
but you also won a beautiful
Kryolan Makeup case
full of supplies.
Having this kit
is going to be really cool
if I can keep my wife
out of it.
She likes makeup
just as much as I do.
All right, you guys,
I will see you tomorrow
for your next
spotlight challenge.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you, Elvira.
- Ooh.
- Oh, I like this challenge.
It's really neat.
So we walk into this room
that looks like a gallery space,
and I see McKenzie and Neville,
and there's
these beautiful paintings,
and I'm really excited
'cause I'm
a huge art history buff.
Welcome to the world-famous
Pacific Design Center,
home to some of the biggest
names in contemporary art.
Professionals working
in film and television
are often called upon
to take a certain style
or period in history and use it
as a catalyst to create
something original.
So on these walls
are paintings that represent
iconic art movements.
Cubism, surrealism, pop art,
expressionism,
and constructivism.
Your spotlight challenge
is to select one of these
iconic art movements
and create a character
that could live within it.
That's rad.
I've daydreamed
about this challenge,
so I'm super-excited.
All right, so Neville
might be best known
as a creature designer
on some of Hollywood's
biggest films, but his art
has also been featured
in exhibits and galleries
all over the world.
So, Neville, what's most
important to consider
when working
with a certain style of art?
Well, you have to be faithful
and well-versed in it,
so you know how to bend
the rules and manipulate it
into your own,
and it needs to feel like
an attractive
piece of living art.
Okay, guys, take a look around.
When you find an art movement
that you like,
grab its card and start
working on your design.
Good luck, guys.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
I know what I want.
I'm moving around this gallery,
and the one that
I'm completely unfamiliar with
is constructivism.
I used to work construction,
so maybe this
is somehow correlated.
Immediately,
I have to get that pop art.
I want her to be a living piece
of social media.
I want to do a sculpt
and then vacu-form that,
so when she comes out,
she takes her face off,
and she'll have a completely
different paint job
underneath of it.
I picked cubism.
So far, I've got a man
in a top hat.
He's a period piece,
but the modern, brightly
colored, cubism version.
I went straight
for expressionism.
I've always been a fan
of Van Gogh.
Starry Night is one
of the most famous paintings,
so I'm taking inspiration
from that.
My concept
is "Stressful Night,"
and I want to merge
flesh tones into reds
as symbolism for stress.
I chose surrealism.
I want to take symbolic pieces
and do this fortress crumbling,
and then I have this bulb
underneath
that releases the actress.
All right, let's go.
We're going back to the lab,
and I think I've made
a bad choice
thinking that constructivism
has anything to do
with construction,
and I don't get it.
So we get to the lab.
We've got six hours today.
First thing we have to do
is pick our models.
I know a little bit
about surrealism,
and I'm thinking about
creating a tribute to my dad.
My dad was an alcoholic,
and he died
of consequences of that,
and I'm putting
some of my stresses
into my character here,
so it could be
a little bizarre.
Tate.
- What's up?
- Does that look cubism-ish?
I'm thinking that I'm going
to do this female musician
who's forlorn because
she lives through her music,
and once she stops, she dies.
- Looks good.
- Thank you.
Constructivism emphasizes
the use of materials,
so my concept is a statue
that's got an iron beam
pointing downwards,
which symbolizes
the fall of iron
and the rise of plastics.
I'm having such a hard time
with this.
Just like...
I chose something
I didn't know anything about.
Alana's getting lost
in second-guessing herself,
and there's just really
no time for that.
Back to the drawing board.
I've spent three hours
of this challenge
trying to understand
what the challenge is.
I'm running out of time.
I've got to get
this concept on the way,
or else I'm going to go home.
Mr. Westmore,
where are you?
Coming up...
I'm not going to tell you
how to do it, that's not--
No, I'm not asking you
to tell me how to do it.
I'm scared.
I don't want to go yet.
So damn good.
I don't see how you could be
so incredibly wrong.
Oh, my God.
Our challenge
is to create a character
that represents
a specific art movement.
My movement is constructivism,
but I'm a little confused.
I don't have
another minute to waste,
and I'm finally just like, "God,
send me Mr. Westmore, please,
'cause I am so lost."
Fuck.
This giant castle piece
is going to be really heavy,
so I'm going to hollow it out
to make it as light as possible.
That face is so cool.
Nice.
- Hey, everybody!
- Hey!
- How are you?
- Hi!
Here to do a walkthrough.
- Hey, Scott.
- Hello.
- So what did you pick?
- Surrealism.
So this is a volcano,
based off of my dad.
The volcano represents
his volcanic temper,
especially when he drank.
He's going to be
carrying a birdcage
with a giant ear in it,
because he had trouble hearing,
and he's also going
to have a crutch,
which is going to be
a cigarette.
I mean, you've got all
of the elements there.
I'm just concerned that you
don't get it too busy.
- Yeah.
- Maybe simplify a few things.
Expressionism is what I have.
That's where
the artists of the time
would use odd shapes to show
what they were feeling,
so I'm gonna take my model
and have the world
wrapped around her
to the point where
her head wants to explode.
Mm-hmm.
This needs to really be shaded
to be able to airbrush
these explosion type of marks
that are going to occur.
Thank you very much.
You're a godsend,
I swear to you.
Okay.
I stupidly picked
constructivism
because I thought it
was architecturally driven,
which is something
I have a heavy background in.
You know, what you're doing
here, the squared-off shapes
and things like that,
it's good.
Just take away
the human features.
Okay.
You don't want two eyes,
a nose, and a chin.
I think I'm going to eliminate
the facial features
almost completely,
and make this into
more of a bended metal
shape of a person.
I chose expressionism.
My base inspiration
is Van Gogh,
and I'm doing a gradation
of lush colors
on the front of the face
to reds.
The thing is,
with Starry Night,
that deep blue is such
a predominant color.
By going into reds,
it's not going to convey
your concept of Starry Night.
All right, guys, we're
heading out, but good luck.
- Thanks, guys.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
As usual, I'm one
of the first people
getting my sculptures done.
I'm feeling pretty good
about where I stand.
I have a lot of stuff to build,
but it all seems
to be coming together well.
Really, really nice.
I feel like cubism was created
because people wanted
to transcend 2-D art.
Cubism is three-dimensional
squares.
You can't think of this
as a makeup.
You have to think of this
as a work of art.
It's looking great, man.
All right guys, it's time!
Ha ha.
At the end of the day,
I really am feeling a lot
more passionate about my piece.
I think I have
some really good ideas,
and I have quite a bit of work
to do tomorrow,
but I got this.
This is day two
of our living art challenge.
We have 9 1/2 hours in the lab.
Look at that, Eddie.
I don't even have to clean out
the fucking mold.
That is perfect.
Today, I head straight
into the cowl.
I take vacu-form plastic
and I start melting it
over a head.
I then take foamcore.
Foamcore
is very stiff cardboard,
so I end up building
this gigantic... thing.
I'm very excited to see
how it'll look.
Bye, Tate.
See you in a couple weeks.
Screw you, Roy.
I get my castle finished.
It looks really good.
So I'm going to get it
blocked up for molding.
I make a gigantic mold.
I mean, we're easily
talking close to 300 pounds
of clay inside it.
It's a huge piece,
so I've got to hurry up.
Do you think I should
use that or the wig?
I'm not going to tell you
how to do it, that's not--
No, I'm not asking you
to tell me how to do it.
I'm just asking if you
think this hair looks odd.
I don't think
I want to keep this hair,
because I feel like
it really looks too much
like a robot,
and not this female musician.
They both will be fine.
I'm sure that they're both
going to be awesome.
Okay.
I'm a little bit behind,
and that's not a place
I want to be
when I have so much to do.
Today, I'm working
on the bodysuit,
creating all the bulges
where the world is squeezing in.
So what I want to do
is create a fat suit.
And then I start
wrapping the L200,
so I know where pieces
need to lay,
and then I actually take another
bodysuit and put over that.
So that way, then,
I have, like, this flesh suit
that I can paint
and match her flesh color.
My mold is ready to crack open,
so I go to tip it over.
Agh. Whew.
Oh, shit.
It completely smashes my hand.
Shit.
My finger looks like
a bloody hot dog bun.
I'm going to need
a few stitches.
There's blood
absolutely everywhere.
- Shit, Tate!
- Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Medic!
Oh, fuck.
My finger's not working.
It's completely numb and dead,
and I can't tough it out.
Oh, my God, are you okay?
This is a terrible point
for it to happen,
because I went huge.
I'm really, really worried.
I don't even know
if he's going to clear me
to come back
to the competition.
So the medic looks
at my finger and said,
"We've got to get this kid
to the doctor right now."
We need to take him to
Emergency Care right now.
And then he wraps me up,
and they send a van,
and they're like,
"You're out of here."
I don't know how long
I'm going to be there,
but this is not something
that I can just ignore.
I got some time to spare here,
so let's see what we can do.
Yeah, yeah, I think
it was right here.
I'm in a good spot
with my makeup,
and I don't want Tate
to have to suffer
because he had an accident.
If we can find
another pry point here.
Roy and I
just jump into action...
There we go.
Okay.
And we open the mold.
And then anyone
who can help comes over
to start cleaning out clay
as well.
It's very refreshing to know
that people do care.
When I go to open up
my cowl mold,
I realize it's so heavy.
Will you help me lean it over?
I don't want to pull a Tate.
I don't have
a lot of muscles at all.
Cool. Yay!
Every time I have a big mold,
I have to have one of the guys
help me, which sucks,
but I just don't
have the muscle power.
That would have probably
taken me 12 hours.
Yeah.
I'm going to make
a giant cigarette
that my character's going to use
as a crutch or a cane.
So I find this big tube of foam
that's about
the right thickness,
and now I'm going to paint it
to look like a cigarette.
I'm feeling pretty confident
that it meets
the definition of surreal.
Whoo-hoo!
- Hey!
- What's up?
Yay!
I saved my finger.
13 stitches, though.
Come here!
Come here, come here.
Let me show you
where you're at.
I'm worried.
I've only got 2 1/2 hours left.
- Here's your molds.
- Okay.
You've got three layers
of latex in them, drying.
My mold is cleaned out.
They've already got
the first layer of latex in.
Pour your foam in 'em,
and you're good to go.
Thank you so much, man.
- Not a problem.
- You're great.
I'm eternally grateful
for everyone's help...
Thank you for your help,
brother.
So I give everybody
all my love,
and then
it's right back to work.
- 2 hours, 18 minutes.
- Thank you, bud.
I finally get my cowl done,
so I start blocking out colors.
Tomorrow, I'm going to have
to paint this entire suit,
so I need to get
as much done today
so I have time tomorrow
to do everything else.
That's absolutely stunning,
Laura.
I'm having a love-hate
relationship right now with it.
It's the end of day two,
and I'm only able to get
my surrealist pieces poured.
When I get in tomorrow,
if there's anything
wrong with it,
I don't have time
to make new ones.
That's time!
I'm trying to keep
my composure,
but I'm fairly confident
tomorrow is going to be
a train wreck.
It's application day,
so today I have to pull
my castle out of the mold,
I have to pull the poppy seed
out of the mold.
I have to hollow them out,
I have to build
a backpack harness...
and then I have
to put it all on my model,
and I have to paint all of it
without the use of my left hand.
This is the most work
I've ever tried to squeeze
into four hours.
Wow.
My cowl is thrashed.
This cool architectural design
that I've done in the neck
is completely shredded out,
and it was one
of my favorite features.
I can fix this.
I can fix anything.
That's what I do.
I fix things.
Models!
You'll be covered in squares
and things like that.
That's amazing.
Head to toe, my model
is going to be in paint.
I will be painting everything,
because in a cubism painting,
there are brush strokes.
You can't airbrush
the entire thing.
So this is literally
a walking piece of art.
We'll see if I can get it done.
God, I need more paint.
The art movement
that I have is constructivism,
which is materials
and futurism.
There's this beam you'll hold
in one hand.
- Dude!
- It's a big tree,
and it's got a face in it
and the whole thing,
so that's kind of where
I'm kind of going with this.
My pieces look good.
I mix up the base color
of my volcano,
and I paint that on
very quickly.
And then I spend a little bit
of time painting in
the fluorescent colors
for the lava,
and everything's looking
like it's on the right track.
So this needs to sit
right about there.
- How does it feel?
- Good.
I have a lot to do
for my pop art character,
but my foam pieces are perfect,
and my model is looking
super-cute.
I find
these big circle stencils,
and they're going to be perfect
for me to do
at least four dots at a time.
I feel like I could
get the paint job done
rather quickly.
I kind of psyched myself out
of some things
that I should have done.
I'm pretty nervous because
I only have a face piece,
and I'm thinking I could
really be in trouble this time.
I still want
to fabricate this guitar,
and I've never fabricated
anything before,
so I know that's going
to take me some time.
13:42!
I refill all the pieces
that are missing from my foam,
but I don't have
anything painted.
I don't think I could
feel any worse.
I'm so stressed out right now.
All right, that's it!
Time's up!
Let's go!
I have never left myself
with this much work to do
going into last looks.
I'm terrified.
Coming up...
This is the end for me.
I'm scared.
I don't want to go yet.
You've got
some massive problems.
- Took my breath away.
- So damn good.
It's time for last looks.
I am so stressed out.
I have to paint this model's
whole body, her whole cowl.
I have never left myself
with this much work.
- You can use my airbrush.
- Thank you so much.
I don't like the way
the hair looks.
I don't have time
to style it at all.
I just have to throw it on.
I just don't like this makeup.
I'm hand-painting
everything
because this style
was a lot of brush strokes,
but it's difficult
in such a short amount of time.
Ten minutes, everyone!
How the fuck
am I going to paint
that huge thing in ten minutes?
_
That's it!
Time's up!
Brushes down!
I don't think
I could feel any worse.
This is it-- I'm about
to be eliminated again.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
Say hello
to our talented judges...
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
Good evening, guys.
Hey, Glenn.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
- Evening.
- Hey, girl.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
- Hello.
- Hey, Neville.
All right, guys, so this week,
your spotlight challenge was
to choose an iconic art movement
and create a character
that could live within it.
So let's take a look
at your living works of art
while the audience at home
tweets about their favorites,
using #FaceOff.
The paint job,
I'm really not feeling it.
These edges
are just God-awful.
This is the end.
I need to just be happy
to have been here this far.
I'm very happy
with the forms I've created,
but I'm unhappy
that my paint job is flat.
I'm really proud.
She looks like she jumped
out of a comic book
and landed on our stage.
I don't like this makeup.
It's totally out
of my comfort zone,
and I know I'm going to be
one of the bottom looks.
I like the asymmetry
of the sculpture
with the symmetry of the color.
The piece screams "Cubism."
I'm really proud of my design.
I think it looks
like a surrealist painting.
I feel confident about it.
I'm really happy
with this piece.
I think I could easily
be top looks, or even win it.
It looks exactly the way
I envisioned it.
The colors really pop,
the big i-beam
with the forced perspective
achieved what I wanted it to,
so I think it all
came together great.
There's so much going on
with my character,
I hope they don't feel
that I ignored the challenge.
Overall, technically,
I think I pulled off
some pretty cool stuff.
Judges, why don't you
take a closer look
at tonight's living art?
I get that her left side
is more of the human,
and her right side
is more of the constructivism.
Thank you.
I'm surprised there's
so many colors in it up close,
'cause from far away,
it doesn't look like it
has that many colors in it.
This feels so compact
and smashed together.
It definitely
does feel pop art.
I think, for me,
it's a question of execution.
- Dolly Parton meets cubism.
- Hmm.
It bums me out that she didn't
do anything to her arms.
Oh, my God, don't look
at that God-awful guitar.
Don't look at those
unpainted arms.
I'm scared.
I don't want to go yet.
Who made your favorite
living work of art tonight?
Tell us on Twitter,
using #FaceOff.
She didn't do anything
to her arms.
Yeah.
I feel disappointed myself
about this makeup.
I'm quite sure
that I'm on the bottom.
It's really interesting,
though.
Yeah.
I really like it.
What is his head
supposed to be?
A certain type
of whiskey bottle?
It seems like he's got
all these cool ideas,
but I do not like that makeup.
Yeah.
Another amazing paint job.
- It really is.
- That's a lot of colors.
I really like this idea
of squeezing it so tightly
that we see bulges.
That's kind of cool.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
I like this thing.
I like the forced perspective.
Yeah, it's fantastic.
As much as I dig
what's going on,
I'm not quite sure if this
design fits surrealism.
I agree.
Okay, the judges
have scored your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Frank...
Roy...
Alana...
Congratulations,
you are all safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Oh, my God.
The rest of you
were the best and the worst.
The judges would now like
to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Let's talk to Miranda.
Tell us about your concept
and the art movement you used
to create this character.
The art movement was cubism,
and I wanted to make
a sorrowful musician
who lives through her music,
but if she stops playing,
she dies.
To be honest,
I'm quite disappointed
in myself this challenge.
I don't see how you
could be so incredibly wrong
about how successful you were
with your makeup.
Really?
Oh, my God!
Anyone familiar
with the cubism movement
would look at it immediately
and say,
"I know exactly
what they were going for."
It's a very successful makeup.
Her face is unbelievable.
My one comment is that you
should have addressed her arms.
That's the only thing
that's missing.
It totally took my breath away.
- Thank you so much.
- Nice job, honey.
So damn good.
The surfacing is fantastic,
the painting is beautiful.
I just love this piece.
Thank you, Neville.
Miranda, please step back.
Tate.
Hey, guys.
Okay, Tate, give it to me.
We all know art is subjective,
especially surrealism.
For this character,
I put the castle on top,
and put a spriteful fairy
to live inside it.
The mold for this tipped over
on my hand.
I had to get 13 stitches
yesterday,
and I missed three hours
in the shop,
so I wasn't able to detail it
as much as I wanted to.
Well, I got to tell you,
I'm just not certain
that it really fits
into the surrealism category.
The whole bottom,
it falls apart for me.
Okay.
I feel that it's not
makeup-y enough.
Mm-hmm.
You've got paint on her face,
and you've got contacts
and eyelashes,
and beyond that,
it's a costume.
It's a really cool costume.
Understood.
Tate, please step back.
Thanks, guys.
Eddie.
Tell us about the movement
you chose for this makeup.
I selected expressionism.
I've always been inspired
by Vincent van Gogh's
Starry Night.
The title of this piece
is Stressful Night,
'cause I really wanted to
portray the emotion of stress.
At a distance, it could be
interpreted as a burn makeup.
It feels a touch monstery.
You've got
some massive problems.
The fact that the eyes
are so wholly untreated,
and they're just poking out.
It feels like something
that's trying to be art
that's just jammed
on somebody's head.
There's just too much red.
There's no delineation in color.
It's too monochromatic.
Eddie, please step back.
Laura, please step up.
Tell us about your concept
and the movement.
I decided to go with cubism.
I wanted to both
incorporate my style
with the style
of the time period.
I think it's an absolutely
stunning job.
It looks like a living,
walking painting.
This is an immaculate makeup.
The asymmetry of it,
all your construction...
It's mind-boggling.
It's absolutely exquisite.
Thank you so much.
Everything they said,
times ten.
- I just love it.
- Thank you.
Laura, please step back.
Thanks, Matt.
Scott, please come forward.
Hi, Scott.
Which movement did you select?
I selected surrealism.
I chose to make this
about my father,
who passed away many years ago.
My father was a loving man,
but he had a lot of demons.
He had a volcanic temper,
hence the volcano.
This is a very personal piece
to you.
Unfortunately,
the makeup on his face
takes me out of the moment.
That volcanic look is one of
the hardest things to do well,
so for me, it doesn't work.
I was a bit lost.
The volcano doesn't look
like a volcano.
It reads more tree stump,
and so that being tied
directly to his temper,
metaphorically, didn't happen
for me as a viewer.
Okay.
Scott, you can step back.
Laney, please step up.
Tell us about the concept
behind this makeup.
I had pop art,
and my concept was
today's media effect on women
in the form
of "Comic Relief."
I think that you nailed
the style and the movement.
You took it a step further
and turned it into a character
that is interesting.
I love the idea of this.
I get the whole thing,
that it's very pop arty.
I do love the red.
It just seems like you
stuck too much of it
right up here
on her head for me.
Other than that,
oh, my God, it's fabulous.
Laney, please step back.
- Mwah!
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
All right, judges,
let's talk about the looks
you liked the most
this evening.
Why don't we start
with Miranda?
Oh, I like Miranda's.
She made ugly beautiful.
The sculpting was so cool,
and the colors were so subtle.
She did a great job.
All right,
let's move on to Laura.
Oh, my God, she knocked it
out of the park again.
Planar surfacing is such
a laborious thing to do.
Yeah.
That, to me, was the most
mind-blowing part of this.
All right,
let's move on to Laney.
In terms of presenting
your movement in a concise way,
Laney may have beaten everyone.
Yeah, I agree.
All right,
let's talk about the looks
you liked the least this week.
Why don't we start with Tate?
I think the entire thing
was a mistake,
just because it doesn't add up.
It doesn't stack up
at all to surrealism.
Yeah, it was obvious
when you looked at it
that it was more of a costume.
Okay.
Let's move on to Eddie.
He had the right idea,
but it needed that other color,
beyond just his apron.
If he would have used some
black scrim over the eyes
and painted graphic,
open eyeballs on the scrim,
it would have changed
the entire tone of the face.
All right,
let's move on to Scott.
Scott needs to work on
simplicity and attractiveness,
because that piece
is just so unattractive.
Everything was too hard,
and too structured.
To me, surrealism
has a softness to it.
He just didn't do it
the right way.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- We have.
- Let's bring them back out.
Glenn, tell us about
the top looks.
Miranda, your character
was soft and beautiful,
and your sculpture
readily conveyed the sorrow
that you were going for.
Laney, you had
a really cool character,
and there was no question
in our mind
when she walked out
that she was from
the pop art movement.
Laura, we loved all
of the great design decisions
in your makeup, and once again,
you've delivered
an immaculate paint job.
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner of
this challenge is...
So who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of this challenge is...
Laura.
You perfectly met this challenge
and integrated your movement.
It truly was living art,
perhaps your best work yet.
Thank you, guys.
I really, really, really,
really appreciate it.
And I'm just so happy
that they appreciate not just
my makeup, but my artwork.
Laura, congratulations.
You, Miranda, and Laney
can head back
to the makeup room.
Unfortunately,
that means the rest of you
are on the bottom this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Tate, we like the piece
that you created
on a general level,
but the bottom line is
it just didn't
read "surreal" to us.
Eddie, while your makeup
did evoke your movement,
we took issue with some
of the shapes of your sculpture
and the fact
that it had a mask feel.
And Scott, we liked your story,
but there were several problems
with the execution
that hindered the way
that it was being conveyed.
So who is going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Scott.
It seems like you
really struggled this week
to pull all of your ideas
together.
It just didn't work
on an overall level for us.
Scott, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
Eddie, Tate,
you are safe this week
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Scott, I am not worried
about you at all.
I have seen
amazing creations from you,
so I am looking forward
to seeing more of those.
- I've had a blast.
- Cool.
Scott, it's been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Bye-bye.
I wish that I had pushed myself
outside my boundaries
a little more.
- Scott?
- Yeah, it's okay, guys.
I'm seriously fine.
Maybe I'm stuck in my
particular way of doing things,
so breaking outside of that
is difficult.
This is a young person's game,
and that includes Roy.
I don't have any concerns
about my future.
I made a lot of new,
awesome friends.
Hopefully, I'll be back
for the finale
and maybe can show
that I've still
got a few tricks up my sleeve.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net