Previously onFace Off...
Laura earned her first win
for her Mother Earth goddess.
Thank you.
And veteran artist RJ
was sent home.
Now ten artists remain,
and tonight,
they'll reimagine
some all hallows' classics.
- Yes!
- All right!
But some will crack
under the pressure.
Oh, damn it.
I cannot go home
on a Halloween-themed challenge.
I don't even have
a concept yet.
I don't know what to do.
I'm literally on the verge
of tears right now.
I really do love
what you've done with this.
It's really cool-looking.
It's uninspired and inadequate.
In the end,
one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
a 2013 Fiat 500C,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Only one will win Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
I'm still very sad
that RJ has left.
It's gonna be rough
around here without him.
That's the second veteran
to go home.
Now we're down to what?
Four of the newcomers
and six veterans?
Some of them are showing
some promise.
I'm feeling a little bit
nervous myself
'cause there's not a dud
in the bunch at this point,
and we're all here to win,
so it's gonna be tough
from here on out.
All right, guys, let's go.
Got a new challenge
waiting on us.
We walk in the lab,
and I see all these models,
and there are boxes
on each table.
I can't wait to see
what's inside.
Makeup artists
are sometimes given
the tiniest bit of inspiration
and asked to turn it
into an incredible character.
Well, today's foundation
challenge will be no different.
I've placed a box
on each of your workstations.
Inside you'll find a single item
that will serve as the basis
for your creations today.
What's in the box?
Before we get started,
I'd like to introduce you
to someone who knows
exactly what it takes
to excel in Hollywood.
She was the makeup designer
on Tim Burton's
Alice In Wonderland,
which won her a Bafta,
and she won an Oscar
for her work
on Lemony Snicket's
A Series Of Unfortunate Events.
Please welcome Valli O'Reilly.
Having somebody
of Valli O'Reilly's caliber
judging your makeup
creates a lot of added pressure
because this person could be
a potential employer someday.
- Hi, Valli.
- Nice to meet you.
- Thank you for being here.
- Thank you.
As the judge
of today's challenge,
what are you going to be looking
for in their final makeups?
I always want to see
a little bit of a human
in the makeup.
I don't like them
to look cartoony.
All right, guys,
we have a major prize
on the line today.
The winner will receive immunity
from elimination
in this week's
spotlight challenge.
Oh, hell yeah.
I really need to win this.
I have been on the bottom
two weeks in a row,
and I don't like it.
All right,
why don't you all go stand
at your workstations?
You will have two hours
to complete this challenge.
On my mark, open your boxes,
and get started.
The time starts... now.
Oh!
- No way.
- Oh, lord.
Ooh, teeth.
Everybody has different teeth.
I look over,
and Scott has cartoony teeth.
Frank has got
these alien-looking teeth.
Oy.
Mine look like demon teeth.
Immediately I go
over to the prosthetics.
I come across a demon brow,
and I decide that might work.
My teeth are sharp,
pointy things, and they're gold.
Let's go ahead and go ahead
and get your teeth fit.
My concept is he has
this disease
that caused all
these little tumors on his face.
It looks like a scale pattern,
so he becomes, like,
this reptile boy.
Yeah.
That's good.
So I got these purply teeth,
and they say
space monster to me,
so she's an astronaut that got
some sort of space virus
and is starting to mutate.
Here you go.
My teeth look like
cartoon teeth,
and I found this little
schoolboy costume,
and I've got a rabbit nose
that I think I can make work
really well.
Very gory.
I got teeth
that were wired shut.
My concept is that
she's some kind of a prisoner,
so she's kind of wasting away.
My teeth look Quasimodo-ish.
They're nicotine-stained,
so my character is
a Spanish gunslinger,
and I decide to do
an old-age makeup,
so this is really going to be
hard for two hours.
My teeth,
since they're grotesque,
I'm making him into a corpse
that's coming out of the grave
to seek revenge.
_
I take fishnet stockings
and apply art gel over it.
It's gonna add
a three-dimensional stencil,
and I have these scales
that look like little tumors.
I got these silver teeth,
so I make her into, like,
a cyborg princess.
You have 15 minutes left.
Time's up.
Brushes down.
- Hi, Laney.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- I got the silver teeth,
so I was thinking maybe
her under-structure
is also made of silver.
I think it's good.
My only suggestion would be,
on this part of the foundation,
the prosthetic has
a lot more fleshy color.
Otherwise it's imaginative.
This isEl Sucio,
the dirty bandit.
I wanted to work
with a human character for once.
I've made a lot
of monsters already.
Very good.
I like what you did
with the skin.
Thank you very much.
This is Ramel.
He got this disease
that caused
all these small tumors,
and so he ran off
and joined the circus.
Wow, good texturing.
Really looks like a reptile.
My idea was that this girl
has been enslaved
by an evil man.
- He has wired her mouth shut...
- Yeah.
...so she can't eat
or talk back.
She almost looks like
a shrunken head.
- Yeah.
- You know?
I think you did a good job.
Hey, girl.
Great to see you.
I'm looking around the lab,
and I'm feeling like everybody's
doing great stuff,
and it's a totally unique take
across the board.
This is anybody's game.
All right, Valli.
How do you think they did?
Overall, I thought
they were very creative.
I can't believe how much
they pulled off.
Who created
your favorite looks?
My first one I really liked
was yours, Tate.
Thank you.
I could see him sitting
on a set in some western.
I thought your work
was very good.
- Thank you very much.
- Roy,
you took those teeth,
and you developed
a whole character
that incorporated everything
that I asked.
I was really impressed.
Thank you very much.
Miranda, I also liked
the makeup that you did.
It was creature-like
but still a little human-like.
I thought you did a great job.
Thank you so much.
All right, Valli, who is
the winner of this challenge?
The winner is...
Roy.
Yeah, Roy!
Oh, wow.
Thank you.
I loved the way
the teeth looked,
and you did a great job
of the human element.
- Thank you.
- Roy, congratulations.
You have won immunity this week
and cannot be eliminated.
I'm really happy
to have immunity.
Now I can breathe
a little bit more freely.
All right, everybody,
I will see you tomorrow
for your next
spotlight challenge.
Lovely meeting you.
- Thank you.
- Bye-bye.
- Oh, boy.
- Whoa.
We walk into the lab,
and there's fog everywhere,
and McKenzie is standing
in front of a graveyard.
It's scary, but it's exciting.
Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- Hey, girl.
Your next spotlight challenge
is inspired
by my favorite holiday,
Halloween.
- Oh, yeah.
- Whoo!
- Yay!
- I sell prosthetics
during the Halloween season
for a living.
This is what I love,
so I'm excited
about this challenge.
Halloween was once
a serious tradition
where people wore costumes
to ward off evil spirits.
Over time,
some of those costumes
have become absolute classics.
Come on in, guys.
Oh, God.
- Yes!
- All right, yes!
- Wow.
- Okay.
I want that clown.
For this spotlight challenge,
each of you will select
one of these
classic Halloween characters--
vampire, clown, scarecrow,
skeleton, devil--
and bring it to life
as a completely reimagined
creature of the night.
This is fun.
Okay, Scott, you're up first.
- Clown.
- Vampire.
I am the devil.
Oh, my God, thank you.
Vampire.
- Devil.
- I was just like,
please not skeleton,
please not skeleton.
Scarecrow.
- Clown.
- Skeleton.
Scarecrow.
Of course,
the last one is skeleton.
I just have no idea
what I'm gonna do
for this character.
Okay, before I send you
off to work,
there's one more component
to this challenge.
In the spirit of Halloween,
I want each of you to add
a trick element of some kind
to your characters.
It could be anything,
from a simple bladder
to a blood gag,
or LEDs or fiber optics.
The first five years
of my career,
that's all I did.
Blood gags, bladders,
things that move.
So I've got a million ideas.
I want you to go ahead
and pick your models,
and I will see you tomorrow.
- See you.
- Bye.
Thank you.
I really have no intention
of letting immunity change
my concept or what I do.
I always go over the top
a little bit,
because if you don't have
the concept
to start out with,
you don't really stand
a chance in this competition.
I want to paint my devil black,
and I'm thinking
it'd be beautiful
to do oranges under the black.
For my trick, I'm thinking
of fabricating bat wings.
My concept is to keep
the devil pale,
which is something
I haven't seen before.
I really want her
to be ram-like,
but instead of doing horns,
I decided to use lava shards.
For my trick, I'm gonna put
LEDs behind silicone,
it'll give the effect of lava.
I'm having trouble
with the design for a skeleton
because you can't take away
the human anatomy.
We can only build on top of it.
A skeleton doesn't have a nose.
Like, you can't cut off
somebody's nose,
so it's extremely difficult.
Frank and I both picked
the scarecrow.
My character's gonna be feeding
on crows.
The chest is made of twigs
and has
a few dead crows on the inside.
Fuck yeah, dude.
My gag is to make
his chest bleed.
What about you?
What you got going on?
This is the silhouette
of the dude.
Oh, that's cool.
I design a very standard
scarecrow monster,
which the judges could like
for its simplicity
or not like because I'm not
reinventing it enough.
And I'm gonna probably make
its eyes glow.
- That's awesome.
- That's my gag.
Once I'm confident
with my design for the skeleton,
I start sculpting.
I think
I'm onto a cool character.
I'm calling it
"The Lady Of The Cemetery."
She is a corpse pushing herself
out of the ground.
Her tombstone
comes up with her.
For my trick, I'm going to do
a beating heart.
I've been struggling
with this damn skeleton all day.
It's so frustrating.
Everyone else is already
sculpting their characters,
and I don't even have
a concept yet.
I am literally on the verge
of tears right now.
_
Coming up...
Oh!
I cannot go home
on a Halloween challenge.
I really do love
what you've done with this.
It's uninspired and inadequate.
It's day one
of the Halloween challenge,
and I'm having trouble
with the design
for a skeleton,
but I start to piece together
an idea.
I have to ask you
about Dia de los Muertos.
Dia de los Muertos
is a Spanish holiday.
It's people offering tribute
to their dead ones
at the cemetery,
and there's a lot of skulls.
Okay.
I'm thinking I can make
this character
a voodoo doctor
that people go to
to bring their loved ones
back from the dead.
I'm doing a face sculpt,
the hands,
and fabricating a headdress.
I'm just nervous about
my ability to complete all this
in such little time.
I'm making this vampire
that's a half man, half bat.
Since it's a nocturnal creature,
I'm using lights in the eyes
as my trick.
- How you doing, Scott?
- I'm okay.
I might be able to get this
molded and out today.
The basic concept for my clown
is that he's a serial killer.
And he has ripped
his own heart out,
so my joke is to have him
holding a heart
that makes noise
when it's squeezed.
I'm having so much fun
with my clown.
For the trick,
I build a fake stomach on her
and have her pulling out
her intestine.
I get it done fairly quickly,
and then I decide to mold it.
I'm the only person
in the mold room,
which feels pretty cool.
I never really make it there
on the first day,
so I'm doing awesome.
I'm really nervous
about sculpting this skull.
The skeleton has to be
anatomically correct.
If I have one contour
out of place,
the judges will just kill me
for it.
What can I do to hide her nose?
Just paint it black.
I don't know what to do
with this area.
- You think this looks fine?
- Absolutely.
Do you think
I should have it, like,
more like she's wearing it?
I wish Miranda would accept
her talent level.
This is a lot of stuff
I don't exactly know how to do.
All of us are looking
at her sculpts going,
damn, you're a prodigy.
You're totally fine.
_
All right, well, then,
I'm gonna quit telling you
it looks fine
if you're gonna keep telling me
it looks stupid.
Oy, fuck.
Laura, what's your concept?
I simplified the design
so that I could concentrate
on details.
My vampire starts out pretty,
but he starts feeding
on himself,
and he becomes very emaciated,
and his skin turns gray.
So my trick's gonna be blood
just kind of spewing
out of his arm.
Oh, wow.
I am definitely not
where I want to be
at the end of day one.
That's time, everybody.
Let's go home.
At this point in the challenge,
we're all drained.
My extra years of life
are starting to show.
Let's do this.
It's day two
of our Halloween challenge,
and we have 9 1/2 hours today.
Oh, you're so ugly.
I still need to refine
some of the features
on my sculpture,
but at this point,
I have to get it molded.
Today I have to get
my sculpt detailed out
and ready for foam.
In a skeleton
where would obviously be
the body cavity,
I decide to go
with deteriorating anatomy,
so the judges
aren't gonna walk up
and see a black painted hole.
Hello, everybody.
Hi.
We're here to do
our walkthrough.
Mr. Westmore and McKenzie
come in.
- Hey, Laura.
- Hi.
I'm extremely excited
to see what kind of advice
he has to give.
I got vampire.
- Vampire.
- For my gag,
I'm gonna put
a strip of foam on his arm
and then have him bite into it.
- So blood will pump out?
- Yeah.
That's why he's all feral,
- and he's getting--
- I like it.
But you're gonna need
a bigger tube...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...'cause that isn't gonna get
much blood through it at all.
Okay.
I picked the devil,
and my trick
is that I want to make wings.
Boy, you have a lot going
for you.
- But it looks great.
- All right, so with immunity,
are you able to relax
a little bit, or--
No, 'cause I want
to win this one.
Well, I got skeleton.
Her black heart is going
to be beating.
I'm going to insert a bladder.
How is she actually gonna make
the bladder work?
- Yeah.
- You think something like this?
You're gonna need something
larger than a turkey baster.
Worst-case scenario,
I can always go with breath,
- but I would really prefer not--
- You can follow behind.
- Yeah.
- I've been there.
- I chose a vampire.
- Okay.
The trick,
I'm adding light to the eyes.
You're gonna have to leave
enough room in here.
Otherwise, he's gonna be doing
this to try to see.
Typically,
when you think "devil,"
it's like that red skin.
And I really want to go albino
because they're underground,
and my inspiration for the face
was a ram.
Are you going to get it
into the nose?
'Cause I'm seeing
human nose here.
That doesn't say animal.
I picked scarecrow.
This is
a very static character.
A devil isn't, a clown isn't,
but the scarecrow is.
I think you should do away
with the human lips on there.
Otherwise, it's gonna look
like a mask on it.
Gotcha.
I'm scared I'm not going
original enough to--
like, you know,
it has the big nose,
the chin, and the cheeks,
and the big ears.
I don't think there's so much
problem with that.
I think it's your painting
that's gonna make
the difference
because all the clowns' faces
are all human beings,
yet they look so different
because of the paint jobs.
All right, everybody.
We're heading out.
It's looking great.
Thanks, guys.
Can't wait to see your tricks
and treats.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye, thank you.
I'm opening my cowl mold,
and I have no trouble at all
getting the back off,
but when I try the front...
Oh, damn it.
It locks.
Want me to help you out?
Come on.
People are trying to help me.
Time is ticking down,
and I'm starting to panic.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
I cannot go home
on a Halloween challenge.
My cowl mold locks.
- Whoa.
- Fuck.
Part of it breaks off.
Finally, after a lot of pulling
and pushing
and digging and help,
I get it open,
and sure enough,
there's a huge crack.
This is the problem that
can absolutely destroy a makeup.
One bad edge can send me home,
so I'm just gonna have to pray
for the best.
So I finished molding
my clown face,
and it's ready for foam.
Next I start fabricating
intestines.
I paint several latex layers
on the floor.
Once it dries,
I roll the latex together,
and it will form a coil.
After I get my molds ready
to be run in foam latex,
I start sewing together
a burlap mask
that the actor's gonna rip off
onstage.
Ten minutes left!
I look across the lab,
and I see
so many outstanding makeups
that I have no idea
who's gonna win this challenge.
I'll finish this up
in the morning.
By the end of the day,
I'm a little nervous.
I know I have a lot of work
to do on application day...
Time, guys!
...but I'm confident
I can get it done.
So today's application day.
Good luck, everybody.
We have four hours in the lab,
and then we have one hour
at last looks.
Oh, boy.
The very first thing I notice
is the cowl.
That's unusable.
It's torn in several places.
Damn it.
There is really no way
to fix that,
other than to scissor out
from the inside
and remake a new thin edge,
and there's no way
I can do that
with all the applying, painting,
and fabricating
I have to get done today.
I'm Eddie.
Nice to meet you.
Matt.
It's good to meet you, man.
Morning. Hoyt?
Laura.
Today you're gonna be
a scarecrow.
- Got you again.
- Yes, sir.
A woman of her word.
There's a lot to do today.
Apply the hands.
Apply the face.
Paint the hands.
Paint the face.
Adorn the dress.
Make this headdress.
Get these LED lights
into these roses.
And I just don't know
how the hell I'm gonna do
all of this.
I have
at least 26 prosthetics...
- Oh, my--
- ...to put on you,
but they're just
little booties.
I'm super excited
about my makeup.
The edges are beautiful.
I put her face on.
That fits her perfectly well.
So does the belly.
I love success!
Now I just hope
the rest of the day
will go this smoothly.
Oh, my God.
I mix five different batches
of silicone
trying to get the translucency
and the fluorescents
that I need of lava.
These aren't working?
And then the light breaks.
Plan fucking B.
So I decide to use
the ball light.
Ah, this isn't gonna stay now.
I need hot glue.
Does anyone have
a hot glue gun on?
I glue these LEDs
into my lava rock,
but when I finally go
back to put the silicone
over the lights...
My silicone just fucking set.
Fuck!
So now I have to remix
the silicone
and get it on top
of this lava rock.
I'm really getting hard
on myself,
and I can't because I have
way too much to do.
I'm feeling
a little self-conscious
because I've been in trouble
with the judges
for using a lot of contrast
and hard lines,
which I'm very used to using
because I'm a body painter.
So doing this
realistic paint job,
it's very nerve-racking.
Old-age stipple latex
has a high ammonia count,
which keeps it thin.
Moments before it fully dries,
it's set,
but it's still
a little fragile,
and it will catch
in certain spots,
creating different-sized holes,
kind of like a run
in a pantyhose.
This will cause your skin
to look all old and withered.
It's a pretty cool trick
for a zombie-type flesh.
This is so awesome.
Laney has made the decision
to use real cotton candy
for hair.
If you know what
cotton candy is,
it's just spun sugar.
And what happens to sugar
whenever it gets hot?
It melts.
These are actually working
really well.
And, you know, I don't think
that she's considered that.
Oh, my God.
I love it so much.
How's that feel
around your nose-- secure?
- Yeah.
- I get my face and my cowl
down onto my model,
and I'm like, oh, my God.
This looks like a cat bunny.
It isn't evil or demonic.
I should have listened
to Mr. Westmore.
He was concerned the nose
could be a bad choice.
I'm such a piece of shit,
I can't stand it.
But it's too late now.
There's nothing I can do.
My heart is racing so hard
right now.
I'm working next to Miranda,
and she's got her shit
all over the place as usual.
Miranda, I need
those scissors back.
I have them.
I'll get them to you
before we go, I promise.
But I'm working
on something now.
Oh, okay, dude.
I'm actually surprised
at how far behind
Miranda seems to be.
- Here's the scissors.
- Jeez.
It's all good.
Yeah, I got it.
- I just gotta...
- Thank you.
...mentally try to figure out
what's going on.
Looking around the room,
everybody's
pretty much finished,
and I've only just started
applying the prosthetics.
11 minutes, guys.
I'll be right back.
Gonna get gloves.
Hopefully I can pull this
together in last looks,
because that's all I have.
All right, that's time!
I really think
I could be going home.
- Coming up...
- Here we go.
There's no way
that I'm gonna finish in time.
This has fallen a little short
this week.
I'm loving this makeup.
- Whoo!
- Here we go.
Last looks, we have one hour,
and it goes by so fast.
Does anybody have
a dark brown airbrush paint?
Yup.
It's right there.
I still have to paint
the entire character
to make it look decent.
There's no way that I'm gonna
finish it in time.
And do something
about this hair.
Her cotton candy hair
completely melted off,
and her prosthetic is falling
off her face.
15 minutes, everyone!
Take a sip of this.
All it is
is corn syrup and water.
Wash it around in your mouth.
There you go.
Yeah.
Time!
That's it, guys.
God!
Welcome
to theFace Offreveal stage.
Tonight one of you
will be eliminated.
Let's say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening.
- Hey, Glenn.
Three time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
- Hi, guys.
- Hey, Ve.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
- Boo.
- Hey, Neville.
All right, so this week,
your spotlight challenge
was to choose
a classic Halloween character
and reimagine it
as a creature of the night,
and in keeping with the spirit
of Halloween,
I also asked you to incorporate
a trick element
into your designs.
So let's take a look
at your creatures.
If I was hired on a movie
to make a scarecrow monster
like that,
I would think I pulled it off.
It's a complete character.
I feel like
I accomplished my vision.
I've always wanted to get
a vampire makeup on this show,
and I'm definitely thinking
that this could even be
a top look.
I could be in bottom looks
because of my poor application
and the cotton candy melting.
I think at least I'm going
to be safe.
I'm feeling better about it
because it's a finished design.
The wings are actually working
the way that they're
supposed to.
I like the profile of it.
I'm liking everything
about this makeup.
I can't see the bird skeletons
from far away,
so the torso looks like
a big mess,
but I'm happy with what I did.
I'm proud of my time
management and execution.
I could see this
on my business card.
The face isn't as creepy
as it should be,
but it's
a beautiful application.
Hopefully that's enough
to spare me
from being a bottom look.
I think I've accomplished
the task.
I really like
the metal rivets
in the cheekbones.
I think it looked pretty cool.
I thought I was gonna be
sending out
an unfinished makeup,
but I look at it,
and it's a cool character.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look
at tonight's creatures?
Can you open your mouth?
I just feel like
we've seen this before.
It's a good execution
of another interesting idea.
Mm.
Hmm.
The teeth are kind of
falling out on you.
One part I do like
is right here.
It's almost as if the gum
has been torn off.
That's creepy.
I think she looks good
from far away
but not so good from up close.
I see the judges
turn her around,
point at the hair, and I know
the wig cap is showing.
The cotton candy's melted.
I think the ears are very odd.
Those are
just unusual sculptures.
Furl your brow.
I'm starting to get
really nervous
because they wouldn't be able
to use this piece for a film.
I think
that could send me home.
Who made your favorite
Halloween creature?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
I think the ears are very odd.
Oh, my God.
I love my make-up so much and
this last hour everything went so wrong.
I could be in bottom looks
because of my cotton candy hair.
I hate this part so much.
I'm just revealing
your superfluous
bony protuberances here.
- That served no purpose.
- None.
I've never seen this paint job
done on the show before.
Give us your wing.
- Bats have fur on them.
- Yeah.
It's kind of a cool idea.
See, this--
if there would have been
more black feathers,
that would have helped me.
Ooh.
It's hard to read that
that is what it is.
- 'Cause it's a cool idea.
- It sure is.
Thank you.
You just got a creepy grin,
don't you?
Yeah, I know.
Getting a little tired
of this motif.
It doesn't really connect nicely
in terms of your form.
- Once-- twice.
- Not needed.
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
I don't get what this face does
for the design that
we're supposed to be looking at.
It's totally disconnected.
I don't get it.
The sculptural details
are better close-up,
but he's obliterated them
with those really hard
red lines.
Mm-hmm.
- It's nice.
- Oh, the hands are cool.
It's well done up close.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Okay, the judges
have scored your creations.
Let's find out
what they thought.
Laura.
Miranda.
Eddie.
Frank.
Congratulations,
because you are all safe
and can head
back to the makeup room.
The rest of you were the best
and the worst this week.
The judges would like to speak
with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Scott, please step up.
Tell us about your concept.
Rather than just go
for a rather typical clown,
he's a reincarnation
of a serial killer.
It feels like artrite treatment
of the head form.
The sculpture is so wacky
and lopsided.
He's like a misshapen
Bert and Ernie.
I'm not thrilled with this.
Okay.
I would have maybe
taken advantage
of a bit more clown-like makeup,
and I know
that it's the classic red nose
and red lips,
but it just looks
thrown together.
Okay.
I'm not sure exactly
what you were doing
with your paint
with the piercings,
but I do like the idea
of those pinched cheeks
pulling up his mouth.
Okay.
Scott, please step back.
Thank you.
Roy, please step up.
Tell us
about your devil concept.
The devil is chained into hell,
but every Halloween,
he's given the strength
to break his bonds
and walk among humans.
Raise your wings up.
Yeah, I like it.
I'm really intrigued
by this paint job.
It's kind of like frozen lava.
To me, the highlight
is that facial sculpt.
I wish, color-wise,
it popped a little bit,
but overall, I do dig it.
- Thanks.
- Roy, thank you.
- Please step back.
- Thank you.
Laney, come forward.
Tell us about your character.
She's a killer clown.
I absolutely loved this
until I realized
that cotton candy hair
was a terrible mistake.
If something goes
terribly wrong,
don't tell me about it.
That wasn't even on my radar.
I really do love
what you've done with this.
There's a whole lot
of character design in this,
head to toe,
and it's powerful graphically.
The piece de resistance for me
was the hairy armpits.
Oh, my God.
You did a great job, Laney.
- Thank you.
- Laney, please step back.
Thank you.
Lyma, please step up.
Tell us about your concept
for this challenge.
He's a bat human,
and he's got this disease
in his skin.
Are you happy
with your work this week?
I am happy, yes.
Unfortunately,
I cannot agree with you.
I feel that it is
desperately starved
for greater sculptural detail,
as it is
for greater paint detail.
This is something that,
for me, never works,
is when creatures have
glowing eyes.
What this does is,
it cheapens it.
I do think the ears
are kind of interesting,
but there's a lot of stuff
going on below them
that I'm not really sure about.
This has fallen a little short
this week, honey.
- Lyma, thank you.
- Thank you.
Tate, come forward.
Could you tell us about
your skeleton treatment here?
She's the shepherd
of the spirits in her cemetery.
She protects them.
I don't even know
where to start.
It's really cool-looking.
I like the way you handled
the rotting fresh on her arms.
What did you use for that?
I painted on a layer
of old-age stipple.
- Very effective.
- Thank you.
It's cohesive and balanced.
Even though the head is big,
it's not disproportionate.
This is a superb display
of visual storytelling.
I'm loving this makeup.
I appreciate it.
Tate, please step back.
Alana, you're next.
Tell us
about your character choice.
Well, I chose the devil.
For the face,
my inspiration was a ram.
I wanted to do something
like I've never seen the devil
interpreted like before.
You did give us
something unexpected,
but I'm not sure
if it's well resolved.
There's just things in the face
that are not even close
to feeling like a devil.
I love the idea
of taking the horns
and going lava-y rock.
That's a cool direction.
You could have taken that
through the whole makeup.
But overall, it's uninspired
and inadequate.
Alana, please step back.
All right, guys.
The judges have heard
what you have to say.
Please head
back to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
- Thank you.
Thanks, guys.
Okay, let's start
with the looks
you liked the most this week.
How about Roy?
I really liked Roy's.
I just liked the fact
that it had
that lava look all over it.
Just such a great idea to go
with a color palette
that is so not traditional.
All right,
let's move on to Laney.
Creepy. Hairy armpits.
I don't know.
I loved it.
Everything she did was
such great character choices.
All right, let's discuss Tate.
What he did with the skull
impressed me the most
because it all felt skeletal.
It's creepy, and it's fun.
He did some really cool stuff,
like how he did
the rotten skin.
It worked really well.
Very cool makeup.
All right, let's move on
to the looks
you liked the least.
Why don't we start with Scott?
Oh, Scott's killing me.
That sculpture was terrible.
The egghead shape
didn't make sense.
That thing could have been
as creepy as all get-out
with a drippy old
messed-up clown makeup.
All right,
let's move on to Lyma.
I've seen her do better.
The lack of form
is unbelievable.
And it was all built up
way up on top of his head.
- Yeah.
- Lastly, we have Alana.
This is a confusing makeup
because it is probably
her cleanest application
she's ever pulled off.
The fact that she thought
this looked like a ram
freaks me out.
It looks like a tabby cat
with a turban on.
It doesn't look anything
like a ram.
She can't just tell us
it was supposed to be something
and then bang out
this super simple form
that she uses in every makeup.
That's not going to cut it.
All right, judges.
Have you made your decisions?
- Indeed.
- We have.
Okay, let's bring them
back out.
Glenn, tell us
about the top looks.
Tate, your character was filled
with smart, artistic decisions,
and they all came together
to tell
a very convincing story.
Laney, we loved the vivid,
graphic nature of your clown,
and everything on it
came together
with great synergy.
Roy, there were some really cool
ideas in your makeup,
and it was a ton of work
in a very small amount of time.
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of this week's challenge is...
Glenn, who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of this week's challenge is...
Tate.
Yeah, Boo.
Thank you.
Your character fused elements
that were both artistic
and beautiful.
Well done.
Thanks a lot.
To win the Halloween challenge,
which is my one day
of the year?
It's fantastic.
I feel renewed,
and I feel like
I just won the title.
Tate, congratulations.
You, Roy, and Laney can head
back to the makeup room.
- Thank you, guys.
- Thank you very much, guys.
Thanks, guys.
Appreciate it.
Unfortunately, that means
the rest of you
are on the bottom,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Scott, we understood
what it was
that you were going for
from afar,
but up close,
your painting and sculpture
on your clown
were really rough.
Okay.
Lyma, we felt that you made
some really odd sculptural
decisions this week,
and overall,
we weren't quite sure
what we were looking at.
Alana, the starting point
of your concept was interesting,
but none of that
was communicated
in your character tonight.
So who is going home tonight?
The person
going home tonight is...
Lyma.
There were many things
that weren't working
for you tonight,
but in the end,
it was your lack
of anatomical accuracy
that was your downfall.
Lyma, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
The rest of you are safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you.
Lyma...
you know, we've seen
some great work from you.
I'm pretty confident in saying
that the next time
we see your talents,
it's going to be
in a professional scenario.
Thank you, Neville.
Lyma, it's been really great
having you here with us,
but if you would please
head back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you, guys.
I had a lot of fun.
- Thank you.
- Good night.
- Thank you, Lyma.
- Good luck.
- Night, Lyma.
Even though some of the stuff
wasn't good enough,
I'm very happy with myself.
- What?
- Aww, Lyma!
All these other artists are
now members of my family.
I don't have any regrets.
I learned a lot.
I feel like I grew.
This competition
changed my life,
and all I want to do
is redirect my career.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net