Previously onFace Off...
Alana's bride of Frankenstein
brought her to victory.
What?
That's awesome, dude.
Sam's sculpt fell short,
and she was sent home.
Now 14 artists remain.
And tonight,
they'll put a new spin
on some classic tales.
The stakes are higher than ever
this week.
- Oh, hell.
- Oh, this is not good.
But with an unexpected twist,
the pressure is doubled.
Time, everyone!
Awesome stuff, guys.
It doesn't seem to satisfy
the equation there.
In the end,
one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Make-Up
to one of their 85
international locations,
the all-new 2013 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Only one will win Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
I'm really sorry you had to go
through that last night.
I know.
You're still here.
And you could, you know,
learn from that.
Ve did mention that
I had to learn how to splatter
and do other kinds of things
with the airbrush
because what I did
was not the kind of paint job
and the realism
that they are expecting.
Yeah.
Being on the bottom was
emotionally difficult for me.
But I'm going to take
those criticisms
and use them productively.
We walk into the lab today,
and Glenn is standing
with McKenzie.
So I'm excited to find out
what the challenge is
and for a chance
to impress Glenn.
Hey, guys.
This week's foundation challenge
is inspired
by a highly acclaimed
horror film.
Insidious.
Yeah!
- Awesome.
- Oh, yeah.
I'm a hugeInsidiousfan.
I might have a little bit
of an edge on this one.
The story centers
on a young boy
who has the gift
of astral projection,
which takes him
into a spiritual realm
inhabited by demons.
The terrifying sequel,
Insidious Chapter 2,
follows the haunted
Lambert family
as they seek to uncover
the mysterious secret
that has left them
dangerously connected
to the spirit world.
Now that my heart's racing--
Okay, your foundation
challenge is to create
your own personal demon
inspired by the world
of Insidious Chapter 2.
Before we get started,
I have a special message
for you
from the director
of the Insidious films,
James Wan.
Hi, everyone.
Today's winner will receive
a copy of Insidious,
out now on home video.
And you'll also win a flight
out to Los Angeles
with a friend to attend
the red carpet premiere
of Insidious Chapter 2.
Wow.
There's one detail
that McKenzie didn't tell you.
In the climactic ending
of the original film,
the boy's father is shown to be
possessed by a female demon.
So I want you to turn
your male models
into female demons.
Demon drag challenge,
all right.
Okay, you have two hours
to complete your looks.
Your time starts now.
This couldn't have been
a better challenge for me.
I walk around battling
my own demons every day.
The challenge is to take
our male models
and turn them into female demons
based on Insidious 2.
And my concept is that
this demon possesses me.
And it's constantly inputting
this temptation
of mortal sin.
Ready?
A woman has a rounder face,
while a man has more angles.
So I'm going to have to start
adding roundness
to his face,
and the best way to do that
is to make him
into an old woman.
I want this demon
to become something
that scared me
when I was a child.
I think horns would be
appropriate,
so I add horns
along the jawbone.
I want to bring
all of my fears into this
Insidious Chapter 2
inspired demon.
So she's an old version
of myself
who continues to mock me.
_
I have this weird,
reoccurring nightmare
that my teeth are loose.
All right,
so that's my personal demon,
teeth falling out.
I choose not to use
a prosthetic.
I'd rather spend my time
on detail in the paint job.
Something that's always
creeped me out
is a creature without eyes,
so I removed my demon's.
And so I take one of
the female heads
and vacuform it,
then just apply this mask,
which will give the male model
a female form.
One of my nightmares involves
this constantly fading character
that goes from black to white.
So I'm gonna try to do that.
Time's up.
Everybody, brushes down.
- Hey, Alana.
- Hi, you guys.
Tell us about what
you did today.
I have a lot of weird fears
and insecurities.
And this is a demon that's
just been hanging on my back.
I think that it's cartoony,
and it doesn't say "demon".
You know, you've got two hours.
Instead of going
heavily prosthetic,
the two-tone graphic nature
of this thing, I think,
is a spot-on decision.
Well done.
Extremely complete image.
Everything goes together.
The wardrobe works
with the colors.
Very cool.
Well done.
I was toying around
with the idea
of making horns extrude
from the jaw line.
I do get where you were going
with the chin,
but I think you missed
the mark.
I think you succeeded in taking
a very masculine man
and perhaps making him
even more brutish.
An idea like this,
the plastic mask
with under paint,
what a brilliant way
to get that feminine aspect
out of your way.
Well done, Roy.
Thank you.
I'm looking around at some
of the other makeups,
and lot of them are
really impressive.
There's solid competition here.
I know that the challenges are
gonna get harder.
So I got to bring my A game
every single challenge
because if I don't do my best,
I'm going home.
So, Glenn,
how did they do today?
I think a few people
found exactly
what we were looking for.
Who were your favorites?
Rick.
Really strong graphic nature
to what you did.
And I love the fact
that you really went
in your own direction with it.
Thank you.
And, Roy, using
the vacuform shell
to obliterate the male
and create that female look,
very, very creepy.
Well done.
Thank you.
All right, Glenn,
so who is the winner
of today's Insidious Chapter 2
challenge?
The winner of today's
challenge is...
Roy.
Roy, congratulations.
You and a guest
will be attending
the red carpet premiere
Insidious Chapter 2.
I'm really excited.
And I know that my wife's
gonna be excited
to come back out here
and go to a red carpet event.
That's awesome.
Thank you.
All right, well,
great job, everybody.
I will see you tomorrow
for your next
spotlight challenge.
You can pick me up
that night, Roy.
I think his wife
might want to go.
We're walking in this park,
and we can see McKenzie
standing in front
of this huge carousel.
It's beautiful.
I love carousels.
Clearly, it's gonna be
pretty fun.
Welcome to the Griffith Park
merry-go-round.
Legend has it that Walt Disney
would bring his daughters here,
and it was during these rides
that he started to dream
the fantastical idea
of Disneyland.
Oh.
Well, this week's
spotlight challenge
is inspired
by other fantastic stories
that have been taking children
to whimsical places
for generations.
You will create an original,
whimsical character
from modern times
inspired by classic Mother Goose
Nursery Rhymes.
That's awesome.
I'm so excited.
I love Mother Goose.
Now you will be working
together in teams of two.
But this time...
you're gonna be choosing
your own teams.
So go ahead and select
a teammate.
I got RJ.
It's nice to be loved.
Thank you so much, sir.
I've always wanted to work
with RJ,
ever since I saw him
on season two.
I know his style,
and I know we can make something
really cool.
I chose Lyma 'cause I think
she's extremely talented.
So its gonna be amazing
to work with her.
So each of these props
represents
a different Mother Goose
Nursery Rhyme.
Frank and Laura,
you get to pick first.
- The spider.
- Okay.
- Going with the spider.
- Ah.
"Little Miss Muffet."
- Alana and Laney.
- Five Toes.
"This Little Piggy
Went To The Market."
Adolfo and Lyma.
You want the egg?
Yeah, I want the egg.
Humpty Dumpty.
RJ and Roy.
- "The Cat And The Fiddle."
- Rick and Eric.
Go with the coin,
whatever that is.
The Crooked Sixpence.
- Scott and Eddie.
- "The Man In The Moon."
And last but not least,
Tate and Miranda.
"Peter, Peter, Pumpkin Eater."
Well, now that you all have
your Nursery Rhymes,
there is one last thing
that I need to tell you
before you start working
on your designs.
The stakes are higher than ever
this week.
Oh, hell,
there is always something
with McKenzie and these twists.
Coming up...
It's scaring me.
- This is not good.
- We need to open this now.
Otherwise, we're fucked.
Oh, no.
The mold is not opening.
I think you did an amazing job
this week.
You missed the whimsical.
It just doesn't play well.
There's one last thing
that I have to tell you
before you start
working on your designs.
This week is
a double elimination,
and two of you
will be going home.
Already, on our third
challenge, a double elim?
That's, like, crazy.
Double eliminations are
basically like double pressure.
All right, I'll leave you here
to work on your designs.
When you're done,
you can head back to the lab
and get started
on your creations.
Good luck, guys.
Yee-haw.
The musical cat,
then where's the fiddle?
The catinthe fiddle.
So our concept is
to take the cat
and have him wearing a fiddle
that he can actually play.
Maybe from the bottom
of the chin
have some whiskers going
down into the strings.
It could be.
The first thing I think of is
a pig in a meat dress.
I'm not sticking to no little
piggy going to the market.
We shouldn't go scary.
It has to say whimsical.
We can't make
five separate pigs.
So we just decided
to pick one of them
from the poem.
This little piggy stays home.
The other little piggies are,
like, her minions.
If she doesn't get
what she wants,
she'll eat the other pigs
and wear them as accessories.
_
"There was a crooked man,
and he went a crooked mile."
Our crooked man,
he's kind of twisted
and mangled.
And that could definitely go off
in a very dark direction.
But we're gonna take
a very whimsical approach.
I think it's
a really cool story.
"Peter, Peter, pumpkin eater
had a wife
and couldn't keep her.
He put her in a pumpkin shell,
and there he kept her
very well."
This is a woman who has been
locked inside a pumpkin.
So if she's ever able
to get out,
I would assume that
she would head
straight to Peter and off him.
It's gonna be a revenge story.
And we're gonna fabricate
this giant pumpkin.
- Yeah.
- It's gonna be pretty dope.
We're really excited about it.
All right, guys,
let's get going
back to the lab.
I'm excited for this challenge,
and I'm ready to do this pig.
We get into the lab,
and we have seven hours today.
You start sculpting,
and I can start building
the pumpkin.
Okay.
I start sculpting,
and the fact that somebody
as talented as Tate
trusts me to block out
these sculptures
means a lot to me.
Adolfo and I want to make
Humpty Dumpty
into a female character
and give it a Lady Gaga feel.
Lyma's sculpting the face,
and I'm sculpting the cowl.
They need to really,
really match,
because it's double elimination,
and we've both been
in the bottom.
I need to be safe.
Our concept is to create
the woman in the Moon
who lives on the Moon
and collects pieces
from Apollo missions.
We really want to give it
a modern take.
So we decide to make
an asymmetrical character.
I just really want to impress
the judges this week.
Yeah.
So our concept is
from the spider's perspective.
Miss Muffet used to have
a prince charming,
but then an evil witch decides
that she's going to curse
the prince
to look like a monster.
Laura is taking lead
on the head.
And then I start making
the mandibles
to go in different places
on the spider.
Hey, everybody.
Here for walkthrough.
Hi.
- Hello.
- We're back.
Let's see what you have.
Explain to us what you're doing
here with--
Tell us about your face first.
The face was something
that Rick actually drew out.
With the paint,
start with a good flesh tone,
and then highlight
down your bone
to make him pop out more.
Oh, okay.
How are you incorporating
the whimsical?
Our witch cursed the guy.
That's whimsical.
As far as whimsical goes,
a lot of it's gonna depend
on your painting.
Start lighter and go back
into your darker part
of your head and everything.
What's going on over here?
We're gonna give her boobs.
What you've done here
is human form,
as opposed to pig.
So you think we should bring
them to more of a point?
- Yeah.
- That's interesting.
I love Mr. Westmore.
I'm so thankful every time
he steps into that shop,
because it's always
the most incredible advice
anyone could ever ask for.
It's like the God of makeup
handing you the book of rules.
- That's your sketch?
- Go right ahead.
Yeah, let's see the sketch.
What part of this reads
whimsical?
I mean, 'cause right now
it looks--
I gotta be honest.
It looks scary.
Yeah, you've done this
almost, like, skeleton,
horror-type of a mouth.
If you just fill her out more,
your character would be
more whimsical.
Cool.
Thank you, guys.
All right, everybody,
we're heading out,
- but it's looking great.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, guys.
- Bye-bye.
Bye, guys.
So this is not good.
Should we extend, like,
a long line back?
Mr. Westmore
gives us the advice
that maybe if we rounded
the face a little bit more,
it would be more whimsical.
So I start adding little bits
of clay right here.
And that is already helping,
making her look more
like she's smiling,
rather than gaping.
_
Hey, everybody, that's time.
Whoo!
At the end of the day,
I'm starting to feel better
about the sculpt.
I've taken
Mr. Westmore's advice
and made some changes
to the face.
I'm hoping that
this all comes together.
It's day two of our
Mother Goose challenge.
We have 9 1/2 hours.
I'm gonna go take a victory lap,
because we already won
this challenge.
Go, go, go, go.
I need to kick ass
in this mold room today.
I need to get our hoof molded,
our face molded.
I need to get our ears molded,
as well as the creature's
gigantic belly and teats.
So there's a lot of stuff
to do today.
I have to mold Laura's cowl,
the back,
and then the chest.
I want to make sure
that all that's done quickly
so they'll be ready
for foam latex.
I want to fabricate a fiddle
out of L200 foam.
And the cool thing
about this foam
is that you can use a heat gun,
and, as it cools off,
it assumes the shape
of whatever way you've held it.
There we go.
So, mold is ready,
mold is clean,
and I have this great idea.
How about we run the molds
through poly foam,
and then we also run it
in foam latex?
So that way we can have
both options and see
which one is gonna work better
than the other one.
We can maybe make, like,
a little fingernail flat rock
or something like that.
Let's do that.
Instead of sculpting
and molding
arm and leg pieces
for our moon character,
I decided to use latex
and foam.
So I take some spandex material
and cut up little chunks
of foam to replicate Moon rocks.
You pull, and I push.
It's time to open the mold.
_
We can't get the poly foam out.
I cannot believe Lyma
just left.
There's no way to open
this mold by myself.
If I don't have this mold ready,
we're not gonna have a head.
_
So it's day two in the lab,
and my partner just left me
to open this mold by myself.
I don't have time to start
from scratch.
On application day,
there's just no time at all.
_
So Laura comes.
And thank God she's here
with me.
_
I feel so relieved right now.
Where's Lyma?
We have to clean this guy.
All right, you can do it?
Yeah.
Yeah, but this
is not going to work.
No, no, no,
I don't care about that one.
I'm not really concerned
about the poly foam piece.
I'm just concerned
about cleaning the mold
so I can be ready to run it
in foam latex.
_
It's one hour.
I've decided to make
my character a bacon bra
to match her bacon bow.
So I'm "bacon" care of business
in the red room.
_
Mm-hmm, just tinted.
15 minutes!
_
We're ready to run this
in foam latex.
There you go.
And I am just hoping
that this piece
is gonna come out amazing.
That's time, everyone!
Whoo!
I'm hoping application day
is gonna run smooth,
and I am just really excited
that this day is done.
Go, go, go!
Good luck, everyone.
- Do you see our cowl?
- It looks really good.
Yay!
Cool.
Well, I'll start cutting.
So it's application day.
We have four hours in the lab.
And we have a back.
We have a chest.
We have a face.
We have a cowl.
We have four legs.
We have two wrists.
This is gonna go crazy.
Okay.
The cowl looks pretty good.
However, there's a lot
of work ahead.
- It doesn't look that bad.
- No.
We're gonna to start
to fabricate all the arm pieces
and everything that needs
to be glued on.
Yay!
Our models arrive.
And the first thing
that we have to do
is make sure that the bodysuit
fits properly.
It's not too uncomfortable?
Eddie made several other
extra pieces
that all tie together.
So he's working on the rest
of the body
while I'm gluing on the head
and the face.
You, ma'am,
are an absolute wonder.
This little piggy
looks fabulous!
- That all right?
- Sweet!
All right, stand up.
Let me put this on you
and see how this fits.
Cool, it fits you.
- Yeah.
- I'm excited.
Who would've thought?
I am really pleased
with the way
this build has turned out.
I think Roy and I
are on the right track,
and I'm really excited
to show this to the judges
and see what they think.
This is gonna be glued here,
so whenever you're done,
you just pull that arm out,
and you'll have your arm free
the whole day.
Awesome.
The makeup Eric and I
are working on
is different than the rest
of the group.
I think both Eric and I
are a little bit concerned
that we might not exactly hit
the whimsical
on this challenge.
And we'll work on the style.
But it shouldn't be monsterly.
- Yeah.
- That's really about it.
Close your eyes.
As I'm making
the giant pumpkin,
I'm starting to notice
that it's looking boxy.
The last thing I want to do
is detract from this makeup.
_
I decide it's not worth it.
I'm just gonna drop it and start
helping paint the head.
Give me what color you want,
and I'll go ahead
and start basing it out.
Most of my day
is finishing up these legs.
And they're just so big.
I'm a little bit worried.
That's for sure.
The whimsical thing
is gonna end up being a problem.
We'll see what the judges
have to say.
I didn't know if you wanted
to do that
that color or not.
Yeah, I'm gonna do it now.
We put some pink in the ears.
It's a very cartoonish
challenge.
We wanted to really accentuate
the cartoon feel of it.
I mean, he's wearing
a giant violin.
This is not gonna be
a realistic cat.
God, you're so cute.
I can't even handle it.
What do you think about this
coming out of her dress
from behind?
Tate and I are just really
bouncing back and forth ideas
past each other
with everything.
I like that, but pull
the whole thing up higher.
Oh, okay.
And I think it's looking
really great.
If you start moving around,
you'll be a scrambled egg.
That's awesome.
15 minutes, guys!
Coming with legs.
Oh, yeah.
You're amazing.
All right, everybody,
that's time.
Let's go.
- Whoo!
- Oh, man.
- You doing okay?
- Yeah.
We've gotten great feedback
from everybody
about how our sculpture looks
like a crooked guy.
But is it fun?
No.
I'm not sure that
what we've accomplished
is what the judges
are looking for
for this challenge.
But it's up to the judges
at this point.
Coming up...
I'll try to make it work.
Did hell freeze over?
There's some totally
arbitrary surfacing.
- Awesome stuff, guys.
- It doesn't read whimsical.
We get to last looks.
We have one hour left.
We still have a lot
of painting to do.
We also need to apply
a whole bunch of little pieces.
I'll try to make it work.
I do the beauty makeup
around the eyes
and around the mouth.
And Alana's spackling some colors.
We're looking so good.
15 minutes, everybody.
15 minutes.
Time is ticking,
and Rick is trying
to wrangle together
the wardrobe.
We have this coat
on our character,
but we don't want it to cover up
all the work we did.
That is a very
awkward-fitting coat.
_
Did hell freeze over?
Because we're finished
before they call time.
That's time!
Time's up, everybody.
We did it.
I think there's a lot
of really great makeups
in the room,
but it's really stressful
for everybody
because there's two people
going home.
And none of us ever know
what the judges are gonna like
or not like.
Welcome to theFace Off
reveal stage.
Tonight two of you
will be eliminated.
But first, let's say hello
to our judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
Hi, everyone.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist Ve Neill.
Good evening.
- Hey, Ve.
- Hi, Ve.
Creature and concept designer
Neville Page.
Hello.
Hey, Neville.
This week,
your spotlight challenge
was to create an original,
whimsical character
inspired by a Mother Goose
Nursery Rhyme.
So let's take a look.
She looks like a supermodel
in a runway show,
just with an egg on her head.
She is rocking out
the snobby swine.
And it looks awesome.
The only time inFace Offhistory
where an actor could get away
with playing with himself
on stage.
He's literally playing
the strings with his tail bow.
Turned out exactly the way
we drew him.
Eric and I are happy
with our makeup.
Whimsical or not,
we're proud of what we've done.
I'm loving my spider.
He's evoking a sense
of longing.
I think he's adorable.
This is my greatest moment
onFace Off.
I've never felt so much pride.
It is what we wanted to make.
It looks cool.
Everything from the tiny,
little craters on her face
and the metallics
on her costume.
We're really pleased.
Judges, why don't you take
a closer look?
It's a pretty well-balanced
paint job.
There's a good beauty makeup
on top of it.
- Where is the edge?
- A pretty good blend, though.
I don't know.
The judges come close,
and they start picking at it
and checking the eggshells
and all that,
and I'm just praying
that those things stay on.
That cracks me up.
It's so cool.
Hold me.
Around the eyes is really good.
- It is.
- Yeah.
It looks really good.
Do you have any singles?
Do you have any singles.
There's some
beautiful forms happening
with the ears flowing
out of the head.
This is sort of like a cartoon.
Yeah.
Can you just turn?
I'm looking at this arm.
And there's totally
arbitrary surfacing
that I just don't understand.
The shapes of the bones
are not even wrong
in a cartoony way.
- Yeah.
- They're just completely wrong.
Our character is definitely
the least whimsical.
But there's a small chance
they'll love it.
I just want to survive.
We want to know what you think
of tonight's transformations.
So tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
- The scapula comes down.
- That bothers me as well.
The shapes of the bones,
they're not even wrong
in a cartoony way.
- Yeah.
- They're just completely wrong.
I'm very, very nervous.
This is a double elimination
this week and
that's what got me eliminated
on season four,
and I don't want to go home.
_
He's got to like
that sculpture.
_
I think they're smiling.
Nice paint job, guys.
There are a ton of awesome
sculptural decisions
in that head.
- Yeah.
- Oh, Jesus, yeah.
_
And let's see the other side.
The stuff with the pumpkin
seeds hanging off of it's great.
Hey.
She's the girl in the Moon.
Let's have you open your mouth.
Oh, this is great.
Look, she can actually move
her face really well.
My only complaint is that it
doesn't quite look
like the Moon's surface.
I agree.
Okay, the judges have scored
your creations.
Roy, RJ...
Eddie, and Scott...
Congratulations, you are safe
and can head
back to the makeup room.
God, that makes me so nervous.
And the rest of you
were the best
and the worst of the week.
The judges will now speak
with each of you
to lean more about your work.
Alana and Laney,
you're up first.
Start telling me
about this work.
Our poem was The Five Pigs.
Alana did the face,
and I did the chest.
Alana made the bow
out of silicone.
- Silicone.
- And the rest is foam latex.
The whimsy is very apparent,
and it's a picture
of porcine perfection.
- Thank you.
- The chest and face
managed to look like
they were done
by the same person.
Awesome stuff, guys.
She's very sweet, I got to say.
It's very clever
with her belly.
And we even addressed the fact
that she has hooves.
Great choice of wardrobe.
And her chest gives a whole new
meaning to pulled pork.
Oh, yes.
This little piggy sizzles.
But I think the white wig
confused me a touch.
It felt a little poodle-like.
But you did a good job
maintaining
her swine-like anatomy.
She is a beaut.
Thank you so much, guys.
- Thank you.
- You can step down.
Frank and Laura, you're next.
So tell us about your creation.
We had "Little Miss Muffet."
We decided to give the spider
his story
from his point of view.
I would have liked
to have seen something
that brought Miss Muffet
into this
and not just a spider
by itself.
The fact that your whimsy
has to do
with your spider coloration
I think was a poor choice.
It doesn't read whimsical.
It reads "A man and a spider
put together."
I just don't think
it suits the challenge.
I think you got lost
on trying to blow us away
with a really big makeup
this week
and missed the fantastical
and the whimsical.
Also, the paint needs
so much more detail,
so much more time.
It just doesn't play well.
Thank you.
If you'd please step back.
Thanks, buddy.
Lyma and Adolfo.
Tell us what the concept is
behind the story.
She's kind of, like,
a reincarnation
of Humpty Dumpty.
A Lady Gaga reincarnation.
Like a female and stronger
version of Humpty.
Who did what?
I sculpted the cowl,
the chest piece,
and I did the arm pieces,
and I painted the base
of the body.
And Lyma sculpted the face,
did all the plastic part of it,
and she did
all the airbrush work.
This is a beautiful rendition
of Humpty Dumpty.
I like that you got
beauty makeup
into the makeup as well.
I'm really pleased
with what you've done.
Thank you very much.
I'm very pleased with this.
It's very stylized.
I will say, Lyma,
do not just keep holding
stencils up
and giving me the same pattern
all over the body.
Other than that,
I feel like we could see this
in a film right now.
Well done.
Thank you so much.
If you'd please step back.
Rick and Eric,
please come forward.
All right, guys,
go ahead and tell me
about your design ideas.
Well, we drew
the crooked sixpence.
It describes the crooked man
who walked a crooked mile.
He was a handsome man,
and as he started to deform,
he became rejected by society.
Rick sculpted
the back and chest.
He also blocked out this arm
and this arm piece.
I sculpted the face entirely.
My big problem with it
is the idea.
It's neither completely real
or completely fantastical.
- Right.
- Also, the fact that his arm
is sort of just jammed
on the back of him,
very abrupt.
It doesn't look like his arm
to me.
It looks like an extra arm.
That's bad.
You know, when I looked
at this guy,
I didn't see a crooked man.
I saw a twisted man.
If you would've done him
really angular crooked,
then that would've been
whimsical.
I just think you guys missed
the mark on this totally.
Right.
Thank you.
You can step down.
Thanks, boy.
Tate and Miranda,
please step forward.
Okay, tell us
about your Nursery Rhyme
and who was responsible
for which parts
of your character, please.
We had "Peter, Peter,
the pumpkin eater".
Tate sketched out the design
of the face first,
and I blocked out the cowl
and the face
and did a lot of the sculpting.
Tate did the hands
and the body,
and I did the head.
I think you knocked it
out of the park.
This is really
a fantastic character.
Yay.
I mean, every little detail
on this
reads whimsy and fantastical.
And I think you did
a great job.
The decision-making
in the sculpture on the face,
where the smile happens
through wrinkle texture,
and it's not carved out,
it looks organic.
It looks like a pumpkin.
It's really impressive, guys.
Well done.
Thank you so much.
If you'd please step back.
Thank you, guys.
If you'd please head
back to the makeup room
while the judges make
their decisions.
All right, judges,
so why don't we start
with some of your
favorite looks tonight?
How about Alana and Laney's
character?
This definitely was high
on the whimsy mark for me.
Mm-hmm.
If it was just a pig makeup,
it wouldn't have been
whimsical.
It's the wig and the bow
and Alana's sense of humor
coming through.
And from a makeup standpoint,
it was some of the best work
that I've seen Alana do.
Let's talk about Adolfo
and Lyma's character.
I loved that makeup.
I loved the whole head treatment
with the cracked egg...
- Yeah.
- ...and all the different layers.
I liked that they added
the couture element,
that they made it
a little runway.
- Yeah.
That was kind of cool.
Let's move on
to Tate
and Miranda's character.
The decisions in the sculpting
and the paint job
are so intelligent.
Miranda's sculpting's
beautiful.
Beautifully painted.
A head-to-toe
complete makeup.
The textures,
everything was weathered
to the same level.
Which is extremely impressive.
All right, so why don't we talk
about the makeups
that you didn't like as much?
Let's start
with Frank and Laura.
I felt that the fact
that it was just a "spider man"
wasn't very inventive.
And I think they're definitely
much more creative than that.
Why didn't they do something
where part of it was
Miss Muffet
and part of it was the spider
and make it real whimsical
and fairytale-like?
Okay, let's move on
to Rick and Eric.
It wasn't whimsical.
It was freaky and scary.
The fact that the arm was just
jammed on the back,
it killed me.
And when you get
up into the face area,
you're struggling with paint
and sculpture.
All right, judges,
have you made your decisions?
- Yeah.
- Yes, we have.
Let's bring them back out.
So, Glenn, tell us
about the top teams.
Alana and Laney,
your pig was a very impressive
character, head to toe.
We really appreciate
the amount of thought and work
that went into this makeup.
Tate and Miranda,
this was a killer design
and a beautifully executed
makeup.
We absolutely loved
the sculpture, the paint,
and the overall harmony
of the piece.
Lyma and Adolfo,
tonight was a huge step forward
for both of you,
and we can easily imagine
your egg creation
in a feature film.
Okay, which team came out
on top?
The top team tonight is...
Okay, which team came out
on top?
The top team tonight is...
Tate and Miranda.
Yeah, girl.
Your pumpkin was one
of the best makeups
we've ever seen on the show,
truly a great collaboration.
- Well done.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Tate and Miranda, great job.
But as you know,
we can only have one winner.
Glenn?
Our winner tonight is...
Miranda.
- Yeah.
- Get it, girl.
It's a great makeup,
and though Tate's design
was very strong,
we absolutely loved the sculpt
and paint you applied.
So great job.
Well done.
- Thank you.
- Thank you guys so much.
It was such a team effort.
But it feels great to win,
and I feel so honored.
Tate and Miranda,
congratulations.
You, Alana, Laney,
Adolfo, Lyma,
you're all safe and can head
back to the makeup room.
Unfortunately, that means
the rest of you
are on the bottom this week,
and two of you
will be going home.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Rick and Eric,
your character was
anatomically incorrect
and did not fulfill
the whimsical aspect
of this challenge.
Frank and Laura,
your spider creature lacked
detail in its paint,
and your concept also failed
to satisfy the criteria
of this challenge.
So who is the first person
going home tonight?
The first person going home
tonight is...
Rick.
We thought
that you were missing
some basic anatomy
in your work tonight,
and we really questioned
the design choices
that you made.
Rick, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
It's really been great having
you here with us.
Thank you.
I saw some really cool stuff
from you.
Hold your head high,
and good luck in the future.
Thank you, sir.
Rick, if you'd please head
back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
I'm not ready to go home,
but there's no regrets.
Being a part of this competition
has been a dream come true.
It's really pushed me
as an artist.
And I'll take all those things
home with me
as well as the relationships
that I've formed.
Glenn, who is the second person
leaving us tonight?
The second person going home
tonight is...
Eric.
We felt that
your facial sculpture
simply did not embrace
the crooked nature
of our challenge tonight.
It just wasn't taken
far enough.
Thank you guys so much
for this opportunity.
Eric, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
That means, Frank, Laura,
you are safe this week.
If you'd please head
back to the makeup room.
Eric, this was
a really tough week.
There were so many great
makeups.
And you should be proud
of everything that you've done
here with us.
Thank you very much, Ve.
Eric, it's really been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head
back to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
- Thank you, guys.
- Thank you.
Good luck, Eric.
I'm going home now,
but there's a lot
to be proud of.
This has all very much been
a way to push myself.
- I'm going home, guys.
- No!
I'm glad I came back.
I was very blessed to have been
a part of Face Off.
I have this extended family
of artists because of it.
- Bring it in, brother.
- Hey, buddy.
We're going together, man.
I'm very proud of what I've been
able to accomplish.
I can only benefit
from having been here.
There is a whole career
out there for me.
And I know that I have a lot
to offer this industry.
I'm definitely not giving up.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net