Previously on Face Off...
Tate's slothful sinner
brought him to victory...
That means a lot.
And veteran Frank
was sent home.
Now, six artists remain,
and tonight, they'll be
creating comedic poltergeists.
Ah, that's fun.
Comedy is not easy.
This is a weird challenge.
But this challenge
is no laughing matter.
- Cancer?
- Yeah.
Funny and scary
is a very difficult balance.
I might be going home
this week.
This is terrible.
I'm starting
to have a panic attack.
If I don't have a wig, my whole
character will be ruined.
Ugh.
- It works.
- I'm very confused.
That's a problem,
when you can't tell me that.
In the end,
one will win a VIP trip
from Kryolan
Professional Makeup
to one of their
85 international locations,
a 2013 Fiat 500,
and $100,000.
Who will be the next great name
in movie magic?
Only one will win Face Off.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
It's kind of nice and relaxing
after the night
I had last night.
That was awful.
How do you feel about that?
Well, I didn't want
to be there again, you know?
Then, all of a sudden, I was.
I don't know if I was just
not there mentally,
but in the last challenge,
I was in bottom looks.
I think I had been so worried
about pleasing the judges
that I'm not being true
to myself.
I'm gonna go back
to what I like doing.
Same here.
Yup.
Right with you.
From here on out,
you're gonna see big.
You're gonna see fabrication.
This is gonna be
a whole new ballgame for me.
- Oh!
- Ohh.
So we walk into the lab,
and there's lightning.
There's smoke.
- Oh, creepy.
- Ohh.
This is scary.
And there's Patrick Tatopoulos.
Hey, guys.
- Hey, McKenzie.
- Hey.
I'm sure you all know
who this is.
Please welcome
today's guest judge,
our very own
Patrick Tatopoulos.
Thank you.
I'm so happy to be back, guys.
It's really good
to see Patrick again.
He's just a fantastic designer.
I have the utmost respect
for Patrick's work.
All right, now...
today's challenge is based
on a dark and mysterious figure
whose face has never been seen.
The Grim Reaper.
Oh, no.
It's really cool.
This entire line of Grim Reapers
start walking in.
They're all cloaked.
You can't see their faces.
I'm really excited about this.
Oh, hell, yeah.
Your foundation challenge
is to create your own version
of the Grim Reaper,
so that we can finally see
what lies beneath that hood.
- Ooh.
- Awesome.
Now, Patrick,
with a character as iconic
as the Grim Reaper,
how can the artists
create something original?
Just have to try
to stay very universal.
It's a character
that everybody knows.
You have to find a way to make
it relatable for everyone.
Now, the winner of today's
foundation challenge
will earn immunity and cannot
be eliminated this week.
All right, your models
have been randomly assigned,
and you have two hours
to complete your makeups.
Good luck,
because your time starts now.
Good luck.
Ever had a bald cap put on?
- Yeah.
- All right.
You have such nice hair.
I really want to keep
my Grim Reaper very classic.
I want his face to be
crackly and gross,
and I want
to sprinkle blood on him,
like he's just taken somebody.
I'm gonna try
some stuff on you.
I find this snakeskin
prosthetic.
I've always been
creeped out by snakes,
so maybe I can play into
one of my own kind of fears.
I just want to try to do
a new take on a skull.
I've actually applied
seven prosthetics,
but they're not being used
the way that
they should be used.
This is a brow piece.
These are old-age folds,
and he just comes up and points,
and he's like,
"You. You're dead.
Let's go."
I'm gonna make this
more Hades than a skeleton.
I want it to feel old and wise.
Big beard, big eyes,
so he has this penetrating
sort of stare.
I think most people are gonna
go with a skull type of look,
so I want to have sections
that are completely black.
I also want to cover his mouth.
You don't want to hear death
sneaking up on you,
so he can't speak.
You have five minutes left!
That's it, everybody!
Time's up!
Brushes down.
- Hello, Tate.
- Hi, Tate.
Tell us about your Grim Reaper.
Well, I just wanted to do
something dry and cracked.
Could you move a little bit?
See, that's what's cool,
because it's unexpected
it's gonna move.
It's fantastic.
Very cool piece.
Mine was kind of inspired
by the look
that Rob Zombie
plays with on stage.
What you created for the skin
is really effective
and very strong.
I wish you did something else
with the-- the mouth.
- What you put-- you know--
- Yeah, I was out of time.
I like the idea,
is to bringing black in it
to the part of the face
that are gone.
It's cool.
It's great.
And the mouth,
that was very daring...
...and it came out great.
My Grim Reaper takes advantage
of people's fears.
I like what she's done
with the nose,
and the delicacy
of how tiny the scales are.
Very, very delicate,
and very real.
I figured the Grim Reaper
doesn't need a voice,
so just get rid of the mouth.
Oh, that's actually
really effective
because it looks like
a sculpted piece, seriously.
You blended them together
very well.
I decided to fuse
human anatomy with roots
and things
you'd see underground.
Right. The way you split
the nose in half,
it's like the roots are forcing
their way through the face.
Very original.
Thank you.
All right, Patrick,
which artists
created your favorite looks
today?
You guys really answered
the challenge very, very well.
Laura, I really was very,
very impressed
with the use
of light and shadows.
- It was very, very effective.
- Thank you.
And Tate, your texture
on the skin was super effective.
It felt dead,
yet could come alive,
and I thought
that was a very big asset.
Great.
Thank you.
All right, who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner
of this challenge is...
Laura.
Congratulations.
Laura, you did something
very special with your makeup.
You used generic appliances,
put them together
in such a great way.
They felt like they
were one piece of sculpture.
Thank you, guys.
Laura, as the winner
of this foundation challenge,
you have earned immunity
and cannot be eliminated
this week.
A shower of relief
goes over me.
Finally, to have immunity,
is just a treat.
All right, everybody,
I will see you guys tomorrow
for your next
spotlight challenge.
Bye.
Big day!
It's really cool to be walking
in the middle of Hollywood.
We see a big marquee
for the Laugh Factory,
and it says "Face Off"
all over the building.
So that's amazing.
This place is historic.
We walk in,
and there's McKenzie with Ve,
so I guess this is where
we're gonna get
our next spotlight challenge,
but I don't understand
what the Laugh Factory
has to do with makeup.
Welcome to the world-famous
Laugh Factory
on the Sunset Strip.
This renowned venue
opened in 1979
with a legendary performance
by Richard Pryor.
Since then,
it has continued to host
the biggest names in comedy,
including Steve Martin,
Eddie Murphy, and Louis CK,
just to name a few.
This club isn't only
known for laughs.
It's also one of Hollywood's
most haunted locations.
In fact, the office upstairs
used to belong
to the comedy legend
Groucho Marx,
and visitors say
that they can still
see him walking around
up there.
Now, while ghosts
are most commonly seen
in horror movies
and paranormal shows,
films like Beetlejuice
made them a source of comedy,
so with that in mind,
your spotlight challenge
is to create
an original ghost character
that is both scary and funny.
Ah, that's fun.
Comedy is not easy, and--
I don't know.
A scary, funny, graphical--
this is a weird challenge.
Lucky for you guys, we have
Ms. Ve with us here today.
Now, as you know, she won
an Oscar for the iconic makeup
she did on Michael Keaton
in Beetlejuice.
Ve, you expertly tread
that fine line
between being both funny
and scary.
How did you find
that perfect blend?
I made a real good contrast
with his eyes and his hair,
put some moss growing on him
like he crawled out
from underneath a rock,
and that took it
out of the ordinary
and gave it that comedic edge
that we were looking for.
The light-hearted
creepy guy.
So what are you gonna
be looking for
in their final makeups
on the reveal stage?
I'm gonna be looking for
something that's really creepy
and scary, but make him
bitchin' and fun, guys.
Go have a blast.
That's awesome.
Thank you, Ve.
All right, guys.
I want you to take advantage
of this atmosphere here
for some design inspiration.
When you're finished,
you can head back to the lab
and get started.
Good luck!
Bye.
I love the idea of Vaudeville,
so my concept is two little
people who used to perform
as clowns in Vaudeville,
would go piggy-back
with a trench coat.
One night, one of 'em's drunk,
and they get killed
stepping into traffic
and gettin' hit by a street car.
So now they have
to spend eternity
stacked on top of each other.
I'm kind of thinking
to do an 18th century duchess
who constantly nags her husband
and spends all his money,
so he has her beheaded,
and then she comes back
to exact her revenge on him
so she can constantly
berate him
for the rest
of their afterlife.
My concept
is "Bone-Cap Bill."
He's a Wild West showman
whose show was raided
by a tribe of Apaches,
and he was shot up
with arrows and scalped.
He might be a host
of a children's television show
in the netherworld.
My concept is that
he's a nerdy scientist
who got blown up
in his experiment
and doesn't even know
he's dead.
He's very fumbling
and he's very physical comedy.
All right, guys.
Let's head back to the lab.
We get to the lab
and pick our models,
and we have six hours today.
Today, it's really important
that I get the lower section,
the first body, done,
and the legs of the top body.
It's really hard to sculpt
something horizontally
that should be upright.
For this thing to work,
all the proportions
have to be right,
so I keep standing over it,
making sure that everything
is proportionally correct.
So is it a doctor
or is it a scientist?
Well, he's, like, a doctor
who's working on a cure.
A cure for what?
- Cancer.
- Cancer?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Something
that's funny and scary
is a very difficult balance.
I'm just not excited
about my concept.
I'm still developing the story.
I'm just gonna try my best
to make this work
'cause I feel that,
this far in the competition,
it's important to take risks.
My character
is "Electro-Cute."
She was electrocuted
during a music festival
on the Sunset Strip, and now
she roams the Sunset Strip
and tries to take over the stage
from all the bands playing.
I'm sculpting an amplifier,
and I want it to look
like it was fused
into her chest.
So I find little
plastic bottle caps
to look like
the On and Off buttons.
I think it'll look pretty cool
when it's all pulled together.
So this character is going
to have a full chest piece,
a facial piece,
and two ear prosthetics.
There's so much involved
with just the chest sculpt
that I get straight to work
on that.
I'm blocking out the cowl
and the face,
and, about three hours in,
I start questioning my concept.
I feel like
this doctor character
doesn't really fulfill
the funny and scary
parameters of the challenge.
That is huge,
because it's arguably
the most important part
of a concept, but I'm worried
that I'm gonna have
to start over from scratch.
On the other hand,
if I move forward
with the concept I have now,
they're definitely
gonna send me home.
I don't have a choice.
I have to make a change.
Coming up...
Yeah. Yeah.
Exactly like that.
This is terrible.
I'm starting
to have a panic attack.
Ugh!
It doesn't look funny.
It just looks weird.
It's quite genius.
This doesn't satisfy
the challenge.
So it's day one
of our challenge,
and we have to create
a scary but funny ghost.
The character
I'm creating right now
doesn't really fulfill that,
so I realize that I have
to change my concept.
It's rough starting
a new design three hours in,
but I think this makeup
will be more successful
if I change it.
I come up with another concept,
and it's about
a '20s baseball player
who has a raging temper,
and he throws his baseball bat,
and it comes back,
hits him in the head,
and kills him.
I feel like this concept
is more comedic.
Although
I'm three hours behind,
I know this
was the right decision.
Hey, guys!
We're here for a walkthrough.
- Hey.
- Hey, Tate.
- Tell us about your concept.
- Wow.
He was a Wild West performer
that was attacked
by a tribe of Apaches,
and now he's a children's
television show
for the spirits of dead kids.
Oh, that's hysterical.
I was thinking about
making the character grayscale.
Do you think that I should
put in some yellows and greens?
- I do. I do.
- Yeah?
And even to the point
of maybe a little dust on him...
- Yeah, okay.
- ...because it's the Wild West.
He hasn't had a bath
for a long time.
I like that.
My girl's gonna be called
"Electro-Cute,"
and she was playing an outdoor
festival with her band...
- She's so cute.
- ...and she got electrocuted
when it started to rain.
I was thinking of having
white lightning bolt patterns
all over her body.
It's almost gonna read
like a large blood vein
as opposed to a lightning bolt.
It could be a blood vein,
maybe around the body
coming down.
- Just not too many.
- Yeah. Don't overdo it.
With the face,
I'm exaggerating the chin and--
Now, you know something?
To make it a little bit
more comedic,
you might add a little bit more
under the chin there.
- Really go for the gusto?
- Yeah.
So, my concept
is this cartoon-style ghost
with a baseball bat
wedged in his head.
What is the purpose
of the chin?
That was just
an aesthetic choice
to balance the top of the cowl.
I could see the judges saying,
"What is it? Tell me."
And you're gonna
have to come up with a story.
- They're Vaudeville performers.
- Okay.
They act during
the intermissions in Vaudeville.
- Okay.
- I'm just trying to get the--
the right expression
on the face.
This man looks like
he's screaming bloody murder.
I almost like
your sketch better,
- where he had a big stogie...
- Yeah.
...hanging out of his mouth
as opposed to...
All right, everybody.
We're heading out,
but it's looking good.
- Thanks, guys.
- Have a good one.
Mr. Westmore suggested
I close the mouth.
I got to find something
to make a cigar out of.
After I make a little quick
cigar and pop it in there,
I see that it's a lot funnier
with the mouth closed.
So I finished sculpting
the chest
and head straight
into the mold room.
And the goal is to get the chest
piece molded and ready for foam.
Now, hopefully, if I can
get the chest out by today,
I can pre-paint it tomorrow,
so that's the goal.
The chest is priority.
But there's gonna be
a baseball bat,
like, wedged in his head.
I can't use a real bat,
obviously,
because that would be
too heavy,
so I'm using a tube of foam
and carving the shape of a bat
with a belt sander.
I'm also sculpting a divot
in the cowl
where the bat
hits him in the head
to keep it in place.
I'll attach velcro patches
to both the bat and the cowl.
Whoa!
You made this?
Yeah. I mean,
it's kind of rough, but--
- That's so good.
- Thanks.
One of the things that
I am a little confused about
is how the hell
I'm gonna make this head
that I have
to have her carrying.
I see that all the wigs
have these styrofoam heads
that they're on top of,
and I'm like,
"Maybe I can
just use one of these
and get away with that."
I start stippling latex
all over it,
and then I start gluing these
pre-made prosthetics onto it,
and I find a nose
that's very similar to the nose
that I'm sculpting
on my female character.
I think that I can make this
work well enough
for what I need it to be.
I like the nose.
- It goes with your, uh--
- Her nose?
Goes with her nose, yeah.
At the end of day one,
I get my chest piece molded
in time to bake overnight
for foam.
That's time, everybody.
I'm all ready
to paint tomorrow,
and I'm feeling really good.
It's day two,
and we have 9 1/2 hours
in the lab today,
and the first thing I do
is check out my bodysuit.
Hey.
Oh, my God.
That is so amazing.
That's so fantastic.
Roy, put it on.
Please?
I got to get stuff made
right now.
All right.
Today, I really have
to finish sculpting the face,
and then I got
to sculpt the arms.
Day two in the lab.
I have to get started
on the broomstick pony.
The skull is a pretty
involved process.
I think maybe
I'll carve some rigid foam
to make the jaw piece,
and then hollow it out
to make the skull.
That's so cool.
I'm going to paint the skull
realistically.
I want the eyes to glow,
so I figure out how to get eyes
in there and mount them,
and then I make a rigging
where my model
can actually pull a trigger
and make the mouth move.
And I just got to make the bridle
and the saddle
and all that other stuff.
I'm about
an hour and a half in,
so I head over to the wet room
and get ready for molding.
I have plenty of time
to knock these two pieces out.
I feel like I'm back on track.
I'm feeling pretty good.
You got your sculpts done
pretty fast, Eddie.
Yeah, not too bad
for starting over.
For my character, I really
want to create my own wig
for her to make her hair
stick straight up
as if she was electrocuted,
but it's really hard
and taking a lot longer
than I thought.
I've tried multiple ways,
but it's so messy and sticky.
It's sticking to my hand,
and then it sticks to the table.
It sticks to my brush,
and it's just so frustrating.
Ugh!
I'm starting to have
a panic attack.
If I don't have a wig, my whole
character will be ruined.
So it's day two
of our funny ghost challenge,
and I can't get this wig
to come out the way
I want it to look.
Ugh!
I have to get my wig done.
If I don't have a wig,
my whole concept will be ruined
because the judges
won't be able to see
that she's been electrocuted.
This is so hard.
Laney's having
a really hard time.
I know all of us guys
promised to stop helping people,
but I can see that look
on her face
and I feel really bad.
Does it look bad?
Well, it doesn't look done.
I'm in a good place
with my stuff,
so I jump over and help her.
This is terrible.
- It's not doing what you want?
- No.
_
You're gonna have to put
some Gafquat here, Gafquat here.
Then you can, like,
roll up these tips into,
like, points and stuff.
I give her a couple ideas
with Gafquat.
It's a very heat-sensitive
hair adhesive,
so if you just hit it
with a hair dryer,
you can pull it right up.
Okay, that's smart.
So that stuff
worked pretty good?
- Yeah.
- Good.
It makes it look so much nicer.
I wish I'd used this
the entire time.
After the science experiment
explosion,
my mad scientist is scratched up
and really burnt,
and I think it'll be funny
to have his ear
kind of falling off,
and I'm gonna make it
out of silicone.
This blue piece
is the silicone mold
that was made
from my model's life cast.
I'm pouring a platinum cure
silicone in,
and when it hardens,
I should be able to get an ear.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my--
I see Roy in the two-part
little person costume.
That thing is freakin' me out,
and Roy is smiling on top of it.
"Hee-hee-hee,"
like, giggling like a kid.
Eeeeh!
That's terrifying.
That's your greatest thing
you've ever created.
Wah!
Roy is pulling it off
again, man.
He's doing an amazing, complex,
crazy thing,
and it looks great.
Bye, guys!
Seeing Roy
create two characters
is making me question how much
I'm doing this challenge.
His concept is very strong,
and it's gonna take a lot
for me to match that.
It's almost the end of the day,
and I'm really stressed out.
I spent so much time
working on the wig,
and now I'm really behind
with everything else.
Time's up!
Let's go home.
I'm really worried
about tomorrow.
There's so much to get done,
and I don't know if I'll
have time to finish everything.
It's the beginning
of application day,
and we only have four hours
in the lab.
When I get
to my prosthetic--
What the fuck is that?
The entire thing
has these big air pockets
between the foam latex
and the skin.
But if I try to glue it,
my whole detail layer
will be eliminated,
and that would be really bad,
because that's what I spent
all the time sculpting.
So I'm gonna have to spend
quite a bit of time
patching this.
Because it took me
a lot longer than I wanted
to finish my wig,
I got really behind.
So I immediately
just start getting
all my stuff ready
before the models get here.
- What's up? Yeah.
- What's up?
You're gonna be midgets today.
She's a rocker girl
that got electrocuted.
Just let me know
wherever it does not feel good.
My first priority
is making sure
that the details on the face
are solid.
Even though I have immunity,
I am really hoping
to impress the judges
because I want
to win this challenge,
and I think
I might have a chance.
The judges are gonna be
looking for a funny ghost.
And you want to close it,
like, all the way.
And a lot of that's gonna depend
on my model's performance.
Walk this way.
And I keep telling her,
it's like,
"Try and make it sell."
No, a little--
little bit shorter--
little bit shorter steps, yeah.
Just that
little, bitty short step.
If she doesn't pull it off,
I'll probably be going home,
no matter how cool it looks.
That-- that's it.
That's the walk right there.
That's the walk.
I'm painting these elongated
forms around the eyes,
and when I take a step back
from my piece,
I notice that they seem
a little awkward,
but I'm just gonna do my best
to make what I sculpted work
and spend more time
improving this paint job.
One hour left, guys.
One hour.
Today, everything
is going ridiculously well.
The face piece fits him great,
it emotes.
He can move his mouth, nose--
everything works,
from the makeup
to the broomstick pony.
Yeah. Yeah.
Exactly like that.
Hopefully,
things keep going well.
12 minutes!
It's almost
the end of application,
and my model's barely painted
and the hands aren't finished.
There's gonna be a lot to paint
in last looks.
That's time, everybody!
Time.
Let's get out of here.
I don't know if I can
finish painting
the entire piece in an hour.
I really think
I could be going home.
Coming up...
Come on, airbrush!
I have a feeling
I might be in trouble.
I think he's terrific.
That's not a good place to be
this week.
What have you done?
Go, go, go.
Good luck, guys.
It's last looks,
so we have one more hour.
Sit down right here.
We have a lot to do.
I need to paint the highlights
and shadows
as quickly as possible,
'cause she's just pink.
Let me see your hand.
Okay.
Can you do this?
Having to start over
was really rough for me.
Close your eyes.
Now I'm worried
this is not gonna read
as the classic, cartoon-style
ghost character.
Anybody have
any black gaff tape?
Yup.
Right over here.
I'm probably
in the best position
I've been in this season.
Now all I got to do
is just touch up the eyes
and her mouth,
and attach the hands
to the trench coat.
Oh, my God.
My airbrush starts acting up,
and I don't have time
to clean it,
and that's what I was trying
to do all my detail with.
Come on, airbrush!
And it's just taking longer
than I expected,
and I'm not getting
the paint I want.
Ugh!
Stop clogging, please.
Ten minutes!
Here.
Come here.
Time's up, everybody!
Whoo!
Looking across the room,
I'm seeing a lot
of amazing makeups.
I think I might
be in trouble this week.
Welcome to the Face Off
reveal stage.
Tonight, one of you
will be eliminated.
Say hello
to our talented judges.
Owner of Optic Nerve Makeup
Effects Studio, Glenn Hetrick.
- Good evening, guys.
- Hey.
Three-time Oscar-winning
makeup artist, Ve Neill.
Hi, everybody.
- Hey, Ve.
- Hi.
Creature and concept designer,
Neville Page.
- Hi, guys.
- Hey, Neville.
This week,
your spotlight challenge
was to create
an original ghost character
that was both scary and funny.
So let's take a look
at your ghosts
while the audience at home
tweets about their favorites
using #FaceOff.
First up, Laura's creation.
I'm proud of this character.
He looks like he belongs in
a world where ghosts are funny.
I just can't stop laughin'
at it.
It's just so funny.
And you can't
send somebody home
that puts a smile on your face.
From afar,
I'm not happy with it.
If I were to do it again,
I would have made the face
more human-like.
I'm proud of this character,
and I'm especially proud
of the amount of work
I pulled off.
I think I definitely nailed
what was asked of me
for the challenge.
I think she looks more silly
than she does funny,
but at least
it's pulled together.
I'm just hoping
to get by this week.
The lightning bolts aren't
as bright as I want them to be.
Hopefully, when the judges
take their closer looks,
they'll be able to see,
but for me,
I absolutely love
what I've created.
Judges, why don't you
go ahead and get up close
to the ghosts?
It's very ghost-like
and ethereal.
I like the way she got
a little bit of it up there.
- That's cool.
- Can you look that way, please?
'Cause there's
a nice little slit ear.
Ooh, look at that.
- That's a lot of work.
- Yeah.
He shouldn't have wasted time
putting prosthetics
on her face.
No, I don't get it.
Although it does at least
make her look dead-ish.
Yeah.
All right.
What the heck?
Turn, so we can check out
the back.
What's with the artichoke head?
I don't get it.
Like, why is that "Ghost"?
- Turn this way.
- Is it, like, an ethereal form?
The hat shape
stuck with his head?
I see Glenn doing this,
and that is never a good sign.
I could be on bottom this week.
Oh, they're little worms.
Yeah.
I love the hair.
- This is so nice.
- That is cool.
And it's stayin' on
really good.
Thank you.
- Who is he?
- Oh, that's my husband.
- Nice.
- Hmm.
This could have benefitted
from some more color in here.
_
It's just so monotone.
I don't like anything
about my makeup this week.
I just hope I'm not going home
for this one.
Who made
your favorite ghost tonight?
Tell us on Twitter
using #FaceOff.
It's just so monotone.
***
I did the best I could
with this challenge,
but I'm just not a fan
of this character,
and I'm probably
gonna be in trouble.
She's pretty cool.
I just don't like
this all-gray look.
It's these hard form choices.
- Yeah.
- Can you open your mouth?
Thank you so much.
Okay.
All right.
Thank you.
The judges
have scored your creations,
so let's find out
what they thought.
Miranda...
Tate...
Congratulations,
you are both safe
and can head back
to the makeup room.
- Thank you, guys.
- Thanks, guys.
Thank you.
The rest of you
were the best and the worst.
Now, the judges would
like to speak with each of you
to learn more about your work.
Laura, please step up.
Laura, tell us
about your concept this week.
I decided on mad scientist,
because he could be
in an explosion
and he doesn't know he's dead.
And once he figures out
he's dead,
then he'll finally cross over.
I think it's superb.
Your decision making this week
was spot-on.
The edges are beautiful,
as they always are,
and it feels like
something from films
like the Frighteners
or the Beetlejuice world.
- It's quite well done.
- Thank you.
You did a massive amount
of work yet again.
You treated his entire body,
and I love the little nurnies
and stuff
you stretched all over.
Once again, a beautiful makeup.
- Thank you.
- It's a good piece of work.
It really is, and I like
the big, bushy eyebrows
and his frazzled hair.
He feels like a mad scientist.
I just wish it was funnier.
I agree.
Thank you.
Laura, please step back.
Eddie.
Eddie, tell us
about your concept
for your ghost this week.
My character
was a baseball player
with a raging temper,
and one game, he decided
to throw his bat
at the opposing team's dugout,
and it came back
and knocked him on the head,
and that's how he passed away.
It doesn't look funny.
It just looks weird.
I'm very confused.
I don't understand this weird,
kiss-like apertures
around his eyes,
and the pointed chin,
and the artichoke head.
Why did you go that route?
Well, that was more
of an aesthetic choice,
just to make it kind of
on the cartoony-side.
I think you missed
the funny part of it.
For me, if this guy gets hit
in the back of the head,
his eyeballs
would be bulging out.
All kids of crazy stuff
should be happening.
I think you fell short
on that whole aspect.
I laughed inside
when he was looking for the bat.
It was kind of funny
that he couldn't find it,
and it was stuck to his head,
but, aesthetically,
it's so nightmarish and weird.
That doesn't fly as comedic.
The kiss makeup
around his eye--
what are you pulling from?
That was kind of
just an aesthetic choice.
That's a problem
when you can't tell me that.
- You see what I'm saying?
- Yeah.
It's not funny.
It's not telling me the story,
- and it doesn't feel at all like a ghost.
- Yeah.
Eddie, please step back.
Thanks, guys.
Roy.
Roy, what have you done?
Well, these
are the Cain Brothers,
and they were Vaudevillian
performers.
They had a drinkin' problem,
and one night
they stepped into traffic
and got hit by a streetcar.
They were killed, so this
is how they have to live
in the afterlife.
It works.
At a distance, head looks real.
It almost passes
for a genuine little person.
I laughed out loud on this one.
Thank you.
It's quite genius,
because you manage so deftly
to capture the humor aspects
of the challenge.
I love the simplicity
of the arm gag.
- Really well done.
- Thank you.
This is a quintessential
Vaudevillian trick.
They would put two little kids
on top of each other
to create an adult,
and you pulled it off
so well with one person.
Unbelievable, honey.
You did a great job.
Thank you.
Roy, please step back.
- Nice job.
- Laney, please step up.
Laney, tell us
about your character.
Her name
is "Electro-Cute,"
and she
was a rock band guitarist
that was playing
an outdoor festival,
and during the show,
it started to rain,
and she became electrocuted
by her guitar.
It does not tell me
the story about her
and how she's a ghost.
I don't understand why
her skull looks like that.
You used
these very confusing forms
to create your head sculpture,
and it does not make me laugh.
It just makes me confused.
Well, she's very cute,
but she looks to me
more like a punk rock alien.
You don't have anything
on her that looks like
she was electrocuted--
like she would have had
singeing marks
or something crazy somewhere.
It just missed for me
this week, honey.
These are good ideas,
but you've got to turn it up,
because it's
supposed to be funny.
You have to make it
a caricature.
I'm pleased
with how ambitious you are,
but I'm disappointed that this
doesn't satisfy the challenge.
Laney, if you'd please
step back.
All right, guys, the judges
have heard what you have to say.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
while they deliberate.
Thank you.
Okay, judges.
Let's start with the looks
you liked the most this week.
Why don't we begin with Laura?
Loved it.
Liked it.
I didn't laugh out loud.
Clean, beautiful,
and sound decision making
each step of the way.
She did a fabulous job again.
She could have pushed it
a little further,
and then it would have
really been funny.
All right,
let's move on to Roy.
Okay, well, Roy really knocked
it out of the park for me.
I got it immediately.
The face on the small person
carrying her is quite funny.
I'm really happy
with his work this week.
I'm happy to see this Roy back.
Okay, let's move on to
the looks you liked the least.
Why don't we start with Eddie?
Just so un-obvious
as to what it is supposed to be.
The things around the eyes
are just so bizarre.
I really don't like it.
I've had enough of backstories
that try to make sense
out of something
that is not fitting in
to what it is
that we asked them to do.
You would never be able
to pull that off on set.
All right,
let's move on to Laney.
She had a really cute idea.
It could have been done
really well.
I loathe the forms
that she used on the head.
They make no sense at all.
She has got to stop
infusing every piece
with her personality.
- Yeah.
- It needs to be stand-alone.
So, judges,
have you made your decisions?
Yes, we have.
Let's bring them back out.
All right, Glenn, why don't you
tell us about the top looks?
Laura...
Your makeup
was especially well done,
and it hit just the right note
for this week's
particular challenge.
And, Roy...
We loved your crazy concept
this week,
and more than impressed
by all the snap decisions
that you've had to make
in order to pull it off
for this challenge.
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner tonight is...
Who is the winner
of this challenge?
The winner tonight is...
Roy.
Yay!
You got one.
Only you could have
come up with and executed
something like this character
on the level
that you did this week,
and it all worked so well.
Thank you very much.
It feels good
to finally win one.
It's our tenth challenge,
and this is my first win.
About damn time.
Roy, congratulations.
You and Laura can head back
to the makeup room.
- Bye.
- Bye, guys.
Unfortunately, that means,
Eddie and Laney,
you are on the bottom
this week,
and one of you
will be eliminated.
Please step forward.
Glenn, tell us
about the bottom looks.
Eddie, while your concept
was interesting,
very little of it
was evident in your makeup
because of the hyper-stylized
choices that you made.
Laney, we were disappointed
in the shapes that you used
in the face and thought
that it maybe looked
more alien than it did ghost.
So who's going home tonight?
The person going home
tonight is...
Eddie.
Your character was neither
here nor there for us tonight.
It wasn't particularly scary
or funny,
and we weren't really sure
what it was
that we were looking at.
Eddie, I'm sorry,
but you have been eliminated.
That means, Laney,
you are safe this week.
You can head back
to the makeup room.
Eddie, you're a young guy.
You got a long road
ahead of you,
and I'm excited to see
where you take it,
because you've got
a real bold aesthetic,
and that's an asset.
Thank you.
Eddie, it's really been great
having you here with us.
If you'd please head back
to the makeup room
and pack up your kit.
Thank you, guys.
I've had
an incredible experience.
Thank you.
Good luck.
Bye, Eddie.
I'm very happy that I made it
ten challenges in,
and I've learned
so many things.
Hey, guys.
It's me.
Aww.
I'm feeling all right.
I've gotten to know
a lot of great people,
and I've gotten feedback
from industry professionals.
Oh, boy.
I know I have a lot to learn,
and Face Off has really
inspired me to keep at it.
I'm gonna go home
with my head held high,
and I feel like I've already won
by just being here.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net